♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
All right!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi dit dit dit ♪
ANNOUNCER: Coming soon
to a planet near you...
Lord Hater's
"No Planets Left Behind,"
Boomapalooza!
The Galactic Destruction Tour.
[explosions]
12 planets in three weeks!
We'll show Lord Dominator
he's not the only one
who can destroy a planet.
We're blowing them up!
Thanks to my--
I mean Lord Hater's--
most diabolical weapon yet--
the Disaster Blaster 5000!
Boomapalooza,
The Galactic destruction Tour.
We're gonna rock their worlds!
Oh... yeah!
Come on,
let me hear it.
You get to blow up a planet.
You get to blow up a planet!
You get a tee shirt!
You get a tee shirt.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
[maniacal laughter]
Whoa!
[imitating guitar licks]
Uh, what about w--
What did I say
before the briefing?!
Nobody here is to ever use
the "W" word again!
Or else...
[ray gun powering up]
No, no, it's cool,
Peepers, it's cool.
Look, as many of you
may know,
I had a problem.
No, an obsession with...
the "W" word.
I wasted a lot of time
chasing a certain goofball
around the galaxy.
But I'm past that now
and ready to focus
on the important things,
like...
[scatting]
Ruling the entire universe!
[chanting indistinctly]
Uh, running over, just gotta
do something real quick.
You're up.
[scatting]
Wander and Sylvia,
prepare to--
Oh, really?
Like this?
What?
I just can't believe,
after our long relationship,
This is how
you're gonna do it?
Huh?
When I pictured you
destroying me,
it wasn't all quick and cheap
in some cramped hallway.
It was special.
It was gonna be...
[shouting angrily]
This is exactly why I--
Let's just say,
for the sake of argument,
how would you make your
untimely doom more special?
Well, for starters,
location.
When you picture
finally getting rid of us,
where do you see it
happening?
Wait, are we doing a,
you know, thing?
Wink.
Wink!
I know just the place!
Oh, this is much doomier.
Right?
Okay, let's do this!
Ooh, are we really going
with the axe?
What's wrong with axes?
Eh, a little old-fashioned,
if you ask me.
Oh, yeah, none of
the cool villains
are using axes these days.
But whatever
makes you happy.
Ugh!
WANDER:
Lava, huh?
Doesn't leave you with
much of a souvenir.
Don't you want to
mount our heads
on the wall or something?
Ugh!
Zap blaster!
SYLVIA: Too quick.
Biter beetles.
WANDER: Heck of a mess
to clean up.
Soul sucker!
Eh, doesn't really feel
like us, you know?
[angry roar]
And while we're at it, is that
really what you're gonna wear?
What's-- What's wrong
with my cloak?
Nothing, but you wear it
every day.
Don't you wanna look
extra spiffy
for when you finally
get rid of me?
LORD HATER:
No, no, no, no, no.
Aha!
We're gonna need
to see more.
♪ Gettin' ready
for the big day ♪
♪ Dressed for success ♪
♪ I've been dreaming
my whole life ♪
♪ About your untimely death ♪
♪ Gettin' ready
for the big day ♪
♪ Gotta find
a cloak that works ♪
♪ I might vaporize you
electrify you ♪
Hey, isn't that just a--
♪ Either way
it's gonna hurt ♪
Ooh, glittery!
♪ Big day ♪
All right.
Lookin' good, feelin' bad!
No more Wander. Here we go!
♪ Big day ♪
Mood music.
[electronic music playing]
[dance music playing]
[Lord hater singing]
♪ I hate to say ♪
♪ That I love you ♪
I don't know what
that's doing on there.
Stupid shuffle!
[dramatic music playing]
Okay, great.
One, two, three, go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
"One, two, three, go"?
That's all you're
gonna say?
I thought this day
meant something to you.
[angry shout]
This is exactly the type
of annoying behavior
that makes me hate you
so much!
Oh, you have no idea how
I've dreamed of the moment
when I will finally
be free of you!
It will be the sweetest,
most beautiful--
Shut your mouth and put
that passion on the paper!
...loathe your stupid,
smiling face,
and where there was
once three,
now there is only one.
[inhales deeply]
Hater, this is the most
beautiful, horrible thing
I've ever read
in my life
about my death.
We can't keep this private.
We ned to share this!
No, this is Perry,
this is Larry.
And if we invite Barry,
we have to invite Gary.
Then we might as well
invite Jerry, Harry, Kerry,
and Sebastien--
Oh, heck, let's just
invite 'em all!
We don't have enough room.
She's right.
We need a bigger venue.
But I already paid a deposit.
To find a new spot
this late is--
Look, you only get
to destroy me once.
If we're gonna do this,
let's do it right.
♪ Still gettin' ready
for the big day ♪
♪ Gettin' everything
just right ♪
♪ I can't wait to destroy
your body tonight ♪
♪ Checking every detail twice ♪
♪ Making something
out of ice ♪
♪ We only get to do this once
let's have some fun ♪
♪ Still gettin' ready
for the big day ♪
♪ Come on, take my hand ♪
♪ Yes I admit
there's more to this ♪
♪ Than we'd initially planned ♪
♪ The decorations
invitations ♪
♪ Gonna be one heck
of a celebration ♪
♪ We get to do this once
let's have some fun ♪
♪ Still gettin' ready
for the big day ♪
Destruction of Wander?
Isn't that the guy he said
he wasn't gonna chase no more?
Wait.
Look!
Free cake?
Whoo-hoo!
ALL: Free cake!
"Wander, I want...
"to destroy you more...
than life it--"
Lord Hater, sir.
Aah!
Nothing.
Nothing!
We're approaching
the first stop
on the Galactic
Destruction tour.
The wha--
Oh...right.
This is a huge moment
for us, sir.
When that Disaster Blaster 5000
hits that first planet
and it explodes,
just know I'll be
exploding as well.
With pride.
Real big day.
[angry shout]
What a fool I've been!
Wander!
Heh, heh, Hater!
It's bad luck to see the victims
before you destroy them.
You... You almost ruined
our plans.
You made me put together
this whole ceremony...
And we didn't even choose
a method of destruction!
[gasps]
What are we gonna do?
Don't worry, I know
just the thing!
Okay, everybody,
this is it.
Boomapalooza begins!
Eh... everybody?
Ugh, gotta do everything
myself!
[system powers up,
powers down]
The Disaster Blaster 5000!
What is going on?
Huh?
"You're invited
to the destruction of...
Don't tell Peepers"?
Oh, no.
[rock music intro]
[gasping]
Aha!
Stop!
PEEPERS: Lord Hater,
what are you doing?
I thought you were past
all this.
I am. This is just
a quickie destruction.
Or it, uh, was.
But we had plans.
We were going to spread evil
throughout the galaxy together.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
What do you think,
buddy?
Time to jet?
Leave?
But the ceremony's
not done.
Wait, I thought
we were doing a thing.
But the-- the wink!
What about the wink?
It started as a wink,
but the ceremony
turned out so nice.
Seems a shame not
to go through with it.
I know, I know.
It was just so nice seeing
Hater enjoy something for once.
It's okay, buddy.
Even though you may seem
out of your mind
sometimes,
your heart's always
in the right place.
Aha!
I thought...
I thought what we had
was special!
Peepers, you've
made me realize two things.
One, you're
absolutely right.
And two...
I don't care!
Wander and Sylvia,
prepare to-- Huh?
[Disaster Blaster
powering up]
Oh, they were doing a thing.
[explosion]
♪ Dee di dee dee do do ♪
♪ Do do di di dit do ♪
SYLVIA: Well, that ceremony
sure went off with a bang.
You think so?
Oh, buddy, it couldn't
have gone any better.
[rooster crowing]
[both snoring]
Mi mi mi mi mi mi.
Mi mi mi mi mi.
[buzzing]
Ahh, good morning,
you delightful new day.
Ohhh...
Ohm...
Stupid, dumb,
lame, dumb.
Nobody cares about
your trip.
Ugh, cats!
[laptop shatters]
[both sniffing]
Ooh!
[humming, scatting]
[groaning]
One more time!
[continues humming,
scatting]
[continues groaning]
Meow!
Uh, thank you, sir.
[toothbrush whirring]
[groaning]
[straining]
One...
hundred.
One hundred.
[grunting, gasping]
[stomachs grumbling]
Sylvia.
[whispering]
Peepers!
I'm starving!
Sir, yes sir!
Sorry, sir.
Yeah, buddy?
Would you like
some delicious
and nutritious breakfast?
[yawns]
Thanks, pal.
In a little bit.
Right now I could use about...
ten more minutes
of sleep, okay?
No prob.
I totally hear ya.
If my friend wants
ten more minutes,
then ten minutes
you'll get.
I'll just go and
rustle up some grub...
[whispering indistinctly]
Whatever.
[stomach growling]
Patience, boy.
patience.
Oh, sorry.
Bon appetit!
[gasps]
Ecch!
Bleh!
Ehh! Yech!
Blecch!
[continues
disgusted grunts]
Need some help, buddy?
No.
No, no, no, no, no!
All your breakfasts
are bad!
Get some more sleep.
Get out of my way.
I'll do it myself.
The kitchen is
the other way, sir.
I got it.
I got it!
[sighs]
"You are here."
Aah, this is so hard!
[upbeat music playing]
[screams]
Whoops!
Oh, sorry.
I don't wanna hear it!
I did it!
I found the kitchen.
Yeah!
Is there a button?
A secret word?
Open!
Go, fridge, go!
Oh...
Gaa! It's so hard
to get eggs!
Aah...
[both screaming]
[both sigh]
And now, toast.
Because I know how
you like your toast.
Now, where am I going
to find toast around...
[sighs]
[sniffing]
Mm-mmm.
[electricity crackling]
Freshly baked.
No...problem...my...
hungry...little...friends.
There's...plenty...
for...every--
one.
No, no, no!
[sighs]
Juice, juice, juice.
Where's the stupid juice?
Found it!
Ah, half full!
Ah, half empty!
And now...
[sniffing]
[groaning]
Aw, poor Lord Hater.
Wonder if he's hungry.
[both sniffing]
Eww!
[animals growling]
Ooh, I'm so scared.
I'd better not steal
this breakfast,
or I might get mauled
by a squirrel.
Heh, stupid nature.
[screaming]
I mean... [indistinct]
Ow, get off, get off!
Stop it!
Aah!
Silly goose, you brought
a water glass,
not a juice glass.
Hmm... I feel like
something's missing.
Aah...
Perfect.
And now...
Dear Lord Hater
please enjoy this
scrumptious breakfast
that I made for you.
Your friend,
Wander.
Aah!
[groaning]
[yawning]
[sniffing]
Oh, thanks, pal.
It was no problem.
No problem at all.
Oh, yeah!
[stomach growling]
Wait, you don't
have any?
Here, buddy,
you want some of mine?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll find some food
somehow.
Right now, I'm just happy
that you're happy.
Always racking up
the karma points, huh, Wander?
"Dear Lord Hater,
please enjoy this
scrumptious breakfast
as a token
of our... friendship?"
[gags, gulps]
"P.S., the secret
ingredient is love."
[gagging]
"P.P.S., if you eat this,
we're best friends..."
[gagging]
"...forever"?
Aaaaah!
[both snoring]
BOTH: Oh, wait.
get back here.
Sir, I really need you
to stay put and keep out of--
Wait, where'd you go?
Okay.
[both snoring]