♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
Don't, don't.
Don't you do it,
Binglebop.
Don't you dare
fall to Dominator.
No!
Nooooooo!!
She did it.
Dominator destroyed
every single planet
in the flarpin' galaxy.
There's nothing
left to conquer.
What are we gonna
do now, sir?
Sir.
Sir?
We're finished.
( Dominator laughing )
They lost!
I did it!
I played this stupid galaxy
like a fiddle,
and then smashed that fiddle
across their dumb little faces.
Ha!
Come on, is this
a party or a funeral?
Well, I guess it's kind
of a funeral for them.
Still, show a little
excitement.
( grunts ) Activate
celebration protocol Omega.
We'll work on that.
But I'm not gonna let
you sad-sack robozos
rain on my parade,
because I came, I saw,
and I dominated!
There's nothing left
of this stupid galaxy!
There's nothing left?
No more dopey
little planets to destroy.
No more annoying
adorable idiots to antagonize.
It's... over.
Activate sympathy
protocol Sigma.
There, there.
It will all be
all right.
Look, a shooting star.
Ha.
Aw, it's not the same.
What I wouldn't give for
one more planet to destroy.
King Bingleborp.
I'm so glad you made it.
Welcome to our little
secret hideaway.
Can we get you anything?
Vengeance!
Dominator destroyed my planet.
My people have fled the galaxy.
I want to know exactly what you
heroes intend to do about it!
Cheer up,
Your Bingle-ness.
We've got some of
the smartest, bravest,
and overall best-est
folks in the galaxy
here to figure out
how to stop her.
SYLVIA:
Everybody, hello.
Ooh, we're starting.
Better find our seats.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Sylvia.
Whoo! Sylvia!
All right!
We've invited you here
because, well,
there's no place else.
Dominator has driven us
from our homes
and kept us on the run
for an entire season...
of our lives.
Well, I'm done running.
I'm making a stand
on this tiny rock
so small and far away
that even Dominator
can't find it, here at...
I feel like that was
a poor choice of words.
This is our galaxy.
And no hot-headed,
cold-hearted psycho
is gonna take it
from us.
( all cheering )
Um, yeah.
What's your plan exactly?
I am open to suggestions.
We should consult
the mighty wizard Neckbeard
the all-knowing nay-sayer.
Yeah, tried that.
Didn't work.
Could've told 'em
it wouldn't.
Legend tells of
an ancient battle mech
known as Robomechabotatron.
Yeah, we kinda sorta
blew that up.
( chanting ominously
in Latin )
Whoa! That is...
That is dark.
Yeah, we're not doin' that.
Why don't we just
cozy up down here
until this Dominator bird
gets bored and hits the bricks?
And let her do the same thing
to another galaxy?
No way. This stops now.
Major Threat,
you used to be
one of the worst
villains around.
A true galactic terror.
What should we do?
I don't know, man.
All this heavy stuff
is really bumming me out.
Hey, who's up for pizza?
I want anchovies!
- Half pineapple.
- No pineapple.
( all clamoring )
No wonder Dominator was able
to take over this galaxy.
Lord Hater?
Barry!
Andy!
Anybody!
Listen up, Watchdogs.
To the untrained eyeball,
it may seem as though
Dominator has won.
Wrong!
I have done
careful research,
and using my extensive
knowledge
of gravity wells
and thermodynamics...
- His what now?
- I have uncovered this--
a class D planetoid
emitting a minimal
gravitational pull,
allowing it to go
undetected by Dominator,
which means...
there's one planet left.
- There is?
- And guess who's on it.
Oh, great.
We will use Wander
as a distraction
in order to conquer
the planet,
turning our greatest weakness
into our greatest strength!
- We will?
- Dominator may have destroyed
every other planet,
but as long as there is
hate in my bones,
she will never get this one!
This is where
we make our stand,
and let her know
that she failed
because this planet,
nay, this galaxy,
belongs to
the Duke of Destruction,
the Monarch of Mayhem,
the greatest
in the galaxy,
Lord Hater!
Hate's great. Best villain.
Hate's great.
Best villain.
Watchdogs, eyes up.
We've got a galaxy to save.
so we can conquer it later!
Where has this guy
been all season...
of our lives?
Hate's great. Best villain.
Hate's great.
Best villain.
( all arguing )
Hello. Ahem.
Yoo-hoo, hey.
Over here.
Hi. ( giggles )
Hi, everybody.
I know you're all upset,
but taking it out
on each other
won't help anything.
Sure, Dominator's cut
a brutal swath of chaos
and destruction
throughout our galaxy,
but if she gets us
to turn on our friends,
then we've really lost.
A planet's just a place
you hang your hat.
As long as
we've got each other,
we've still got a shot.
( cheering )
Together, there's nothing
in the galaxy we can't do!
ALL: Yeah!
So, what are we gonna do?
ALL: Destroy Dominator!
- Yeah... what now?
- Destroy Dominator!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Resheath that sword.
Undraw those guns.
Deflex those pecs.
I don't wanna destroy
anybody.
Sylvia, help me out here.
Sylvia?
I... I'm sorry, buddy.
But I thought we were
gonna figure out
how to stop her
from being so evil.
There's gotta be a reason
she's so mean.
If we could just
figure that out.
An enemy's just a friend
you haven't made yet.
Right?
Sometimes an enemy
is just an enemy.
Thanks, but we'll
handle it from here.
Okay, Starbella, Ripov,
Major Threat,
you've all got ships.
The Baa'haalans have an army.
Neckbeard's got tons of magical
weapons and stuff.
It's a bold move,
but someone's gotta do it.
( all chattering )
Dumb. Stupid.
Sigh. Boring!
Suggested course of action:
Dominate another galaxy.
But that means
starting from scratch.
Meeting a bunch
of new people,
figuring out the right way
to crush their spirits.
( frustrated groan )
Demolishing this galaxy
was my masterpiece.
It was so full of dorks
ripe for the dominating.
Where am I gonna find
anyone as dumb
and hopeful
and pathetic and...
( deep, distorted voice )
Perfect.
( evil laughter )
WANDER: Hello.
Dominator?
I wanted to stop by,
have a chat,
Is this a bad...
...time?
DOMINATOR:
Bots, stand down.
- You're not gonna
have them destroy me?
- No.
Ah, see? I knew
you weren't all bad.
I'm going to destroy you.
- Run.
- What the what now?
( screaming )
Pete, man the torpedo tubes.
Ted, prepare Eye Fighters
for launch.
Captain Tim,
heel, sit.
Good boy.
Sir, you're on point,
you're formulating
strategies.
You actually know
the Watchdogs' names.
This is incredible!
No, Peepers.
This is incredible.
Activate
skull crusher mode.
♪ Here comes
the skull crusher ♪
- Whoa!
- Peepers, no time
for distraction.
We need to focus on
getting our galaxy back.
Are you crying?
( crying )
No, sir.
Barry, Jerry,
punch it!
( laughing )
Hey, get back here.
What fun is you
running in terror
if I don't get to watch
you run in terror?
I just wanna get to
the root of your pain.
Maybe hug it out.
Ow!
( laughing )
Sylvia, oh, thank Grop.
We gotta get
outta here before...
Sylvia!
Noooooo!
( Dominator laughs )
The look...
( laughing )
on your face.
"Sylvia, no!"
Thought your friend...
dead. ( laughing )
Why are you like this?
Ha ha. Just lucky,
I guess.
I'm serious.
Everyone else is out there
trying to destroy you.
But I figure there's good
way deep down  in everyone.
There's gotta be
some reason you're
so Grop darned
evil all the time.
If you just tell me
what's ailin' ya,
maybe I can help you out.
What do ya say?
Really?
You mean it?
Of course I do,
because I believe an enemy
is just a friend
you haven't made yet.
Wow. I gotta
thank you
for letting me know
there's more of you idiots
out there to destroy.
What? No!
You said everyone else
was trying to destroy me.
That means they're
still out there.
Where are they?
They're nowhere.
I mean, there's
no one anywhere.
Even if there was,
it's not like
they're secretly hiding out
and plotting your demise.
It's just little old me,
so you better hurry up
and destroy me now
please. Thank you.
Bots, scan him.
Shut up!
There's another planet
to dominate?
And it's full of
your weird little pals?
Oh, this is just
the cherry on top
I was looking for.
But I just wanted
to help you.
Oh, you were a big help.
Friend.
Okay, rebels,
what are we gonna do?
ALL: Destroy Dominator.
How are we gonna do it?
Destroy Dominator!
Sorry.
Yeah. Yeah, no, I get that.
Love the enthusiasm.
But how? We need a plan.
We can't waltz up
and punch her ship, you know?
Wander, you've snuck onto
her ship more than anyone.
Do you have
any bright ideas?
Wander? Wander!
Where could he have gone?
There's no place
left in the galaxy except...
Oh, no.
Hey, guys,
how's it going?
Guess who I found.
- Wanna say hi?
- Hi.
Wander. Oh, thank Grop
you're still okay.
I was so worried
about you.
I was worried
you'd be worried.
Well, I was worried that
my worry would worry you.
I was worried--
Enough! You should
all be worried.
( evil laughter )
HATER: No!
It is you who
should be worried,
Lord Dominator.
- Huh?
- Hatey!
You can steal my planets,
you can capture
my enemy,
you can even
break up with me.
You realize we were
never dating.
You wanna destroy
my galaxy?
You gotta get
through me first!
Well, that was weird.
Where was I? Oh, yeah.
( evil laughter )
ALL: Phew!
( all screaming )
Phew!
Phew! Phew! Phew!
Please stop this.
It's terrible,
and emotionally exhausting.
Okay, let's get
down to business.
And I know
just where to start.
- Grab the Zbornak.
- No!
Flab-drassin' tin cans.
I destroy your best friend,
then I watch you cry.
( evil laughter )
♪ Who is the universe's
ultimate evil doer? ♪
- Hater?
- Hater!
ALL: Hater!
An enemy is just a friend
you haven't made yet.
You guys saved my life?
Don't get used to it.
This is a one-time
stop the badder bad guy thing.
All right!
How is this idiot
doing this?
He's a terrible bad guy.
But he makes
a pretty good
good guy.
I think I see
a crack in your armor.
That's it.
This ends now.
I'm doing it.
I'm actually winning.
We're all
very impressed.
What exactly do you think
is gonna happen here?
Um, I'm gonna stop you.
Ha! Please.
Even if you could,
you'd still be a joke.
The lamest
in the galaxy.
Just a dopey,
soft-centered jerk
that nobody has ever,
or will ever, respect.
Face it.
You are literally
the worst
villain ever!
Hate's great.
Best villain.
ALL: Hate's great.
Hate's great.
Best villain.
Hate's great. Best villain.
Hate's great.
Best villain.
Hate's great. Best villain.
Hate's great.
Best villain.
Hate's great. Best villain.
( alarm blaring )
How is this happening?
They're just a bunch
of goofy idiots.
Bots, help me!
Fine. I don't need you.
I don't need anybody.
That's silly.
Everybody needs somebody.
( gasps )
That's it.
You need us.
I have Sylvia,
Lord Hater has
Peepers and the Watchdogs.
But you're all alone
up here.
Shut up. I got
lots of friends.
Bot 79, Bot 108,
Bot 13.
No, wait, I blew up
Shut up!
I've got lots of friends!
You could've destroyed us
when you first showed up.
When we put on
that concert for you,
heck, you spent a whole night
out with Syl.
But you didn't
because you like
hanging around us.
Even if it is in
a "Rrrr, grr, I'm
gonna kill you" way.
Stop it.
Just stop talking.
That's why you're
such a bully.
You're lonely.
( growling )
I'll destroy you!
( cheering )
Wander!
( all cheering )
Wh... what?
Why did you save me?
I tried to kill you,
like, a lot.
Because an enemy's
just a friend you
haven't made yet.
And there's a whole bunch
of potential friends down there.
Sure, you sorta tried
to destroy 'em,
so there'll be a few
awkward dinner parties,
but if they can
cheer for him,
they can accept
anybody.
You realize I, like,
demolished
your entire galaxy.
You'd be surprised
what you can grow
from a little
bit of kindness.
It's never too late
for a fresh start.
So, let's try this again.
Hello to you.
Folks call me Wander.
That's my pal Sylvia.
Welcome to the galaxy.
We hope you'll accept
our humble gift of friendship.
Shut up!
Ugh. You guys
are so weird.
I'm leaving.
Didn't wanna destroy
your goofy little
galaxy anyway.
You're all a bunch
of dorks!
I'm taking this
'cause I'm hungry,
not 'cause
we're friends.
Buddy, I am so sorry
I doubted you.
You were
totally right.
I don't know about that.
I really thought
I could make a new friend.
I think you may
just yet.
PEEPERS: You did it, sir.
You saved the galaxy!
A galaxy of new planets.
For me.
To conquer.
Starting with this one!
Or it's a whole new
galaxy for us to explore.
Come on, buddies.
( shrieks )
We're not your buddies!
PEEPERS AND SYLVIA:
Nothing ever changes.
Come on. Stupid
friendship orange.
Dumb peel.
Bunch of dorks.
They'll get what's
coming to them.
( Hater's laughter
echoing )