♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
Whoo!!
That's one more.
Peepers, put it
on the board.
You're number three, sir.
I'm so proud of you.
Hear that, biggieborp?
Number three.
I conquered your planet,
I conquered
all your planets.
And now it's time for...
( imitates drum roll )
your ultimate destruction!
To the torture room.
Whoo!
Sir, I really love
the enthusiasm,
but it's really late,
and I'm really tired.
Can't we just
destroy them in the morning?
Oh!!
But I wanna
destroy 'em now.
Right, guys?
Sir.
Okay.
Sorry, guys.
Peeper says we gotta
wait till tomorrow.
So just enjoy yourselves.
Don't even think about it
being the last night
of your sad little lives.
Hater out.
Whoo!
Gah! I just wanna take
his bony little skull--
Destructor,
your blood pressure.
( sighs )
- ( crying )
- Baby, it's gonna
be okay.
Probably not.
We are all clearly doomed.
WANDER: Well, now,
I wouldn't say that.
( prisoners exclaiming )
If brave Wander
and noble Sylvia are captured,
then surely
all is lost!
Captured? Please.
We just needed a place
to crash for the night,
so we popped in.
Don't worry. We bust
outta here all the time.
We'll get you out.
- What the...
force field?
- That's new.
Grop dang it.
Now what are we gonna do?
( all muttering )
Come on, you are
brave and noble rulers.
You laugh in
the face of danger.
You live every day
as if it was your last.
- But it is our last.
- Even better!
Are you gonna let
a little thing like certain doom
get you down?
No! We shall not
go quietly
- into that good night.
- ( all agreeing )
We shall rage until
we're out of fight.
ALL: Yeah!
We shall party!!
ALL: Yeah!!
What?
Prison party!
( snoring )
What the...
That sounds like a...
surprise victory party.
Come on, guys,
where are you?
You can't hide
my party from me.
Caught you, C-peeps.
Huh?
ECORDED VOICE:   You are strong,
you are evil,
you are tall.
So, buddy,
appreciate you
keeping spirits up,
but shouldn't we,
oh, I don't know,
get outta here before
we're blasted into oblivion?!
Syl, never underestimate
the power of a party.
I don't care...
...eoke! There's
a karaoke machine?
♪ Sweet bingleborp ♪
♪ Bingleborp, bingleborp ♪
♪ Let the sunshine
push away the rain ♪
How dare they
throw a party in my prison
and not invite me?!
Where's the party?
No party here.
Just bemoaning
our impending doom.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm gonna
throw my own awesome party,
and it's gonna be awesome.
( steady beeping )
Whoo!
( beeping continues )
( flatline sounds )
( steady beep resumes )
( sighs )
( music and laughter )
What's that?
Oh, it's just those
stupid rulers
and their stupid party.
There's another party?
Yeah, a super lame one
in the prison
with karaoke, games,
and scrumptious crudités.
But it's in no way...
as awesome as this one.
- Excuse you!
- Ow!
- Hey!
- Come on!
Lord Hater,
number one superstar.
Not on the list.
How does one
get on the list?
Watchdogs and deposed
royalty only.
- Ow!
- What's your
problem, man?
( falsetto voice )
Ahem! It is I,
deposed king, uh...
Schmater.
Nailed it.
All right. Time to show
these chumps
how to party
Hater-style.
I mean, Schmater-style.
( music playing )
Cool party, huh?
Just a bunch of
totally legit kings
celebrating
being destroyed
by the terrible
and handsome Hater,
- what what?
- ( slurping loudly )
I like your bracelets.
These are shackles.
Uh... cheerio, aye.
We gotta let Lord Hater
join the party.
( all disagreeing )
Come on.
What happened to being bold,
and living tonight like it's
the last night of our lives?
Taking risks,
doing crazy things,
and what's crazier
and riskier
than partying with the guy
who's gonna destroy us?
ALL: Nothing.
Right! Never underestimate
the power of a party.
( spitting )
Wander, what are
you doing here?
Same thing you are.
Havin' fun, right?
Schmater, is it?
( sputtering )
( falsetto voice )
Oh, yes. Totally.
I, uh, King Schmater,
love havin' fun.
Not like that
no-fun-having,
planet-taking
Lord Hater.
Ooh, I hate him so much
for taking my planet.
Grr!!
( all sighing )
But I've got
nine more songs to go.
You've had enough!
♪ Oh, if you're not happy ♪
♪ If you're filled
with sorrow ♪
♪ Just party, everybody ♪
♪ Like there's no tomorrow ♪
♪ Oh, we're gonna boogie ♪
♪ Going wild ♪
♪ We're gonna party like
it's your last night alive ♪
'Cause it is, everybody.
Let's party!
You are important.
You are talented.
You are a tiny little
unicorn prince...
( giggles )
...with a luxurious,
flowing mane.
( all giggling )
♪ Are you filled
with anger? ♪
with hate? ♪
♪ Just party, everybody ♪
♪ And you'll feel great ♪
- ♪ We're going bonkers ♪
- We're going bonkers!
- ♪ Going nuts ♪
- Going nuts!
- We're shakin' our booty ♪
- Shakin' our booty.
- ♪ Shakin' our butt ♪
- Shakin' our butt!
- ♪ We're gonna boogie ♪
- We're gonna boogie!
♪ Going wild ♪
♪ We're gonna party like
it's your last night alive ♪
( all laughing )
Let's go, everybody!
♪ Oh, we're gonna
party, party ♪
♪ We're gonna
Schmate's great.
So chillin'.
Schmate's great,
so chillin'.
ALL: Schmate's great,
Schmate's great,
so chillin'.
Let us party
till the break of dawn!
♪ Party, whoo! ♪
( rooster crowing )
- Toodle-oo.
- Good-bye.
- Salutations.
- Bye, you guys. Thanks.
So long, friends,
and remember...
Never underestimate
the power of a party.
Or a good night's sleep.
( weary sigh )
Can we go break back
into the prison?
- ( snoring )
- ( door unlocking )
Sir? Sir!
- Sir!!
- ( groaning )
Sir, where are
the deposed rulers
scheduled for
destruction?
I, uh...
don't know exactly
where they went.
To tell the truth, it was
a pretty wild party.
I'm not exactly sure
what happened.
Was Wander there?
Uh... yeah?
Maybe.
Man, what a party.
- Whoo!
- ( snoring resumes )
( sighs )
( raucous laughter )
Oh, yeah!
That's five...
five more planets
that are mine.
All mine!
Peepers, how great am I?
Tenth planet this week, sir,
which means...
I'm ten steps closer
to once again becoming
the greatest
in the galaxy!
Nothing can stop me now!
( alarm blaring )
Lord Hater,
your reign of terror is over!
Oh, my Grop.
It's him.
It's Major Threat!
PEEPERS: His telekinetic powers
can crush planets.
That dude is the evilest
evil-doer
- that ever do-ed evil.
- Sir, we're doomed!
After all these years
of conquering,
it comes down
to this.
When I finally meet my...
idol!
Huge, huge fan.
I know, like,
all your evil deeds.
You're pretty much
the reason I got into
villainy in the first place.
Threat's best.
Great villain!
Call me Jeff.
Okay, Jeff.
You are like,
the worst, the best.
Best at being
the worst.
Uh, thanks, bud.
Bud!
But I'm really
embarrassed about all
that conquering stuff.
It was just
take, take, take,
without giving a thought
to, you know,
the people, man,
and how they
were feeling.
( confused yelp )
( laughs )
Sorry, man, this must be
a bit of a shock.
I'm sure
you were expecting...
Roar! I shall destroy
your soul!!
And here I am,
all peace and love, man.
( laughs )
You must be all,
What? Did Major Threat
go all cuckoo
in the head, right?
Uh, yeah. Kinda thought
cuckoo head, yeah.
Well, I did.
I went cuckoo.
Cuckoo for conquering,
until I crossed paths
with this wandering weirdo.
Oh, no.
Strange visitor from
who knows where
who came to my galaxy
with powers of positivity
far beyond those of
anyone.
Oh, no.
Yeah, he went around
helping everyone.
Totally drove me
even cuckoo-ier.
Oh, no!
I chased him
around the galaxy,
vowing to destroy him.
Yes! I mean,
oh, no.
Yeah, and in the end,
do you know what he wanted?
No, what? What did
Wander want?
I mean, what did
he want?
Just to be...
my friend.
( anguished shriek )
Yeah, it's crazy, man.
It was like he wanted me
to hate him at first.
When he eventually
wore me down,
and we became friends,
I realized that if
I learned to like
this one thing
I used to hate,
then what was
the point of hating
all the other stuff
I hated?
With less hate in my heart,
I might start to
be happy and not be...
Such a bad guy anymore?
Exactly, man!
So like I was
saying earlier,
your reign of terror's
gonna have to end, man.
This aggression
won't stand.
No!!
I warned you, Peepers.
Sir, just because
Major Threat fell prey
to that wandering weirdo,
it doesn't--
It's hopeless!!
Don't you see?
Threat was the villainiest
villain of all time,
and Wander loved the hate
right out of him.
He Wander-ized him.
And now he wants to
Wander-ize me.
Here, man, let me
help you fix this.
That's it.
I can fix you.
Sir, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
No, if I can remind him
how good he is at being evil,
it'll prove once and for all
that bad is in the bones.
You are not good.
You are just bad
at remembering
how good
it was being bad.
Like the time you conquered
the unconquerable Klangors.
Grop yeah, the Klangors, man.
I gave up being
their evil dictator,
and turned them on
to democratic elections.
Okay, okay,
bad example.
You blew up
the sun of Solarion.
Now it's Skilorian,
a winter getaway
and non-profit research facility
to study climate change.
( frustrated scream )
You're bad!
Ninety-ounce Nihilists?
You were the loudest,
most evil band in the universe.
Oh, no, no, no.
I could never
quit music, man.
Me and the guys still
hang out and jam.
You see?
You can be even greater
by saying "later"
to the Hater.
Stop hugging everything!
Okay, time for
the big guns.
Victimon.
They are primed
and ready for destruction.
I would like you
to do the honors.
You're sure?
Oh, please.
If this doesn't get
the evil juices flowing,
nothing will.
I insist.
Well, uh, if you insist.
Yes. Yes!
No!!
Whoa, take her easy, man.
Just take her easy.
Oh, yeah?
What are you
gonna do about it, Jeff?
Huh, man?
You gonna play
your stupid flute
for some poor
puppy orphans?
I'll have your hug
waitin' when you're ready.
Fine. You can't
keep us prisoner.
We're leaving.
Come on, Peepers.
Sir, he never actually
took us prisoner.
Also, technically,
this is our ship.
Shut up!
I know that.
Hey, hug it out,
don't slug it out.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Does that
bother you, Jeff?
Seriously, sir,
you really... ow!
My retina.
Hey, how do you like it if I
treated you like that, you know?
What if I slapped
your helmet off, man, huh?
What if I pushed you
to the ground?
Yeah, and take over
your ship?
Yeah, and what if I take over
your whole army, huh?
Then what would...
By Grop, I forgot how good
being bad feels.
Yeah!
Major Threat is back,
and I'm gonna conquer
every planet
in this whole
stinkin' galaxy,
starting with yours.
Yeah! What?
I can't beat him.
It's over,
I'm finished.
Done, conquered.
That dude, I mean,
Major Threat is
the evilest evil-doer
that ever do-ed evil.
The only reason he was
stopped last time
was because...
oh, no.
Not that.
Oh, yeah,
that's five.
Five more planets
that are mine.
All mine!
Pipsqueak,
how great am I?
( shivering ) Tenth planet
in the last five minutes, sir,
which means...
I'm ten steps closer
to once again
becoming the greatest
in the galaxy!
Nothing can stop me now.
Threaty, is that you?
It's me.
Your old pal,
Sunshine Banjo Face.
Why the frowny face,
Sir Frownsalot?
Let's go tickle
some caterpillars,
and make lemonade
out of snowflakes!
Major Threat
will not abide by
such a disgusting display
of optimism.
Take that and that,
you grop-derned flabdrassers.
There's only one thing
to trump the grumpies,
and that's...
♪ When you wander
over that way ♪
♪ And wear a stupid hat ♪
♪ Then you help
some stupid people ♪
♪ And wear a stupid hat ♪
♪ When the bad guys
come a-creepin' ♪
♪ And lookin' really cool ♪
♪ Just do some friendly
dumb things ♪
♪ And act just like
a fool ♪
( singing continues )
Friendship!
( screaming )
( laughing )
Sorry I had
to fool you there,
but I knew there was
good deep down
in those bones.
Oh, no.
You not only helped
your friends here,
but you also
saved yourself, man.
Oh, no.
You'll thank me later.
It's like Tumbleweed
always said,
it never hurts to help.
Who?
Um, Tumbleweed.
That goofball that
drove me crazy,
then made me
a better person.
Wait, wasn't
his name Wander?
Nope. Folks called
him Tumbleweed.
Yes!!
Whoo!
Thank Grop.
Oh, I was worried
for a second
that I was doomed
to suffer the same
fate as you.
But I'm obviously
so much better
and more evil.
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out.
I don't know what
I was freaked out about.
My annoying wanderer
is totally different.
He plays a dumb banjo
and hands out stupid
sandwiches and...
Ha! Mustard or mayo,
mustard or mayo,
mustard or mayo?
Oh, no.
( laughter )
We could plant
a handful of jellybeans
and grow a rainbow,
or shake hands
with the ladybug at
the carnival in the clouds.
Or shave a candy cane
down to peppermint glitter.
Or give butterfly kisses
to an actual butterfly.
Or...