♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laugh )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT.
SHORTCUTS THROUGH
ASTEROID FIELDS--
NOT THE BEST IDEA.
WE'LL BE FINE!
AS LONG AS WE DON'T
RUN OUT OF--
--ORBBLE JUICE.
AAAAAH!
AAAAH!
UHH!
UHH! UHH! OHH!
ARE WE COMPLETELY DRY?
BUT DON'T WORRY!
LOOK, THERE'S A NICE
LITTLE TOWN OVER THERE.
♪ DOOMSTONE
I BET THEY CAN RUSTLE US UP
SOME ORBBLE JUICE.
I'M'A GO ASK 'EM FOR HELP.
WHAT?! DON'T YOU KNOW
WHERE WE ARE?
THIS IS DOOMSTONE!
REFUGE FOR THE MEANEST,
NASTIEST OUTLAWS
IN THE GALAXY.
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK IN THERE
ASKING FOR ORBBLE JUICE.
THEY'LL TEAR YOU APART!
WHAT IF I ASK  REAL  NICE?
NO! IF WE'RE GONNA
GO IN THERE,
YOU GOTTA DO
THE OPPOSITE OF THAT.
YOU GOTTA ACT TOUGH,
NASTY, MEAN!
YOU GOTTA ACT
LIKE A BAD GUY!
BAD GUY?
GOT IT!
NO PROBLEM.
( growling, roaring )
GRRR! LAAAA!
GRRR!
IS THAT--
IS THERE SOME DINOSAUR
IN THERE?
LITTLE BIT.
OHH. WE'RE DOOMED.
( rowdy chatter )
( glass breaking )
( room goes silent )
( roars )
( chatter resumes )
OHH. OKAY. I'M GONNA
GO SEE THE OWNER
ABOUT HOOKING US UP
WITH THE JUICE.
JUST REMEMBER: GRRRR!
GRRRR!
( continues growling )
YOU'RE IN MY SEAT,
LITTLE MAN.
WHY, I'M SORRY. I--
(lowers voice)
I MEAN, GET YER OWN...
( gasping )
( growling )
DO YOU KNOW WHO I AM?
DO  YOU  KNOW
WHO  I  AM?
I'M A WANTED MAN.
TEN MILLION CREDIT REWARD
FOR THE CAPTURE
OF BADLANDS DAN,
MEANEST MAN IN
THE WHOLE DURNED LAND!
( tearing noise )
I'M A WANTED MAN.
TEN MILLION AND ONE CREDIT
REWARD FOR THE CAPTURE
OF WILD WOOLY WANDER,
WICKEDEST WAN
IN THE WHOLE WURNED WAND!
GRRRR!
Sylvia: SO...
ANY IDEA WHERE A PERPETRATOR
OF GENERALLY UNPLEASANT THINGS
LIKE MYSELF CAN BUY
SOME...ORBBLE JUICE?
WELL, I DON'T HAVE ANY,
BUT, UH...
OHH.
THERE  IS  SOMEONE WHO...
MIGHT  HAVE...
HIS NAME IS PAPA DOOM.
HERE'S HIS ADDRESS
AND DIRECTIONS TO
HIS PLACE. ENJOY.
SO WHAT'S THE CATCH?
THERE IS A CATCH, RIGHT?
PAPA DOOM'S THE MEANEST,
NASTIEST CRIME LORD
ON DOOMSTONE!
HA! HA HA HA HA!
YOU AIN'T TOUGH ENOUGH.
HE'S GONNA BLAST YOU INTO ATOMS
AND KEEP THE CRYSTALS HIMSELF!
HA HA!
BUT THAT SHOULDN'T BE
A PROBLEM FOR YOU AND YOUR
PARTNER, RIGHT?
HE SEEMS  REAL  TOUGH.
TOUGH?
LET'S TAKE IT OUTSIDE,
LITTLE MAN.
LET'S DO IT!
LET'S TAKE IT  ALL  THE WAY
OUTSIDE!
LET'S TAKE IT FOR
A NICE WALK IN THE PARK--
YOU AND THE REST OF THESE
WIMPY WIMPERSONS.
( all gasping )
THE NAME IS  WILLIAM  WIMPERSON,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GRRR!
ARE YOU THREE KINDS OF CRAZY?
I ASKED FOR BAD, NOT DEATH WISH!
NOW, WE NEED TO FIND A WAY TO
GET THESE CRYSTALS ACROSS TOWN--
WANDER?
( motorcycle engine revs )
HOP ON.
WHAT?!
WHERE DID YOU--
( engine revs )
HE STOLE MY RIDE!
YOU STOLE FROM
THOSE  GUYS?!
YEAH. SHOULD I GIVE IT BACK?
( growling )
NO. GO, WILD WILLY WANDER!
GO!
YEAHHH!
GET HIM!
( screaming )
WATCH OUT!
AAAAH!
WATCH THIS.
TRUCK FULL OF EXPLOSIVES!
TRUCK FULL
OF EXPLOSIVES!
GOOD IDEA.
AAH!
AAAH!!!!
BEIN' BAD...
IS RAD!!!!
YOU CRAZY WHAMMER JAMMER!
YOU--YOU--
--GOT US EXACTLY WHERE
WE NEEDED TO BE!
THIS MUST BE PAPA DOOM'S JOINT.
OH, NOT BAD, WANDER.
NOT BAD AT  ALL.
"OH, NOT BAD, WANDER."
SO YOU'RE THINKING
WE SHOULD ASK NICE THIS TIME?
NO. NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE ALMOST HOME FREE.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP THE ACT NOW.
SO DON'T BE NICE!
BUT YA KNOW, DON'T
BE CUCKOO EITHER.
OH! HOW ABOUT YOU LET  ME
DO THE TALKING?
AND YOU PLAY
THE STRONG, SILENT TYPE.
RIGHT? BAD, BUT QUIET.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
CAN I?!!!
SHH!
( door hinges creak )
WHAT KIND OF EVIL CRIME LORD
LEAVES HIS FRONT DOOR UNLOCKED?
Papa Doom: THE KIND WHO KNOWS
THERE'S NOBODY STUPID ENOUGH
TO WALK THROUGH.
( thunder )
I, UH, I HEAR YOU HAVE
SOME ORBBLE TRANSPORTER
JUICE FOR SALE.
ME AND MY PARTNER HERE
NEED TO GET OFF THIS ROCK
TO CONTINUE OUR LIFE
OF BAD AN UNSAVORY BEHAVIOR.
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
I TAKE YOUR MONEY,
I DON'T GIVE YOU
ANY ORBBLE JUICE,
AND MY FRIENDS HERE
CRUSH YOU INTO FLOOR WAX.
( gargoyles growl )
( hissing )
WHAT'S THE MATTER, TWERP?
AIN'T YA SCARED?
GRRRRR!
HOLD ON!
THIS IS THAT GUY
I HEARD ABOUT,
THE GUY WHO STOOD UP
TO BADLANDS DAN!
WHO WRECKED THE MOTOR HOGS!
BOSS, THIS IS
WILD WOOLY WANDER!
( wheezing )
IS THAT TRUE?
( roaring )
( nervous laughter )
I'M SORRY!
I DIDN'T KNOW!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME
AND MY ASSOCIATES--
LUNKER! GET OUR NASTY FRIEND
WANDER HERE
A BOTTLE OF OUR
FINEST ORBBLE JUICE.
( growling )
( roaring )
SEE? WE'RE ALL SENSIBLE
BUT EVIL FOLKS HERE.
NOW WE HAVE OUR JUICE
AND YOU HAVE YOUR--
Papa Doom: BAG OF ROCKS?!
I SWITCHED THE BAGS!
NOW WE HAVE THE CRYSTALS
AND  THE JUICE.
PRETTY BAD, HUH?
AFTER THEM!!!
( gargoyles shrieking )
( roaring )
GAME OVER, FUR BALL.
BRING IT ON, FELLAS!
I'M WILD WOOLY WANDER!
I'M THE TOUGHEST
MEANEST THERE IS!
COME ON!!!!
I'LL TAKE  ALL  OF YA ON!
( roaring )
STOP!!!!
HOO-HOO-EE!
THAT WAS SOME KIND OF FUN!
YOU FOLKS ARE ALL
REAL GOOD SPORTS.
All: HUH???
LOOK, WE'RE NOT BAD GUYS.
WE WERE  ACTING  BAD
TO TRY TO BLEND IN.
WE'RE JUST LOST TRAVELERS
WHO NEED SOME HELP,
AND WE'RE VERY SORRY
FOR ALL THE TROUBLE WE CAUSED.
COULD YOU FIND IT
IN YOUR HEARTS TO
HELP US OUT?
NO!
WE DON'T HELP STRANGERS!
AND WE AIN'T GOT HEARTS!
( all growling )
SO, SOMEONE'S
GONNA HIT US,
RIGHT?
WAIT A FLOSSIN' SECOND.
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH OF FAKERS,
AREN'T YOU?
JUST LIKE WANDER WAS!
WELL, OF ALL THE--
YOU--I CAN'T BELIEVE--
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I NEVER HURT ANYBODY.
I HEARD DOOMSTONE
WAS A TOUGH PLACE,
SO I ONLY FAKED TOUGH
TO SURVIVE.
OH, THAT'S SUPER NEWS!
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE
PRETENDING!
NO! (sobbing)
BOYS,
I WAS FAKIN', TOO.
AW, ME TOO!
OH, I WAS  SO  SCARED OF YOU!
THIS ISN'T EVEN
A REAL TATTOO.
I JUST WANT SOME
CHAMOMILE TEA.
I HATE THESE BIKES.
THEY'RE  SO  DANGEROUS.
I WAS JUST FAKIN' IT.
NICE TO MEET YOU!
I MISS MY GARDEN.
WELL, HOW ABOUT THAT?
YEAH, YEAH,
YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE JUST HAD TO ASK NICELY.
( glass breaks )
THIS SHOULD BE ENOUGH JUICE
TO GET YOU GUYS
WHEREVER YOU WANT TO GO.
AND A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR THE ROAD.
( sniffs )
AHH.
Y'ALL COME BACK AND VISIT,
YA HEAR?
WHY, THANK YOU.
WE SURELY WILL.
HEE HEE HEE!
TICKLED.
Wander:
WHAT A NICE BUNCH OF FOLKS.
Sylvia; AH, BUNCH OF SOFTIES
IF YOU ASK ME.
( loud banging )
( banging )
( banging continues )
UM...
YOU GONNA GET THE DOOR?
TO ARMS!
GUESS THEY DON'T
LIKE SOLICITORS.
MY FRIENDS FORGIVE US
THIS RUDE INTRUSION
ON THE FEAST MEANT TO HONOR
OUR MOST RECENT FEATS
OF STRENGTH AND BRAVERY.
WE NEVER COULD HAVE DREAMT
IT WOULD BE INTERRUPTED
BY OUR GREATEST OF ENEMIES--
( banging )
HOIST THE FOOD SACK
OF THURINGIAN!
( pulleys squeak )
( clank )
OUR MOST VALUABLE RESOURCE.
FOR CENTURIES, IT HAS HELD
OUR ANNUAL HARVEST
AND KEPT OUR PEOPLE FED
AND MIGHTY THROUGH EACH
OF THE SEVEN SEASONS.
WE PROTECT IT WITH OUR LIVES,
FOR WITHOUT IT,
WE WOULD STARVE!
( banging )
ND IT IS WHAT  HE  HAS COME FOR.
WARRIORS OF BAAAA-HALLA,
ASSEMBLE!
( war cries )
( bleating )
AAAH!
( all bleating )
( loud banging )
HEY, DUM-DUMS!
I THOUGHT I TOLD YA
NOT TO LOCK THIS GATE NO MORE!
WHAT AN ADORABLE
LITTLE TROLL!
( grunting )
THAT?
( laughing ) THAT'S WHAT
THEY'RE SO AFRAID OF?
AWAIT MY COMMAND!
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
PRINCE CASHMERE.
I HOPE YOU LOSERS
FILLED UP THAT
PRETTY LITTLE FOOD SACK
AFTER LAST YEAR--
I'M  HUNGRY.
YOU ARE NOT WELCOME HERE,
TROLL!
RETURN FROM WHENCE YOU CAME,
AND WE SHALL NOT HARM YOU.
(mocking)
"RETURN FROM WHENCE YOU CAME."
I'M CASHMERE,
AND I SOUND LIKE THIS--
HURDY GURDY, GURDY,
GURDY, HURDY, HURDY!
HOW DARE YOU!
I AM BORN OF THE SEVENTH TRIBE
OF MARKHOOR!
I SPEAK WITH
GREAT ELOQUENCE!
( evil laughter )
AAAH!
YEAH!!!
TAKE THAT, LOSERS!
OH.  I SEE.
Warriors: AAAAAAH!
Troll:
YOU CALL THAT HITTING?
IT FEELS LIKE
SWEET LITTLE KISSES!
(gasps) CUR!
I WOULD NEVER KISS ANYONE
EXCEPT SOMEONE WHO
I ADMIRED AND RESPECTED,
AND ONLY AFTER WE DATED
FOR QUITE A WHILE!
JA.  KISSING IS
VERY INTIMATE.
I'M SAVING MY FIRST KISS
FOR MY SPECIAL SOMEONE,
NOT YOU!
( evil laughter )
HERE WE GO!
WAAAAH-HA-HA-HA-HA!
HEROIC WANDER
AND MIGHTY SYLVIA,
I MUST COMMAND MY TROOPS
FROM THE GROUND.
CAN I RELY ON
YOUR BRAVERY
AND IMPRESSIVE
PHYSICAL PROWESS
TO HOLD DOWN
THE GREAT HALL?
HO HO! ARE YOU KIDDIN'?
FIGHTING, MY THING.
HELPING, HIS THING.
RIGHT, WANDER?
WANDER? WANDER!
YEP.
OH, THANK YOU,
MY FRIENDS.
GROUND SQUAD, FOLLOW ME!
ALL RIGHT, ARCHERS,
HEAD TO THE ROOF
AND START FIRING!
CATAPULT GUY,
MAKE IT RAIN!
GO! GO! GO!
( all baaing )
WANDER, LET'S GO!
BATTLE TIME!
DON'T I KNOW IT?
( growls )
NICE BEARD!
DID YOUR LITTLE SISTER
BRAID IT FOR YOU?
OHHH! AS A MATTER
OF FACT, SHE DID!
JA,  AND SHE DID
A VERY GOOD JOB!
SHE'S A TALENTED BRAIDER,
AND I AM VERY PROUD OF HER!
( evil laughter )
( laughter continues )
HURDY, GURDY, HURDY!
HA HA!
HEY, BUDDY BOY,
YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD BE AWESOME?
IF YOU HELPED ME OUT HERE!!!
I  AM  HELPING.
BOY, THOSE PEANUTS SURE KNOW
HOW TO GET STUCK IN THERE.
( Wander sucking his teeth )
( all bleating )
WHA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
HEY! WHY YOU GOTTA BE
SO STUPID?!
AAAH! I HAVE
ABOVE-AVERAGE INTELLIGENCE!
THANK YOU!
OUT OF THE WAY, BALDY!
IT'S NORMAL
FOR MY AGE!!!
( roaring )
HEY, CASHMERE!
I TOTALLY FORGOT
HOW LAME YOUR CAPE IS!
HOW...  DARE  YOU?!
MY DEAR SWEET NANA BA BA
MADE THIS FOR ME!
RRRRAAARRR!!!
WHAAAA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
AH-AH-AH-AH-AHHHH!
HEY, LAZY,
I'M THINKING OF A WORD.
IT STARTS WITH AN "H"
AND IT RHYMES WITH "HELP"!!!
AHHH. I  AM  HELPING.
OH, I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
CASHMERE! I'M COMING!
( roaring )
I IMMEDIATELY REGRET
THAT DECISION.
( slobbery growling )
SCORE! LOOKS LIKE THIS GUY
IS GONNA GET HIS FOOD SACK ON
AFTER ALL!
WANDER! WAKE UP!
THE FOOD SACK!
HUH? HUH? HUH?!
YOU!
HEY, YA DUMB YOKEL!
I'M TALKING TO  YOU.
HUH?
HMM.
YOU LOOK LIKE
A HAIRY SPOON!
( yawns )
YOUR SHOES
ARE OUT OF STYLE!
ARRGHH!
THAT'S THE STUPIDEST HAT
I'VE EVER SEEN!
( groaning )
WHAT THE--?
DING!
THE TROLL HAS BE SHRUNKEN!
THE SACK OF THURINGIAN
IS SAFE AT LAST!
( all baaing )
THANK GOODNESS!
NOW LET US PROCEED TO
STOMP UPON HIM!
OH, LOOK!
JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
Troll:
YOUR MOM IS UGLY!
YOU ARE SUCH A MEANIE!
YOUR DAD IS UGLY!
UH-UH!
YOUR GREAT-AUNT TWICE REMOVED
IS UGLY!
WASH YOUR MOUTH OUT
WITH SOAP!
( Troll laughing )
MY FRIENDS?
WHY DO YOU STAND IDLY BY?
NAY! NAY!  LYING  IDLY BY
WHENCE THE INVADER
THREATENS TO DESTROY MY PEOPLE!
WE CANNOT ONCE AGAIN AFFORD
TO FEED THIS MONSTER!
THEN STOP FEEDING HIM.
BUT THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE TRYING TO DO!
DUDE, JUST IGNORE THE GUY.
YOU GETTING ALL UPSET
JUST MAKES HIM STRONGER.
UH, YEAH. DON'T...FEED...
THE TROLL.
( evil laughter )
JUST GIVE ME ONE MORE,
YOU DUM-DUM!
Cashmere: NO!
GIVE HIM NONE!
DON'T YOU SEE, MY FRIENDS?
WE ARE PROUD AND BRAVE
AND STRONG.
WE ARE GOOD PEOPLE
WITH GOOD HEARTS.
AND WE ARE ALL BEAUTIFUL
ON THE INSIDE.
WE KNOW THIS TO BE.
SO WHY SHOULD WE CARE
WHAT THIS SAD, PATHETIC,
PITIFUL CREATURE
THINKS OF US?
YOU BELIEVE THAT
SCHMALTZY GARBAGE?
WHAT A BUNCH OF WUSSES!
( groaning )
AND--AND BABIES!
YEAH! YOU'RE SAPPY-WAPPY BABIES!
( groaning )
YOUR ARMOR COULD USE A POLISH?
YOUR HAIR IS KINDA MESSY?
YOU'RE TWO INCHES TOO SHORT!
YOUR MOTHER WEARS
COMBAT BOOOOOTS!
( all cheering )
( music, laughter )
HEY! YOU'RE ALL WIMPS!
WITH TINY MUSCLES!
YOU'RE WEAK,
AND YOUR FOOD
IS TERRIBLE!
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT IT ANYWAY!
HEY! PAY ATTENTION TO MEEEEE!
OHH!
( grunting )
( shouting, grunting )
( grunting continues )