♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laughter )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
DON'T DO IT, WANDER.
SYLVIA...
DON'T DO IT!
I...CAN'T HELP IT.
WANDER!
I GOTTA KNOW
WHAT'S IN THIS BOX!!!
NO, YOU DON'T, WANDER.
WE'RE GONNA DELIVER THAT BOX
JUST LIKE WE
PROMISED THAT GUY.
Sylvia: IT'S THE  LEAST
WE CAN DO.
AND WE'RE  NOT  GONNA OPEN IT,
JUST LIKE WE PROMISED.
LOOK, WANDER,
DON'T SWEAT IT.
IT'LL GO LIKE THIS:
WE TAKE A LITTLE DETOUR,
GET THE BOX TO GLEN--
WHOEVER HE IS--
HE OPENS IT RIGHT THERE.
YOU GO, "WHOA.
THAT'S AMAZING."
WE GET ON WITH OUR LIVES.
BA-DA-BING,
BA-DA-BOOM.
( whimpering )
YOU CAN DO THIS.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
( laughs )
WHATEVER'S IN HERE'S PROBABLY
NOT ALL THAT INTERESTING,
ANYWAY--
LIKE... ( scoffs )
BLANK ADDRESS LABELS...
OR STICKERS,
OR FLASH CARDS...
OR A CHOCOLATE SPOON,
OR A GREEN ERASER...
OR A DISPOSABLE "PILLA,"
OR A NIGHT VISION MONOCLE,
OR A FAKE LUNG,
OR TINSEL...
OR A BAT, OR A HAT,
OR A BAT WITH A HAT,
OR A HAT WITH A BAT!
HERE. GET YOUR MIND
OFF THINGS.
( sighs )
GREAT IDEA.
SINGING SONGS
ALWAYS SOOTHES MY SORROWS.
( plucking )
OH...
♪ BOX, BOX, BOX, BOX
♪ WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
♪ CLOCKS, BLOCKS,
ROCKS, LOX? ♪
♪ A FELLER NAMED JACQUES?
( discordant notes )
MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TURN IN.
( sighs )
EVEN BETTER.
SNOOZIN' A SPELL ALWAYS
WHILES AWAY MY WORRIES.
NIGHT, WANDER.
NIGHT, "BOX-IA."
( insects chirping )
( intermittent plucking )
( grumbles )
FOR GROP'S SAKE,
KEEP IT--
( plucking, whimpering )
YOU WERE UP ALL NIGHT,
WEREN'T YA?
THINKIN' ABOUT THE BOX?
OH, WE REALLY
GOT TO GET TO GLEN'S.
AND FAST.
OKAY, THESE SPACE COASTERS
ARE GREAT--
WAY  FASTER THAN THE ORBBLE
TRANSPORTER.
YOU WAIT HERE,
AND I'LL GET THE TICKETS.
SYLVIA?
( squeakily )
I DON'T THINK THIS
IS SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
( sighs )
LISTEN, IT'S--
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING INSIDE.
IT'S JUST A-- ( stammers )
A DUMB PAIR OF SOCKS.
( chuckles )
( whimpering )
WHENEVER YOU FEEL TEMPTED,
JUST SAY TO YOURSELF,
"PAIR OF SOCKS."
( whispers )
Pair of socks.
PERFECT.
YOU GOT THIS.
( crowd murmuring
indistinctly )
PAIR OF SOCKS.
GIVE ME THE BOX.
NO. GIVE  ME  THE BOX.
( screaming ) PAIR OF SOCKS!
PAIR OF SOCKS! PAIR OF SOCKS!
PAIR OF SOCKS!
( shouting gibberish )
( screams )
( gasps )
( cackling wildly )
( bawling )
GIVE US THE BOX!
♪
( screaming )
WANDER! OH, GEEZ,
I'VE BEEN LOOKIN'
FOR YOU EVERYWHERE.
YOU SCARED THE FLARF
OUT OF ME!
( gasping )
THERE WERE THESE GUYS!
THEN THERE WAS SCREAMING,
AND THE LAUGHING,
AND THE CRYING IN THE NIGHT!
W--JUST POINT 'EM OUT, BUD.
I'LL TAKE 'EM DOWN.
THEY'RE RIGHT OVER...
THERE?
MMM. COME ON, PAL.
YOU CAN REST ON THE TRAIN.
( train whistle blowing )
( snoring )
( Sylvia snorts, groans )
( gasps )
WANDER?
( echoing )
( distorted )
WANDER?
♪
♪ BOX, BOX, BOX, BOX
♪ WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
♪ MIGHT BE A ( indistinct )
♪ OR A BRAND-NEW
PAIR OF SOCKS... ♪
♪ BOX, BOX, BOX, BOX, WHAT--
( growls )
♪ BOX, BOX, BOX, BOX...
( repeating )
( growls )
( screams )
AAH!
( panting )
( sighs )
IT'S OKAY, BUDDY.
WE'RE HERE.
( train whistle blowing )
WHEW!
THANK GOODNESS THAT'S OVER.
NOW I CAN FINALLY FIND OUT
WHAT'S IN THIS B--
( groaning loudly )
( screaming )
FINAL STRETCH, PAL.
YOU CAN MAKE IT.
♪
HUH?
( sniffing )
COOKIES?
THE SALTY SEASHORE
OF TRALFAR FIVE?
( sniffing )
NANA'S OLD-TIMEY POTPOURRI?
I GOTTA KNOW
WHAT'S IN THIS BOX!!!
Sylvia:
RESIST IT, WANDER.
I KNOW YOU CAN!
( whimpering )
( gasps )
HANG ON, BUDDY!
♪
I DIDN'T OPEN THE BOX!
NO, YA DIDN'T, MY FRIEND.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
Wander: GONE FISHIN'?
( whimpering )
( screaming )
NO!!!
( both groaning )
♪
YOU CAN'T BOX ME, BOX-IA!
I'M GONNA BOX THIS BOX,
AND THERE'S ( indistinct )
BOX CAN BOX, BOX, BOX!
( sighs )
GO AHEAD. DO IT.
HUH?
LISTEN,  I  BELIEVE
YOU CAN OVERCOME THIS,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF YOU DON'T
BELIEVE IT YOURSELF.
( sighs )
I SURE HOPE GLEN
CATCHES SOME FISH SOON.
PROUD OF YOU, BUDDY.
AS AM I.
( gasping )
FOR YOU, GLEN.
Glen: THANK YOU, MY FRIEND.
THIS IS A FINE DEED
YOU HAVE PERFORMED.
( ethereal voice )
I AM A LORD OF ILLUMINATION.
( echoing )
AS ARE THEY.
UH-HUH.
SO...
WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
THE BOX...
WAS A TEST.
Lord of Illumination:
AND WANDER,
YOU PASSED.
WOW. THANKS.
THAT IS AMAZING.
SO WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
( chuckling )
NO, YOU SEE,
THE BOX WAS A SYMBOL.
BECAUSE YOU DID NOT OPEN IT,
YOU HAVE EARNED
STRENGTH OF CHARACTER.
MM-HMM.
BUT COULD YOU SHOW ME
WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
'CAUSE IT COULD BE
SO MANY THINGS.
LIKE A BAT, OR A HAT,
OR A BAT WITH A HAT,
OR A HAT WITH A BAT,
OR TINSEL,
OR A FAKE LUNG. OR--
THIS WHOLE THING WAS A SETUP.
THERE'S NOTHIN' IN THE BOX,
IS THERE?
YES. YES. YOU GET IT.
COULD YOU PLEASE
HELP ME EXPLAIN?
...PAIR OF SOCKS,
OR A PAIR OF SOCKS,
OR A PAIR OF SOCKS--
LISTEN, YOU COSMIC CREEPS,
MY BUDDY HERE DOESN'T  WANT
YOUR  GREATER CONSCIOUSNESS
HULLABALOO.
WHAT HE  WANTS
IS TO SEE  SOMETHING
IN THE BOX!
( rhythmically )
SO PUT SOMETHING
IN THE BOX.
( stammers in normal voice )
WE ARE THE LORDS
OF ILLUMINATION,
AND I DON'T THINK YOU CAN
TALK TO US THIS WAY.
( stammering )
OKAY, OKAY. IT'S COOL.
IT'S COOL.
( whispering indistinctly )
...FLASH CARDS, OR STICKERS,
OR BLANK ADDRESS LABELS,
OR A PAIR OF SOCKS--
UH, WANDER?
UH...
( ethereal voice )
BEHOLD.
Lord of Illumination:
( singsongy ) DUH-DA-DA!
Wander: OH,
WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT.
A PIECE OF STRING,
A HARD CANDY,
AN OLD PENNY, AND A "WORLD'S
GREATEST GRANDPA" KEYCHAIN.
♪
'KAY, THANKS.
SEE YA, FELLAS!
OUR INTENT
WAS TO TEACH WANDER,
BUT IT SEEMS AS THOUGH
WE  WERE THE ONES IN NEED--
OH, JUST STOP IT.
♪
( normal voice )
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE A GRANDPA.
YOU NEVER  ASK ME
ABOUT MY PERSONAL LIFE.
♪
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WOKE UP
THIS MORNING,
ALL I WANTED WAS A NICE PIECE
OF SLARNACK'S DELI'S
DELECTABLE JELLYFISH PIE.
( gagging )
BUT INSTEAD,
THIS IS HAPPENING!!!
( creature roaring )
♪
Wander: LET'S SEE
IF THE OLE HAT WILL HELP.
( groans )
THANK YOU, HAT!
( screaming )
( grunts )
( Wander yelling indistinctly
in distance )
Wander: OKAY, SYLVIA,
I'M GONNA JUMP,
AND YOU JUST REACH OUT
AND CATCH ME!
GOT IT?!
WHAT?!
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
Sylvia: ( in distance )
...SPEAK UP!
LOOK WHERE YOU ARE
AND LOOK WHERE I AM!
HMM.
♪
I MEAN SERIOUSLY,
HOW CAN YOU EXPECT ME
TO HEAR YOU FROM--OW!
Wander ( over phone ):
RING, RING, RING.
I SAID, "CATCH ME!"
( roaring )
REACH INTO THAT HAT
AND GET SOMETHIN' ELSE
TO GET US OUTTA HERE!
♪
( roaring )
OH, GIVE IT TO ME!
FLAMETHROWER. FLAMETHROWER.
COME ON, FLAMETHROWER!
YOGA MAT?
( chimes tinkling )
WIND CHIMES?
SCENTED CANDLE?
Woman ( on machine ):
TAKE A DEEP, CLEANSING BREATH
INTO YOU CHAKRAS.
OH! WHY WON'T THIS
OVERGROWN
( metal clangs)
SUN VISOR GIVE ME
WHAT I WANT?!
FUNNY THING, SYLVIE--
YOU SEE, OVER THE YEARS,
I'VE LEARNED THAT THIS HAT
DOESN'T GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU WANT.
IT GIVES YOU WHAT YOU  NEED.
AND RIGHT NOW, IT THINKS
YOU  NEED  TO CALM DOWN.
Sylvia: I...DO...
NOT...NEED...
TO...CALM...DOWN!
A STRESS BALL.
( groaning )
( spouts gibberish )
( panting )
W-WAIT, I--WHAT?
VICTORY DANCE!
♪
THE HAT WORKS FOR YOU,
NOT FOR ME.
LOVES YOU.
IT TOTALLY HATES ME.
( gasps )
WANDER.
WANDER!
WANDER!!!
Wander ( over phone ):
RING, RING, RING.
SYLVIA!
WANDER!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
SYLVIA?
SYL-VI-A!
( feedback whining,
Wander tapping microphone )
IS THIS THING ON?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
WANDER!
I CAN'T HEAR YOU AT ALL.
ARE YOU MOVING AROUND?
YOU SHOULD MAYBE
TRY MOVING AROUND.
( grumbles )
JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE!
HMM. OH!
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
TELL YOU WHERE  I  AM.
WELL, I'M NOT SURE
WHERE  I AM.
IT'S WET, DARK, AND WARM.
AND THERE'S WATER SLOSHING
ALL AROUND ME.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT ME.
I GOT THE HAT!
I'VE GOT THE HAT.
OH, WAIT--
YOU'VE GOT THE HAT.
JUST STAY PUT!
I'LL COME FIND YOU!
I GUESS I'LL JUST
STAY PUT,
AND YOU CAN FIND ME.
( grumbles )
Sylvia: HMM.
"WET,
"DARK,
WARM."
BINGO!
HANG ON, WANDER!
I'M COMIN' FOR YA!
♪
( creature roaring )
OOH, GROP.
ALL RIGHT, HAT,
IT'S JUST YOU
AND ME NOW.
NO MORE PLAYIN' AROUND!
THIS IS A MATTER
OF LIFE AND DEATH.
( creature roars )
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING FANCY,
SO HOW 'BOUT YOU JUST
GO AHEAD AND GIVE ME
ONE OF THOSE
LITTLE BALLS, OKAY?
♪
( creature roars )
LET'S DO THIS!
( roars )
( yells )
( creature groans )
( creature roars )
WHAT  WAS  THAT BACK THERE?
ARE YOU  TRYING
TO GET ME EATEN?
( inhales deeply, sighs )
OKAY. MAYBE I WASN'T
MAKING MYSELF CLEAR.
WE  NEED TO SAVE WANDER.
SO  WE  NEED TO GO  THERE
WITHOUT ATTRACTING ATTENTION
OF THE GIGANTIC,
ZBORNACK-EATING MONSTER.
UNDERSTAND?
GOOD. OKAY.
HERE WE GO!
♪
( siren wailing )
( yelling )
( roars )
( yells )
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
( sighs )
NOW YOU LISTEN HERE, HAT.
I WANT SOMETHING
TO FLY UP THERE.
AND YOU'RE GONNA
GIVE IT TO ME.  CAPISCE?
( gasps )
A JETPACK!
YES!
THANK YOU!
ENGAGE THRUSTER!
OH, GROP.
( Sylvia yelling )
( pinball effects )
( Sylvia grunting )
( grunting continues )
Wander ( over phone ):
RING, RING, RING.
HEY, SYLVIA.
IT'S ME, WANDER.
WHEN DO YOU THINK
YOU MIGHT GET HERE?
( creature growling )
NO BIG RUSH,
BUT JUST A HEADS-UP,
THE WATER'S NOW
UP TO MY-- ( gurgling )
WHAT?
( Sylvia yelling )
( grunts )
YOU! I'M GIVIN' YOU
ONE LAST CHANCE,
YOU EMPTY BRAIN-BAG!
( groans )
SO THAT'S HOW YOU'RE
GONNA BE, HUH?!
WELL, FINE.
FINE!
I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
( creature roaring )
HEY, YOU NO-NECK-HAVING,
HALITOSIS-BLOWING,
DENTISTRY-NEEDING MAGGOT!
COME AND GET ME!
( roars )
WHOA!
♪ RIDE, SYLVIA, RIDE
YEAH!
( laughing )
♪ RIDE, SYLVIA, RIDE
♪ NOW RIDE, SYLVIA, RIDE
HAH!
IN YOUR FACE, HAT!
Wander ( over phone ):
RING, RING, RING.
OH, HEY, SYLVIA,
I'LL ALWAYS L--
( gurgling )
I'M ALMOST THERE, WANDER!
HEE-YAH!
WANDER!
WANDER?!
( creature roars )
( screams )
( grunts )
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO SAVE WANDER
WHEN ALL I HAVE
IS THIS LOUSY,
BACKSTABBING, UNHELPFUL,
UNCOOPERATIVE HAT
THAT DOESN'T GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU  WANT
AND ONLY GIVES YOU
WHAT YOU  NEED?
( gasps )
DOESN'T GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU WANT.
IT ONLY GIVES YOU
WHAT YOU NEED!
( chuckling )
LOOK,
I  KNOW WE'VE
HAD OUR PROBLEMS.
YOU HATE ME,
AND GROP KNOWS
I HATE YOU.
BUT THIS IS  WANDER
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
HE'S OUR FRIEND,
AND I WILL DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES TO HELP HIM.
SO DO YOUR THING
AND GIVE ME WHAT I  NEED
TO SAVE WANDER.
( yelling )
ROLLER-SKATES?!
WHY, YOU--
( calmly )
NO--OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S COOL. THAT'S COOL.
I COULD WORK WITH ROLLER SKATES.
( inhales deeply )
OKAY. I'M READY!
ANY TIME NOW.
ANY...TIME.
ANY...
( creature roars )
I HATE YOU, HAT!!!
( screaming )
( guts burping )
I'M GONNA TEAR YOU
BRIM FROM BRIM!
WANDER!
( gasping )
HI, SYLVIA!
YOU'RE ALIVE.
YOU'RE ALIVE!
SO THAT MEANS YOU,
AND THE WORM,
AND THE FALLING INTO THE--
AND THE HAT--
THE HAT--
MWAH--WAS GIVING ME
EXACTLY WHAT I  NEEDED
TO FIND YOU!
OH, I LOVE THIS HAT!
I KNOW, RIGHT?!
NOW, TO GET ON OUTTA HERE.
PLEASE...ALLOW ME.
SLARNACK'S DELI'S
JELLYFISH PIE?
WHAT THE...
( gagging )
( groaning )
( gurgling )
( retching )
( groaning )
( vomiting )
Wander and Sylvia: WHOA!
LOOK, SYLVIA!
WE MADE IT!
SLARNACK'S DELI!
♪
I HATE THAT HAT.
( retching )
( panting )
( retching continues )
( creature vomiting )