♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit,
Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit
Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Hater! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit
Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit
Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit
Wander Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip yip yip yip yip ♪
LORD HATER:
( screaming )
Stupid Wander!
Blew up my top secret
storage facility
and stole back all the stuff
I rightfully stole first.
( scream )
How could this day
get any worse?
( scream )
( laughing )
Captain Tim! OK! OK!
I give! You win!
Who's a good boy?
You's a good boy!
Ha ha ha!
Stupid Dominator!
Stealing my planets!
I hate him so much!
( laughter )
Heel, Tim. Heel.
Stupid Dominator!
Blowing up my concert
to impress her!
I like her so much!
Ha ha ha!
Stupid--!
Dumb--!
Terrible--!
Worst--!
Day--!
Ever--!
( burping )
( laughing )
Oh, Tim, you always
brighten up a bad day!
Hahaha!
Stupid cafeteria!
Serving tacos when
I specifically asked
for taquitos!
Captain Tim, this is
the worst thing that
has ever happened!
The worst thing that
Tim?
Taquitos!
You rang?
Who are you?
I'm Tim,
the lovable Watchdog!
No, I'm looking
for Captain Tim!
Ooh, I'm a captain now?
What? Ew, no!
You're the wrong Tim
and always will be!
My mistake!
Tiiiiiiii...!
Yeah?
Oops, sorry. Not me.
Watchdogs!
We have toppled mighty empires,
laid waste to fearsome enemies.
But today we face
a mission more important than
any we've ever encountered.
(Weeping like a baby)
My Tim-Tim went bye-bye
and I don't know where he is
I miss my Tim-Tim!
(Weeping like a baby)
( cheering )
WATCHDOG: He's gone.
We survived!
The nightmare is over!
Happy Tim-Tim is gone?
Overjoyed!
Hahaha!
Whoo!
Oh, uh, sorry, sir.
I know you cared
for that... thing,
but Captain Tim wasn't
really a pet so much as a...
um, hideous monster trying
to maul everybody on the ship.
But he was my hideous
monster trying to maul
everybody on the ship!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
( sobbing )
Well, forget them!
I am the great
and terrible Lord Hater!
I get what I want,
when I want,
and right now
I want my buddy back!
I shall unleash
all of my power to find him!
Excuse me,
have you seen this Tim?
Hey, has anyone tried
to eat your face off recently?
Do you have a tummy ache?
'Cause sometimes he
spits acid in your tummy
while you're sleeping.
Has anyone seen Captain Tim?
( loud screeching )
Yeah. I've seen that... thing.
Every night in my dreams
before I wake up screaming,
drenched in sweat and regret.
So...you have
seen him then, or...?
I know his kind!
Arachnomorphs.
Blood-sucking,
acid-spitting beasts
that can tear through the hull
of your ship like tissue paper
or your entire crew...
That's my Tim-Tim!
Name's Ripov.
I've been trackin'
the trail of mayhem and tears
his species has spread
across the galaxy.
Kinda like a dogcatcher?
Yeah. Kinda.
But I'm always
one step behind them.
Never met anyone 'sides me
who came up against one
and survived.
With your help,
I can finally
hunt down this monstrosity
and every one of his kind!
I'm really just looking
for the one, but great!
Let's move!
LORD HATER: (singing sadly)
♪ My best buddy's
name is Captain Tim ♪
♪ There's no one in
the universe quite like him ♪
♪ Quick and snappy
happy little guy ♪
♪ I love him just
so much I think ♪
♪ I might  (sniff)
just  (sniff)  die... ♪
Hey! I'm having
like a moment here!
Quiet!
I'm scanning for traces
of the 'Morph's DNA.
Then I'll be able to track him.
( scoffs )
Nothing.
Wait, is this a robot arm?
Oh, sorry, that
was a whole thing.
Here, try this.
( squeaking )
Hey! Careful that's his
favorite Squeepy-beepy!
'Morphs don't have
a favorite anything!
They're instinct-driven
killing machines.
If you wanna survive,
remember,
they don't care
about Squeepy-Beepies
and they definitely
don't care about you.
( stone grinding sound )
That's not true.
Captain Tim's a g'boy.
Quinton VI.
'Morphs wiped out
a colonial mining operation.
Tried to take my arm with it.
Oh, yeah? Wander ruined
my invasion of Kameron,
so Tim cheered me up
with some love bites.
'Morph tried to eat me
alive on Wutani.
Drooly Acid Kisses on Cluckon.
Ambush at
the Farbrix Lavadrome!
Game of fetch
on Seacironicus V!
( both growling )
( Klaxon blares )
My grop.
So that's where they are.
What? What is it?
It's Arachnomorph
mating season.
Arachno-what's-this-now?
Every mating season,
the Arachno-Queen
summons all eligible males
to their home world.
( screeching )
( growling )
RIPOV:
They travel on solar winds
across the galaxy
to fight for the Queen's
honor and amusement.
LORD HATER:
Um, bros before Arachnos.
Tim would never leave me
for some monster lady.
RIPOV:  No emotion! Instinct!
They fight to the death!
And the lone survivor
will emerge as
the new Arachno-King.
LORD HATER:
Aw, Tim's a scrappy little guy!
He can take care of himself!
It's Captain Tim!
Pull over! Pull over!
The 'Morph home world.
After years of searching,
the war is almost over,
and nothing will
keep the weary warrior
from earning her rest
on the fiery field of--
I'm coming, Tim-Tim!
Don't open that...
...door.
Umm...
( screeching )
( mad laughter )
You bugs messed with
the wrong grizzled loner!
I'm not gonna stop until
I put down every last one of ya!
You're gonna what?
Bye-bye, Tim-Tim!
Get away from
my special little guy.
Rawr!
Tim-Tim! Come to da-da!
( snarling )
Are you nuts?
(grunt) They're mindless
killing machines!
( calling out )
( screeching )
Look who's (grunt)
talking!
( both screaming )
Ewww, gross!
You got a moist towelette
in one of those pouches?
Quiet, you idiot!
You don't want to alert...
( loud screeching )
...the...Queen...
( growl )
( loud screeching )
It's OK. Captain Tim will
rescue me any second now.
For the last time, no, he's--
Captain Tim!
Sir!
I'm sorry I let you go alone,
but I'm here to rescue you!
No!
Captain Tim!
Hater! I saw this missing
Tim sign and rushed to--
Captain Tim!
Wander! I saw this missing
Tim sign and assumed you would--
What!
Captain Tim!
Nope. Watchdog Tim again.
Hey, what's goin' on in here?
( screaming )
( growling )
( loud screeching )
( snarl )
( growling )
Captain Tim!
In your face, Ripov!
He beat up all those
other jerks and now he's...
...doing exactly what
I said he was doing.
He doesn't care.
He can't change.
Their just gonna
make more little monsters
And we're gonna be baby food!
Happy?
( loud screeching )
Tim!
Mmmm! I missed you so much!
Ha! Double fake-out!
Captain Tim
burned you good!
Aah! Captain Tim
burned me good!
Aaahhh!
Never leave me again.
Never ever ever.
You!
Pretty impressive.
Even I couldn't take out
a 'Morph Queen like that.
I guess bad things can change.
Ehhhhhhhhhhhhhhh?
( content growl )
Aww!
( screaming )
Heh, Heh. Baby steps.
Hee hee hee!
Quit it! OK! Hahaha!
Oh, Tim you always
brighten up a bad day!
( loud screeching )
( owl hooting )
SYLVIA:  Deep in
the darkest woods I hide.
I keep you safe
from what lurks outside.
Even the strongest
cannot resist my power.
I can strike anyone,
anywhere at any hour.
Only once you master me
will you defeat your enemy.
Yeesh. Creepy.
Ah, this riddle
doesn't make any sense,
but the map says
this is the place.
Somewhere in these woods
lies an ancient power,
a power that could
help us stop Dominator!
So all we have to do
is carefully sneak in,
run a meticulous
survey of the area,
approach the ancient power
with caution and...
You're already in there,
aren't you?
Um...
Isn't this is where
you leave me hanging
and charge headlong
into some horrible danger
you're somehow
oblivious to... or not?
( creepy music )
Wander, you're not...scared?
What?
Nooo, Of course not!
Everyday is an adventure and
everything is amazing, right?
I just...got a bad feeling
about this Sylvia...
this place gives me...
I'm sure there's puh-lenty of
other ways to thwart Dominator
that aren't hidden in
a dark and gloomy forest
of terror and despair.
So let's Orbble on
outta here and see--
Wander, nothing in this forest
could possibly be as terrifying
as Dominator destroying
the entire galaxy.
But what if there's
a Frankenstein in there...?
Wander, there is not a--
( roar )
Forest bad!
( crashes )
Well... there aren't
any in there now!
Seriously, what are
you so afraid of?
Come on.
Wander.
( Wander sighs )
You're right, Syl.
This ain't so bad!
( screams in fear )
Sylvia! We're already lost!
Wander! Just relax.
Try taking some deep breaths.
( wood creaking )
( creaking and snapping )
( snap )
( scream )
Wander,
leaves rustle in the wind.
Old trees creak.
( creaking )
And twigs are snapping
because I'm stepping on them.
( slow snapping )
( Wilhelm scream )
Aw, don't worry,
that's just a Wilhelm Warbler!
( Wilhelm scream )
Annoying and all over the place,
but totally harmless.
( impact grunt )
( chirping )
( slow creaking )
( bat calls )
( whispering winds )
Syl! Thing! Woods!
Wander,
there's nothing there.
Your eyes are just
spooking out your head, buddy.
And if there was?
Lady and Dutchess
won't let anything hurt you,
and neither will I.
( spooky noises )
( owl hooting )
Ha!
Now what?
( growling )
Wander, I don't know
what's gotten into you,
but you're seeing
stuff that's just not--
There!
OK, look...
Behind you!
Sylvia!!!
Wander?
Mime! Phantom!
Phantomime!
Oh, no, I've named them,
thus giving them power!
( whimpering )
Calm down, buddy.
Your super-vivid imagination
has taken the wheel
and is driving you bonkers.
You need a distraction.
Here. How about you
strum a happy tune
while I double-check
the scroll?
♪ Cat-sittin' for kittens ♪
♪ While wearin' my mittens ♪
♪ The thump a heart makes
when lovebirds are smittin' ♪
♪ Drawing a doodle of
a poodle named Noodle ♪
♪ The cinnamon scent
of warm blorpberry strudel ♪
♪ Old dusty scrolls on which
curses are written ♪
♪ Becoming a zombie
right after you're bitten ♪
♪ Dancing ghost mimes
that bounce just like springs ♪
♪ The dry mouth and shivers
that true terror brings... ♪
Oh, grop! What are
these terrible things?
( whimpering )
( screams )
( scream )
Guys, stop!
Wander.
OK, OK, it's all good, pal.
There's nothing around here
except your best bud
and I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you, got it?
Maybe you need some rest.
You're right, Syl.
As long as I've got
my bestest bud by my side,
I've got no reason to hide!
Bud by my side...
no reason to hide...
( snoring )
Sylvia? Hello? Syl...?
King Binglebord,
is that you?
( scream )
Phew!
Just a dream.
( scream )
Phew! That was just a dream.
Phew. Just a dream
in a dream in a dream.
Frankenphantomimenstein!
( scream )
Wander, you okay ?
Huh? Oh, wow,
what a crazy dream.
Wait, that ancient scroll?
Got it.
Did it give you
a great power?
Dom won't know what hit her!
Then that means...
There was nothing
to be afraid of.
( sigh )
Unless...
Awwww, man! Come on!
Sylvia?
Where are you?
Oh, right, I'm obviously
still dreaming.
( slap ) Nope, still there.
( slap ) Still there.
Oh no...
Sylviiiiiaaaaaaaahhhhh!!!
I noticed the fire
was dying so...I...Wander?
Wander? Can you hear me?
Wander, where are you?
Wan...der?
W-Wander...?
Don't goof around.
Sweet jumpin' flabbdraserry
in a handbasket,
he was right!
( scream ) Wander!
She'll find me.
She always finds me.
She'll find me,
they always find me.
They'll find me,
Mimes find me.
I'm really tired of screaming!
Aaaaaahhh!
Aaaaaaahhhhhhh!
( impact grunts )
Ah, you're OK!
Thank grop, you're alive!
Sylvia,
I've got a lil' hunch
we are not welcome
in these woods.
Agreed. Ancient power
or no ancient power, I say
get the grop outta here!
Ow!
Stop bouncin', ya creeps!
Oh, that's actually
way creepier.
I'm sorry, Syl!
This looks like the end!
Hey! You want me?
Come and get me.
But keep your jazz hands
offa my best friend!
No! You can't go
through her to get to me,
because you have to
go through me to get to her!
No, I'm gonna protect you.
Nuh-uh! Let me protect you!
Sylvia... look!
Huh? Where'd they go...?
Look, Syl. They only show up
when you're scared.
Ooo. Idea!
Wander? Wander?
Where are you?
I'm here, Syl.
( sighs )
Wander!
Hiya, Syl.
( sigh )
Wander!
Howdy.
How do you do?
Quit it.
Sylvia, I'm very, very, very,
very glad you're okay,
but I'm sorry we didn't
find the great power
to stop Dominator.
But we did find it, Wander.
The answer to
the scroll's riddle,
"Only once you master me
will you defeat your enemy."
It's fear!
There's more power
in overcoming your fear
than in any weapon.
Even Dominator isn't as scary
as the thought of losing you.
And without anybody to scare,
those Phantomimes are
powerless to petrify
any more people...
right?
( creepy circus music )