♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER OVER OVER
YONDER YONDER WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER,
OVER YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER
OVER, OVER ♪
♪ YONDER YONDER
WANDER WANDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
( rooster crowing )
UH, WANDER?
SH, HE'S SLEEPING.
THE NERVE OF SOME PEOPLE.
WANDER, WAKE UP, BUDDY.
WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE.
( yawning )
THEY MUST'VE NABBED US
WHILE I WAS CATCHIN' SOME ZEES.
HARD TO BELIEVE
I SLEPT THROUGH IT.
YOU, HOWEVER,
YOU CAN SLEEP
THROUGH ANYTHING.
HECK, WHEN YOU'RE
REALLY BEAT, NOTHING CAN...
...WAKE YOU UP.
( snoring )
WANDER, COME ON,
WAKE UP, BUDDY.
IT'S GONNA BE
A LONG DAY.
WANDER, WANDER,
COME ON. TIME TO WAKE UP.
( snoring continues )
( alarm ringing )
( cymbals crashing )
( playing banjo
off-key )
HM, COUPLE OF SLEEPYHEADS.
COME ON, LITTLE BUDDY.
TIME TO GET VAPORIZED.
REALLY? I THOUGHT HATER
WAS GONNA DIP 'EM IN LAVA.
NO, LAVA PIT'S
ON THE FRITZ.
AH, MAN. I LOVE THE LAVA.
I KNOW, I KNOW,
BUT VAPORIZATION'S
PRETTY COOL, TOO.
TIME TO BUST OUTTA
THIS SKULL.
( loud snoring )
ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
DOIN' IT YOUR WAY.
BRING IT ON,
YOU LITTLE MONSTERS!
OH, GROSS. CAN A LADY
GET SOME TOWELS?
- GUESS SO.
- YEAH, SURE.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
I MEANT
AROUND YOUR WAISTS.
- OH, MY BAD.
- THAT MAKES
WAY MORE SENSE.
THANK YOU.
WANDER.
WANDER, YOU THERE?
WANDER!
WORST IDEA
I'VE EVER HAD.
OH, NO, THIS IS TRULY
A DARK DAY FOR SYLVIA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I HAVE BEEN CAPTURED.
( relieved sigh )
HERE, LET ME
GET THAT.
AND WHAT DO WE SAY
WHEN SOMEBODY HELPS US?
( teeth chattering )
UH, THANK YOU, SIR.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
I SEE WE FINALLY
CAPTURED THAT HIDEOUS ZBORNAK.
ACTUALLY, WHILE SHE MAY NOT BE
CONVENTIONALLY BEAUTIFUL,
MANY PEOPLE FIND
HER PERSONALITY
AND STRENGTH OF CHARACTER
TO BE VERY ATTRACTIVE.
...IS WHAT SHE WOULD SAY.
SHE WOULD TOTALLY SAY
SOMETHING DUMB
AND CORNY LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, SOLDIER.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
IT'S...
( muttering gibberish )
BORING CONVERSATION
ANYWAY.
WHY, THE MAIN HANGAR!
- ( snoring resumes )
- HMM.
NOW I JUST NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO MASH THROUGH THESE MOLARS.
WANDER. WANDER?
WANDER!
WANDER, YOU FOUND
THE HANGAR RELEASE.
WANDER, PULL
THE GREEN LEVER.
THAT GREEN LEVER
OPENS THE MOUTH.
GLOWING RED COOKIE.
NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO. NO, NO.
( muttering gibberish )
( alarm blaring )
WOO-HOO!
LATER, LAME-OIDS.
WE ARE OUT OF HERE.
WELL, THAT'S NEW.
( evil laughter )
FORCE FIELD GENERATOR.
BOO-YA!
SUPER EXPENSIVE.
COULDN'T PAY PEEPERS FOR MONTHS,
BUT THE LOOKS
ON YOUR FACES...
TOTALLY WORTH IT!
AS LONG AS
THIS BABY'S ON,
YOU'RE NEVER
GETTING OUT OF HERE.
WANDER, BUDDY.
I KNOW YOU'RE PROBABLY
OFF DREAMING OF
FRENCH FRIED FLOWERS
AND DOLPHINS,
BUT I REALLY NEED YOU
TO WAKE UP RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, WEIRDO,
LET'S GET MOVING. WHOA!
OR DO I?
SIC 'EM, SLEEPYHEAD.
WHAT IS GOING ON
DOWN THERE?
- GET HIM!
- ( all shouting )
WANDER, WATCH OUT!
AND PIE MONKEYS
NEED BALLET LESSONS.
WANDER, THE CHEESE TOWER
IS TURNING INTO NARHWAL BACON.
AH, MY MOST HATED NEMESIS.
YOU'VE COME TO FACE ME
FACE TO FACE TO FACE.
WANDER, WATCH OUT.
THREE NOODLES ARE CONSIDERING
BUYING PLEATED KHAKIS.
GET OUT OF THERE.
NOW! FLARK THAT WET
SPRAGMUFFIN
WITH YOUR TOAD BANGER.
NO!
ALL RIGHT, WANDER,
TIME TO GO.
WANDER?
YEE-HA!
I JUST FEEL SO AWAKE!
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE SUN'S
SETTING,
BUT YOU JUST FEEL
ENERGETIC.
SENSIBLE, PERKY,
INDEFATIGABLE.
SYLVIA?
I JUST FEEL SO AWAKE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE SUN'S
SETTING,
BUT YOU JUST FEEL
ENERGETIC.
SENSIBLE, PERKY,
INDEFATIGABLE.
SYLVIA?
I'M HERE.
STOP THE BUS.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
CAMP HERE, HUH?
IT'S THAT NAP I TOOK.
AFTER A BIG NAP,
I ALWAYS HAVE TROUBLE
GOING BACK TO SLEEP,
BUT NAPS JUST FEEL SO GOOD!
I'M ALL, LIKE...
YEAH, THIS IS AWESOME.
OOH, NAPS!
SOMETIMES YOU WAKE UP
AND THERE'S THAT GUNK
IN YOUR EYES
AND YOUR MOUTH TASTES WEIRD.
AND I ALWAYS GET
THIS FUNNY CRICK
IN MY FOURTH VERTEBRAE.
DO YOU GET
A CRICK IN YOUR FORTH...
LOOK, BUDDY, I KNOW
YOU'RE JAZZED AND ALL,
BUT TODAY WAS TOTALLY NUTS,
AND I REALLY NEED
A SOLID SHUT-EYE SESH.
THINK YOU CAN LOCK UP
THE CHATTERBOX FOR THE NIGHT?
OF COURSE.
SO SORRY.
SEE? NO TALKING.
I'LL JUST BE SITTIN' HERE.
JUST PLAYIN' MY BANJO.
WANDER!!
IN CASE
I WASN'T CLEAR,
I NEED PEACE AND QUIET
TONIGHT, OKAY?
AND WHEN I SAY
PEACE AND QUIET,
I MEAN REALLY PEACEFUL
AND REALLY QUIET.
CAN YOU HELP ME
WITH THAT?
SYLVIA, MY FRIEND,
FOR YOU, I'M GONNA MAKE THIS
THE QUIETEST NIGHT...
( whispering )
EVER.
THANKS. I REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
( yawning )
( owl hooting )
SH!
WHO?
( snoring )
OH.
( leaves rustling )
( wings flapping )
( water rushing,
frogs croaking )
SH!
( gnawing quietly )
SH! SH!
SH!
SHH!!
- ( fire crackling )
- SH!
( chirping noises )
SH!
YEAH!
( stomach rumbling )
( paper crinkling )
( shoe squeaking )
( muffled yell )
( yells )
OOPS, FORGOT MY PURSE.
AND MY KEYS. OH!
CAROL, I SWEAR, YOU'D FORGET
YOUR OWN DEADLY VENOM SAC
IF IT WASN'T
ATTACHED TO YOUR THORAX.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED.
WE'RE GONNA LIVE FOREVER!
WHOO!
SYLVIA?
SYLVIA!
SYLVIA?!
SYLVIA, SYLVIA.
SYLVIA!
( muttering )
UH, WANDER.
SH, HE'S SLEEPING.
THE NERVE OF SOME PEOPLE.