♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
( crowing )
Okay, Wander,
I'm up.
You don't have to...
Since when am I
the first one up?
Good morning, Sylvia.
What a beautiful day.
Uh, you feeling okay
there, buddy?
Okay?
I'm feeling great.
How's about a rousing
"good morning" song
to get this day
started right?
( humming and playing
discordantly )
Wander, are you... sick?
Me sick? No way.
Sylvia, I can assure you
that I am the farthest thing
in the world
from being...
( sneezes loudly )
...sick.
I'm fine, Sylvia.
Really. I have too much
to do today to be sick.
I'll just power through
with the power...
friendship, smile, sunshine.
Banjo face or something.
Oh, no. The only way
you're gonna get better
is if you get some rest.
I'll take care
of everything.
Oh, don't go out of
your way for me.
I got this.
I got this,
I... I did it!
Okay, I'm gonna go get
some wood for a fire.
You stay here and rest.
Okay.
Wander, what are you...
Helping you collect
firewood.
( thunder crashing )
You don't have to
do anything, okay?
If you need something,
just ask.
Is there anything
you need?
Well, a glass of water
might be nice.
One water,
coming right...
...up.
- Stay.
- You got it.
Just as soon as I help you
start this fire... ( sneezes )
Buddy. ( sighs )
I know you always
wanna help,
but sometimes, you have to
take care of yourself first.
But I can't be sick.
I'm already way behind on
my morning helping routine.
If I don't help everyone
who needs helping,
terrible things
might happen.
Yeah, like you getting
so sick you can't help anyone.
So you miss out
on a few chores.
It's not the end
of the universe.
( muffled groan )
How about I do
your helping routine for you?
Really?
I don't know.
It's kind of
a tall order.
Come on. You've helped
me so many times.
It's time for you
to let me help you.
Just tell me what
you need me to do
and I will go do it while you
stay here and do nothing.
Well... okay.
I usually start my morning
by making brekkies for you,
me, and any locals
that might be around.
Did you feed
all the locals?
All the locals?
Next, I usually go give
Buster a good scratch
behind the ears.
You've gotta go hit
the snooze button
on Lord Hater's
alarm clock,
or he'll be really
cranky all day.
( screeching )
Give the black cube
a banjo lesson.
Raise the soles of Peepers'
shoes another eighth of an inch.
Oh, way to grow,
Commander Peepers.
Let's get awesome.
And feed Emperor Awesome's
white tigrexes.
Oh, the Watchdogs'
intramural tetherball finals
are today,
and they need a referee.
( whistle blowing )
- Point, Barry.
- Whoo hoo!
Give the floor at Blorpee's
a good mopping.
You missed a...
( sneezes ) spot.
Double check that no one
on Okeydokeyia needs help/
We never do.
Hit Hater's
snooze button again.
( screeching )
Change Huckleberry
Knucklehead's diaper.
Throw out anything that
doesn't have a name in
the Watchdogs' fridge.
Return any
lost socks.
( sobbing loudly )
Isn't that your sock?
Oh, yeah.
Make sure to hit
Lord Hater's snooze button
one more time.
- ( sneezes )
- ( screeching )
Oh, and there's
one more thing.
Water Dominator's cactus.
What? But... wait.
Why does Dominator
even have a cactus?
( sniffing wetly )
I left a cactus
in her guest bathroom
the last time
we were there.
I thought it really
brightened up the place.
( coughs, sniffs )
But you're right, Syl.
I shouldn't ask you
to do something so dangerous.
I will do it myself.
Flab drass it, Wander.
Crab-hammerin' cactus.
Where is this
guest bathroom anyway?
- ( loud sneeze )
- Oh, no.
Wander!
Hey, Sylvia.
Wait. Is this the...
Is this the guest bathroom?
But where's the cactus?
Yeah, that's what
I wanted to tell you.
I actually think
I might've just dreamed
about getting
Dominator a cactus.
You know what?
We should go get
her a cactus.
Call it Spike.
( sighs )
Stay there...
and rest!
Okay?
( sniffles )
Okay, Sylvia.
Oh, you seriously do
all this every day
before I'm even awake?
You're a very
heavy sleeper.
I could use a nap
now, that's for sure.
- Sylvia!!
- What is it?
I forgot to visit
Ms. Myrtle.
- Who's what now?
- ( sniffles very wetly )
Every week, I visit
this kindly old lady,
Ms. Myrtle,
and bring her a can
of snickerdoodles,
so we can chat,
we can catch up.
Oh, she loves snickerdoodles.
I can't let her down.
Oh, Wander, you not
visiting an old lady
is not the end
of the universe.
But, but, but!
Wander, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay. I will go visit
Ms. Myrtle for you.
But you have to promise me
that you're gonna
stay right here
and finally get
some rest, okay?
( sighs )
I promise.
Good. Now sleep.
You got it.
Sylvia!
The snickerdoodles!
Huh. Weird place for
some old biddy to live.
Ms. Myrtle?
- Ms...
- ( loud rumbling )
Ms. Myrtle?
I'm coming, Sylvia.
Who dares disturb the slumber
of Ms. Myrtle,
the eternal turtle,
keeper of the cosmos,
weaver of the very fabric
of the galaxy?!
Only I can save the universe.
Must deliver
snicker... doodles.
( sneezes )
Ms. Myrtle, please don't
destroy the universe.
I'm here, I'm here.
I brought your snicker...
( laughing )
And then the ballet
dancer says,
"Annihilation?
I thought her name was Susan."
( laughter )
Myrtle?
Oh, hello, Wander.
Your delightful friend
Sylvia and I are having
such a grand time.
But, but, but...
the cookies.
Why hasn't
the universe ended?
Oh, Wander dear,
though I do enjoy
your visits,
Sylvia said you were sick,
so I understand
why you couldn't come.
It's all right to let
other people help
you, you know.
It's not the end
of the universe.
( laughter )
Yeah, never hurts to
let someone... help.
( snoring )
Snickerdoodle?
( laughs )
Oh, no.
I can't stand those things.
( laughs )
Seriously, get them
out of my sight,
or I'll destroy
the universe.
Wow!
Sylvia, there's a whole
little planet in here
full of these little
itty-bitty Bitties.
Wander, put that down
before he sees you.
You dare touch the stuff
of the mighty wizard Neckbeard,
the all-knowing naysayer.
( coughs )
Sorry, sorry.
He was just making sure
no one else touches it.
And now, he's putting
it back, right, Wander?
( sighs ) Look, I'm like
the most laid-back guy there is.
But this is my shop
full of rare and dangerous
magic items too complex
for your tiny minds
to comprehend.
So if you don't wanna unleash
the wrath of the greatest
wizard in the universe,
you gotta treat
my word as law.
Law one: no touching!
Especially not my orb.
Feel me, muchacho?
Sorry, O great Neckbeard.
It won't happen again.
So you want me
to help you find something
to deal with
this "Dominator" lady?
Yes. We heard you have
an item of great power
that can zap her as
far away from this
galaxy as possible.
- Is that right?
- No.
I have something that will
translocate her
as far away as possible,
but "zapping,"
I have no idea
what that is.
Okay. We heard you have
an item that can
translocate her as far
away as possible.
Please, O mighty Neckbeard,
you're our only hope.
( loud groan )
Fine. Follow me.
Translocate you into
the next dimension, you big...
Wander, no!
Even if he is being
a real jerk,
this guy may have
the only thing that can help us.
So stay put,
don't question him,
and stay out of
his business.
What bad can come from learning
about these little guys?
I mean, the more you know,
the more you grow.
No. No knowin',
no growin',
or we'll be
throwin' outta here,
and Dominator will be
blowin' our galaxy to bits.
Well, your point
did rhyme, so okay.
Oh, what could one little
eyeball in somebody else's
business hurt?
( gasps )
Look at all those
little Bitties
on their itty-bitty world
leading their itty-bitty
Bitty lives.
Why, it's Billy Bitty.
He's lost his entire family.
Oh, no.
Will he have to
scour the universe
leaving no stone...
oh no, there they are.
It's Billy's wife Betty,
kissing him sweetly
on his way to work.
Meanwhile, Betty meets
her sister-in-law Beatrice
a professional masseuse
who's unlucky in love.
Unbeknownst to Beatrice,
her true love Benedict
is on the opposite
side of town,
searching for
something to fill
the Beatrice-sized
hole in his heart.
If only they could
find each other.
But I promised
not to mess with 'em.
Whoops.
( happy squealing )
Romance is in the air.
What was that?
- Banjo, huh?
- ( humming )
Yeah, well, I play...
the Theremin.
- ( tiny screams )
- Oh, no!
Oh, yeah, Theremins are
super complicated.
When people hear I play,
they're all, like,
"No way!
That's too hard."
But then I show them,
and they're, like,
"Stop. Stop being
a wizard immediately,
and be a pro musician."
And I'm all, "Thanks,
but I'm killing it
in the magic biz."
Hey, speaking of magic,
do you have any idea
where to find this zapping...
I mean, this translocating
device?
Because we know
your time is so very valuable,
and we are ashamed
to waste even a second of it.
Do not question
my methods, lady.
I am Neckbeard,
the all-knowing naysayer,
and my methods
shall be revealed
when I... see... fit!
( sighs )
I think it's over here.
( Bitties screaming )
Whew! You're safe.
Oh, uh... hi.
- Uh, folks call me--
- ( screaming )
( Wander stammering )
Hushy-hush,
hushy-hush.
Don't be in such
a crushy-rush.
Just hushy-hush,
hushy-hush,
and fussy won't make
such a fuss.
That was a close one.
Phew!
ALL: Phew!
Whoa!
Whoa!!
That's amazing.
Amazing!
♪ Yep a dip dip,
bip a ditty yip ♪
( repeating )
( laughter )
( laughing louder )
NECKBEARD:
What's so funny?
I'm just thinking
how foolish and lame we are
compared to you.
Huh, yeah.
That's pretty hilarious.
Oh, wow!
A statue for me of me?
I'm so flattered.
Oh, a bigger statue?
Thank you.
And you learned
to dance, too?
I told Sylvia
nothing bad would happen.
See, the more you know,
the more you...
( Bitties screaming )
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Ye... no.
Please, we really
need something.
Anything to stop
Dominator.
Which is it,
stop Dominator
or get rid of
Dominator?
Because those are
two different things.
Sounds like you need
an ultimate weapon.
A stick?
A bow staff.
In the proper hands,
it's the deadliest weapon...
- ( growling )
- ...but you wouldn't know...
Zapping device--
what, where, how?
Translocate.
Okay, okay.
Oblivion mirror.
It'll magically
transport anything
to the farthest regions
of the universe,
never to return,
but it only works once,
so you gotta be careful.
Finally.
Things are lookin' up.
( Bitties shrieking )
Empathy, not enemies.
Please there's plenty more
impressive things in the galaxy
to be into than little ol' me.
There's supernovas and meteor
showers and puppies and banjos
and best friends and triple
pickle pie and--
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
( screaming )
These guys were
mint in box.
They aren't ready to
understand a bigger universe.
They've already seen
too much.
That's crazy.
The more you know,
the more you grow.
Wrong, 'cause nobody
knows more than me.
And what they don't
know won't hurt them.
Here. Oblivion mirror.
Use this on Dominator
to send her wherever you want.
Now get outta here!
You mean it was
right there the whole...
Oh, never mind.
I thought we'd
never get outta here.
But Sylvia,
the Bitties.
Buddy, I know,
but we've got bigger problems
than those small fries.
If we don't stop Dominator,
there may be no galaxy.
Besides, aren't they
better off not knowing about
all the horrible stuff
that's out there?
- No.
- Good.
- Wait, what?!
Hey, nay!
I say nay!
( Bitties screaming )
NECKBEARD:
Magic. Magic, magic,
magic, magic!
Magic, magic,
magic, magic. Magic!
Just because you act like
you know everything
- doesn't mean you do.
- Magic!
You can't keep other people
in the dark
just to make yourself
seem smart.
Magic, magic, magic.
Magic, magic. Magic!
Magic!
Wow!
( growling )
( deep voice )
Magic!!
Hey! I have
what you want,
you have what I want.
Unwinnable situation.
Now give me the orb.
Wander, we need
that mirror.
But Sylvia, everybody
deserves a chance
to try and understand
the universe.
( all squeaking )
Sorry, buddy.
Say good-bye
to your Bitties.
'Cause they're goin' on
a long trip.
Yo, know-it-all.
Catch!
Not in the face,
not in the face!
Noooo!
Not cool. They're
too small and stupid
to survive out there
in the universe.
They're too primitive.
They're...
( squeaking )
...totally fine?
Sylvia, that mirror
only had one use.
We won't be able
to send Dominator away.
Good. That'll give
the Bitties a fresh
new galaxy to explore
where nobody else
can mess with 'em.
And I'm sure,
if we keep exploring,
we'll figure
something else out, too.
After all, the more you know,
the more you grow, right?
You are totally
gonna pay for that.
That'll be 17.50
for the mirror
and 37.99
for the orb.
That's amazing!
Amazing!
( Theremin playing )
( Bitties exclaiming )