♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laugh )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
YOU'RE TOO LATE,
EMPEROR AWESOME!
THE UNIVERSE WILL SOON BE MINE!
( laughs )
YEAH, RIGHT, BRO.
I'M TAKIN' YOU ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO AWESOME TOWN.
FIRE BREATH!
( roars )
YOU FOOL!
DON'T YOU SEE,
ONCE A MILLENNIUM,
THE PLANETS OF THIS GALAXY ALIGN
OVER THIS VERY SPOT!
AND TODAY, THE ONE MOST WORTHY
TO STAND HERE
IS NONE OTHER THAN I, LORD--
HATER, IS THAT YOU?
IT'S ME-- WANDER!
ARE YOU HERE TO WATCH
THE PLANETS ALIGN, TOO?
LOOK! I EVEN PACKED A PICNIC!
SOON, AT THE PRECISE MOMENT
OF THE COSMIC CONJUNCTION--
HATER! YOU REMEMBER ME, RIGHT?
AT THE PRECISE MOMENT
OF THE COSMIC CONJUNCTION,
A CELESTIAL STAR BEING
OF INFINITE POWER
SHALL COME FORTH!
I TRAVEL THE GALAXY,
I'M ABOUT THIS TALL,
WEAR A HAT, AND SOMETIMES
I MAKE THIS FACE....
OR THIS ONE...
OR THIS...
OR SOMETIMES
IF I'M FEELING REALLY CRAZY...
STAR BEING OF INFINITE POWER,
COME FORTH AND GRANT WHOEVER
STANDS HERE A SINGLE WISH!
AND MY WISH WILL BE
TO CONTROL THE ENTIRE UNI--
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERIN'
WHERE BY BEST PAL SYLVIA IS,
HUH?
NO! STAR BEING--
NO, I SAID THAT ALREADY!
OH, WHERE WAS I?!
SHE WANTED TO COME, BUT SHE
HAD TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
BORNAX ONLY GO ONCE
EVERY, LIKE, FIVE MONTHS.
CRAZY, HUH?!
SHE TOLD ME IT TAKES A WHILE
AND IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING,
AND SO SHE DOESN'T WANT
EVERYBODY KNOWING ABOUT IT.
SO SHE SAID, "WANDER, DON'T GO
BLABBIN' LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO."
OH.
I DON'T CARE!
WHERE? I DON'T KNOW WHERE
SHE'S GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
WHO DO YOU WANNA KNOW?
WEIRD.
IT'S OKAY, THOUGH,
'CAUSE I PROMISED HER
I'D TAKE PICTURES!
SMILE!
DUDE, TEXT ME THAT PHOTO!
ANYWHOSER, I'M GONNA
GET OUT OF YOUR HAIR
AND GO FIND
A GOOD WATCHIN' SPOT!
LATER, HATER!
SIR? SIR! SIR!
I'M COMIN' FOR YA, HATEY.
FISH FIGHTERS,
BATTLE MIX TRACK 17! PUMP IT!
♪ LET'S GET AWESOME
PEEPERS, FLAMING SKULLS! NOW!
ALREADY LOADED, SIR.
♪ LET'S GET AWESOME
EXCELLENT!
NOW, SIR,
THE TRAJECTORY IS LOCKED.
SO YOU NEED TO HIT THE TRIGGER
EXACTLY WHEN AWESOME'S TROOPS
REACH THE BOTTOM OF THE--
PEEPERS, ARE YOU TELLING ME
WHAT TO DO?!
OF COURSE NOT, SIR!
CARRY ON.
( chanting )
AWESOME! AWESOME! AWESOME!
TEN...
OH, YEAH!
NINE...
UH, UH, UH-UH.
EIGHT...
WHOA... WHOA... WHOA...
( grunting )
( continues grunting )
HERE WE GO, PICNIC TIME!
( sighs )
( grunts )
HMM.
LATCH.
OH, WILL YOU--
COME ON, JUST UNDO THE LATCH.
NO, NOT THE--
WHAT'S HE DOING?
IT IS SO OBVIOUS.
( grunts )
SIR!
HUH?
♪ LET'S GET AWESOME
AAH! SEVEN, SIX, FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE! GO!
♪ AWESOME, AWESOME
( laughs )
BRICK!
( groaning )
TAIL, TAIL, AND LASER!
AAH!
( grumbling )
Wander: OH, THE LATCH!
SILLY ME!
SERIOUSLY?!
SIR, DON'T WORRY!
WE STILL HAVE DEFENSE PROTOCOL
EPSILON XO973 TESSERACT!
( roars )
LET'S DANCE, FISH MAN!
BRO, DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HOW HARD I SLAM?
DINOSAUR CHARGE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SYLVIA'S MISSING THIS.
WELL, THAT IS JUST AWFUL!
I ALMOST ATE WITHOUT
OFFERING TO SHARE.
( laughs )
NOOGIE, NOOGIE, NOOGIE!
HEY THERE, MR. ROBOT MAN!
YOU WANT A SANDWICH?
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD!
HE AIN'T LYIN'.
IT'S LIGHT YET FILLING!
I KNOW, RIGHT?
COME ON!
I ONLY HAVE TURKEY LEFT,
BUT I'LL LET YOU PICK!
MUSTARD OR MAYO?
( roars )
I DON'T WANT A SANDWICH!
BOOYAH!
♪ AWESOME, AWESOME
I'LL JUST LEAVE THIS HERE
IN CASE YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
( whispers )
IT'S THE MUSTARD.
Peepers: SIR! SIR! SIR!
WHAT?!
THAT!
AND THAT!
( chanting )
AWESOME! AWESOME! AWESOME!
I'M COMIN' FOR YA, BABY!
( laughs ) GOT FORCE FIELD?
BOOYAH!
BRO, SERIOUSLY,
CAN WE WRAP THIS UP?
I HAVE A TANNING SESSION
IN, LIKE, 15.
THE COSMIC CONJUNCTION
IS AT HAND!
SOON THE CELESTIAL BEING
WILL GRANT ME MY WISH!
AND THE UNIVERSE
WILL BE MI--
Wander: ME OH MY!
HATER, YOU FOUND
THE PERFECT SPOT
TO WATCH
THE PLANETS ALIGN!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
FRONT ROW SEATS!
GET OUT OF HERE!
OKEY-DOKE.
BONK!
SORRY, HATER,
I WOULD IF I COULD,
BUT THERE SEEMS TO BE
SOME KIND OF FORCE FIELD.
( grumbling )
( slowly ) SORRY,
I CANNOT GIVE YOU ANY POPCORN.
( slowly )
THERE IS A FORCE FIELD.
( roars )
HERE YOU GO.
( roars ) GET BACK HERE!
SLOW DOWN!
I JUST WANNA DESTROY YOU!
SORRY, LORD HATER.
DID YOU WANT THE MAYO?
♪
( Hater panting )
YOU KNOW WHAT, HATER?
I WAS WRONG!
THIS IS
THE PERFECT WATCHIN' SPOT!
YOU CAN SEE EVERYTHING
FROM UP HERE!
THE PYRAMID, THE PLANETS,
THAT SHORT GUY
ABOUT TO RECEIVE
SOME SORT
OF ULTIMATE COSMIC POWER.
HUH?!
UH, UH, OH, YEAH!
♪ AWESOME
NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO!
OKAY, GO, BUT I STILL THINK
THIS IS THE BEST WATCHIN' SPOT.
NO!
NO! NO!
( roars )
NO!
YES! YES! YES!
YOU LOSE, HATEY!
( laughs )
THE UNIVERSE IS--
NO!
YEAH! LORD HATER!
NUMBER ONE SUPER STAR!
RULER OF THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE!
( whirring )
HEY THERE.
SO, UH, I'LL BE THE ONE
GRANTING YOUR WISH TODAY.
OKAY?
YES! I WISH--
Wander: YOU KNOW, HATER,
WHEN YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
BEST SPOT EVER!
AAH!
OW! MY EYE!
SO THIS WISH, IS THIS A THING
YOU'RE STILL WANTING OR NO?
YES! OF COURSE!
I WISH--
LOOK AT THAT GUY!
HE IS JUST OUT OF THIS WORLD!
LITERALLY.
I WISH--
OKAY, NOW ME AND YOU.
I-I WISH--
NOW FOR THIS NEXT ONE,
MAKE YOUR SILLY FACE!
YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO TAKE A SILLY ONE!
I WISH YOU WOULD
LEAVE ME ALONE
FOR FIVE SECONDS!
YEAH, OKAY,
I CAN SWING THAT.
( whirring )
HUH?! NO, NO, I MEAN--
THAT IS NOT WHAT I MEANT!
DO OVER! DO OVER!
SORRY, UH, MAYBE
NEXT MILLENNIUM.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
'CAUSE A SILLY PHOTO
SHOWS YOU'RE HAVIN' FUN,
AND YOU ALWAYS WANT
TO REMEMBER HOW MUCH FUN
YOU HAD ON
A DAY LIKE TODAY.
DON'T YA, HATER?
THAT ONE'S A KEEPER.
( toilet flushes )
LORD, ALMIGHTY. SURE ARE SOME
FANCY BATHROOMS THEY GOT HERE.
SO WHAT'D I MISS?
WELL...
GOOD GROP! THIS PLACE
IS CRAWLING WITH WATCH DOGS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO FIND
A SNEAKY WAY OUT OF HERE.
AND FAST!
( grunting )
LET ME TIDY THESE
UP FOR YA!
WOULDN'T WANT YOU
LOOKING LIKE A SLOB.
WANDER, WE ARE WANTED
FUGITIVES, WE'VE GOT
TO LAY LOW!
WELL, I DON'T WANT TO LAY LOW.
WHEN I SEE SOMEONE
WHO'S A-NEEDING,
I JUST GOTTA HELP.
IT GIVES ME THIS
FEELING THAT STARTS
DOWN IN MY LEFT TOE,
RISES UP THROUGH
MY GUTTY WORKS,
MAKES MY HEART ALL
WARM AND TOASTY,
FLOATS UP PAST THE DANGLY
THING IN MY MOUTH--
UVULA.
AND ENDS AT
THE TOP OF MY HEAD!
( sing-songy )
IT JUST FEELS SO GOOD.
PHEW!
ARGH!
LISTEN, I KNOW HELPING
FOLKS IS OUR THING,
BUT UNLESS YOU WANT
TO HELP YOURSELF INTO
LORD HATER'S BONEY HANDS,
YOU GOTTA MEASURE
JUST HOW IMPORTANT
EACH GOOD DEED IS.
KEEPING YOURSELF
AND YOUR BUDDY OUT OF
AN EVIL WARLORD'S PRISON?
( whistles )
HIGH.
HELPING SOME GUY
TIE HIS SHOE?
( whistles )
LOW. WAY LOW.
THERE THEY ARE!
YOU SEE THAT SHIP?
Sylvia: I'M GONNA SNEAK
OVER THERE AND HOTWIRE IT.
AND WHEN I GIVE THE SIGNAL--
( yelling )
YOU COME RUNNING,
AND DOO!
WE WILL BLAST OFF
OF THIS ROCK TO SAFETY.
NOW, JUST STAY HERE
AND DON'T CALL ATTENTION
TO YOURSELF.
THIS PLACE IS CRAWLING
WITH WATCH DOGS.
GOT IT?
YESSUM.
GOOD.
( gasping )
( clanking sounds )
( yelling )
( squeaks )
AH, WAIT!
( grunts )
FLAB CRABBIN'
HAMP SPANGLER!
A ROCK?
YOU BLEW OUR
ESCAPE FOR A ROCK?
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM?
YOU DROPPED THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
BOTCHED OUR ESCAPE
FOR SOMETHING
AS UNIMPORTANT AS--
MY BABY!
BABY?
BABY!
( giggling )
( all giggling )
OH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
YOU'RE SO WELCOME!
OKAY, NEW PLAN.
ALL WE GOTTA
DO IS FIND
AN INTERDIMENSION...
INTERDIMENSION...
THERE!
Sylvia:
INTERDIMENSIONAL DOOR.
OUT OF MY WAY!
WANTED FUGITIVES COMING THROUGH.
MOVE IT, MOVE IT, MOVE IT!
WATCH DOGS?
HA!
THEY SHOULD CALL THEM WATCH-US-
ESCAPE DOGS, HUH, WANDER?
I LOVE HOLDING HANDS.
WAIT! STOP!
OUTTA MY WAY!
THIS IS A MATTER
OF LIFE AND DEATH.
( grunting )
GOT IT!
PHEW!
REALLY? REALLY?
YOU RUINED ANOTHER PERFECT
GETAWAY FOR--
AHH! OH, MY STARS.
I COULD HAVE
BEEN KILLED!
MY DEAR BOY,
I OWE YOU MY LIFE.
HOW CAN I EVER
THANK YOU?
( squealing )
PHEW!
( roaring )
ALL RIGHT,
NEW, NEW PLAN.
WANNA PLAY DRESS UP?
WHEN DON'T I?
GO!
NOW, WANDER, IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT THAT YOU STICK
TO THE PLAN.
YOU'VE GOT TO PRETEND
TO BE MY BUTT LONG ENOUGH
FOR US TO ESCAPE.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
Sylvia : HANG ON!
HERE WE GO!
WHOO-HOO!
SEE YA LATER, SUCKERS!
WHO LOOKS STUPID NOW?
( belches )
( screaming )
STAND BACK.
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
EVERYTHING IS UNDER CONTROL.
GENTLEMANS, PLEASE.
MIGHT I PROPOSE
A PROPOSITION TO YOUR PERPLEXING
AND PONDEROUS PEANUT PROBLEM?
THERE. AND NOW YOU GOT--
Both:
PEACE!
BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
DROP YOUR WEAPONS.
THE WAR IS OVER!
( cheering )
PEACE!
EXCUSE ME,
YOUR TINYNESS,
MAY I BORROW YOUR
NATIONAL TREASURE
FOR A JUST A MOMENT?
THANKS.
YOU RESCUED A BABY.
YOU SAVED A MAN'S LIFE.
YOU STOPPED A 1,000-YEAR
WAR. I GET IT,
YOU'RE A HELPFUL GUY.
OH! SYLVIA.
YOU'RE MAKING ME BLUSH.
BUT YOU ARE GOING
TO HELPFUL US TO DEATH.
PLEASE, NO MORE HELPING!
AND IF YOU MUST HELP
SOMEONE, THEN HELP ME
HELP US TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I TOTALLY GET IT.
FROM NOW ON,
NO MORE HELPING.
FINALLY.
THANK YOU.
( sighing )
SO, HERE IS THE NEW,
NEW, NEW, NEW,
AND MAY I ADD,
LAST, PLAN.
( fly buzzing )
UGH! THIS PLAN--
STINKS. I KNOW.
BUT IT'S THE BEST
WE'VE GOT.
Sylvia: OKAY, SO THIS
SEWAGE PIPE LEADS
TO THAT GARBAGE BARGE,
WHICH WILL BE LEAVING
THE PLANET IN PRECISELY
THREE MINUTES.
AND WE'D BETTER BE
ON IT WHEN IT DOES.
GOT IT?
NO HELPING.
OKAY: ONE, TWO, THREE...
THEY COULD BE ANYWHERE,
SIR.
IT WOULD BE HELPFUL
IF WE HAD SOME IDEA
OF HOW TO FIND THEM.
HELPFUL! THAT'S IT.
( whispering )
( screaming )
HELP!
( whimpering )
( grunting )
HELP!
( whimpering )
( screaming )
( sighing )
THAT'S BETTER.
( clanking sound )
HERE, YOU DROPPED THIS.
( gun charging up )
WHAT? WAIT!
SYLVIA! SYLVIA!
SYLVIA...
BOY, APPREHENDING YOU
IS REALLY GONNA HELP
MY STANDING
WITH LORD HATER.
SO, THANKS!
WELL, I LOVE TO HELP.
IT'S A FEELING THAT STARTS
DOWN IN MY LEFT TOE,
RISES UP THROUGH MY GUTTY WORKS,
MAKES MY HEART ALL WARM
AND TOASTY,
FLOATS UP PAST THE DANGLY
THING IN MY MOUTH--
UVULA.
AND ENDS UP AT
THE TOP OF MY...
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
( explosion )
( screaming )
( squealing )
SYLVIA, I'M SO HAPPY
YOU CAME BACK.
I HARDLY NOTICED THAT
YOU SMELL LIKE SPOILED
FISH, ROTTEN EGGS,
AND MOLDY SNEAKERS.
WELL, WHILE I WAS
SLUSHING THOUGH THAT PIPE,
( shudders )
I GOT TO THINKING.
HELP MYSELF ESCAPE?
( whistles )
OR HELP MY BEST FRIEND.
SYLVIA, YOU'RE GLOWING.
THIS? I THINK THAT'S FROM
THE RADIOACTIVE SEWAGE.
OH, THAT'S... BEAUTIFUL.
NOW MARCH!
SO, WHAT'S THE NEW, NEW,
NEW, NEW, NEW PLAN?
ASIDE FROM TAKING A BATH,
I KINDA DON'T HAVE ONE.
( squeaking sound )
OH, GOD!
Both:
YAY!
( yelling )
HMM?
( fly buzzing )
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
SEE?
THAT'S THE OTHER NICE
THING ABOUT HELPIN' FOLKS.
SOMETIMES THEY HELP
YOU RIGHT BACK.
BUT BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
THIS IS THE DIRTIEST
CLEAN GET-AWAY
WE'VE EVER MADE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
HELP TIDY UP!
( ants squeaking )