♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander, Wander!
Over, over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
All right!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander, Wander!
Over, over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
( frantic clucking )
That's it,
run, you chickens, run!
For, here to destroy
your fowl little lives
is none other than
the Duke of Dread,
the Monarch of Mayhem,
the Emperor of Evil,
Lord Hater!
I don't get it.
Oh, our leader Lord Hater
was supposed to show up
and act all evil
and stuff but--
Nobody move!
( knocking on door )
PEEPERS: Lord Hater?
Are you in here?
LORD HATER: No.
Maybe.
Go away.
Sir, you missed your cue.
The Cluckons
won't surrender without you.
So?
What's the point anyway?
What's the point?
Sir, if Cluckon falls,
we'll control all of
the Zegma System!
All of it!
Just like we've always
dreamed of doing!
( mumbling )
I'm not feeling it anymore.
You are peeling apples
to the core?
I'm not feeling it anymore.
Stealing pennies
from the store?
I'm not feeling it anymore!
Earring fell on the floor?
( clearly )I said
I'm not feeling it anymore!
Evil used to be all...
( roaring )
Now it's just all...
Know what I mean?
Everybody back in the ship!
Nobody move, you're still
almost conquered, okay?
We'll be right back.
( chickens clucking )
So you're in a bit
of a slump.
That's fine.
Happens to everyone.
You just need to do
something to remind yourself
how fun evil can be.
Something like--
Blowing up a moon.
Come on,
I know you want to.
( cheering )
Blowing up a moon
not doing it for you?
That's fine.
I ordered the citizens
of Ionia 7
to make a giant statue of you
out of themselves.
Eh?
( frustrated groaning )
What if we terrorize
the Warrior Women of Amazonia?
That always cheers you up!
Eh?
( groaning )
PEEPERS: Awaken
the space demon Tormento?
It's Tormato!
( muffled screaming )
Loot all the loot
from Museopolis?
Eh.
Mess with Greg?
"Eh," it's all
a big bunch of "eh."
( sighs )
I'll be in my room.
Sir, listen we've been
working really hard
on taking control
of the Zegma System for months.
Cluckon
is the last step,
and it's just sitting there,
waiting to be conquered.
So?
Get off your bony butt,
do your stupid job,
and conquer 'em already!
( growling )
I mean, you want to
talk about it?
( sighs )
No, it's just...
I don't know.
When did being evil
become so complicated?
I mean, it used to be so cool,
you know?
Back in the old days,
just being a jerk,
cruising around the galaxy,
picking on the weak
and defenseless.
It just made me
feel so awesome!
And now I got this big ship,
and this army
and these responsibilities.
You make the plans,
the army conquers the planet,
and all I do
is come in at the end
and do my big scary...
( roars )
( evil laughter )
...thing.
It's...
It's just no fun anymore.
Sir, I have an idea.
PEEPERS: Ignition.
Rear-view mirrors.
Seat belts for safety.
♪ Hater!
( tires screeching )
Bet you didn't even know
we restored your old van, huh?
Kinda cool, I guess.
What lame place
are you taking me to now?
Oh, you'll see.
So you miss the old days, eh?
Need to be reminded
of why you got into
evil in the first place,
huh?
You mentioned the weak
and defenseless.
Well, I'd like you to meet
the Mooplexians.
Whoa, they're so dumb.
I mean, look at 'em,
all weird and stuff!
Man, I just want to go up
to their dumb faces and...
Rarrhh!
Well?
( groaning )
Peepers, that felt good.
I want more.
BOTH: Yeah!
♪ When you feel alone
like your top's gonna blow ♪
♪ And you're ready
to drill it through ♪
♪
♪ 'Cause hate's great
♪ You know you like it,
hate's great ♪
♪ Hate's great,
makes you feel awesome ♪
♪ Being evil is good
So dumb!
♪ Getting down
and getting on your nerves ♪
♪ And you don't exactly
know just why ♪
♪ No need to bother
to figure that out now ♪
♪ Just try and make them cry
♪ 'Cause hate's great
♪ You know you like it,
hate's great ♪
♪
♪ Hate great,
makes you feel awesome ♪
♪ Being evil is good
How you feeling now, sir?
Bad?
So bad!
♪ Now let's be clear
when I say bad is good ♪
♪ I don't mean that
literally ♪
Take that!
Oh, you tell 'em, sir!
♪ Bad is just good
while it's-- ♪
♪ Hate's great
♪ You know you like it,
hate's great ♪
♪
♪ Hate's great
♪ Being evil is good
( guffawing )
♪ Hate's great
♪ Being evil is good
LORD HATER: Yes!
I am back, baby!
Phew!
Finally.
You hear that, universe,
the Duke of Dread,
the Monarch of Mayhem,
the Emperor of Evil
has returned!
Now with my mojo back,
there is nothing that can stop
Lord Hater!
The greatest
in all the galaxy!
( evil laughter )
Hate's great!
Best villain!
( evil laughter )
Huh?
We tire of the sense
of superiority
you seem to garner from
picking on the physical shells
that we happen to inhabit.
Perhaps you need to see
just how insignificant
your so-called greatness
really is.
Little do you know
that we have evolved beyond
impressive corporeal forms.
Our real lives
are spent in our minds!
We sail the seas
of cosmic consciousness,
a vast and endless ocean
of knowledge
in which you are nothing
more than a miniscule molecule
drowning
in misunderstanding.
( giggling )
Now back in your van,
sad little man,
and never forget
how you, Lord Hater,
are so not the greatest
in all the galaxy.
Now be off with you!
Oh, great and noble
Mooplexians,
we humble ourselves
in the presence
of your all-knowing wisdom.
Seriously, we came
all this way to see these guys?
Ultimate cosmic knowledge
comes in all shapes and sizes.
Forgive her!
She knows not
what she does.
So how long do we
have to stay down here?
At last.
The Lost Temple of Tagathoria!
Resting place of the light half
of the all powerful
Sword of Synergy!
Which, when combined--
( exclaiming )
( mutters )
Which, when combined
with my dark half,
graciously lent to me by
the warrior monks of Malakar...
will give me
the power to conquer...
the entire univer--
Too late, Hater!
The sword of synergy
will soon be where it belongs.
In the hands of a true hero!
Brad Starlight!
I should have known
you'd show up
with your stupid chin
and your dumb cape!
It's not dumb!
It's hand-stitched!
And my chin is perfect.
( gasps )
( screaming )
You'll never defeat me,
Starlight!
You might as
well give up now!
Not as long as
there's an ounce of strength
left in my lithe,
well-sculpted body!
Hey, hello.
( screaming )
WANDER: Bradley!
Hateley!
Buddies!
What are you
sillies doing here?
Hey, I'm playing
hide and seek with Sylvia.
Y'all wanna play too?
Okay.
Come and get me!
TOGETHER: Wander?
I can't believe
he came here to stop me!
Whoa, whoa.
Came here to stop you?
Uh, yeah,
he's my greatest enemy.
WANDER: Hey, guys,
hide and seek, let's go!
Wander ruined my wedding!
If it wasn't for him,
I'd be married
to a super pretty princess!
So? Wander ruined
dozens of my plans,
one of which also
involved my wedding!
Really?
How?
His dumb friend Sylvia
was in disguise.
You mean his steed.
You almost married his horse!
It was a very convincing
disguise.
WANDER:
Bet you can't find me!
( growling )
Want to put this whole
sword thing on hold for a sec
and go destroy him?
So you're offering me
your services to help me
in my quest
to destroy Wander?
Yeah, sure, whatever--
By Zargo, I'm in.
To battle!
LORD HATER: Here, follow me.
Great idea.
The scout goes first,
the leader takes up the rear.
What--
No, I'm the leader.
That's why
I'm in the front.
Leading.
( growling )
First one to find
Wander is the leader!
♪ Hiding and seeking,
running and peeking ♪
♪ Playing with my friends
♪ And searching and
in tree trunks and wedges ♪
♪ Oh, the fun never ends
♪ Climbing rock creatures
♪ Kicking small creatures
♪
♪ Hiding and seeking
WANDER:
You're getting colder!
Colder!
Aw, come on,
you're practically living
in an igloo!
Oh!
Warmer!
So warm!
Boiling hot like
a whole lot of lava!
Aw, nope, cold again.
Real frigid.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
are we just playing
hide and go seek right now?
We totally are!
Just like he wanted!
This always happens!
I hate him so much!
No matter.
I will devise a snare
most devious
and force our quarry
to come to us.
Hey, if we're doing traps,
I'm totally the one in charge.
I'm, like,
the best at traps.
Fine.
Set your own snare.
We'll see
who snares Wander first.
It shall be me
to snare him.
I shall be the snare-master.
Stop saying snare!
Man, those guys are not
very good at this game.
Now, Wander,
that's not fair.
They might compensate
for their poor seeking skills
by being spectacular hiders.
You never know.
Help!
Help me!
Gasp!
Someone is in need of help,
I must be off!
( in girly voice ) I'm in
the most horrible trouble!
I need somebody
to wander by and help me!
Please!
Oh, thank goodness!
A brave and noble
do-gooder approaches--
(normal voice)
To fall right into my trap!
Brad?
Are you serious?
Fair maiden with skin
of finest alabaster,
it is I, Brad Starlight.
I'm here to rescue you.
Brad, it's me.
Thank goodness
I found you first.
For roaming these woods
is an ill-tempered
skeleton man,
as mean as he is ugly.
Oh, it's you.
That was your plan?
Please!
That would have
never worked!
It just worked on you!
You totally just thought
I was a stupid fair maiden.
A beautiful fair maiden.
I mean,
can we try my plan now?
It's way better.
Fine.
Whatever.
This is the exact same plan.
It certainly is not.
My high cheekbones make me
a much more effective lure.
Also, I'm a redhead.
WANDER: Time-out!
I have been hiding forever!
Are we even playing
hide and seek?
Or are we playing
some kinda dress-up game
with each other?
Got you!
WANDER: Well, technically,
you gotta let me hide
again first.
Leader.
Peepers!
Come get me!
No, I don't have the sword
but I captured Wander!
Long story!
Ready to torture.
Not so fast, Hater!
Only one of us
shall have the duty,
nay, privilege, nay,
pleasure of destroying Wander!
And that's me!
Sir Brad Star--
( evil laughter )
Snared!
Ha ha!
Um, if either of you all
need a refresher on the rules
of hide and seek--
Quiet!
LORD HATER: He's mine!
BRAD: No!
( screaming )
LORD HATER:
I hate you so much.
( screaming )
( both shouting )
Well, I'm gonna go hide again
so Sylvia can find me.
Y'all join in
whenever you're ready.
BRAD: That's enough.
( gasping )
TOGETHER:
You let him get away!
Me?
Yeah, you!
If you'd just given me your half
of the sword of synergy,
I could have destroyed him!
( evil snicker )
SYLVIA: 4,999,997...
4,999,998...
4,999,999...
Five million.
( yawning )
Hoo boy, I sure love
these "hide and seek" sessions.
Best idea I ever had.
Wander gets a game,
I get a nap,
and everything
works out just fine--
( explosion )
Uh-oh.
TOGETHER: Yes!
We have assembled
the sword of synergy!
And together!
Each contributing equally---
And taking exactly
half the credit--
TOGETHER: We will use it
to destroy Wander!
Now where is he?
BRAD: Aha!
( evil laughter )
TOGETHER: Finally my--
I mean,  our  most hated enemy
will be destroyed.
Even though
this may be the end,
I'm just so happy
the last thing I get to see
is good and evil
putting aside their differences
to work together.
Stop being so positive!
Just ignore him,
it's kind of his thing.
I'm serious!
Brad, it's so nice
that you talked Hater
over to the side of good.
Say what now?
Why, thank you,
Wander.
He is quite the scoundrel.
Hold on!
If anything, I converted you
to the side of evil.
Please!
I demurred
for the sake of compromise,
but I am clearly the dominant
force in this partnership!
Are you kidding me?
Look at him!
He's a good guy!
A helpful, friendly good guy
that you're helping me
destroy
for the forces of evil!
Nuh-uh!
I'm the hero!
And heroes fight bad guys,
and kiss pretty ladies!
Ugh, working with you
was a big mistake.
Give me the sword!
I'll destroy him myself.
No!
I wanna do it!
Even when you guys fight,
it's clear
you make a really good team.
TOGETHER: We do not!
( growling )
( screaming )
Wander!
Are you okay, buddy?
Sylvia!
You found me!
They're having
a bit of a BFF tiff.
TOGETHER: We are not BFFs!
Not my face.
We should probably
get going.
Okey-doke.
Also, it's your
turn to hide.
LORD HATER:
Ow, watch the ribs!
BRAD: Stop it!
Stop it!
LORD HATER: I hate you!
BRAD: I hate you more!
( grunting )
BRAD: Ouch!
LORD HATER:
Oh, are you okay?
( screaming )
BRAD: Stop it!
LORD HATER: I hate you!