♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
PEEPERS: Tomorrow is their
Festival of Florkanalia,
which leaves their capital
completely unguarded.
That's when we...
( screams )
- Suddenly...
- ( growls )
- Not yet, sir.
- Yeah, sorry.
Suddenly, a battalion
of watchdogs...
"Hate's great, best villain,
hate's great, best villain..."
led by Commander Peepers,
secure the city
for the arrival of...
Now, sir.
Oh, yeah.
( growling )
And they will
be all, "Ahhhhh!
Lord Hater
is so terrifying!"
Arrggghhh!
And I'll be all, like,
Halt, you swine,
and bow down to him!
He is your new ruler
and you will do as he says,
because he is Lord Hater,
the number one superstar
in the galaxy!
Take that and that and that!
Commander Peepers!
BOTH: Whoo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
and then,
the prettiest girl
in the galaxy comes in,
and she's all, "Oh, Hatey,
you're so cool and powerful.
I wish I had millions of people
screaming my name like you."
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
♪ Hater ♪
BOTH: Whoo!
( laughing )
( crash )
Whoa. This isn't
the car wash.
Emperor Awesome,
you're going to pay for this.
With money.
Hope you got good
insurance, buster.
And with pain!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Chill, man, chill.
It's just a little ding.
We can work
this out, right, bro?
I thought
you were cool.
You...
You think I'm...
Gettin' there,
but dolls?
Not really
a cool guy thing, bro.
They are strategic
figurines
used for precisely
plotting invasions.
And we were just
making fun
of how lame it would be
to be a dork
who still plays with toys.
Radical. Makin' fun
of stuff is tight.
What do you say
we forget all this,
and you tag along
while I rage tonight.
I'm talkin' power.
I'm talkin' ladies.
I'm talkin'
millions of people
screamin' your name.
- Lord Harry!
- Hater.
Hater!
Wow, hangin' with you
would really elevate
my street cred...
I mean, yeah.
Sounds cool, I guess.
I can chill with that.
Sir, what about
our plans?
What about 'em?
We'll finish
when we get back.
Come on, buddy, let's...
...have you stay here
and keep planning
the invasion without me.
Peace out.
Whoa!
Bro, being impressed
is lame.
If you wanna be cool...
you gotta be
impressive.
Whoa!
Which starts with
looking awesome.
Thinkin' leather
jacket for sure.
Definitely a hat.
Fedora? Nah.
Visor? Almost.
Sideways flat brim?
Yeah.
These line-y
stripey shades
are hot right now.
And there's nothing
we can do about your face,
so let's hit the club!
I've gotta call Peepers.
He's not gonna believe this.
Forget Mr. Insurance Claims.
Wouldn't you rather
talk to her?
My pet's name
is Captain Tim.
Face pretty.
You pretty face.
Doin' all right, bro?
Yeah, I'm bored, too.
After-party!
♪ Wicked awesome ♪
Oh, snap,
roll down the window.
Hey, bros,
you lookin' to party?
Ha! Are we ever!
Too bad, suckers.
Yeah, suckers.
( both laughing )
♪ Awesome! ♪
Some people
are just born dorks.
He'll be back.
I bet he's bored with Awesome
and his phony popularity.
He'll probably call
any second now.
Yep, any second.
This is the most fun ever!
How can he be
so irresponsible?
He's out partying
with that doofus
when we have a major
invasion tomorrow.
What could be
more important than that?
We put our faces on it!
( cell phone rings )
Come on, answer.
Where are you?
The fun has to be
drying up by now.
Right?
Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer?
ALL: Hater!
Yeah!
( sighs sadly )
What's the point?
It's done.
He's gone,
moved on,
kicked old Peepers
to the curb.
Probably doesn't even
remember I exist.
But you know what?
I'm glad.
Lord Hater never
really cared about
conquering the universe
in the first place.
He just wanted
to be popular.
Well, that is fine by me.
I can handle this
by myself,
'cause some of us
still care about
things like
galactic domination!
♪ Peepers ♪
( rooster crowing )
Dope. Tight.
Sweet. Sick.
You are a gentleman
and a scholar, bro-rangutan.
Yeah, so...
( yawns )
Unless you've got
some other super cool
thing we can do,
I think I'm gonna hit it.
We done here?
We could, uh, see who
can eat pizza faster.
Or go to
the comic store.
Oh, wait, let's tie
glow sticks to our bikes
and night ride.
What? Bro, we're
not dorks.
We make fun of dorks,
remember?
No, I got a plan.
I got a really
good plan.
You are gonna
love it.
( laughing )
- It's Lord Hater!
- ( screaming )
You've got this, Peepers.
You've got this.
( screaming )
Attention, Flankar 5.
I hereby declare
this planet under new rule!
Pretty cool
invasion, huh?
Not as cool as
makin' fun of
this nerd is gonna be.
- Good call, Hatester.
- Thanks.
Wait, what?
No.
Bow down to
your new master!
AWESOME: Oh, sorry. I can't bow
that low, pip squeak.
So, dudes, are you
really afraid of this runt?
( laughter )
Loser!
That guy couldn't
hurt a fly.
- He's teensy-weensy.
- Yeah, he's tiny.
Silence! I am your new ruler,
and you will do as I say,
because I am
Commander Peepers
of the Hater Empire.
Aw, ha ha.
He's so cute.
( crowd jeering
and laughing )
Hear that, nerd?
So just go back home
and nerd out
with your nerd toys.
Nerd!
Oh, yeah?
( derisive laughter )
I'm a nerd?
Well, that's fine.
'Cause nerds
use their brains.
I set goals for myself,
and then, through
education and hard work,
I figure out ways
to achieve them.
Yes, but your goals
are evil.
Shut your face!
What have you got, Awesome?
Arm bands, a hot tub?
Ha! One day, you'll wake up
and realize
all you've got
is a bunch of ugly clothes,
no real friends,
and as a villain,
you're a failure!
I'm sorry.
You really made me think.
You dorks
are good for one thing.
You make awesome
punching bags.
Literally.
Nobody picks on Peepers
but me!
I really do hope
you have that insurance.
( ferocious yell )
Whoa, cool.
"Ah! No, Lord Hater,
please spare me.
You're too cool
and powerful.
I surrender."
And I was all,
"That's what you get
for pickin' on my pal.
Commander Peepers"!
And then,
Hater was all,
"Hey, maybe true friendship
is better
than being cool
and popular."
Get out of here!
Ah, the annual
Tetsuon Jellyfish Migration
over the Statue
of the Galactic Guru.
It's supposed to be one
of the most beautiful sights
in the galaxy.
Okay, up early.
Just gotta make it
a couple of blocks to...
...here. Oh, what
could go wrong?
Oh, right.
Wander!
Gasp!
Yeah, that is
a real nice hunk
of plastic junk.
But if you wanna see
the real Statue of
the Galactic Guru,
we should probably...
Bigger gasp!
You know, the actual
jellyfish migration
might be more...
Biggest gasp possible!
Sigh.
( exclaiming )
( Wander screaming )
Can we please not stop
for every little thing?
We're gonna be late-er
than we already are.
Wander. Wander!
Wander, what are you
looking at?
Kitties.
Sylvia, Sylvia, Sylvia.
I want this.
Since when are you
into souvenirs?
This is different.
I need it.
Please, Sylvia.
Please, please, please,
please, please, please,
pleeeeeaaaase?
This little thingamahoozit
is great.
Oh, my gosh, Sylvia, look.
Kitty went into
a sock and got stuck.
Yeah, that's nice, pal,
but I don't do cute.
- Come on.
- Sylvia.
Kitty is wearing
little boots.
Sylvia, now it has
milk all over its 'ittle face.
Sylvia, the kitty
is dancing now!
Oh, babycakes, you really
are the most amazing kitty
in the galaxy.
Tell me, what is
so amazing
about cats being
bad at stuff?
- ( wacky laughter )
- Wander?
Huh. Hey, look at that.
Whoa, I think that guy
needs help.
Huh. Wow, thanks, kitty.
We'll be at the Statue
of the Galactic Guru
in no time.
- ( horns honking )
- Wander, no!
SYLVIA: Hey, we're not supposed
to be walking here.
Wander.
( screaming )
( laughing )
Wander!
Ooh!
Who's in the box?
Youse in the box.
No! Wander!
Rassafrassin'
thingamahoozit.
Rassafrassin' cat videos.
Rassafassin' thingamahoozit
cat videos.
Oh, babycakes,
the predicaments
you get yourself in.
SYLVIA: We're gonna miss
the sunset.
Hold on, Wander!
Whoa! Hold on there,
Scabby.
Wander, you missed
the whole thing.
( catlike growling )
( hissing and meowing )
Man, what is with
these videos anyway?
Meow.
Oh, no, I'd know those
big gloopy eyes anywhere.
Lil Bits!
The most ruthless
mercenary in the galaxy.
( meowing )
Oh, this is bad.
Who else has seen these?
This just in.
Breaking news.
Babycakes is the cutest
kitty in the whole galaxy.
If you don't love
this adorable cat
more than anything
else in life,
you probably have no soul,
and I want to destroy you.
I mean, just look at
her 'ittle face.
Meow. Aw!
Show your love
for Babycakes
by prostrating yourself
before her
and giving her
all your riches.
I know I will.
Babycakes!
Meow.
All right, Lil Bits,
where are ya?
Not sure how I missed that.
( sneezes)
ALL: Awww!
Making these videos
is so insulting
to my intelligence.
It will all be worth it
when the gawaxy
is under my contwol.
No one can resist
my cuteness.
( giggling )
Wong...
I mean, wrong!
( gasps )
Babycakes!
Well, if it isn't
Wander and Sylvia.
This is working out
even better than I planned.
Wunning scams...
Running scams seems stwange,
seems strange
for a bounty huntah...
hunter.
What's the angle, Bits?
I saw an opportunity,
and I took it.
This is way more profitable.
And now, on top of
all my wiches,
and gawaxy-wide domination,
I can also have
my wevenge on the two of you.
We won't let you get away with
this, will we, Wander...
Oh!
Babycakes, I love you.
That's wight, Wander.
Just give in, Sylvia,
and pwostrate yourself
before me wike everybody else.
Sorry.
What?
I don't do cute.
Too wate.
I've gone viwal.
Are you gonna beat up
the gawaxy's favowite kitty
wive on camera?
( purring )
Aww!
No. No way is she
gettin' away with this.
Okay, everybody,
listen up.
I know you think this is
the cutest kitty in the galaxy,
but she's really
a greedy swindler
controlling all of you
with these videos
- for her own profit.
- ( all booing )
I mean it.
You have to fight back.
Look away from
the screens.
She's brainwashing you
with her...
( laughing )
( laughter continues )
- Sylvia, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Wander, whatever you do,
keep those cameras rolling.
Awww!
( laughing )
Aww!
( laughter )
( all chanting ) Sylvia, Sylvia,
Sylvia, Sylvia, Sylvia!
Sylvia, you saved us.
I don't know from
exactly what,
but you did it.
It was nothing, really.
Don't even... ow...
mention it.
I'll get my wevenge
on you, Wander and Sylvia.
You haven't seen
the wast of me.
Do the one where
you fell down!
Sylvia, Sylvia,
Sylvia, Sylvia.
( chanting continues )
Hey, look at this video
of a turtle eating a pancake.
Turtle, turtle, turtle,
turtle, turtle...
I guess I missed the jellyfish
migration, didn't I?
I really wanted
to see that.
Maybe not.
It's even more beautiful
than I thought it would be.
Let's post a selfie!
No, no more flab-drassin'
useless gizmos--
Imaginary memory selfie!
( makes clicking sound )
SYLVIA: Oh, that's a keeper,
all right.
AUDIENCE: Ooh!
Aaaah!
Oooh!
Aaah!