♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
( ferocious yell )
Whoopsie. That is
one corker of a chipped tooth.
How'd this happen?
( muffled ) Fath frufid
str nfmd Wandfer
hibbuh dabba toof Wandfer!
Wandfer!   Wandfer!
All righty. This should
help calm you down.
You might feel
the teensiest
stinging sensation.
There we go, there we go.
Wander.
Excuse me,
Mr. Hater.
Can I get the name
of your emergency contact
to come pick you up?
Wander...
Wakey, wakey, Hatey
no more toothache-y.
( muffled )
I know you.
What are you guys
doing here?
We came to
pick you up.
You listed us as
your emergency contact.
What?!
Well, if you're
my femergency frontact,
then we must be
best friends.
There's a slight chance
the sting of the painkillers
has scrambled
his brain a bit.
It should wear off,
but until then,
it's important you see
that he gets home safe.
I love you guys.
Okay, this is weird.
I know, I know.
Hater's not actually
my best friend.
That's just a gajillion volts
of electric squid talking.
My mouth feels
like purple.
- Exactly.
- And the smart thing to do
- is get him safely
back to his ship.
- Yep.
It's not like having
a day of fun with us
would cause Hater
to realize
that being a good guy
is way better
than being a bad guy.
- That would be crazy.
- I know.
Maybe this bonding experience
would actually make us
become best friends
and we can hang out
and help people,
and have our own
secret friend language,
and people would be, like,
"What are they talking about?"
What are you
talking about?
And I could be, like,
Glee-bibble-glorp, Hatey!"
and he'd be all,
"Slamdibble-doo, Wandey!"
HATER: Hey!
Quit your jibber-jabber
and let's go have some fun.
Slamdibble-doo.
( squealing )
Sorry, Syl, but I'm
holdin' out hope for Hater.
Sigh.
BOTH: Friendship Day!
( shrieking )
It's Lord Hater.
( all screaming )
Games, prizes, people,
pizza, ice cream!
I want a fudgy-pudgy blorp-berry
swirl with nuts
and chocolate sprinkles
and rainbow sprinkles and nuts!
And no skimpy scoops!
My tooth!
Too cold!
Oh, it's okay, buddy.
Hey, you wanna play
some games?
( sniffles )
Uh-huh.
( chuckling ) Ah, maybe today
won't be so bad after all
And posted.
HATER: Left. No, right.
A little down.
Okay, go.
Come on, come on.
Yeah!
Ooh, scary skull ring.
Look out. It's coming
to get you.
I'm not afraid of that.
( chuckles )
I know it's
not really scary.
Come on, pal!
♪ ♪
♪ Twisty slide, music,
arcade ♪
♪ Cheesy dip, ice cream,
soda pop, corn on the cob ♪
♪ We got it all
and Gelatinous Bob ♪
( laughter )
♪ ♪
♪ We got it all
and Gelatinous Bob♪
and Gelatinous Bob ♪♪
Joey Protozoa.
What's worse than finding
a space worm in your apple?
I don't know,
Gelatinous Bob.
What is worse than
finding a space worm
in your apple?
Finding half
a space worm
in your apple.
'Cause the other half
is probably devouring
your insides.
( laughter )
Whoa!
That's the coolest thing
I've ever seen.
Whoa!
That's way better.
Can you hear
my thoughts,
my buddy from
a distant star?
I'm not sure I even know
who you are.
Look at me
like a kid out of school,
hanging out with a fool.
A fool who I think
is actually kinda cool.
I don't think he knows
he's talkin' out loud.
I'm countin' on it.
Why am I starting
to drool?
Okay, this has been fun,
and more importantly,
hilarious.
But we really
have to take him back.
But he hasn't tried
to destroy us once all day.
But who knows how long
his brains'll stay scrambled?
You can't force him to be
something he's not.
But what if this is
our chance to prove
that deep, deep, deep,
deep, deep, deep, deep, deep,
( voice deepens )
deep, deep, deep, deep down,
Hater's an okay guy?
( screaming )
Because he's not.
No! Bad Lord Hater.
Bad!
( giggling )
Thanks for the boost,
Mr. Hater.
No problem, Olive.
Good luck
on that spelling test.
Oh, what is this warm
feeling inside?
Is it heartburn?
That's the feeling
you get
from helpin' folks.
Wow, I wanna help more.
This day can't get
any weirder.
One, two, three, four!
♪ Yeah, Hater's on the sidewalk
helpin' Granny cross ♪
♪ He's in a restaurant pulling
out a lady's seat ♪
♪ Stop a train crash,
take out the trash ♪
♪ Found a needle in
a haystack ♪
♪ Scratch
an armadillo's back ♪
♪ Raise a barn,
protect an egg ♪
♪ Show an elderly man
how to email a jpeg ♪
♪ Stop some crime,
solve a paradox in time ♪
♪ Help me come up with, up, up
up, up, up, up, up, up, up ♪
ALL: Rhyme!
♪ Thank you, friends ♪
♪ Chaperone the prom,
calm a mom ♪
♪ Lend a friend lip balm ♪
♪ Then we spruce up
a theme song ♪
♪ Here we go now ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip,
Hater makes it better ♪
♪ Hater Hater,
makes it, makes it ♪
♪ Makes it better ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip,
Hater makes it better ♪
PEEPERS: Lord Hater? Sir?
Are you down there?
What is that thing?
It looks... familiar.
It's nothing.
Look away!
What should we do?
Run away!
No, stay perfectly still.
No, let's check him
for cavities
so that dentist will
zap him so loopy
that he'll stay nice
from now on.
I don't wanna
go up there.
It's scary.
I wanna stay and have
fun with my best friend,
Sunshine Banjo Face.
( sighs )
Oh, he must've been
zapped harder than we thought.
Ooh, I know.
All we have to do
is dishwash the tinkle kitten
until the bandage
is impossible,
and we're
floppin' crone scone.
( sighs )
No, we gotta
take you back.
I wanna be your friend,
but not like this.
True friendship
comes from the heart,
not an electric squid
to the face.
Come on, pal.
I had a fun day with you.
But a true emergency contact
delivers his friend home safe.
I know you don't
want to,
but you gotta go.
We'll be fine.
It's over!
Go on. Get.
Leave us alone!
( whimpers )
We don't wanna
hang out with you,
ya big dummy!
( sobs loudly )
I just hope we rubbed
off on him a little bit.
Good to have you back, sir.
And just in time for
our full-scale invasion
of Crystalline 7.
( screaming )
( gasps )
Invasion?
That's not nice!
PEEPERS:
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir!!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip,
Hater makes it better ♪
Oh, thank goodness.
It was all
just a bad dream.
If only, sir.
If only.
( groaning )
Hangin' out
with a fool.
A fool I think
is actually kinda cool.
Why am I starting
to drool?
Wander!!
Frab-drassin' ham spangler.
I slept terribly.
Anything I can do for you?
( bones cracking )
Nah. I got six or seven
cricks in my neck.
It's like my pillow
was extra flat last night.
Wander, something wrong?
No, it's no big deal-io.
He's back.
- To the lab.
- The lab?
It's not that big a deal.
Pillows get flat
all the time.
Exhibit A.
A whoopee cushion?
A message.
The calling card
of the most villainous
villain to vex this
or any other galaxy.
( air escapes )
Lord Hater?
Emperor Awesome?
It's not Dominator,
is it?
Worse.
Someone from my past,
someone who thinks he's good,
but is really bad.
Good news is
we're gonna stop this bad guy
from doing any more
bad things
he thinks
are actually good.
Since when do you
stop bad guys?
Usually you sing a song
or play some silly game
to drive 'em nuts.
( imitating Batman )
This is no game.
What?
( evil laugh )
( alarm sounding )
( sirens blaring )
( makes whooshing sounds )
What's the trouble?
Snatched statues?
Ransacked rubies?
Misappropriated
masterpieces?
What? Oh, no.
Someone just stole
the display pillows
from our gemstone
exhibit.
It's worse
than we thought.
It is?
I mean, it is!
I'm gonna need
full background checks
on all museum visitors.
Get me names,
birthdays, favorite colors,
summer vacation plans.
According to the footage,
our pernicious pillow pilferer
- struck at
precisely 3:14.
- So?
3.14 are the first
three digits
in the numerical
value for pi.
Pie is delicious,
which rhymes with wishes.
If wishes were fishes,
we'd all have enough to eat.
I know where he's
going to strike next.
- Quickly, old chum.
- Old chum?
Now I get it.
Emperor Awesome
is sabotaging all the pillows
so he can throw
an evil slumber party...
and I don't get it.
You have a rather extensive
collection of feather
boas, do you not?
Where are they?
Feather boas are so out.
Now it's all about
actual boas.
I threw those ratty
feather ones away.
Curses. Empty.
We're too late.
But he left a message.
Wander, wait for me.
What's your hurry, becs?
Oh, gross.
( evil laughter)
Despair, citizens of
Cluckon.
Your inevitable domination
is... gaaah!
Oh, gross!
Peepers, I can see
their nuggets.
Ah, finally.
A villain I can
sink my fists into.
Not so fast.
Oh, come on.
It's Lord Hater.
He's like the definition
of bad guy.
( whooshing)
Go away!
And yet, he's small potatoes
in the baneful broth
of the real villain's
gumbo of repugnance.
Gumbo of...
Okay, that's it.
I am sick of
the grim and gritty routine,
and getting dragged
across the galaxy
for some missing
pillows,
frilly scarves
and plucked Cluckons.
It's not
that big a deal.
I'm not moving until you tell me
who we're up against.
Him.
Attention, galaxy.
My fowl plan
is almost complete.
Prepare to face
the wrath of the mischievous
Dr. Screwball Jones.
Now tremble in
eggs-cruciating terror
as my latest plot
leaves you shell-shocked.
Behold my fantabulously
fantabulous
tickle machine.
This joker
is who you think
is the most dangerous
villain in the galaxy?
HATER: He what?
Of course. He stole
all those feathers
in order to create
a weapon that would
make everyone laugh,
thus forcing the universe
to be happy.
Isn't that like
your whole deal?
I only present
the positive path.
I don't force you
to follow it.
( giggling )
This is kinda fun,
in a baby way.
Okay, I get it.
( all laughing )
That's enough.
All right,
it's getting annoying.
Quit it.
( laughing )
Stop! Please
make it stop.
This is the worst thing
that's ever happened...
( laughing )
I guess this is
no laughing matter.
Get it, because of the...
Great. Now he's got me
doing it.
Hey, Chuckles.
I got a punchline for you.
Then you'll need a set-up.
What's worse than
a tickle machine?
Literally anything.
Wrong!
Two tickle machines.
Oh, please. Too bad
I'm not ticklish.
Except for
behind my knees.
( laughing )
Holy somatosense, Wander.
This is awful.
He is a monster.
Huh?
- WANDER: Knock, knock.
- JONES: Who's there?
- Orange.
- Orange who?
Orange you glad
I didn't say banana?
No need to split.
You might find this
a-peeling.
Get it? 'Cause you said
banana back there.
What's the matter?
Seeing stars?
Your noxious nightmare
is over, Dr. Jones.
Why do you continue
to resist me?
After all, we both want
to spread joy
throughout the universe.
♪ Hey there,
let's have some fun ♪
♪ Join my good-time gang ♪
♪ Just one question first ♪
♪ Rhubarb or meringue? ♪
♪ We'll make folks happy
through the land ♪
♪ Have them howling
on their knees ♪
♪ So, my little
orange friend ♪
♪ Lend a hand
if you please ♪
♪ Hey, don't look so shocked ♪
♪ Ain't it about the time ♪
♪ To let the pun
fit the crime? ♪
♪ Screwball,
you try too hard ♪
♪ Dr. Screwball,
if you please ♪
♪ I've got an online PhD ♪
♪ Folks should be free
to find their own happiness ♪
♪ You can't force 'em
to have fun ♪
♪ Sure, I can.
Watch this! ♪
Accordion!
Banjo retort!
♪ Hey, you're pretty good ♪
♪ But I think
that we both know ♪
♪ It's time to let
my Sylvia go ♪
Never!
String break.
♪ Here's a joke ♪
♪ How are you just like
a lollipop stick? ♪
♪ In the end, you're both
worn down ♪
♪ By the force of my licks ♪
Ha, ha, ha-ha!
♪ Ain't it a laugh,
ha ha ha ha ♪
♪ Looks like
the end of the line ♪
♪ So let ♪
♪ The pun ♪
♪ Fit the... ♪
Crime.
( panting )
Wait. I've got
one last pun for you.
Oh, oh, oh,
let me guess.
You're ending on
a sour note?
You snapped your C-sharp,
so now you'll B-flat?
Ha ha!
How about...
who's laughing now?
( hysterical laughter )
This isn't funny.
I mean, it's kind of
ironic, I guess.
( laughter continues )
Curse you, Wander!
Boy, what a super day.
Buddy, from now on,
if you say
something's dangerous,
I'll believe you,
even if that was
the stupidest danger
we've ever been in.
What just happened?
Well, sir, looks like,
once again, the day is saved,
thanks to Wander
and Sylvia.
HATER: Meh.
Now tremble in
eggs-cruciating terror...
That's good, good.
As my latest plot
leaves you...
shell-shocked. Yeah.
Oh, I am so good.
I am so good!
Oh, this is gold!