♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
You snuck onto
Dominator's ship to--
Discover her breakfast
beverage of choice.
Coffee gal. Would've pegged
her for a tea person.
Now she's gonna
peg us.
Oh, that's it!
I am sick and tired
of Dominator!
Sick and tired of running,
of being blasted,
and I am sick and tired
of this galaxy.
This is too hard.
I... need... a...
break!!
Sorry, pal, but we have
gotta get outta here.
No, Sylvia, we've gotta get
Dominator and Hater together.
There is literally
nothing in the galaxy
that could stop me from
uniting those two in love.
You wanna
meet my family?
Sylvia's home world,
here we come!
Sylvia, did you play
on this street?
Sylvia, did you eat
in that diner?
Sylvia, do you know that guy?
What about her, or him?
Just because I'm from here
doesn't mean I know everybody.
- Hey, Joe.
- Whassup, Syl?
Long time no see.
( sighs )
Hey, house. Glad to see
you haven't changed.
Man, Ma's gonna flip
when she sees me.
Wander, she's not gonna
flip that much.
Put that hug away.
But I've got room in here
for your whole family.
No!
Perfect.
- I'll get it.
- No, I will!
( voices arguing )
SYLVIA: Uh, hey, Bill,
Phil, Gil.
ALL: Syl!
SYLVIA: Glad to see you, too,
you narfin' froods.
MOTHER: Language.
Ma!
Oh, hey, Sylvia.
Good to see ya.
Take the groceries, huh?
She seems... nice.
Oh, she'll be fine.
She's probably just
a little sore
because I kinda sorta left home
without telling anybody.
You did what?!
Oh, she's a tough
old broad.
She'll bust my chops
for a bit,
and then everything
will be right as rain.
( groans )
Now that that's done,
time for a little rest
and reclination.
( sighs )
Lord Dominator has taken down
yet another planetary system--
Ugh! What else is on?
Whew!
( snorts angrily )
Syl, dinner isn't gonna
cook itself.
I can help.
No, you're our guest.
Sylvia!
So, you guys must have all kinds
of wacky stories about Sylvia.
Sylvia, quiet that monkey down.
I'm trying to watch this, uh...
colors show.
Oh, I'm no monkey.
Folks call we Wan--
He's not a monkey.
He's a cat.
So let me ask you
something there, monkey-cat.
How much you bench?
Oh, please, when have
you seen a cat?
Uh, just last week,
I saw two cats.
Two cats, he says.
Uh, this guy.
( all arguing )
So, Gram, you must have
some stories about Sylvia.
I don't like you.
Peel these.
- And those.
- Grop!
- Language.
- Sorry.
Do you have a...
peeler?
So, Ma, things seem like
they're...
( blender whirs )
I like what
you've done with--
( blender whirs )
It's...
- ( blender whirs )
- just so...
- nice to be home.
- ( blender whirs )
- What was that?
- Nothin'.
Good. When you're done,
you can start on the carrots.
Um, is there a salad?
I'm sorry.
A what?
It's all right, Ma.
He means, like,
bananas and nuts.
Stuff monkeys eat.
You sure you wouldn't like
a nice saucer of milk...
kitty?
Here you go,
buddy.
Syl, you remember
the butter?
So, cat-monkey, how do you
and my sister know each other?
Actually, Sylvia's been
helping me help folks
all over the galaxy.
Oh, yeah. What do you
get paid to help?
Just the warm satisfaction of
knowing our friends are happy.
Huh. So nothin' then.
Where do you live?
We live wherever
the stars take us.
They're space hobos.
No, look, we help people
by trying to thwart villains--
Fat-free.
Cholesterol.
Seriously?
You beat up bad guys?
Oh, gracious, no.
I don't hit anyone.
I prefer to use
the power of love.
Besides, there's no stronger
muscle than your heart.
Dirty space hippie.
You tellin' me you never
hit no one?
Cats don't hit,
they scratch.
So do monkeys.
They'll scratch
your eyes out.
He's not a monkey!
( thrashing and crashing )
All right. Finally.
I am...
May I please
be excused?
Okay.
After you clean
the dining room.
( anguished shriek )
I'm sick and tired
of Mom.
So... how's it going?
I'm sick and tired
of working,
I'm sick of being
bossed around,
and I'm sick and tired
of this house!
This is too hard.
Like I said,
I need a break.
Sorry, pal, we've
gotta get outta here.
Oh, so you're
leavin' again.
Ma, don't start.
Oh, it's fine.
Things are maybe
a little too tough
for you here.
I feel like things are getting
to that yelling place
where I get thrown
against the table again, so...
Well, maybe if you were
a little easier on me,
like you are with
my stupid stay-at-home
brothers.
- Are you callin' me stupid?
- Yeah, you're stupid!
( all arguing )
Flabdrassit,
that's enough!
Language.
Everyone, TV room,
now!
This is a talking stick.
Only the person holding
the talking stick can talk.
Now, Miss Dorothy,
you go first.
"I feel..."
I feel like an idiot
holding this stick.
But how do you feel
about Sylvia?
She'd also look like
an idiot holding this stick.
See? That's what
she always does.
You can only speak
when you're holding the stick!
Any questions?
- Do you like bananas?
- Or tuna fish?
I've been meanin' to ask you,
how much did you say
you can bench?
Did anyone else see
the cat-monkey eyeing my pearls?
He's not eyeing
your pearls, Gram.
No, no, no!
No, this is not promoting
positive family values.
Stop!!
Ma, I'm sorry you're
mad at me because I left.
( laughs ) I'm not mad
you left.
I'm mad because
you came back.
Huh?
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
DOROTHY:
I'm wicked proud of you.
Your pop would've
been, too.
You... you kept all this?
Of course I did.
You harass that Hater jerk
something fierce.
Now that there's
a bigger jerk
trying to conquer the galaxy,
you're givin' up?
That's not my fearless,
gutsy girl.
So you either go out there
and deal with Dominator,
or stay here
and deal with Dorothy.
But either way,
it's not gonna be easy.
Okay, Ma, I'll take care
of the galaxy.
Then I'll take care
of the dishes.
I can't take
this anymore!
I love you,
Sylvia's family!
BILL: Oh, so that's
how much you bench.
GRAM: I think he's
going for my purse
HATER: Okay, there's
Dominator's ship.
What do I say to her?
"Hey, baby, are you
10,000 tons of molten lava,
'cause you're melting
my heart."
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Okay, here she comes.
You're totally
cool and awesome.
You're awesome, awesome,
you're... ( gasps )
Awesome?!
Peepers!
PEEPERS: Emperor Awesome?
What's he doing there?
That's what I said.
Okay, stay calm.
Lots of people have
white-striped space limos.
It might not be him.
Oh, you're right, Peepers.
It could belong to anyone.
Hey, babe, it's me,
Emperor Awesome.
Can I come in?
( screaming )
This is the worst thing
that's ever happened.
This doesn't
make sense.
Why would Dominator
let Emperor Awesome
on her ship?
He hasn't been
a contender in ages.
Unless... ( gasps )
He's got some kind
of new secret weapon.
What's the point
in trying anymore, Peepers?
I might as well just spend
the rest of my days
aimlessly wandering
the galaxy,
singing songs
and helping folks.
BOTH: They'll be
unstoppable.
Nothing will ever
be the same!
They'll take over
the galaxy together.
They're totally
gonna date each other.
BOTH: What?
Do you think Dominator and
Awesome are just dating?
You think Dominator and
Awesome are just gonna take
over the galaxy together
in a totally
non-girlfriend-boyfriend way?
BOTH: That's way better.
Oh, too bad
I'm right.
I hope so, sir.
We have to find out
the truth.
But how?
What are
they saying?
Don't worry.
I can totally read lips.
( as Dominator ) Can you
take my rabbit for a walk
on Tuesday?
( as Awesome )
No way, bro.
His leash is made
of beefsteak,
and that's not sanitary.
I could make him
a congressman instead, bro."
Whew! Nothing
to worry about.
They're only talking about
weird stuff that doesn't
make any sense.
( gasps )
What? What is it?
No! Oh, he's so smooth!
Well, I can dance, too.
♪ ♪
He's not trying
to woo her.
He's demonstrating how
he destroys planets
with his planet-destroying
parties.
♪ ♪
No, he's doing
a smooth dance,
and Dominator's gonna be
super impressed,
and they're totally
gonna smooch!
( shrieks )
Where'd they go?
Probably to
the smooching room.
The smooching room?!
I've mapped out
her whole ship
with a super scientific
algorithm
based on what I've seen
of it so far.
Here's her inner sanctum,
here's the war room,
the arsenal,
the smooching room, bedroom,
this part is mostly shoes
and purses and stuff.
The back-up
smooching room.
Sir, I seriously doubt
an evil villain
has   a   smooching room,
let alone two.
We've got six.
Sir, we've gotta
get a closer look.
One of us will
have to sneak onboard
her terrifying ship.
WATCHDOG: Lord Hater,
it's an honor to be
chosen for this mission.
I won't let you down,
I swear.
All right, soldier, you're
looking for a big, scary--
- But beautiful--
- Lady lava villain.
Don't let her see you
or you're doomed.
And also a totally lame
but thinks he's cool shark guy.
Yeah, watch out
for him, too.
If he sees you,
you're also doomed.
The bots.
Don't forget the bots.
Right, the bots.
Watch out for her army
of literally thousands
of killer bots.
If they catch you,
you're super doomed. Got it?
( nervously )
Uh-huh.
On second thought...
Good luck, soldier.
( screams )
( screaming continues )
BOTH: Yes!!
( Watchdog shivering )
Uh, Jerry, stop
shaking the camera
and find
the smooching room.
It's down the passage
on your left.
There is
no smooching room!
Look for the war room.
See if you can find
Awesome's secret weapon.
Jerry, bots coming
from up ahead.
- Go back the way you came.
- ( Jerry screaming )
No, they're coming
from behind you.
- Rush forward
in a blind panic.
- ( screaming )
Zig-zag, zig-zag.
Run in a zig-zag pattern.
You'll be harder to shoot.
Run right at 'em;
it'll totally confuse 'em.
( shrieking )
Jerry, get outta there.
We didn't send you
to spy on the inside
of a closet.
Sh! Listen.
AWESOME:   I'm tellin' ya, D,
you're gonna go crazy
for my secret weapon.
It's gonna sweep you
off your feet.
I'm interested.
Tell me more about
this secret weapon.
BOTH: This confirms
my worst fears.
Wait, what?
( Jerry sobbing )
Jerry, stop crying.
We can't hear
anything!
( sobbing continues )
No! What happened?
Come back.
Oh, his tears must've
shorted out the camera.
There's only one
thing to do, sir.
If we wanna know
what's going on,
we'll have to go
see for ourselves.
But how?
Okay, it looks like
a left ahead.
On my signal, and now.
Turn left.
I said left, sir.
Left!
My left or your left?
We have the same left!
Do you know which way
left is?
What's that?
It must be Awesome's
secret weapon.
We can't let it
reach Dominator.
Gotta play this cool
so as not to rouse suspicion.
HATER: Hello, fellow
fist fighter.
What a lovely...
I'm taking this out!
Left!
No!!
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
( whinnying )
There you are.
Finally.
PEEPERS: Eep.
O mighty lord Dominator,
we present to you
Emperor Awesome's
totally awesome
top secret weapon,
guaranteed to conquer
the galaxy,
and your heart.
PEEPERS: Oh, no,
we were both right.
They are taking over
the galaxy together.
And they are dating.
Peepers, what do we do?
Hey, babe,
heard you were looking
for a secret weapon.
Well, check out
these guns!
No! That's so cool!
Karate.
Let's get awesome!
As you can see,
I've set them to stun.
Huh?
Wow. Oh, and I thought
you were all talk.
I didn't think you'd
actually try anything.
I'm impressed.
Oh, thank grop,
you were right.
They're just dating.
There's no secret weapon.
What a relief.
Now they're gonna smooch,
get married, and have babies,
and I'm gonna be
alone forever.
Oh, you're not alone, sir.
You have me
and the Watchdogs.
Who needs Dominator
anyway?
If she can't see
that you're really
the greatest in the galaxy,
then she doesn't
deserve you.
- Really? You think?
- Of course.
Besides, I don't think
there's gonna be
any smooching. Look.
You know,
when you showed up,
I was, like, right,
like I'm letting
that scrub on my ship.
But it was a slow day,
no big planets to dominate,
nothing but reruns on,
so I figured, maybe
he does have
some kind of
secret super weapon.
At least it would
be entertaining.
But you know what?
I never guessed
what a pathetic
waste of time
you'd be.
Do you really think
I'd let you ride my coattails
to the top? Ha!
Get real, buster!
Not even that idiot Hater
is as delusional as you.
She knows my name!
She called you
an idiot.
An idiot whose
name she knows.
Don't be like that, babe.
Come on, what about
all the good times?
Hey, take it easy, D.
That's Lord Dominator,
if you're nasty.
Baby, wait!!
Bots.
She hates Awesome
and loves me.
Sir.
Hater's gonna date her,
Hater's gonna date her.
- Oh, yeah,
oh, yeah!
- Sir!!
Yeah! She likes me!
♪ ♪
Sir, she's cold
and heartless.
I really don't think
she wants to date anyone.
♪ ♪
Cold and heartless?
You're just jealous.
She's not so bad.
( Dominator laughing )
JERRY:
Sir? Come in, sir.
You left me on
Dominator's ship.
( shrieking )
Ugh! What is
with these guys?