♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Wander!
Yonder! Wander! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Do-do-do-do-do
Should we say hi?
No.
What is he doing here?
Leave it!
She'll be here, okay?
I totally
did not get stood up.
And bring me a new candle.
This one's stupid.
Poor Lord Hater.
Are you kidding?
This is hilarious.
We got a fancy dinner
and a show.
That serves him
right for being
such a jerk all the time.
( snoring )
Aw, maybe if someone
gave him a chance,
he wouldn't be
so darn evil.
And maybe we should
mind our own beeswax.
So he got jilted.
It's not the end
of the world.
Hey, Peepers.
Yeah, the king of
this stupid planet
was totally lying.
His lame daughter
was a no-show.
Whatever.
I'm gonna
head back to the ship,
curl up with a pint
of Fudgy Pudgy Vanilla
and blow this planet
to kingdom come!
( alarm blaring )
Okay, so it is
the end of this world.
Gasp!
This is a disaster!
We got to find him
a replacement date
or his self-esteem
will drop dramatically!
Also, the planet
will be doomed!
E-easier said
than done, Wa-wa-wander.
Who in their right mind
would go on a date
with Lord Hater?
I don't have to tip
if I just had the bread, right?
Oh, no.
I cannot believe that I,
a comely single gal,
have been stood up.
I feel oh-so rejected
and vulnerable.
Hold the countdown.
Things just got interesting.
Click.
You know, getting blown up
doesn't seem that bad.
Come on, Syl.
The fate of the planet
depends on your sparkling
dinner conversation.
All you have to do
is make him feel
good and confident.
He's coming over.
It's working!
It's really not.
Heaven must be
missing an angel.
Because here I am.
Oh, brother. Oh!
Are you charming.
You have me
at a disadvantage.
Obviously,
everyone knows me,
Lord Hater,
Hate's Great,
Best Villain.
And you are?
Uh, I don't know.
Linguini...Von...
Breadstick.
Lynn for short.
Von.
Fancy.
Wait.
Don't I know you?
Nope.
I don't think so.
Aren't you...
the lucky lady
about to have
the best night of her life?
And that's
the top-secret origin
of the galaxy's
greatest dictator.
Me, I'm really
quite fascinating,
don't you think?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Uh-huh.
Scusi, signorina.
Maybe you like
to order
something
off-a the special menu?
Your lightning bolts
are so pointy.
I know.
Can you believe I just
roll out of bed this way?
Let's order,
then you can tell me
more things
you like about me.
( grumbles )
( guests complaining )
It's just dinner.
So...
( speaking gibberish )
And then on Thursdays,
I blast my quads, delts,
and quadriplexis.
( speaking gibberish )
And a third order
of sliders, half rare,
half well done.
Oh,
did you want something?
( grumbles )
( speaking gibberish )
Then the butcher says
"Not on my dime!"
( guffaws )
( speaking gibberish )
Not on my dime!
( guffaws )
( speaking gibberish )
There is a pea
touching my potato.
Do it again!
( whistling )
Fine!
Whatever it takes
for this dinner to be over.
Yup.
Dinner's over.
Now we can get on
with the rest of the date.
Rest of...
( music playing )
Step right up.
Everyone's a winner
when love is in the air.
Two, please.
Hatey's first.
♪ Oh, tonight is going
to be a night to remember ♪
It's just dinner
and a carnival.
It's just dinner and a carnival.
♪ Tonight is going
to be an evening ♪
♪ You never will forget
♪ Oh, tonight is going
to be a night to remember ♪
♪ A night to remember
♪ Girl,
you're gonna love me soon ♪
♪ If you love me,
we'll ride, we'll romance ♪
♪ Oh, tonight is going
to be a night to remember ♪
♪ A night to remember
♪ Girl,
you're gonna love me soon ♪
♪ Even if you
don't love me today ♪
♪ You're gonna love me soon
♪ Even if you
don't love me yet ♪
♪ Oh, yeah
That was a night to remember.
No matter
how hard I try to forget.
You know,
Lynn, of all the many,
many women
I've totally dated,
you're the most
easily impressed.
I like that.
( crying )
Uh, Lord Hater.
I'm not crying!
You're crying!
I try so hard,
you know.
But I have a big personality.
Gah, I'm such an idiot.
You're so cool and I just...
want a girl to like me.
( groans )
( exclaiming loudly )
You know what?
I don't even want to blow up
this stupid planet anymore.
Well, thanks
for the memorable night.
We'll do this again.
How about every night
for the rest of our lives?
Oh, no.
Lynn, say yes.
The thought of spending
even one second without you
makes me
want to blow up
all the planets
in the universe!
What do you say?
( gulping )
( siren blaring )
No pressure.
( playing rock version
of "Here Comes The Bride" )
I always cry at these things.
It's just dinner and a carnival
and a lifetime of misery.
It's just dinner
and a carnival
and a lifetime of misery.
It's just dinner and a carnival
It's just dinner
and a carnival
and a lifetime of misery.
It's just dinner and a carnival
Oops!
Stupid heels.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered today
to marry this stunning
vision of loveliness...
to some broad
he met at a restaurant.
If anyone objects
to the marriage of Lord Hater
and Linguini Von Breadstick,
let them speak now or...
Stop!
I object.
I do declare, Lord Hater,
I am your number one fan.
I've pined for you
from afar for ages,
always too afraid
to approach.
Oh!
But now that I see you
in the arms
of this cheap horse,
no offense, I must say
fiddle dee dee to that
and say my piece.
Take me instead.
I got you into this mess,
I'm gonna get you out.
By putting yourself
into the mess?
It's not a perfect plan.
Ooh, hey.
Awkward.
Ladies, there's no need
to fight over me.
When you're the most dynamic
overlord in the universe,
women are gonna
throw themselves at your feet.
I'm Lord Hater.
Why should I settle
for a "six" and a "four"
when there's
a whole galaxy of "tens"
seeking the Lord
Dater experience?
Listen,
I've had a swell time,
but I forgot
about this thing
I've got
somewhere else.
You've been awesome.
Keep in touch.
Phew!
Planet L'Amouria is saved,
Hater's regained
his confidence...
And we're both still single.
I better have been the "six,"
or I'm gonna go
back there and deck him.
Whoo!
Free man!
Peepers,
set a course for ladies.
Whoever we find has
got to be better than those two.
You mean Sylvia
and Wander in dresses?
What?
This is it, Wander!
This is where our wretched
rivalry finally ends.
Peepers!
Activate the portal to the pit
of perpetual pain.
( evil laugh )
Ooh,
pretty!
It's not pretty!
It's a portal
to the prison dimension
where I have banished
my most despised enemies!
Say good-bye, Wander.
Hello.
No, not hello, good-bye.
Sylvia.
'Sup.
Get her!
Uh-oh.
This is bad!
Don't worry, Hater!
I'll save you.
This is worse!
Wander!
'Sup.
Oh, grop.
Ugh, smells like
zombie armpits down here.
Zombie armpits.
Good name for a band.
Come in, Peepers,
you've got to get me
out of here.
You have no idea
how horrible this place is.
Man,
I'd hate to be the guy
who has to stay here
for all eternity.
Peepers.
No, what the...
Dude, what the...
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't be mean,
we don't have to be mean.
Huh? Wander?
That you?
What the heck
are you doing here?
BOTH:
Hey, it's Wander!
Hey, look who's back,
boys.
Hurray, it's Wander!
Hey, where have you been,
Wander?
You--
You know these guys?
Know him?
He helped me start up
my used bookstore.
He taught me
how to whistle.
He helped me deal
with my violent tendencies.
Man, oh man, fellas,
it sure has been a while.
What the heck
you all been up to?
Well, I was
a small business owner...
until somebody
destroyed my bookstore,
all because I told him
his novel wasn't selling well.
So he threw me in here!
( growling )
Stop! I can't have
some of my friends
hurting my other friends.
Whoa,
Hater is your friend?
Oh, yeah, he may be
the ultimate evil and all,
but I know
deep down inside--
No!
I totally hate this guy!
I mean totally hate!
I would never...
( growling )
want to be...
apart from a good friend
like him.
Right back at you, buddy.
If you're friends,
prove it.
Best bud handshake?
Oh, yeah,
totally our "best bud
bro" shake that we do, like,
all the time.
Let's do it.
♪ Hit me high,
hit me low ♪
♪ Make a turtle,
man, he's slow ♪
♪ Right hand left,
left hand right ♪
♪ Do a twirl,
Outta sight! ♪
♪ Cookies in the oven,
let 'em bake ♪
♪ And that's how you do
the best buds shake ♪
Ta-da!
Okay,
guess you are best buds.
But you best not be joshin'!
Yes, sure,
no way, no joshin'.
Best buds.
Best...
Buds.
Agh, Lord Hater, no.
You are too powerful
and awesome
and I'm all dumb
and dying now. Agh!
Wah-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, Lord Hater,
number one superstar.
( crunching )
( stomach rumbles )
( snarling )
Sorry, Hatey, bo-batey.
I tried to rustle us
up some grub.
But they got the last one.
Literally. So hopefully,
this will help
manage those munchies.
You expect me
to eat this...
( snarling )
...wonderful meal
you've prepared for me,
oh, pal of mine.
( vomiting )
( shivering )
♪ Rise and shine,
it's such a lovely morning ♪
♪ It's gonna
be a perfect day ♪
♪ But if it should get
rainy without warning ♪
♪ We'll still be
best buds anyway ♪
♪ Happiness is all around us
♪ I sure hope this
feeling never ends ♪
♪ We're best friends forever
in all kinds of weather ♪
♪ Morning, noon and night
♪ Yeah, we'll always
be together ♪
♪ Eternity is gonna
be so awesome ♪
♪ 'Cause together
we're the best of friends ♪
♪ Our friendship is like
skipping through the flowers ♪
♪ Dancing and giggling
with glee ♪
♪ So much better
than my evil powers ♪
♪ Friendship makes
my heart soar free ♪
♪ You can make my heart
fill up with sunshine ♪
♪ And rainbows are
just around the bend ♪
♪ We're best friends forever
in all kinds of weather ♪
♪ Like kitty cats
and puppies ♪
♪ We're birds of a feather
♪ Oh, something something
♪ Something something
♪ 'Cause forever
we're the best of friends! ♪
( screaming )
Phew!
( shrieking )
♪ Something, something,
best of friends ♪
( shrieking )
Move it, buddy,
we got to go.
We're not safe out here.
Hey!
Buddy,
little help?
♪ Oh, it's gonna
be a perfect day ♪
Grab a buddy.
Assemble the chain.
Huh?
Whoa!
Hater, come on!
Grab your buddy!
Oh, no, he's too far.
You have to save him.
Being consumed
by a sand snapper
is the most painful
demise imaginable.
That good, huh?
Fine, grab my hand.
Grab my hand?
( sighs )
Buddy.
Whoa!
This place is amazing...ly
horrible.
But at least I know
there is good in you.
♪ 'Cause together
we're the best of friends ♪
I am in a prison.
A prison of sunshine.
Finally!
Way to go, Peepers.
Buddy?
No!
I'm not your buddy!
I never was!
I was totally joshin'!
( guffaws )
Take me home!
Yes!
Uh, Peepers?
Hold on, buddy,
I'm getting you
out of there!
Oh, man, am I glad
to see you, good buddy.
Wander, what are you doing?
He may not be my buddy,
but I'm still his.
Ha-ha!
See you never, you smelly--
Matter of fact,
so are the rest of those guys.
They're all my buddies!
Uh-oh.
Later, Hate... buddy.
But I thought
we were buds.
( crying )
Ah!
I was kidding again.
(crying)