♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Wander!
Yonder! Wander! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
( Lord Hater laughs )
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Wander! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Do-do-do-do-do
Welcome.
I've gathered you
all here today
because I am dy...
...ing to tell you something.
I'm dying.
But before I die, I will
bequeath to one of you villains
my vast empire
and the extensive power
which I have spent
1,000 years building.
( chuckling )
Are you 1,000
years old?
You don't look
a day over 400.
Am I right?
Who's with me?
( crickets chirping )
( banging )
Wait. No! What if I say
you do look your age?
Or older?
No!
( screaming )
That was desperate.
I cannot stand desperate.
Whomever I bequeath
control of my power to,
must be one who possesses
great strength,
someone deserving.
I do not want weaklings!
This is perfect, sir.
Now there's nobody
standing in your--
WANDER: Sorry I'm late.
Hey, it's Hater
and Mr. Peepers.
Sylvia, and you said
we wouldn't know anyone.
Pbbt!
Wander.
So glad you made it,
my dear boy.
Ooh, sit next to me.
W--W--Wander?
What is he doing--
Why--why--who?
Queen Entozoa,
I can't thank you enough
for inviting me and Sylvia
to your swanky shindig.
I can't wait
to meet all your
fascinating guests.
And any of you
well-behaved creeps
get out of line,
I got a couple of guests
I'd like you to meet, too.
The Lady Haymaker
and the Duchess of Wailing.
( gasping )
Duchess, look.
Finger sandwiches.
Oh, yeah.
But, Your Majesty,
he's not even a villain,
he's like the gooodiest
good guy ever!
On the contrary,
Lord Hater,
Wander is the number one
most wanted
fugitive in the galaxy.
So impressive.
Someone has some competition.
( laughing )
But he's wanted by me.
I did that.
Wander,  I will not
allow you to foil
another one of my plans.
Now you shall d--
PEEPERS: Excuse us.
We need to use
the little villains' room.
Sir, we've been over this.
You cannot destroy anyone
at a dinner party.
It's very rude.
And the Queen
is very, very particular
about proper manners.
But Wander doesn't even want
Queen Entozoa's power.
I do.
( toilet flushing )
BLACK CUBE: Omino deus!
Decto illuminata!
Sancto invictus!
Sir, let me
take care of Wander.
She's sure to pick you
if you stick to the plan
and act like
the ultimate gentleman.
Polite, proper,
witty and charming.
Okay. I can do this.
TOGETHER:
Whoo-ha! Hate's great.
What a lovely evil
castle you have here.
Oh, stop.
You know just what
to say to a girl.
I like it, too.
It's got good parts
and then other parts
that are also good,
too, as well.
Don't be a suck up.
"Esther Ate
Planets For Tom."
( gasping )
Heh-heh-heh.
Oh, Wandy.
How I love your
devil-may-care attitude.
Grr!
Say goodbye,
you wandering weirdo.
Better call the farmer
because these calves
are ready for market.
( robot voice singing )
♪ Captain Awesome
You can't handle this.
♪ Not so Awesome
( Kremlons hissing
and growling )
I can't understand these
disgusting creatures.
Someone else talk.
Oh, I have a very pithy
and impromptu story
that's sure
to make you laugh.
So the other day,
I'm flying through space
and there's this planet
that's just begging
to get blown up.
Why?
Because it was.
But why?
Because it was
dumb looking.
Why?
Because it was purple
and I hate purple.
Why?
Because this girl
I liked had purple hair
and she didn't want to date me
but it doesn't matter
'cause I, like, didn't
want to date her either
so, like,
she's the loser, not me.
So whatever,
purple is just stupid, okay.
Hey, I can do this.
(laughing )
Ah!
Ooh, time for dancing.
Dancing!
But before I let loose
on the dance floor,
I got to let loose in the
little gentleman's room.
So if you'll excuse me.
That's gonna
hurt coming off.
WANDER: Whoop,
door's stuck.
( knocking on door )
Hello?
I did it.
Sir, Wander
is all taken care of.
This is the moment
we've been waiting for.
Your Majesty,
may I have this dance?
♪ Time as old as you
♪ Lord Hater
and the Queen ♪
♪ Beautiful
♪ Pretty things
♪ Dancing in the room
♪ Bequeath
yourself to me ♪
♪ Hater and the
queen ♪
Lord Hater, maybe I was
wrong about you.
I can't think of anyone
more deserving of my power.
( metal scattering )
Phew! And I thought
I missed it.
Follow my lead,
look for breaks,
don't put anything in your ear
bigger than your elbow.
Let's go!
May I cut in?
Oh my, you are
a wild one, Wandy.
Whee!
BLACK CUBE: Credo
viri rominus...
May I cut in?
Ow.
No.
No! No!
I got to save this.
What can I do?
I know.
Mwah!
( grunts )
What are you doing?
I'm 1,000 years old.
But--but--but--but
you don't look
more than 400.
Desperate, weak, pathetic.
I can't stand desperate.
The party is over.
I have made my choice.
No, please.
You can't give it to Wander.
He's an idiot.
He'll use it for good, not evil!
Give me what?
Wander, it is my wish
to bequeath to you--
( exploding )
Forget polite and proper.
Forget witty and charming.
I am not the
ultimate gentleman.
I am Lord Hater,
the ultimate evil.
When I want something,
I take it.
And I want your power, now!
Okay.
Huh?
Really?
Such strength.
Such force.
Oh, so we are doing
the kissing thing then?
I will enjoy
inhabiting your body
so much better than
this old hag's.
Yes. Wait, what?
Oh, yes, Lord Hater.
That's the catch.
Just as I did
with the Queen,
when I bequeath
my empire to a vessel,
they may control my power,
but I will control them
for the next 1,000 years!
( gagging )
Lord Hater.
Oh-ho! Okay, I'm full.
You stuck me in a sandwich
for a 1,000 years?
Destroy them!
Whoo-hoo!
Heck of a party, huh?
Later, Hater.
Run, you fools.
But mark my words,
I will find you
and you will pay!
So you're a sandwich now?
I'm totally into that.
Evil sandwich!
WANDER:
You been there?
Been there?
OLD LADY:
Yes. Uh-huh.
You betcha.
Indeedy-do.
So you saw the...
Ooh, it was terrific, but it was
no Arooga-dingle-ling-ling.
You've been
to Arooga-dingle-ling-ling, too?
Sylvia, isn't this amazing?
SYLVIA: Uh, it sure is.
WAITER: Welcome
to Planet Ziziks.
What will it be?
One Flarvarian float,
two straws.
I can't believe
you've been
to
Arooga-dingle-ling-ling-ling.
And a translation guide,
if you got one.
Sylvia, I met
another wanderer.
Can you believe she's
been to as many places
in the universe as me?
Name's Trudy, Trudy Traveler,
and I'm pleased
as punch to meetcha
and greetcha.
Yeah, likewise.
Ooh, and speaking of punch,
when you went to Glowerp,
did you see the Pbbt?
And the Rawr?
And the Bzzt?
WAITER: I'll just
leave it there.
I loved the Pbbt
and the Rawr,
and the Bzzt,
and the Flooshy Slooshy Sloosh.
I loved
the Flooshy Slooshy Sloosh.
Wait a minute.
I didn't see
the Flooshy Slooshy Sloosh.
Well, you're young.
You'll catch up someday.
Anywho, I should toodles.
Places to go, sights to see,
you understand.
Or do you?
( sighing )
Nothing like a Flarvarian
float to start off
a relaxing vacay, huh?
Aww. I can't stop thinking about
the Flooshy Slooshy Sloosh.
You really want to see
the Flooshy Slooshy thingy?
Well, then come on.
Let's go. The vacay can wait.
Sylvia's awesome.
I got to admit,
this is exciting.
That thing seem
slow to anyone?
Ooh!
Well, that's done.
Let's go.
Happy, Wander?
You got your Flooshy
Slooshy thingy
and I got my Flarvarian float
waiting for me back on Ziziks.
Let's get this
vacay underway.
Well, isn't this a treat?
Where y'all coming from?
We just saw Old Flooshy.
My favorite part
was the slooshing.
And now we're even.
Isn't that nice?
By the by, while you were
off seeing Old Slooshy,
I toured the Museum of
Ginormous Antiquities.
I tasted the galaxy's
biggest hoagie.
And stayed
at a fancy-shmancy hotel.
Seasoned traveler like you,
surely you've been
to all those places?
Gee, whackers.
I'm no math whiz,
but I think
that means I'm ahead
by three.
Toodles.
Not that it's a contest,
that'd be silly-willy.
But if it was,
I am winning.
So who's parched,
aside from me?
I want to eat, see,
and stay at those places,
respectively.
Wander, you're not getting
competitive, are you?
Sylvia, I am offended
at the implication.
I am simply expressing
a natural curiosity.
Yeah, all right, all right.
Don't get your
socks in a bunch.
Uh, I guess they do
sound like fun side-trips
and the vacay can wait.
But soon as we're done,
we're headed straight back
to Ziziks for my float,
got it?
Yeah-yeah-yeah,
sure, fine.
Just hang
a right and ignore
the speed limit.
It's so big.
Beautiful, impressive,
inspiring,
just as good as
the real thing.
Hey!
Then again,
I am kind of peckish.
( burping )
Check please.
SYLVIA: If you think a stay
at Fancy Shmancy's
Fancy Hotel will make up
for you eating my dinner--
Ooh!
There's a spa.
BELLHOP: Enjoy your stay.
We will.
We did.
We what?
WANDER: Trudy was right,
those places were amazing.
Were they?
I wouldn't know.
Take it from me, one of the
two most traveled folks
in the universe, they were.
I really
hate that sound.
Well, isn't this
a nice surprise?
Isn't it?
It is.
We just got back
from those three great
places you told us about.
Well, I guess
that'd make us tied
if I hadn't just gone
to five more.
WANDER: Impressive.
Impossible!
She drives at the speed
of dusty molasses.
Five.
I want to climb, observe,
witness, enjoy, and ride
those things, respectively.
Wander, I don't
think it's--
Please.
No. No.
Uh-uh.
No way.
Not gonna--
Okay. But only if you agree
to take it nice and slow.
Deal?
Eeee!
Let's go.
I'm sensing
a troubling pattern here.
The Temple of
Backalakabingbong
was a place of solemnity
and fortitude.
WANDER: Done.
The delicate Tardilius
plant blooms hourly,
awakening slowly to show
its splendid petals.
Done.
The courtship ritual
of the Lorb requires patience.
Done.
The Klerblatz ceremony
you are witnessing
has been unchanged for
thousands of years.
Done.
BUS DRIVER: And now
we are entering Shatterton,
the town made
entirely of glass.
Of course, we are.
We better take it slow or--
WANDER: Done.
I think we're clear.
Gah!
Well, howdy hoo.
Five, I saw five.
Five.
Oh.
I only saw four.
Really?
Tee.
Four-tee.
Forty.
Got it.
Hee-yahh!
Hee-yahh?
WANDER: Seen it,
saw it, done it,
did it, yep, yeah,
sure, fine.
Good, great,
got it, win it.
Victory will be mine.
( Sylvia panting )
You're a worthy
opponent, Wander.
Seems we are now even.
I don't do even.
Planet Pharphlung,
you, me, there,
now!
You're on.
Let's go, Sylvia.
Come on!
Adventure,
sights exploring, fun!
My feet hurt.
I'm tired.
I don't even want to think
about how thirsty I am.
Ugh, now
I'm thinking about it.
You got to choose, Wander.
It's her or m--
( groaning )
Gah!
WANDER: Oh my.
It's the birth of a star.
It's so beautiful.
Puts things
in perspective,
doesn't it?
I-- I don't know
what to say.
Actually, I do.
Eat it, Fuzzball.
I've been doing this
all wrong.
WAITER:
One Flarvarian float, one straw.
Better make it two.
Wander.
Sylvia, I am so sorry.
I got so caught up
in proving myself
the most traveled tourist
in the entire universe!
I forgot the real reason
I love wandering
in the first place.
The roses you stop
and smell aren't as sweet
without your best pal
to smell it with you.
Aw, man, what are you
trying to do to me
with all the
sappy sappiness?
Garcon,  one more straw.
Where are you?
Did you find him yet,
Trudy?
Nope.
Did you, Trudy?
You, Trudy?
Nope.
How about you, Trudy?
Nah.
Any luck, Trudy?
Sorry, Trudy, nope.
You?
What?
How about you?
You? You?
Ugh,
we'll never find him.
Give it up, Trudy.
Technically speaking,
the furry fella did win.
TRUDIES: Oh, just stow it,
would you, Trudy?
Destroy them!
( horse neighing )
( engine revving )
( soft music playing )