♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER OVER OVER
YONDER YONDER WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER,
OVER YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER
OVER, OVER ♪
♪ YONDER YONDER
WANDER WANDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
( screaming )
IT'S HORRIBLE!
WHAT? WHAT'S HORRIBLE?
IT'S TERRIBLE!
IT'S...
...AWESOME!
LET'S GET AWESOME.
THAT'S RIGHT, IT'S ME,
EMPEROR AWESOME,
AND I BRING NEWS
FOR YOU NERDS.
I'VE CHOSEN THIS PLANET
FOR ONE OF MY FAMOUS
PLANET-ENDING PARTIES.
( frightened yelling )
I KNOW YOU CAN'T BELIEVE IT,
BUT IT'S TRUE.
THIS IS HAPPENING.
YOU'RE SO LUCKY!
LET'S GET AWESOME.
WE'RE GONNA BE BLASTING
MAD-HOT JAMS
OUT OUR JAM BLASTERS.
WE'RE GONNA BE BUSTING
MAD-SICK MOVES
WITH OUR MOVE BUSTER,
AND THE BEST PART IS,
YOU'RE ALL INVITED.
I'VE THROWN DOWN ON TYLAR 5.
I'VE CUT LOOSE ON CRAZON.
I EVEN TRASHED MY MOM'S
HOUSE ONCE.
AND NOW I'M HERE TO GIVE
YOUR STUPID LITTLE PLANET
THE BEST NIGHT
IT'S EVER HAD,
FOR I AM EMPEROR AWESOME,
AND I AM...
( rock music blaring )
OH, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
IF THAT FLARPIN' IDIOT
KEEPS PARTYING
LIKE THERE'S NO TOMORROW,
THERE WILL LITERALLY BE
NO TOMORROW.
COME ON, WANDER, WE GOTTA
PULL THE PLUG ON THIS PARTY.
WANDER.
WANDER!
PAR-TAY!
WANDER. WANDER!
WANDER, I KNOW
YOU LOVE PARTIES,
AND HATE PARTY POOPERS,
BUT THIS IS A BAD PARTY.
IT DESERVES TO BE
POOPED ON, YOU GOT ME?
YEAH, OKAY,
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
LOOK, I'M GONNA
GO IN THERE
AND TAKE DOWN AWESOME
ON MY OWN.
YOU STAY HERE
AND JUST CONTROL YOURSELF.
THINK YOU CAN DO THAT?
I'LL TRY.
GOOD. I'LL BE
RIGHT BACK.
ALL RIGHT, TIME TO
GET THIS PARTY ENDED.
WHERE YOU GOING,
SADDLEBAGS?
TO PUNCH AWESOME'S
TEETH IN--
UH, I MEAN, DANCE.
NOT DRESSED LIKE THAT,
YOU AIN'T.
SERIOUSLY? YOU SUPERFICIAL,
SHALLOW KNUCKLEHEADS
ARE ALL THE SAME.
YOU WANT EVERY GIRL TO HAVE
BIG, STUPID HAIR LIKE THIS.
AND A DINKY LITTLE OUTFIT
AND UNCOMFORTABLE SHOES,
AND A BUNCH OF
CLOWN MAKEUP,
AND, I DON'T KNOW,
SOME OF THIS STUFF,
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
HUH? IS IT?
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
NO, I DON'T...
I WAS JUST TRYING TO PROVE...
OH, FORGET IT.
OKAY, HARD PART'S OVER.
NOW TO JUST
GET TO THAT STAGE AND...
STOP IT.
WE CAN'T.
THEY'RE PARTYING TOO HARD.
PLEASE HELP US.
WHO WANTS GLOW RODS?
BE CAREFUL, THEY'RE
MILDLY RADIOACTIVE.
PSYCH!
NOBODY SHOULD EVER
BE CAREFUL EVER.
( laughs )
AWESOME, I AM COMING...
FOR YOU!
YEAH, YOU WANT THIS.
WHAT? EW, NO WAY.
SYLVIA, I THINK...
I THINK...
I THINK THE RHYTHM'S
INSIDE ME.
JUST A LITTLE
WHILE LONGER.
YOU GOTTA HOLD ON!
THERE'S GOTTA BE A WAY
TO GET UP ON THAT STAGE.
EXCUSE ME, LADY.
AWESOME SAW YOU OUT THERE.
HE WANTS YOU
UP ON THAT STAGE.
UH... OKAY THEN.
JUST HANG IN THERE, PAL,
A FEW MORE MINUTES.
( teeth chattering )
NO PROBLEM.
LET'S GET AWESOME.
COME ON, COME ON.
WANDER'S ABOUT TO POP
ANY SECOND NOW.
CALM DOWN, DANCIN' FOLKS.
HE'LL BE OUT ON STAGE
ANY SECOND NOW.
YES, FINALLY!
WHAT?!
CONGRATS, REBECCA.
YOU'RE PART OF
THE AWESOME CREW NOW.
I'M TAKIN' YOU TO
EVERY PLANET I PARTY ON.
B.T. DUBS, HAD NO IDEA
WHAT YOUR NAME WAS
OUT THERE IN LAME TOWN;
IT'S REBECCA NOW.
BECKS. YEAH, NOW
YOU'RE BECKS.
"B."
LET ME OUTTA HERE,
AWESOME.
I'M GONNA
SHUT THIS PARTY DOWN.
DON'T WEAR YOURSELF
OUT, B.
WE'RE JUST GETTIN' STARTED.
OH, YEAH, LOVIN' WHAT
I'M SEEIN', PARTY BROS.
LET'S CRANK THE VOLUME UP
AND BRING THIS PLANET DOWN.
SOON, EVERYBODY IN THIS LAME
OLD UNIVERSE WILL KNOW...
( echoing )
NOBODY PARTIES HARDER
THAN EMPEROR AWESOME!
AWESOME, AWESOME.
WANDER!
WANDER!!
LET 'ER RIP, BUDDY.
TIME TO DANCE!
DANCE, DANCE!!
HEY, WHAT'S WITH THE FUR BALL?
DON'T WE HAVE A DRESS CODE?
THAT'S WANDER,
AND HE LOVES PARTYING
MORE THAN ANYBODY ELSE
IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE.
EVEN YOU.
YEAH, RIGHT.
IF HE LOVES PARTYING
SO MUCH, CAN HE DO THIS?
WELL, I'LL GIVE IT
A TRY.
OH, DO YOU KNOW THIS ONE?
GO, WANDER,
GO, WANDER!
YEAH!
HEY, LOSERS,
LISTEN UP.
HISTORY'S BEEN MADE TODAY.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER,
I'VE FOUND A PLANET
TOO LAME FOR ME
TO PARTY ON.
YOU'RE ALL DUMB,
AND I'M LEAVING.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID?
YOU'RE ALL UNCOOL,
AND I'M OUTTA HERE.
AND I'M NEVER
COMING BACK. EVER.
( growling )
I'LL GET YOU.
AND I'LL GET YOU.
YOU CAN'T HANDLE THIS.
EVERYBODY
BACK IN THE SHIP.
WE'RE GONE.
AWESOME OUT.
I SAID EVERYBODY
IN THE SHIP!
JUST GO.
WE STILL HAVE
ONE HECK OF A MESS
TO CLEAN UP.
CLEAN UP...
- PARTY?
- SURE.
WOWEE!
ALL RIGHT, WANDER,
WHERE ARE WE THIS TIME?
"YOU ARE HERE."
WE'RE HERE.
SEE THAT RED DOT?
THAT'S US, RIGHT HERE.
AND THAT GUY'S OVER THERE.
HELLO.
LOOKS LIKE THREE DAYS
TO THE NEAREST EXIT.
( stomach rumbling )
WE'RE GONNA NEED
SUPPLIES.
I'LL GET SOME GRUB.
TWO, PLEASE.
CARE FOR SOME ROYAL
SAUCE, MY LADY?
NAH, MY PAL AND I
LIKE TO KEEP IT...
SIMPLE?
WANDER, WHO IS...
A BIG HUNGRY GUY.
IS IT YOU?
I BET IT IS.
- WHY IS HE...
- SO ADORABLE?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE WAS JUST WANDERIN'
AROUND ALL BY HIS LONESOME,
AND SO, WELL, I GUESS
WE'RE A FAMILY NOW.
( babbling )
I LOVE YOU,
MY HUCKLEBERRY KNUCKLEHEAD.
HUCKLE... WHAT?!
WANDER, THAT'S DEFINITELY
NOT HIS, OR ANYBODY ELSE'S NAME.
HE SURE LOOKED LIKE
A HUCKLEBERRY KNUCKLEHEAD TO ME.
IN ANY CASE,
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMEBODY
LOOKING FOR THIS LITTLE...
( squeaks )
- THIS GUY.
( sighs )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU HEAR THAT, HUCK?
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
BACK TO YOUR FOLKS.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
( happy giggling )
OKAY, GLAD THE BABY'S
ON BOARD.
NOW, LOOK FOR TWO
FREAKED-OUT GIANTS.
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
MALL SECURITY OUGHTA
BE ABLE TO HELP US
FIND HIS...
FOLKS.
( baby giggling )
( crash, glass breaking )
OH, NO.
I LIKE LOLLIPOP.
HIYA, SYLVIA.
WHO'D HAVE THUNK A BABY
WOULD LIKE CANDY SO MUCH?
( cash register jingling )
WANDER, WE'VE GOTTA
GET THIS KID TO SECURITY
TO FIND HIS PARENTS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
THE BEST WAY TO GET KIDS
TO DO WHAT YOU WANT
IS TO LET 'EM DO
WHATEVER THEY WANT.
( laughing )
PLEASE. YOU KNOW WHAT
THE MOST IMPORTANT WORD
IS WITH KIDS?
NO.
AND THEY NEED TO BE
TOLD NO A LOT.
SYLVIA.
YOU SHOULD NEVER SAY...
THAT TO A BABY.
( loud whisper )
IT HURTS THEIR FEELINGS.
NO, NO.
BAD BABY. BAD.
GOOD BOY.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TAKING OVER.
NO. WE'RE GOING TO
MALL SECURITY RIGHT
NOW, MISTER.
OH, STUBBORN, HUH?
WELL, GUESS WHAT.
I AM, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, KIDDO,
YOU'VE GIVEN ME
NO OTHER OPTION.
( Sylvia straining
and laughing )
UGH. WE ARE NEVER
HAVING KIDS.
WE'RE NOT HIS PARENTS.
ISN'T THE BIG LADY
A BIG SILLY WILLY?
THAT'S RIGHT, SYLVIA.
YOU'RE GIVING HIM
WHAT HE WANTS. FUN!
( babbling )
DING!
OH, HUCKLEBERRY
KNUCKLEHEAD.
OVER HERE.
PEEK-A-BOO.
PEEK-A-BOO!
SEE, SYLVIA?
ALL IT TOOK WAS
A LITTLE FUN AND GAMES.
NOW I GOT HIM
RIGHT WHERE I WANT HIM.
SH! DON'T SPOIL
THE SURPRISE.
PEEK-A...
BOO?
PEEK-A-BOO.
EXCUSE ME. PARDON. SORRY.
I KNOW I'M
DOING IT WRONG.
UH-OH.
( people screaming )
HUCKLEBERRY
KNUCKLEHEAD!
STILL NOT
A REAL NAME.
HUCKLEBERRY!
OH!
ROARIN' ORANGE.
BACK UPSTAIRS.
SAM'S SLUSHY STAND.
THERE HE IS!
HE'S SOCIALIZING
SO WELL.
HUCK, NO.
SYLVIA, WE CAN SOLVE THIS
WITHOUT STIFLING HIS CREATIVITY.
D-OH! WANDER,
YOU'RE NOT HELPING.
( gasping )
( ear-piercing shriek )
THAT'S MY BOY.
WHAT A SET OF PIPES.
YOU TWO ARE
HORRIBLE PARENTS.
LEARN HOW TO CONTROL
YOUR KID.
YOU TAKE THAT BACK.
HE IS A PERFECT
LITTLE ANGEL.
HE'S NOT OUR KID!
WHAT? WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT DOES IT WANT?
AW, POOR LITTLE FELLA.
HE'S ALL TUCKERED OUT.
HE WANTS SOME
COMFORT, SYLVIA.
UM, HOW YA DOIN'?
( loud belch )
WELL, THIS IS
UNPLEASANT.
WHAT? WANDER, LOOK.
OUR PRAYERS
HAVE BEEN ANSWERED.
HEY, WE FOUND YOUR KID!
SH! SYLVIA!
YOU'LL WAKE HIM UP.
( loud whispering ) GOOD.
IF YOU STOPPED CODDLING HIM,
AND TOOK CHARGE FOR ONCE,
HE MIGHT LISTEN LONG ENOUGH
SO WE COULD GET HIM
TO SECURITY
AND FIND HIS
FLARF-NARBLING PARENTS.
WELL, IF YOU STOPPED
BEING SO STRICT,
AND DID SOMETHING
FUN FOR ONCE,
HE MIGHT LISTEN
LONG ENOUGH
SO WE COULD GET
HIM TO SECURITY
AND FIND HIS
FLARF-NARBLING PARENTS.
AND I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT
THEY NARBLE FLARFS, IMHO.
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT
THEY REALLY NARBLED
FLARFS.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S A FIGURE OF...
( loud crying )
NOW LOOK WHAT
YOU'VE DONE.
ME? YOU WERE THE ONE WHO...
WHY ARE WE
STILL WHISPERING?
I'M NOT
ENTIRELY SURE.
DON'T WORRY,
HUCKLEBERRY.
MEE-MAW AND PEE-PAW
ARE JUST HAVING
A DISAGREEMENT.
WE'RE NOT HIS PARENTS.
( whimpering )
( gasping
and screaming )
( clock chiming )
LOLLY.
OH!
HUCKLEBERRY
KNUCKLEHEAD.
NO!
OOH! LOOK,
HUCKLEBERRY KNUCKLEHEAD.
A LOLLY.
( screaming )
( cheering )
YES, YES.
COME GET YOUR
FURRY LOLLY.
I DO LICK LOLLIPOP.
NO, NOT YET.
YOU CAN LICK
MY HEAD LATER.
YES, WE'RE
ALMOST THERE.
( baby exclaiming )
UH-UH, NOT YET.
SIR, MADAME,
NO NEED TO THANK US,
BUT WE FOUND YOUR SON.
EW, GROSS. SHE THINKS
I'M SOMEONE'S DAD.
EW! WE JUST CAME TO SEE
IF SOMEONE TURNED
IN MY PHONE.
WE'RE NOT EVEN
GROWNUPS.
GROSS.
I DON'T UNDER...
OH, THANK GROP!
THERE YOU ARE.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
MAMA, DADA.
( kissing )
WAIT. THOSE ARE--
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN,
HUCKLEBERRY KNUCKLEHEAD?
AND THAT'S REALLY HIS--
YOU HAD US WORRIED SICK.
DON'T BE TOO HARD
ON HIM, DEAR.
ARE YOU HUNGRY, THIRSTY,
OVERTIRED, UNDER-TIRED?
HOW'S ABOUT A GAME
OF GOTCHERNOSE?
WELL, BYE-BYE, KID.
COME ON, WANDER.
LET'S GO.
CAN I SAY GOOD-BYE?
OH, I HOPE IT WASN'T
TOO MUCH TROUBLE
GETTING HIM
OVER HERE.
HE CAN BE
A BIT OF A HANDFUL.
NO PROBLEM AT ALL.
IT WAS EASY AS
TAKING CANDY FROM A...
DROP IT!
OH, STUBBORN, HUH?
WELL, GUESS WHAT.
I AM, TOO.
( baby babbling )