♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
The ring of invincibility
shall be mine!
This wasn't exactly
part of my plan.
Your plan?
What do you mean,
your plan?
Well...
There's a Fall
Flower Fling
atop the Alkaloid
Trapazoid Station.
Pass it on!
There's a tall shower thing
in Vince and Lilly's shop
on the android planetoid
for Dalmatians.
Pass it on.
( indistinct whispering )
There's an all-powerful
Ring of Invincibility
at the top of the Blastroid
Asteroid Formation?!
Set a course.
With that ring,
I shall be unstoppable!
Perfect.
Wait. I'm confused.
How did you even know
there was a ring of
invincibility here?
- I put it there.
- What? Where did you
find a... a...
Well...
Ahem. Excuse me,
kind sir.
Which of these candy rings
is the most romantic?
Okay, so you planted
an "ultimate weapon of power,"
and then you told
everyone in the galaxy
about it,
and you didn't expect
every villain in the galaxy
to come and claim it?
Uh-uh. I was just hoping
for Hater and Dominator.
But why?
If Hater's gonna ask
Dominator to get married,
she's gonna need a ring.
What?!
( squeals )
Well...
( cackling laughter )
That's right.
Dominator's greater.
Best villain.
Ooh, aah.
That's right,
ooh, yeah.
Oh, one of these,
one of these.
And one, two, three.
Lady?!
You've really gotta start
filling me in on these plans.
Hater's always talking about
how he wants a girlfriend.
So I devised
a perfect set-up
to get Hater
and Dominator
to show up here.
They'll fall in love,
that love will cancel out
all their evil,
and everything will
be great forever.
Or they become
twice as evil,
and conquer
the galaxy together!
Nah!
Keep at it, sir.
This is our chance.
If we get to
that ring of invincibility,
then we can trounce
these chumps,
and finally reclaim
the title of...
BOTH: The greatest
in the galaxy!
- Let's get awesome.
- Please.
Ha! Huh?
Let's get awesome.
Later, nerds. Smashtag
greatest in the galaxy,
smashtag Awesome out!
Oh, no. We gotta get
Hater to the top.
Dominator's not even
here yet.
Good.
I don't think I can
protect you out there.
Sylvia, Sylvia,
Sylvia.
They say love
is a battlefield.
This is an actual
battlefield!
( explosion )
Look, I get it.
You wanna help everybody,
no matter how many times
they try to destroy us.
It's like your thing.
But all this
is beyond nuts.
Wander!
Quit hitting yourself.
Why are you hitting yourself?
- Quit hitting yourself.
- Hey, Hatey!
I'm gonna go get
that ring of invincibility
and use it to make everybody in
the galaxy best friends.
Betcha can't catch me!
Wander!!
Please, sir,
we're so close.
- Don't...
- ( ferocious roar )
...stop doing
what you're doing.
Go, sir! Go!
( yelling )
Don't worry, buddy.
I'm coming.
Not this time,
Zbornak.
You don't understand.
The ring's a fake.
Enough tricks.
It's go time.
Darn it, we don't
have time for...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I've been so looking
forward to this.
WANDER:
Best meet-cute ever!
Hey, hey, it's me.
I did it, so I'm
gonna get this ring now,
and I'm the greatest
or whatever.
Wait!
Who are you?
Oh, oh, um...
I'm the terrible,
super mean villain
something the so-and-so.
I'm really strong.
And I'm gonna
use this ring
to... take over
the solar system,
or blow it up or...
or maybe just turn
you guys into...
my minions or monkeys
or something.
Shoot,
I don't know.
I really should've
put more thought into this.
But it's late...
I have this cape,
so, uh...
Dude, put down the ring
and come back
when you're
better-prepared.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm really...
I'm sorry.
I was just, uh...
Just put this back.
Yeah, sorry.
Uh... bye.
Get back here.
That's it, just a couple
more platforms until
happily ever after.
Now, Lord Hater,
tremble before the might of
Kraagghthrrr.
Fat chance,
Kragthar.
No, no, it's pronounced
Kraagghthrrr.
That's what I said.
Krggaggathar.
Kraagghthrrr.
Like, raagghthrrr,
but with a K in front.
Oh, no,
what else could go wrong?
Oh, I don't know.
How about...
evil sandwich?!
♪ Evil sandwich ♪
Sourdough?
Thank you so much
for distracting
Lord Hater.
With him out of the way,
there'll be no stopping me
from claiming
the ring,
and becoming
the greatest in the galaxy!
♪ Evil sandwich ♪
( shuddering )
I am sorry
to have to do this,
but you leave me
no choice.
What? Bro, bro,
you can't eat me.
You're a vegetarian.
I don't need to eat you
to beat you.
Picnic time!
Help me, help me,
you buffoons!
- Over here.
- No, here, you imbeciles.
I'm the sandwich
that's talking.
I am really sorry about this,
but love is on the line.
Thank you for
understanding.
Oh, no, you don't,
you furry orange freak.
Later, Krrrraigtharrr.
It's
Kraagghthrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
I am so sorry.
I feel real bad about this,
but it's all
in the name of love!
Quickly, my robots.
( wheezing )
Get them!
( dance music plays )
Sorry. I'll make sure you get
an extra slice of cake
at the wedding.
( wheezing cough )
I'm too old for this nonsense.
I need a nap.
( wheezes )
( squeaking )
I'm trying to tell you,
there's no ring
of invincibility.
It's just a con.
How do I know
you saying it's
a con isn't a con?
I was ready to get off
this stinkin' rock,
and leave you jerks here
to destroy each other.
But then, he ran off
without thinking,
even though I told him
not to,
and threw himself
into a dangerous situation
without any kind
of plan or exit strategy,
and left me behind
to save his butt
and clean up his mess.
BOTH: Do you have any idea
what's it's like
to have a fool
for a friend?
( gentle lilting
music plays )
( needle scratches )
Okay, so I kinda sorta
helped Lord Hater
to beat a bunch
of rival villains,
thus making him
even more of a bad guy
than he already was.
But it'll all be worth it
when he's in love,
reformed, and going
antiquing on his honeymoon.
Right?
A banana peel?
Who would've left a...
Oh, no. Not...
Dr. Screwball Jones!
Ah, there you are.
I was starting to miss you
a whole bunch.
Your senseless spree
of punnish pandemonium is over
before it began.
I didn't want
to do this,
but I have to.
For love.
Oh, blast.
I've been blasted.
The situation is grave.
No time for...
gallows humor.
I should be
deadly serious.
Oh!
( shuddering groans )
Oh, I hope I get
a tomb with a view.
Oh, doom with a view
would also work.
Okay, come on now.
That's enough.
She came!
Whoo-hoo!
Finally,
Operation Romance is go!
Ooh, hoo-hoo!
Oh, man.
I can't believe
all these idiots
are in the same place.
This'll be like
shooting dorks in a barrel.
But what'll I use
to stop 'em?
It's gotta be perfect.
Blood scythe?
Hammer hand?
Ooh, giant spinning
buzz saw arms?
A zillion tiny spikes
that shoot out a zillion
tiny poison darts
that make your tongue
swell up and you're all,
"Gah, no!
Betrayed by my own tongue!
Curse you, Dominator,
curse you..."
( choking sounds )
( gasps )
Oh!
Magma cannons.
Classic.
Yes.
( evil laughter )
Okay, calm down, D.
Focus. Game face.
Game face.
It's... ( gravelly voice )
go time!
( diabolical laughter )
Oh, no. If the Black Cube
gets the ring of invincibility,
- he'll be unstoppable.
- ( all gasping )
♪ I'm just a little
black cube ♪
♪ Of darkness ♪
♪ A little black cube
of darkness ♪
I'm so cool.
She's coming, she's coming,
she's coming, she's coming!
This is it!
Come on, Hatey.
( groans )
Hatey?
Oh, no,
what have I done?
You're too wounded
to woo.
Too harmed to charm,
too pooped to propose.
Come on, buddy.
Just one more platform,
and I promise you'll
get what you want most
in the universe.
Hey, Hater, I'm gonna
tell everyone in the galaxy
how we're best friends.
Don't you wanna stop me?
Let's go. Whoo!
Oh, it's no use.
I guess Dominator'll just take
the ring of invincibility,
and become
the greatest in the galaxy.
Dominator?
I hate that guy!
This is it.
It's all happening.
Oh, boy, they're
gonna love each other.
Lord Dominator.
Lord Hater.
Oh, no, they're
gonna kill each other!
Stop, stop.
New plan, new plan.
( wicked laughter )
Get away from there.
I call dibs on the ring.
( panting )
Had enough...
( wheezing )
Zbornak?
I'm just gettin' started,
you optic nerd.
- ( explosion )
- Huh?
Must stop their fighting.
Must give toast at
30th wedding anniversary.
BOTH: Oh, no!
Dominator's gonna kill him.
Five-minute break?
Five-minute break.
♪ Commander Peepers
and Sylvia ♪
Stop it. There's
got to be a better way.
You two have
so much in common.
You both want to control
the galaxy.
You both want
to destroy each other.
You both like skulls.
Let's use that as a foundation
and build from there.
I was totally
holding back before,
but now you shall know
the full fury
of Lord... ow!
That super burn-y!
Stop... being...
so...
...cool!
Okay, new plan.
If romance won't
come to the mountain,
then the mountain
must become romantic.
( bad French accent )
Such a beautiful couple
deserves
ze beautiful flowers.
( bad Italian accent )
Or a romantic dinner.
Okay, maybe
we're being too forward.
How about a low-stakes
coffee date?
( screaming )
The cinnamon,
it burns!
How can he stare
longingly into your eyes
if he can't
see your face?
Yes!
Nothing will keep me
from that ring,
for I am Lord Hater...
Wander. Oh, thank Grop
you're okay.
I thought something
terrible happened.
Something terrible
did happen.
This is less of
a meet-cute
and more of
a meet ( growls )
"I'm going to
destroy you!"
Your heart's
in the right place, buddy,
but if we don't bolt,
the rest of you
is gonna be splattered
all over the mountain.
But if Hater and Dominator
don't fall in love,
they'll never get married
and invest in
a mid-size time share
on Zyzzx!!!!
- What?
- That's what I said.
( evil laughter )
I am Lord Hater!
The greatest in
the galaxy!
- ( screams )
- Let's get outta here!
No. This has
got to work.
I have a series
of ice breakers.
"What's your favorite
time of day?
What embarrassing thing
have you never told anybody?
What's your favorite
type of chocolate?"
( evil laughter )
( all gasping )
( maniacal laughter )
Kneel. Kneel before
Dominator.
The greatest
in the galaxy.
No, but they were
supposed to...
and now they...
And now she...
And... it didn't work?
I really thought,
with love in his life,
Hater would finally learn
there's no point in being
so angry and evil
all the time.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Love is a battlefield,
and sometimes, you lose.
VILLAINS: Dominator's greater.
Best villain!
Dominator's greater.
( chanting continues )
Haaaaate!
( all gasping )
Lady?
( giggling )
I... you.
Lady.
I... so cool.
Pretty.
Not hate. Like.
( evil laughter )
Mmm. Blorpberry.
( slurping )
Sir? Sir? Sir?
Well, at least I think
he likes her.
We kinda
sorta won.
Whoo-hoo!
Pretty.
Lady.
Soft.
Smells nice.
Lovely.
Not hate.
Pretty.
( laughs )
Sir?
This is gonna be
a whole thing, isn't it?
( goofy laughter )
Pretty.