♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
All right!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
( gasping )
Here you go.
Watch your step.
Lovely day
for a mass evacuation.
Whew!
And just before
Mt. Krackyourbigtoa
could blow her top.
( sighs )
Saving an entire species
from fiery doom
deserves a little R & R.
That's rest
and really fruity drink
with a tiny umbrella.
Right, partner?
Partner?
WANDER:
We didn't save everyone!
( sighs )
Wait for me,
tiny umbrella.
( Sylvia snorts )
( rumbling )
That's not good!
That's less good!
Wander, are you nuts?
This place is gonna
pop its cork any minute!
But, Sylvia, look!
Ah, so you are nuts.
Good to know.
We can't
just leave them.
They're too cute to perish
in a pool of hot magma!
Don't worry, little guys.
I know things
seem bleak now.
But I have a plan
and I promise,
no one shall die this day!
( explosion )
( squawking )
Wander, it's impossible
to try and save them.
We can't do it!
( sniffs )
Eww!
You smell that?
Oh, you mean 10,000 gallons
of hot liquid death?
No.
( sniffs )
It smells like a big pile
of "can't doo-doo."
Woowee!
Come on, Syl.
How many times
do I got to tell ya?
Anything is possible
with a pep in your step
and a grin on your chin.
What you need
is a positive can-dotitude!
( explosion )
Observe.
I have complete
and total confidence
that I will scoop up
this lovely little family
and carry them to safety,
thus saving them
from a burn-y lava-y demise.
( shrieking )
Ow!
What a good mama you are!
Let's try this again.
Aah!
( sheepish chuckle )
Can-dotitude can often require
try-try-againiness.
Ee-ow!
Ow!
I respect that.
Yee-ow!
You're so protective!
Ow-ow!
Ow!
Now let's go!
Ee-ow!
This can't end well.
( explosion )
( chirping )
Whoa, slow down there,
Scaredy!
Where's the fire?
Um, everywhere.
Gah, get back here!
I'm-- agh--
trying to save your kid.
Oh, great! Now we'll
never find him in time.
We're doomed!
Sylvia, can-dotitude!
( explosion )
( grunts angrily )
Remember, everybody,
the path to positive thinking
starts with a single step.
( screams )
Scaredy!
We're so happy
we found you here.
SYLVIA:
Inside the volcano!
Wander!
Ow!
Hang on!
We're saved!
Or not.
Wander, these little guys
can't make a jump like that.
I told you
this was impossible.
No! The chasm
between can-dotitude
and give-uppittiness
may be wide,
but I believe
you can bridge that gap!
Wait, what now?
You can bridge that gap.
( whimpering )
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
( grunts )
See, kids,
Sylvia's got it, right?
You just have to look
deep, deep down
and find that spark
in yourselves and--
Enough pep talk!
Just hurry!
Sorry.
I'm gonna
try to pick up your kids, see.
And then I'm gonna
hug 'em, see.
And you're not gonna
like it, see.
( screams )
I can't hold on much...
Hmm?
Agh!
Tiny!
Alan.
Alan?
Looks like an Alan.
Do something, okay?
But he's too far!
Alan! I know everything
seems bleak-- Ow!
But you've got to channel
that positive power and--
Ow!
Jump!
Are you crazy?
You can-dodit it, dude!
Yeah!
No!
Phew!
( screams )
( shrieking )
Question, what do you call
that pointy thing
that hangs down
from a cave?
Not the best time
for a geology quiz, Wander!
Just wondering
if I should yell
"Grab onto that stalagmite!"
or "Grab onto that stalactite!"
Everybody hang on!
I admire-- ow--
your consistency.
Momma.
Ow!
Get ready!
( screams )
I will take that
as a thank-you.
♪ Pum-pum-pum-boo!
♪ See what your life can bring
♪ When your do-titude is can!
♪ We thought positive-a-ly
♪ Now we're right back
where we began! Whoo! ♪
Yeah,
that's not a good thing.
Sure it is, Sylvia.
All we need is to stay positive,
push forward, and--
( loud rumble )
And what?
Die?
It's okay.
We can just go back
to the other side
of the volcano.
Um...
Uh...
Perhaps if I can
signal the mainland, we--
Oh, for zingle-zang's sake!
Every little thing
that could go wrong has.
You win, volcano!
Are you happy?
I give up!
Listen, little fellers,
I promised I was gonna
get you out of here alive,
but I can't do it.
Ow!
( loud explosion )
( Sylvia sniffs )
Eww!
Do you smell that?
Smell what?
( sniffs )
It smells like
what a good friend of mine
would call a fresh pile
of can't doo-doo!
Now I have a plan,
an awesome plan
that's 100% positive,
sure to work.
And I promise
no one shall die this day!
Promise.
Uh, Sylvia,
mainland is that way.
( shrieking )
( loud explosion )
Stalag-o-mite!
( chirping )
( sighs )
We meet again.
( chirping )
Ow! Ow!
It worked, Sylvia!
Your plan totally worked.
Nothin' you can't do
with a little can-dotitude.
Never doubted
it for a second.
( giggles )
( clock chiming )
Layin' it on a little thick,
isn't she?
( Wander gasps )
Sylvia!
Ah, I'm sorry,
but the goo-goo eyes,
the trembling widdle lip.
Yuck!
( thunder crashing )
( Wander whimpers )
( sighs )
Okay.
Hey, Little Bits.
Need some help?
( stomach rumbles )
This little kitty is gonna get
whatever she wants!
You've got to be
kidding me.
Sylvia!
Be nice.
Now, sweetie pie.
Tell us
where your whelping box is
and we'll take you on home.
( gasps )
You don't have
a whelping box?
Where does your
mama cat live?
You don't have a mama cat?
Who takes care
of your litter mates?
Any pet sitters?
Kindly neighbors?
Concerned veterinarians?
Groomers?
Milk men?
Sympathetic dogs next door?
Do you have anyone
to take care of you?
A distant relative
or perhaps a kooky cat lady?
( gasps )
Where are they?
Can you show us
the way to them?
Great, so we'll call you a cab
and you can--
Sylvia!
We can't send a defenseless
little ball of fluff
like this out alone!
Come on, Little Bits,
we're taking you
to a distant relative
or perhaps
a kooky cat lady.
Just saying,
when I was your size,
I already had a good job
scraping graz bits
out of plasma cores.
( Little Bits sneezes )
( gasps )
Oh, my gosh,
she's catching a cold!
( Little Bits sniffles )
Sylvia, we have to warm her up
immediately!
Jeez, calm down.
We'll just get her
a warm orange fur coat?
How's that, sugar lump?
( Little Bits giggles )
( groaning )
You sure we're heading
the right way, fuzzball?
'Cause we just left
the only town
on this entire planet, so...
( Little Bits whimpers )
( gasps )
Oh no! What's wrong?
Oh no!
Your poor exposed
little footsies.
How could we have been
so insensitive?
Sylvia, we're monsters!
Oh, I'm sure our gifts of food
and clothing
have scarred her for life.
( sighs )
You want me to carry her?
What's your preferred style,
ma'am?
Piggy-back?
Horsey-saddle?
Fireman carry?
Kangaroozle?
Anything!
Just let me know
what you want.
Ouch!
Ow!
Oof!
( painful grunts )
Wander, buddy,
at least let me carry you.
Naw-uh.
Got to keep a close
eye on our girl.
Just in case.
( gasps )
Watch out
( Little Bits giggles )
Wander, we need to talk.
Isn't she adorable?
( shrieking )
( growling )
Wander, don't!
( loud crash )
( Little Bits giggling )
Again.
She likes this game.
( panting )
( grunting )
Again.
All right,
that's enough!
Yeah,
I don't think so, missy.
You had enough fun
with Wander.
Now take us to your
kooky cat lady or whatever.
Wander ain't got nine lives,
you know.
( snarling )
She's so cute
when she's angry.
Ugh!
This is why
I don't have pets.
And now I know
all 17 of Lord Hater's
secret tickle points.
( giggling )
( yawning )
( snoring gently )
Aw, Sylvia, look.
She's using me as a pillow.
( loud crunch )
No!
It's fine.
Ow!
Ow! Ow!
( sighs )
Wander,
I know she's cute,
but I got to say
there's something real weird.
What's that, Little Bits?
You want a lullaby?
♪ Close your eyes,
rest your head ♪
♪ Let my belly be your bed
♪ I won't move
through the night ♪
♪ If it helps you sleep
all right ♪
( snoring gently )
Like I was saying,
there's something
bothering me about--
Sorry, Sylvia, just a sec.
♪ You need help,
I'm here to stay ♪
♪ I'll do anything you say
Doesn't it at least seem
suspicious to you that--
♪ And when I say "anything"
I literally mean anything ♪
( yawning )
Okay, weird lullaby.
Wander, your heart's
in the right place, but--
( snoring )
Fine.
We'll talk tomorrow.
( evil laugh )
Oh, just playing with her bear
in the woods.
At midnight?
( chuckles )
I have tested
the limits of my pwisonuh.
Wanduh is fully
under my contwol.
Very impressive.
And you're set to deliver them
on schedule?
As wong as
you have my rewahd.
( stifled laughter )
What's so funny?
I'm sorry.
It's just the way
you say "reward."
Little Bits
is a bounty hunter.
I knew it.
Well, I didn't know that,
but--
Wander!
I got to tell Wand--
( loud crash )
( evil laugh )
( rooster crowing )
Lord Hatah, I have arrived
at the wawn-duh-voo point.
Activate
the tel-wuh-poor-tation pad.
Engaging.
But before I do,
say "teleportation" again.
Te-wuh-poor-tation.
( laughing )
Okay, okay, okay,
now say, um,
"six thick
thistle sticks stacks."
Ah, you're no fun.
( evil giggle )
As soon as the pad is charged
you will be dewivered to Hater
for your torture
and ultimate destwuction!
Won't you, Wandah?
SYLVIA: No, he won't!
( snarling )
Ahh!
Sylvia!
Hey!
I like the pretty bracelets
Little Bits made for you.
( grunts )
Wander, what are you doing?
We've got to get out of here.
Well, gosh,
I'm sorry, Sylvia,
I--I didn't realize you--
( clears throat )
No!
I mean...
Oh, Wander.
Wandah.
Oh, Wandah.
Wee-ee!
Wandah.
Wandah!
Yes.
( giggles )
It's usewess, Thylvia.
Wander will never
weave my thide.
Justh wike you'll never
leave his.
You're right.
I'll never leave his side.
Wherever he goes, I go.
And we're not going
anywhere.
No fair!
Where--Who--Ugh,
my aching head.
( gasps )
Wait, there was a little kitty
in the street.
Did we help her?
I like to think we did.
Now can we head back
to town?
Pwease?
Of course!
As soon as we
figure out what's
wrong with your eyes.
Also, why am I wearing
a potato sack?
LORD HATER: Sorry, kid,
no prisoners, no bounty.
You get the boiling oil.
Oh, please don't insult me.
Sorry, just too much hate
in here.
LITTLE BITS: Sthix sthick
sthistle sthicks sthacks.
LORD HATER: Oh, dang it!