♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
PEEPERS:  Eons ago, a beacon
of hope shone forth
to guard the good
and wipe out the wicked.
The might, the myth,
the mech known as
Robomechabotatron!
A nearly indestructible
suit of armor,
created to save the galaxy
from threats
no one planet alone
could face!
Its mission complete,
the Robomechabotatron was
entombed on a hidden planet
until the galaxy
needed it again.
A cosmic super-weapon!
A crusader for justice.
Robomechabotatron!
Sure sounds nifty.
Nifty? We are talking about
a legendary robo-suit
that could save
the entire galaxy
from Dominator.
Sorry, was neato more of
the response you were
looking for?
PEEPERS: Equipped with four
unique battle stations,
lunatanium shields,
and a laso-matic broad-axe
stronger than 23 krampulons!!
Ooh! I have no idea
what any of that means.
PEEPERS:
It means, with this mech,
we can conquer Dominator,
and the entire galaxy!
I want that
Roboshamalamadingdong!!
And have it, you shall.
Behold.
The robomechabota...
- You?!
- Me!
- That!
The Robo-mekaleka--
Mechahimichonga-- Habbahooba--
ALL: Ooh!
Dibs!
Nuh-uh. That mecha's ours.
We're not gonna let you
use it to take over the galaxy.
No way, horse-ay.
We're taking down
Dominator.
You're just gonna use
the mech to give out
giant hugs or something.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
If we're all saving
the galaxy from Dominator,
why don't we drive
this thingamajig together?
The four of us working
side by side
as one big, happy team.
HATER:
It's my robobabybuggybumper!
Flab drass it.
Locked.
Did you check
under the mat?
Wander, this is an ancient
class nine ultra-mech warrior
- They're not gonna hide--
- Found it.
Aw, looks like I got
the Robomeenieminiemotron
and you got nada.
Sorry!!
Just to be clear,
I'm being sarcastic.
I do not feel bad
about this at all.
( Dominator laughing )
Run, run, you...
easily terrified chicken
things and...
This is weak.
Lord Dominator,
sensors have located
the four individuals
designated "those idiots."
Subjects are commandeering
a D-commission class nine
ultra-mech warrior.
Wait, what?
Robomechabotatron?!
Shut up!!
Now that's a challenge.
Initiate metamorphosis.
All right, bring on
the giant robot fight.
"Congratulations on your
purchase of Robomechabotatron.
For optimal use and care,
please read this manual
completely before--"
Manual schmanual!
Go, Roborowyourboat, go!
Arm cannon. Nice.
Laser axe. Sweet!
What's this do?
Oh, yeah!
But wait. It feels like
something's missing.
PEEPERS: One step ahead
of you, sir.
HATER: Let's go kick
some Dominator butt!
( music distorts,
slows, stops )
Why aren't we kicking
Dominator butt?
Uh, well, there are
four control centers.
Two arms and two legs,
which means...
( loud knocking )
- SYLVIA: Open up!
- Four pilots.
- Forget that.
Just gotta use momentum
to shimmy us forward!
( screaming )
Go, Roboblahblahblah.
Go!!
SYLVIA: Sorry, Hater.
We got a leg up on you.
Hey, since we're
all here,
why not drive
this doohickey together?
Now is not the time
to teach these selfish jerks
about teamwork.
It's time to save
the galaxy!
SYLVIA:
Go, Robomechabotatron, go!
Huh? The flarfin' door
is jammed.
Oh, you gotta
be kidding me.
- ( loud knocking )
- HATER: Open up!
Sure seems like
we could use a hand.
And by hand, I mean
a metaphorical
helping hand.
But also,
a literal hand.
Yep, a helpful
hand-helping hand
sure would
come in handy
right now.
I get it. The hand.
And no, they can't.
I got this.
( Sylvia running upstairs,
panting and muttering )
( footsteps running )
( sighing )
( humming )
Where are they?
Finally. Let's do--
Oh, it's you.
Situation report.
Robomechabotatron has
not yet arrived.
Oh, really?
What tipped you off?
The complete lack of
awesome robot fighting?!
Get outta my mech face.
What is taking
those dorks so long?
( panting )
Maybe if you hold one foot...
Wander?
Mi roboto
es su roboto.
Whoa! Wander,
are you nuts?
You can't trust these two.
It's my Robomccrackalackadon!
You're not even
saying it right!
Stop!!
( sighs )
Come on, guys.
Robomechabotatron...
That's not how you say it.
...was created to save
the galaxy from threats
no one planet could face.
The galaxy is bigger
than any one of us,
and it needs
all of us to save it.
In the spirit of
this mighty mech,
should we not put aside
our petty differences
to work together
and save the galaxy?!
If we have to.
- Fine.
- Whatevs.
Seems like we're
becomin' friends!
ALL: Battle stations!
Hey, it's actually
working.
That's because
there is no "I"
in Robomechabotatron.
I think.
Door-opening sequence,
activate.
- Go, Robo...
- Mecha...
- Bota...
- Tron.
ALL: Go!
- ALL: Dominator?
- WANDER: Dominator!
I'm done waiting.
Mama wants a robo battle,
and Mama wants it now!
- Bring...
- It...
- On!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I didn't know we were gonna
be fighting with this dudette.
What else do you do
with a super-charged
attack suit?
This who-sama-whats-is
could be doing
so much more good
than harm.
Fixing roads,
transporting supplies,
giving out giant hugs.
I knew it.
Every time!
Um, any day now!
SYLVIA: One second.
Look, you're the one
who wanted us
to team up.
Are you gonna
join us in this...
Sure to be totally ugly...
Robot fight
or not?
( sighs )
If that's what
the group wants,
I won't try to stop you.
The galaxy
thanks you, buddy.
Activate battle mode!
Finally!
- Go, Robo...
- Mecha...
- Bota...
HATER: What the...
Why did...
I wanna use my laser axe!
( sobbing )
Wander, what's going on
down there?
Sorry. I won't stop ya,
but I gotta stand for
what I believe in.
Hey, we doin' this
or what?
Forget it.
We don't need him.
Feel the might of
Robomochasaskatchewan!
No, no, no, no, no!
( screaming )
Activate escape mode!
DOMINATOR: But my giant
robo fight.
( sighs )
You know what?
Fine. I can still roast
those dumb Cluckons
with this thing.
In your absence,
the Cluckons had
enough time to evacuate.
The chickens
have flown the coop.
( shrieking )
Forget it.
You guys are the worst,
and I hate you all.
Would ya look at that?
Even without a fight,
we still rescued Cluckon.
See. Working together
saved the day.
All in favor of never
working together again...
PEEPERS
AND SYLVIA: Aye!
Seems like we're
becoming friends.
( yells )
Flab drassin' Dominator...
won't fold right...
grop darn map destroyin'
the entire galaxy!! Gaaaaaaa!
( sighs )
She can't be stopped.
She's too powerful.
There's no hope.
Uh, hello?
She can't be stopped.
Too powerful,
no hope. Oh, no!
Put that thing
back in there.
I'm supposed to be
the worried one.
If you give up,
then we really are saying
nope to hope, and I just
can't cope with that,
so suck that back up,
mister.
Oh!
Gotta find some hope,
gotta find some hope.
Ha. There.
See. If that flower
can blossom amidst
the chaos,
then there
really is hope.
No, no, no, no!
Dominator might destroy
every planet from here
to eternity,
but she will not
destroy this.
We're gonna do
everything we can
to save
this flower.
Okay, before we begin,
we need to deduce what species
this flower belongs to.
That will allow us
to accurately pinpoint
its specific needs
while we conduct
a full seismological study,
and then we can go forward
and find out what exactly
the needs are
to reproduce the flower.
No need to
overthink this.
Plants need water.
Stop!
You can't just dump
water on it willy-nilly.
Too much and you risk
drowning the root system.
Too little and it won't
get the nutrients it needs
from the soil.
I'll be careful.
Okay, that's
too careful.
What, are you crazy?!
Just a little...
too much!
Little more.
Agh! More!
A little less.
Less more!
Hey, you know what?
- Plants also need sunlight.
- No sun.
No problem.
Let there be light!
Plant food.
Plants gotta
eat, right?
Hey, yeah.
I just happen to have
a pint-size potluck
perfect for our
puckered plant.
Oh, no.
Plant food coma!
You know we're trying to
save your stamen here, right?
Music. I hear plants
love the good vibrations
of a positive ditty.
Guess it's worth a shot.
♪ When darkness
comes a-creepin' ♪
♪ And you're feelin' down ♪
♪ Just accept your sadness ♪
♪ And... ♪
oh, who cares?
All right.
I got this.
♪ Little planty, please know
we are here to help you ♪
♪ Oh, little planty,
the whole of the galaxy ♪
♪ Rests on you,
but no pressure ♪
♪ Doo-da-doo-doo doo... ♪
That bad, huh?
No. I really appreciate
the effort, Syl.
I don't mean to be
so teary and dreary.
I just have to accept
that nothing in the world
can save little Planty.
Nothing on this world.
This place is great!
( both shrieking )
- Wander.
- Quicksand!
Nature's devious trap.
( screaming )
A greenhouse.
A controlled environment,
a friendly caretaker.
This is for the best.
Why is it so hard
to find a place
with a mild climate,
slightly acidic soil,
and absolutely
no grop darn giant bees?!
( sighs )
Mild climate,
slightly acidic soil,
free of giant bees.
Gentle breezes out of
the northeast.
That'd be
the icing on the cake,
but it's okay, Syl.
I'll be fine.
I just have to accept
that Planty's a doomed bloom.
An ephemeral perennial.
A sprout that
must drop out.
A plant who
simply can't.
This place
is perfect!
We did it!
We saved the flower!
Maybe there's hope
after all.
Aw, that's so sweet.
( evil giggle )
Planet K-129CX
is ready for domination.
Change of plans.
Set destination coordinates
for some soul-crushin' fun.
No, no, no.
Is it a giant bee?
Just the biggest bee
in the galaxy.
Dominator!
( sniffling
and whining )
Dominator, you can
destroy planets,
you can destroy
the galaxy...
But as long as
we're standing,
you'll never
destroy this flower.
Wow. I had no idea...
what hokey saps
you were.
Blah blah blah.
"As long as I'm standing..."
I can't believe you
actually said that out loud.
For that, I'm taking you
all down.
( laughing )
( laughter continues )
Give it.
Give it back!
You know, when you
utterly demolish
planet after planet,
it's easy to lose sight
of the little things
that you are also
demolishing in the process.
A bird singing,
this stupid flower.
Any hope of your survival
all crumbling within
my cold, fiery grasp.
Gotta love what you do,
am I right?
Oh, wow.
This is seriously
really sad for both of you.
Hold up.
All right, enough fun.
Say good-bye,
Wander and, the Zbornak.
I wanna say Sybil.
Ah, who cares?
You're both doomed.
- Ah-choo!
- Gesundheit.
- Ah-choo.
- Gesundheit  again.
( sneezing continues )
Get them... ah-choo!
Did not compute.
This--choo isn't--choo
over--choo!
I'll get--ah-choo!
( sneezing continues )
( Sylvia laughing )
Dominator isn't unstoppable.
She can be defeated.
Sure, hay fever really isn't
an effective long-term plan
for thwarting
a maniacal evil villain,
but it's something.
See, Wander,
there's always hope.
( crying )
No. It's too late.
SYLVIA: Noooo!
I can... bring it... back.
Sylvia.
I think I feel a pulse.
- Sylvia.
- I won't fail you, Wander.
No!
Sylvia, you tried
your hardest
to save this flower.
And it decided
to return the favor
by saving us.
It's not bad
to be sad.
But I can't have you sad
or everything's hopeless.
Just because I'm sad
doesn't mean
I've given up hope.
- You haven't?
- Nope.
Wander, I promise,
we'll stop Dominator
and we'll figure out a way
to restore this galaxy.
Ya think?
I sure hope so.
- ( sneezing continuously )
- Bots!
Ah-choo! After...
Ah-choo... will you get...
Ah-choo!
( groaning )
( blows nose loudly )