Applejack: boy howdy!
I got my work cut out for me!
That there is the biggest
bumper crop of apples
I ever laid eyes on.
Eeyup!
Too big for you to handle
on your own.
Come on, big brother.
You need to rest up
and get yourself better.
I haven't met an apple orchard
yet that I can't handle.
Oops. Sorry.
I'll take a bite
out of this job by day's end.
Biting off
more than you can chew
Is just what
I'm afraid of.
Are you sayin'
my mouth is makin' promises
My legs can't keep?
Eeyup.
Why, of all the --
This is your sister Applejack,
remember?!
The loyalest of friends
And the most dependable
of ponies!
But still
only one pony.
And one pony
plus hundreds of apple trees
Just doesn't
add up to --
Don't you use
your fancy mathematics
To muddy the issue.
I said I could
handle this harvest,
And I'm gonna
prove it to you!
I'm gonna get
every last apple
Out of those trees
this applebuck season
All by myself!
[ Gulps ]
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
And one muffins plus hundreds of Derpy doesn't add up !
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Well, I better get kickin'.
These apples aren't gonna shake
themselves out of the trees.
[ Rumbling ]
Hey!
Oh, no!
Stampede!
[ Cows mooing ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Pinkie Pie giggles ]
[ Vibrating ] hey!
This makes my voice
sound silly!
Pinkie Pie,
are you crazy?!
Run!
Everypony calm down.
There is no need
to panic.
But, mayor,
whatever shall we do?!
Look there!
Yeehaw!
[ All exclaiming indistinctly ]
why, Applejack's
gonna save us!
Other side, Winona.
[ Barking ]
Put 'em up, girl!
Oh!
This is the best rodeo show
I've ever seen!
[ Munching ]
Come on,
little doggies! Turn!
[ Whistles ]
Winona, put 'em up.
[ Barking ]
Ha ha!
Gotcha!
[ Grunts ]
[ Barking ]
Thatagirl!
[ Grunts ]
Yeehaw!
[ All cheering ]
Whoa!
Hoo-Whee!
Now, what was that
all about?
[ Moos ]
[ Clears throat ]
Oh, my.
Begging your pardon, Applejack,
But mooriella here
saw one of those nasty snakes.
[ All gasping ]
And it just gave us all
the willies, don't you know?
I completely understand.
Just, next time, try
and steer clear of Ponyville.
We certainly will,
Applejack.
So long, Winona!
[ Barks ]
[ All cheering ]
Yeehaw!
[ Barks ]
Ride 'em, cowpony!
Applejack was just --
Just --
Appletastic!
[ Thud! ]
Exactly!
We must do something
to thank Applejack
For single-Hoofedly
saving the town.
I know!
A party!
We all ready?
Just one last thing.
[ Tinkling ]
Now we're ready.
Is Applejack all set?
Actually,
I haven't seen her all week.
Not since the stampede.
But she'll be here
for sure.
Applejack is never late.
[ Tinkling ]
Welcome, everypony.
Today, we are here
to honor a pony
We can always count on to help
in matters great and small...
a pony
whose contributions to --
Did you see Applejack's
slick moves out there?
What an athlete!
This week, she's gonna help me
with my new flying trick,
And I know
it's gonna be so awesome!
Exactly. And --
This week, I get to run
sugarcube corner
For the first time!
What does that have to do
with Applejack?
[ Blink! Blink! ]
Oh, Applejack,
one of the best bakers ever,
Is gonna help me.
Applejack makes
everything great,
So free samples
for everypony!
[ All cheering ]
Okay, that's great.
Now, if I could just make
a point without being inter--
Twilight?
--Rupted.
Twilight, I'm so sorry,
but I just wanted to mention
That Applejack is also
helping me this week
With the official
bunny census,
Where we count up
all the new baby bunnies
That were born
this season.
She's gonna help
gather them
Using her wonderful
herding skills.
Anyone else?
Anyone?
No?
[ Tinkling ]
Well, then,
as I was trying to say --
Ugh!
Never mind.
[ Clears throat ]
And so, with no further ado,
it is my privilege
To give the prize pony
of Ponyville award
To our beloved guest of honor,
A pony of the utmost
trustworthiness,
Reliability,
and integrity,
Ponyville's most capable
and dependable friend,
Applejack!
[ Ponies cheering ]
[ Ponies gasp ]
Way to go, Applejack!
That was awesome!
I mean --
[ Chuckles ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Blink! ]
Awkward.
I'm here!
[ Yawns ]
[ Ponies grunting ]
Sorry I'm late.
Well, I was just --
Whoa!
Did I get your tail?
[ Pony grunts ]
Miss mayor...
thank you kindly for
this here, uh, award thingy.
[ Yawns ]
It's so bright and shiny,
And [chuckles]
I sure do look funny.
Whoo, whoo!
Whoo!
[ Giggles ]
whoo!
Whoo!
Okay.
Well, thank you, Applejack,
For saving us
from that scary stampede
And always being there
for everypony.
[ Yawns ] yeah.
I like helpin'
the pony folks and --
[Yawning] and stuff.
[ Snoring lightly ]
Oh! Uh, yeah!
Uh, thanks!
[ Metal scraping ]
Was it just me, or did
Applejack seem a little --
Tired?
Dizzy.
Messy?
Well, did you
see her mane?
She seemed fine to me.
Whoo! Whoo!
Hmm.
[ Applejack grunts ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
Whew!
Bl-Bl-Bl!
Whoa!
What on earth
is that pony doing?
Whoops.
Hey, Applejack!
[ Snoring lightly ]
Applejack!
[ Snoring continues ]
[ Tinkling ]
Applejack!
Oh! Bl-Bl-Bl!
Howdy, Twilight.
What is all this?
It's applebuck season.
[ Tinkling ]
Whoa.
Apple-What season?
[ Grunts ]
It's what the apple family
calls harvestin' time.
We gather all the apples
from the trees
So we can sell them.
But why are you doing it
all alone?
'Cause Big Macintosh
hurt himself.
Well, what about
all those relatives I met
When I first came
to Ponyville?
Can't they help?
They were just here
for the apple family reunion.
They actually live
all over Equestria
And are busy
harvestin' their own orchards.
So, uh, I'm on my own.
Which means I should
really get back to work.
[ Clears throat ]
Hint, hint.
Get back to work.
Fine.
Uh, could you step aside,
Twilight?
I...just did.
[ Echoing ] Applejack,
you don't look so good.
Uh...uh...
don't none
of you three worry none.
I'm just fine and dandy.
Whoa!
Do you want some help?
Help? [ Scoffs ]
No way, no how!
But there's no way
you can do it all on your own.
Is that a challenge?
Um, no.
Well, I'm gonna prove to you
that I can do it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got apples to bucket.
There you are!
[ Yawns ]
I'm a might sorry,
Rainbow.
I was busy applebuckin',
And I guess i-I closed my eyes
for a second,
And when I woke up,
I was late.
Now, what's this new trick
of yours?
See this contraption?
Uh, yeah.
Well, I'm gonna stand
on one end.
Then you're gonna jump down
from that platform,
Launching me into the air
Faster than I can take off
on my own.
Once I'm in the air,
I'm gonna do some amazing flips
and spins
That are sure
to impress the Wonderbolts.
I-Isn't that
a might dangerous?
[ Scoffs ]
not for a pony who can fly.
Well, all righty, then.
Applejack: oh, my.
Ready?
1, 2, 3!
[ Grunts ]
Uh, maybe I wasn't clear.
You're supposed to land
on the other end.
[ Snap! ]
Got it.
[ Grunts ]
Applejack,
what the hay is going on?!
I mean,
I thought I was working
With Ponyville's
best athlete!
You are!
I'm okay!
Really.
I-I have an idea.
Watch this.
[ Grunting ]
Ta-Da!
Oh. Maybe not.
Okay, one more try.
I'm sure to get it
this time.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Here I go.
Wait!
Appleja-a-a-a-ck!
You're welcome!
Aah! Unh!
[ Thud! ]
Can I help you?
I think somepony else
needs your help.
Applejack?
Yep.
[ Thud! ]
Ow!
[ Ears ringing ]
Applejack,
can we talk?
[ Ringing ]
[ Muffled ]
Applejack, can we talk?
Can bees squawk?!
I don't think so!
No. Can we talk?
20 stocks?!
Bean or celery?
No! I need
to talk to you!
You need to walk
to the zoo?!
Well,
who's stoppin' you?!
I need to talk to you!
Oh! Well,
why didn't you say so?!
What you want
to talk about?!
Rainbow Dash dropped in
to see me today.
That's quite neighborly
of her!
Yes, except that
she crashed onto my balcony
After you launched her
into the air.
Oh, yeah.
I wasn't feelin'
quite myself this mornin'.
Because you're working too hard,
and you need help!
What? Kelp?
I don't need kelp.
I don't even like seaweed.
Help!
You need HELP!!
Nothin' doin',
Twilight.
I'm gonna prove to you,
to everypony,
That I can do this
on my own.
[ Thud! ]
Ow!
[ Grunts ]
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I got to go
help Pinkie Pie.
[ Groans ]
Now, Pinkie Pie, are you sure
you're up for baking the muffins
And running the store
this afternoon?
Yes, sirree bob,
mrs. Cake!
Plus, I have Ponyville's
prize pony to help me out.
Why, she's the best baker ever!
Right, Applejack?
[ Echoing ] Applejack.
[ Rattle! ]
No? You're not
the best baker ever?
What? Oh, no!
I mean,
don't you fret.
I can bake anything
from fritters to Pies
In the blink of an eye.
[ Chuckles ]
all right.
Well, see you later,
girls.
[ Rattle! ]
Stop with the shakin'!
It's time to get bakin'!
All righty.
I'll get the sugar
and the eggs.
Can you get me
some chocolate chips?
Uh...what was that?
[ Distorted ]
chocolate chips.
Chips. Got it.
Tater chips.
A little salty and dry.
Okeydokey.
What next?
[ Distorted ]
baking soda.
Soda? Perfect!
That'll get the tater chips
nice and wet.
Now what?!
[ Normal voice ]
a cup of flour.
A cup of sour?
Well, lemons are sure sour.
One cup of sour comin' up.
Anything else, Pinkie?
One last thing --
Wheat germ.
Wheat worms?
Oh, that must be fancy talk
for earthworms.
Now, that's gonna
be delicious!
If you say so.
Free-Muffin-Sample
spectacular!
Derpy: Muffins
Yeah!
Muffin spectacles!
Get 'em
while they're hot!
We came
as soon as we heard.
Oh, thank you, Twilight.
We need all the help
we can get.
[ All groaning ]
Oh, no.
What happened?
It was a mishap
with some of the baked goods.
No!
Not baked goods.
Baked bads.
Ugh!
Applejack.
Oh! Mmm!
Want one?
[ Grunts ]
[ Snores ]
What? Huh?
[ Grunts ]
Ohh! Unh!
[ Snoring lightly ]
Applejack,
we need to talk.
What?! Huh?!
Oh, it's you, Twilight.
[ Yawning ] I know
what you're gonna say.
But the answer
is still no.
Not to upset your apple cart,
but you need help.
[ Sighs ]
hardy-Har.
[ Grunts ]
and, no, I don't.
Here. Let me help.
Help? No, thanks.
[ Grunting ]
A little more.
A little...
[ grunts ]
There.
I'll prove that this apple
can handle these apples.
Come on [grunts] apples.
[ Grunts ]
fall off! [ Grunts ]
A.J., I think
you're beating a dead...
tree.
I knew that.
Actually, Applejack,
I had something else
to talk to you about.
I just came back from
Ponyville urgent care and --
You know,
I'm a little busy
To get lectured
right now, Twilight.
If you'd just
let me help --
Ugh!
No! No! No!
How many times
do I got to say it?
I don't need no help
from nopony!
Ugh! That pony
is stubborn as a mule!
[ Mule brays ]
no offense.
None taken.
Fluttershy: oh, Applejack,
thank you so much
For offering
your herding skills
For the annual
rabbit roundup.
[ Sighs ]
why are we doing this?
Well, lots of new baby bunnies
have been born,
So it's my job to get a count
of all the new families.
Fine.
Can we just
get on with it?
Certainly, but remember,
These are bunnies
we're dealing with, not cows.
They're a timid bunch
and need to be treated gently.
I do not need any direction
on corrallin' critters.
Right, Winona?!
[ Barks ]
[ Bunnies sniffing ]
Okay, little bunnies.
I need you to all gather
here in the middle.
That's right!
Let's go, bunnies!
In the center!
Hop to it!
[ Zip! ]
Swell.
Just swell.
Put 'em up, Winona!
[ Barking ]
Applejack! Winona! Stop!
You're scaring them!
We know
what we're doin'!
Get along, little bunnies!
[ Barking ]
[ Growling ]
Oh, no.
[ Bunnies scream ]
[ Rumbling ]
Stampede!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Moans ]
[ Humming ]
[ Gasps ]
The horror!
It was awful!
A disaster!
A horrible,
horrible disaster!
[ Birds chirping ]
I don't get it.
Our gardens destroyed.
Every last flower
devoured.
By -- By...them!
Fluttershy: oh, my!
Oh, please stop, little bunnies.
Oh, no!
Please, let's go home.
No! Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
All right.
Enough is enough.
Must keep buckin'.
Just a few more.
Must finish harvestin'.
All right, Applejack,
Your apple bucking hasn't
just caused you problems.
It's overpropelled
pegasus,
Practically poisoned
plenty of ponies,
And terrorized bushels of
brand-New bouncing baby bunnies.
I don't care
what you say.
You need help.
[ Grunts ]
Ha! No, I don't.
Look, I did it.
I harvested
the entire sweet apple acres
Without your help.
How do you like
them apples?
Oh, how do you like
[ Whimpering ]
[ Mumbling indistinctly ]
Applejack?
Huh?
Oh, good.
You're okay.
Now, Applejack,
I completely respect
The apple-Family ways.
You're always there
to help anypony in need.
So maybe you can put a little
of your stubborn pride aside
And allow your friends
to help you.
Okay, Twilight.
I am not taking no
for an answer. What?
Yes, Twilight.
Yes, please.
I could really
use your help.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
Twilight Sparkle:
"dear princess Celestia,
"My friend Applejack is the best
friend a pony could ever have,
"And she's always there
to help anypony.
"The only trouble is,
when she needs help,
"She finds it hard to accept it.
"So while friendship is about
giving of ourselves to friends,
"It's also about accepting
what our friends have to offer.
Your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle."
How about y'all
take a little break?
I got some fine apple juice
waitin' for you.
[ Sighs ]
Girls, I can't thank you enough
for this help.
I was actin'
a bit stubborn.
A bit?
Okay, a might stubborn.
And I'm awful sorry.
Now, I know the town gave me
the prize pony award,
But the real award is
having you five as my friends.
[ Slurping ]
Whew! That applebucking
sure made me hungry.
And I've got
the perfect treat!
Ew! Spike,
I threw those away!
Where did you get them?
From the trash!
Ew!
Ew!Ew!
Just a little nibble?
Come on!
Ew! Gross!
Gross, Spike!