Come on, Twilight.
You can do it.
Okay. Here goes.
Ha ha! You did it!
Growing magic --
That's number 25.
25 different types of tricks
and counting.
And I think this is
the best trick so far.
Hello, Rarity.
What's that?
Oh, it's nothing --
Just my awesome mustache.
Sorry, romeo.
As attractive and enticing
as you look,
It's just for practice,
and it's got to go.
Wait!
Aw. Rats.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
The Great and Powerful Muffin!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
25, Twilight --
25 different kinds of tricks
and counting.
I thought unicorns were only
supposed to have a little magic
That matches
their special talents.
True --
For ponies whose talents
Are for things like cooking
or singing or math,
But what if a unicorn's
special talent is magic?
Like you, Twilight,
and you know a ton of magic.
Oh, Spike, stop.
I'm sure there are lots of
ponies right here in Ponyville
That know
just as much magic as me.
Are you kidding?
I don't think there's another
unicorn in all of Equestria
With your kind of ability,
Twilight.
Gangway!
Coming through!
Ugh!
Snips, snails,
wh-What's going on?
Well,
haven't you heard?
There is a new unicorn
in town!
Yeah!
They say that she's got
more magical powers
Than any other unicorn
ever!
Really?
Aw, no way.
That honor goes
to Twilight here.
Where is this unicorn?
Oh, she's
in the town square.
Come on!
Yeah! Come on!
Ooh!
Come one! Come all!
Come and witness
the amazing magic
Of the Great and Powerful
Trixie!
Watch in awe
as the Great and Powerful Trixie
Performs the most spectacular
feats of magic
Ever witnessed by pony eyes!
My, my, my.
What boasting.
Come on.
No pony's as magical as twi--
Twi-- Twi-- Ohh!
H-Hey, Rarity, I, uh --
Mustache!
There's nothing wrong
with being talented, is there?
Nothing at all,
Excepting when someone
goes around showing it off
Like a school filly
with fancy new ribbons.
Just because one has the ability
to perform lots of magic
Does not make one better
than the rest of us.
Especially when
you got me around
Being better
than the rest of us.
Uh, I mean -- Yeah!
Uh, magic schmagic!
Boo!
Well, well, well.
It seems we have some naysayers
in the audience.
Who is so ignorant as to
challenge the magical ability
Of the Great and Powerful
Trixie?
Do they not know
that they're in the presence
Of the most magical unicorn
in all of Equestria?!
Pbht. Just who
does she think she is?
Yeah! Since we all know
that Twilight here is --
Spike, shh!
What? What's wrong?
You see the way
they reacted to Trixie?
I don't want anyone thinking
I'm a show-Off.
So,
Great and Powerful Trixie,
What makes you think
you're so awesome, anyway?
Why, only
the Great and Powerful Trixie
Has magic strong enough
To vanquish
the dreaded ursa major!
What?!
No way!
When all hope was lost,
The ponies of puffington
had no one to turn to,
But the Great and Powerful
Trixie stepped in
And, with her awesome magic,
vanquished the ursa major
And sent it back to its cave
Deep within
the Everfree forest!
Aw, sweet!
Sa-Weet!
That settles it.
Trixie truly is
the most talented, most magical,
Most awesome unicorn
in Ponyville.
No!
In all of Equestria!
How do you know?
You didn't see it.
And besides, twi--
It's true, my enthusiastic
little admirers --
Trixie is most certainly
the best in Ponyville.
Don't believe
the Great and Powerful Trixie?
Well, then, I hereby challenge
you, ponyvillians --
Anything you can do,
I can do better.
Any takers?
Anyone? Hmm?
Or is Trixie destined to be
The greatest equine
who has ever lived?!
please!
She's unbearable!
You got to show her
you just got to!
There's no way I'm gonna use
my magic now, Spike,
Especially since --
Hmm.
How about...you?
Well, how about it, hmm?
Is there anything
you can do
That the Great
and Powerful Trixie can't?
I-I...
well, little hayseed?
That's it.
I can't stand
for no more of this.
You show her, A.J.!
Can your magical powers
do this?
Ooh!
Ooh!Ooh!
Whoo-Hoo!
Yeah!
That was great!
Top that, missy!
Oh, ye of little talent,
Watch and be amazed
at the magic of Trixie.
Whoa!
Ugh!
Yay!
Once again,
The Great and Powerful Trixie
prevails.
There's no need
to go strutting around
And showing off
like that.
Oh?
That's my job.
They don't call me "Rainbow"
and "Dash" for nothing.
When Trixie is through,
The only thing
they'll call you is "loser."
Whoa! Whoa!
I think i'm...gonna be sick.
Seems like any pony
with a Dash of good sense
Would think twice before
tussling with the great Trixie.
Yah!
What we need is another unicorn
to challenge her,
Someone with some magic
of her own.
Yeah! A unicorn
to show this unicorn who's boss.
A real
unicorn-To-Unicorn tussle.
Uh...
enough.
Enough, all of you.
I take your hint,
But Rarity is above
such nonsense.
Rainbow Dash and Applejack
may behave like ruffians,
But Rarity conducts herself
with beauty and grace.
Ohh!
What's the matter?
Afraid you'll get a hair
out of place
In that rat's nest
you call a mane?
Oh...it...is...on.
You may think you're tough,
With all of your
so-Called powers,
But there is more to magic
than your brutish ways.
A unicorn needs to be
more than just muscle.
A unicorn needs to have style.
A unicorn's not a unicorn
without grace and beauty.
Rarity won't let Trixie
get the best of her.
She's strong.
She's beautiful.
She's --
Ohh!
Quick! I need a mirror!
Get me a mirror!
What did she do to my hair?!
I know she did something
terrible to my hair!
Nothing.
It's fine.
It's gorgeous.
It's green.
What?
No. Green hair?!
Not green hair!
Such an awful, awful color!
Aah!
Well! I never!
Well, Twilight,
guess it's up to you.
Come on.
Show her what you're made of.
What do you mean?
I'm nothing special.
Yes, you are.
You're better than her.
I'm not better than anyone.
Ha! You think you're better
Than the Great and Powerful
Trixie?
You think you have
more magical talent?
Well, come on.
Show Trixie what you've got.
Show us all.
Who, me?
I'm just your run-Of-The-Mill
citizen of Ponyville --
No powerful magic here.
I, uh -- I think
I hear my laundry calling.
Sorry. Got to go.
Twilight?
Once again,
the Great and Powerful Trixie
Has proven herself to be
The most amazing unicorn
in all of Equestria.
Unh.
Was there ever any doubt?
Here's the oat smoothie
you asked for --
With extra hay,
just how you like it.
Mmm. Hay.
Yes?
Oh, tell us another story,
Great and Powerful Trixie.
Yeah, tell us about how
you vanquished the ursa major.
Trixie is far too exhausted
From performing feats
beyond imagination.
Be gone with you
until morning.
Oh, of course,
Great and Powerful Trixie.
Anything you say.
We are at
your beck and call.
What are two doing?
Just bringing
the G&PT a --
The what?
The Great
and Powerful Trixie.
Sheesh!
Just bringing her
a smoothie.
How can you fall
for her lameness?
She's just a show-Off,
Unlike Twilight, who --
The Great and Powerful Trixie
vanquished an ursa major.
Can your Twilight
claim that?
Oh, really?
Were you guys
actually there?
Well, uh, uh...
no, but --
But nothing.
The proof
is in the pudding.
I like pudding.
Look, unless an ursa major
comes waltzing up the street
For Trixie to vanquish,
I am not gonna believe
a word she says,
And neither should you.
Hmm.
An ursa walking
up the street, eh?
Snails, you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Why is it
they call it a flea market
When they don't
really sell fleas?
Yeah! Uh...
oh, come on.
Twilight, would you put down
that book
And just listen to me?
Didn't you see how they hated
Trixie's bragging, Spike?
If I go out there
and show off my magic,
I run the risk
of losing them as friends.
It's not the same thing,
Twilight.
You'd be using your magic
to stand up for your friends.
No, Spike,
it's exactly the same.
Come on, Twilight.
Any one of these tricks,
even the teeniest,
Would be enough
to show up Trixie.
I don't want to be seen
as a bragger like Trixie.
Unh!
But you're the best!
Ugh! Please, Spike.
I said no.
If that's the way
you want to be, then fine.
Whoa!
How we gonna find
an ursa major
When I can't even see
my own hoof in front of my face?
Hold on.
ohh!
Oh. Heh.
That's better.
Aah!
Aah! Ha ha ha!
Hey, guys,
where you going?
Can't talk now!
Got a major problem!
Yep!
Ursa major, to be exact!
Trixie!
Twilight!
Come on out!
Trixie!
You got to help!
Trixie thought she said
The Great and Powerful Trixie
did not want to be disturbed.
Uh, w-We --
We have a tiny problem.
Actually,
it's a big one.
What is so important that
you cannot wait until morning
To disturb Trixie?
Aaaaaaah!
Aah!
Twilight,
you've got to come quick!
I've already told you,
Spike --
I don't want to
show up Trixie.
No, you don't understand.
It's --
Uh, is that
what I think it is?
Majorly.
Great and Powerful Trixie,
You've got to vanquish
the ursa.
Yeah! Vanquish
so we can watch.
It took a lot of trouble
to get that thing here.
Wait.
You brought this here?
are you out
of your little pony minds?!
But you're the great
and powerful Trixie.
Yeah. Remember?
You defeated an ursa major.
Uh, okay.
Stand back.
Ahh. Piece of cake.
Aw, come on, Trixie.
Stop goofing around
and vanquish it, eh?
Well, that was a dud.
Yeah, pbht!
Come on!
Where's all the cool explosions
and smoke and stuff
Like earlier, you know?
Uh-Oh.
Aah!
What's going on?
We brought an ursa
to town.
You what?!
Don't worry.
The Great and Powerful Trixie
will vanquish it.
I can't.
What?!
I never have.
No one can vanquish
an ursa major.
I just made the whole story up
to make me look better.
Made it up?!
Mnh!
Nice use of number 16.
Unnnnh!
Golly. Don't ya know?
That's new.
Unnnnnh!
Uhh.
That was amazing!
Heavens to betsy!
We knew you had ability,
but not that much.
I'm sorry.
Please, please don't hate me.
Hate you?!
Why, whatever do you mean,
darling?
Well, I know how much
you all hated
Trixie's showing off
with her magic tricks,
And I just thought --
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Magic's got nothing
to do with it.
Trixie's
just a loudmouth.
Most unpleasant.
All hat
and no cattle.
So...you don't mind
my magic tricks?
Your magic is a part
of who you are, sugar cube,
And we like who you are.
We're proud to have such
a powerful, talented unicorn
As our friend.
And after whupping
that ursa's hindquarters,
We're even prouder.
You are?
Uh-Huh.
Mm-Hmm.
Wow, Twilight!
How'd you know what to do
with that ursa major?
That's what I was doing
when you came looking for me.
I was so intrigued
by Trixie's bragging
That I was compelled to do
a little reading up on them.
So, it is possible
to vanquish an ursa major
All by yourself?
That wasn't an ursa major.
It was a baby,
an ursa minor.
That was just a baby?
And it wasn't rampaging.
It was just cranky
because someone woke it up.
Ohh.
Well, if that was
an ursa minor,
Then what's
an ursa major like?
You don't want to know.
Ha! You may have vanquished
an ursa minor,
But you will never have the
amazing, showstopping ability
Of the Great and Powerful
Trixie!
Why, that little...
Just let her go.
Maybe someday
she'll learn her lesson.
Now, about you two.
Uh...
We're sorry
that we woke up the ursa minor.
We just wanted to see
some awesome magic.
Yeah!
And the way you vanquished
that ursa minor was awesome!
We deserve
whatever punishment you give us.
For starters,
you can clean up this mess.
And...
what do you think, Spike?
Should I give them
number 25?
Oh, 25? Yes.
And I think
I deserve it, too.
Huh?!
I think you're right.
Sweet!
Dear princess Celestia,
I have learned a very valuable
lesson about friendship.
I was so afraid of
being thought of as a show-Off
That I was hiding a part
of who I am.
Hy friends helped me realize
That it's okay to be proud
of your talents
And there are times when it's
appropriate to show them off,
Especially when you're
standing up for your friends.
So, you finally admit
That you're the most talented
unicorn in all of Ponyville?
Well...
yeah.
But it's nothing
to brag about.
So, uh, how did it go
with Rarity?
Eh, she didn't go
for the mustache.
You know, Spike,
That mustache has nothing to do
with who you really are.
Maybe you should just try
being yourself.
Or...maybe the mustache
wasn't enough.
Maybe if I had a mustache
and a beard.
Oh, not this again.
Okay, imagine me with
a nice long fu manchu-Type beard
Or maybe a goatee.
Oh, no --
A soul patch...