Narrator: once upon a time, in
the magical land of Equestria,
There were two regal sisters
who ruled together
And created harmony
for all the land.
To do this, the eldest
used her unicorn powers
To raise the sun at dawn.
The younger brought out the moon
to begin the night.
Thus, the two sisters
maintained balance
For their kingdom
and their subjects --
All the different types
of ponies.
But as time went on, the younger
sister became resentful.
The ponies relished and played
In the day
her elder sister brought forth
But shunned and slept
through her beautiful night.
One fateful day,
the younger unicorn
Refused to lower the moon
to make way for the dawn.
The elder sister
tried to reason with her,
But the bitterness
in the young one's heart
Had transformed her into
a wicked mare of darkness --
Nightmare Moon.
[ Thunder crashes ]
She vowed that she would shroud
the land in eternal night.
Reluctantly, the elder sister
Harnessed the most powerful
magic known to ponydom --
The Elements of Harmony.
Using the magic
of the Elements of Harmony,
She defeated her younger sister
And banished her permanently
on the moon.
The elder sister took on
responsibility...
Both: for both sun and moon...
Twilight Sparkle: and harmony
has been maintained in Equestria
For generations since.
Hmm, Elements of Harmony.
I know
I've heard of those before.
But where?
* My Little Pony
* Ah-Ah-Ah-Ah
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
This magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
Pony:
there you are, Twilight.
Moondancer is having
a little get-Together
In the west castle
courtyard.
You want to come?
Oh, sorry, girls.
I got a lot of studying
to catch up on.
[ Zip! ]
[ Sighs ]
Does that pony
do anything except study?
I think she's more interested
in books than friends.
I know I've heard
of the Elements of Harmony.
Ugh!
Spike! Spike!
Spike?
[ Groans ]
there you are.
Quick, find me that old copy
of "Predictions and Prophecies."
What's that for?
Well...
it was a gift
for Moondancer, but...
[ squeak! ]
Oh, Spike, you know
we don't have time
For that sort of thing.
But we're on a break.
[ Tinkling ]
No. No.
No.
No, no, no.
Ugh!
Spike!
It's over here.
[ Thud! ]
Ah!
Elements, elements.
"E," "e," "e."
Aha!
"Elements of Harmony.
See mare in the moon"?
Mare in the moon?
But that's just
an old ponies' tale.
Mare, mare.
Aha!
"The mare in the moon --
Myth from olden pony times,
"A powerful pony
who wanted to rule Equestria
"Defeated by the elements
of harmony
And imprisoned in the moon."
"Legend has it that on the
longest day of the 1,000th year,
"The stars will aid
in her escape,
And she will bring about
nighttime eternal."
[ Gasps ] Spike!
Do you know what this means?
No. Whoa!
Ow!
Take a note, please,
to the princess.
Okeydokey.
My dearest teacher,
My continuing studies
of pony magic
Have led me to discover
That we are on the precipice
of disaster.
Hold on.
"Preci-- Preci--"
Threshold.
"Thre--"
Uh, brink?
Ugh!
That something really bad
is about to happen.
For, you see, the mythical mare
in the moon
Is, in fact,
Nightmare Moon,
And she's about to return
to Equestria
And bring
with her eternal night.
Something must be done to make
sure this terrible prophecy
Does not come true.
I await
your quick response.
Your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle.
"Twilight...Sparkle."
Got it!
Great. Send it.
Now?
Of course.
Uh, I don't know, Twilight.
Princess Celestia's
a little busy
Getting ready
for the Summer Sun Celebration.
And it's like
the day after tomorrow.
That's just it, Spike.
The day after tomorrow
is the 1,000th year
Of the Summer Sun Celebration.
It's imperative that
the princess is told right away.
"Impera-- Impera--"
Important!
Aah-Aah!
[ Thud! ]
Okay, okay!
[ Inhales deeply ]
There.
It's on its way.
But I wouldn't hold
your breath.
Oh, I'm not worried,
Spike.
The princess trusts me
completely.
In all the years
she's been my mentor,
She's never once
doubted me.
[ Gulps ]
[ Burp! ]
See?
I knew she would want to take
immediate action.
[ Clears throat ]
"My dearest, most faithful
student, Twilight,
"You know that I value
your diligence
And that I trust you
completely."
Mm-Hmm.
"But you simply must stop
reading those dusty old books."
[ Gasps ]
"My dear Twilight,
"There is more to a young pony's
life than studying.
"So I'm sending you to supervise
the preparations
"For
the Summer Sun Celebration
"In this year's location,
Ponyville.
"And I have
an even more essential task
"For you to complete...
make some friends."
[ Groans ]
Look on the bright side,
Twilight.
The princess arranged for you
to stay in a library.
Doesn't that make you
happy?
Yes! Yes, it does.
You know why?
Because I'm right.
I'll check on the preparations
as fast as I can,
Then get to the library
To find some proof
of Nightmare Moon's return.
Then when will you make friends,
like the princess said?
She said to check on
preparations.
I am her student,
and I'll do my royal duty,
But the fate of Equestria
Does not rest
on me making friends.
[ Both neigh ]
Thank you, sirs.
[ Both whinny ]
Maybe the ponies
in Ponyville
Have interesting things
to talk about.
Come on, Twilight.
Just try.
Uh...
hello?
[ Gasps ]
[ Zip! ]
Well, that was interesting,
all right.
[ Sighs ]
"Summer Sun Celebration
official overseer's checklist.
"Number 1 --
Banquet preparations,
Sweet Apple Acres."
Applejack: Yee-Haw!
[ Whoosh! ]
[ Sighs ]
let's get this over with.
Good afternoon.
My name
is Twilight Sparkle.
[ Crunch! ]
[ Southern accent ] well,
howdy-Do, ms. Twilight?
A pleasure making
your acquaintance.
I'm Applejack.
We here
at Sweet Apple Acres
Sure do like
making new friends.
[ Vibrating ] friends?
Actually, I, uh...
so, what can I do you for?
[ Laughs ]
[ Clears throat ]
Well, I am, in fact, here
to supervise preparations
For the Summer Sun Celebration.
And you're in charge
of the food?
We sure as sugar are.
Would you care
to sample some?
As long as it doesn't take
too long.
[ Ringing ]
Soup's on, everypony!
[ Rattle! ]
Now, why don't I introduce y'all
to the apple family?
Thanks, but I really need
to hurry.
This here's
Apple Fritter.
Apple Bumpkin.
Red Gala.
Red Delicious.
Golden Delicious.
Caramel Apple.
Apple Strudel.
Apple Tart.
Baked Apples.
Apple Brioche.
Apple Cinnamon Crisp.
[ Inhales deeply ]
Big Macintosh.
Apple Bloom.
And...Granny Smith.
Up and at 'em,
Granny Smith.
[ Snoring ]
we got guests.
[ Snorts ] what?
Soup's on?
I'm, uh, I'm coming,
I'm coming.
Why, I'd say they're already
part of the family.
[ Spits ] bleh!
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, well, I can see
the food situation is handled,
So we'll be on our way.
Pony: aren't you gonna stay
for brunch?
[ Ting! Ting! ]
Sorry.
But we have an awful lot to do.
[ Ponies "aww" ]
Fine.
[ All cheering, laughter ]
Food's all taken care of.
Next is weather.
[ Groans ]
I ate too much pie.
Hmm.
There's supposed to be a pegasus
pony named Rainbow Dash
Clearing the clouds.
Well, she's not doing
a very good job, is she?
[ Zoom! ]
[ Groans ]
[ Chuckles ]
Uh, excuse me?
Mm.
[ Chuckles ]
let me help you.
[ Zip! ]
[ Boing! Boing! Boing! ]
[ Laughs ]
Oops.
I guess I overdid it.
Um, uh, how about this?
My very own patented
Rainblow Dry.
No, no.
Don't thank me.
You're quite welcome.
[ Ting! ]
[ Stifled laugh ]
[ Laughs hysterically ]
[ Laughs ]
Let me guess --
You're Rainbow Dash.
The one and only.
[ Zip! ]
Why? You heard of me?
I heard you're supposed to be
keeping the sky clear.
[ Sighs ]
I'm Twilight Sparkle,
And the princess sent me
to check on the weather.
Yeah, yeah.
That'll be a snap.
I'll do it in a jiffy,
Just as soon
as I'm done practicing.
Practicing? For what?
The Wonderbolts.
They're gonna perform
at the celebration tomorrow,
And I'm gonna show them
my stuff.
The Wonderbolts?
Yep.
The most talented fliers
in all of Equestria?
That's them.
[ Scoffs ] please.
They'd never accept
a pegasus
Who can't even keep the sky
clear for one measly day.
Hey, I could clear this sky
in 10 seconds flat.
Prove it.
Hyah!
Loop the loop around and whap!
What'd I say?
10 seconds flat.
I'd never leave
Ponyville hanging.
[ Laughs ]
You should see
the look on your face.
Ha!
You're a laugh,
Twilight Sparkle.
I can't wait to hang out
some more.
Wow!
She's amazing!
[ Laughs ]
[ groans ]
Wait! It's kind of pretty
once you get used to it.
Decorations.
Spike: beautiful!
Twilight Sparkle: yes.
The decor
is coming along nicely.
This ought to be quick.
I'll be at the library
in no time.
Beautiful, indeed.
Not the decor -- Her.
No, no.
No.
Oh, goodness, no.
How are my spines?
Are they straight?
[ Pop! Pop! ]
Good afternoon.
Just a moment, please.
I'm in the zone,
as it were.
Oh, yes!
Sparkle always does the trick,
does it not?
Why, Rarity,
you are a talent.
Now, um, how can I help you --
Aah-Ha-Ha!
Oh, my stars, darling!
Whatever happened
to your coiffure?
Oh, you mean my mane?
Well, it's a long story.
I'm just here to check
on the decorations,
And then I'll be
out of your hair.
Out of my hair?
What about your hair?
Wait.
Where are we going?
Help!
[ Whirl! Whirl! ]
Rarity:
no. No. Unh-Unh.
Too green.
Too yellow.
Too poofy.
Not poofy enough.
Too frilly.
Too shiny.
Now go on, my dear.
You were telling me
where you're from.
[ Creaking ]
I've...[groans]
Been sent...from Canterlot...
to --
Huh?
[ Thud! ]
Canterlot?!
Oh, I am so envious.
The glamour,
the sophistication.
I've always dreamed
of living there.
I can't wait to hear
all about it.
We are gonna be the best
of friends, you and I.
Emeralds?!
What was I thinking?
Let me get you
some rubies.
Quick, before she decides to dye
my coat a new color.
[ Sighs ]
Wasn't she wonderful?
Focus, casanova.
What's next
on the list?
[ Clears throat ]
oh, uh, music.
It's the last one.
[ Birds singing ]
Oh, my.
Um, stop, please, everyone.
Um...excuse me, sir.
I mean no offense,
But your rhythm is just
a teeny, tiny bit off.
Now follow me, please.
A-one, a-two,
a-One, Two, Three.
Twilight Sparkle: hello!
[ Gasps ]
Oh, my.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to frighten
your birds.
I'm just here to check up
on the music,
And it sounded beautiful.
[ Squeak! Squeak! Squeak! ]
I'm Twilight Sparkle.
What's your name?
Um...I'm...[mumbles]
I'm sorry.
What was that?
Um...my name is...
[mumbles]
Didn't quite catch that.
[ Whimpers ]
Well, um, it looks like
your birds are back.
So I guess
everything's in order.
Keep up the good work.
[ Whimpers ]
Okay.
Well, that was easy.
[ Gasps ]
a baby dragon!
Oh, I've never seen
a baby dragon before.
He's so cute.
Well, well, well.
Oh, my.
He talks.
I didn't know
dragons could talk.
That's just
so incredibly wonderful.
I-I just don't even know
what to say.
[ Tinkle! ]
Well, in that case,
we better be going.
Wait, wait.
What's his name?
I'm Spike.
Hi, Spike.
I'm Fluttershy.
Wow, a talking dragon.
And what do dragons
talk about?
Well, what do you want
to know?
Absolutely everything.
[ Groans ]
Well, I started out
As a cute little
purple-And-Green egg.
And that's the story
of my whole entire life...
well, up until today.
Do you want to hear
about today?
Oh, yes, please.
Wuh!
I am so sorry.
How did we get here
so fast?
This is where I'm staying
while in Ponyville,
And my poor baby dragon
needs his sleep.
No, I don't.
Aah!
[ Baby talk ] aww!
Wook at that.
He's so sweepy, he can't even
keep his wittle bawance.
Poor thing.
You simply must get him
to bed.
[ Zip! ]
Yes, yes.
We'll get right on that.
Well, good night.
[ Slam! ]
Huh. Rude much?
Sorry, Spike, but I have to
convince the princess
That Nightmare Moon
is coming,
And we're running
out of time.
I just need to be alone
so I can study
Without a bunch
of crazy ponies
Trying to make friends
all the time.
Now, where's the light?
Surprise!
[ Horn blows ]
[ Groans ]
Surprise!
Hi.
I'm Pinkie Pie.
And I threw this party
just for you.
Were you surprised?
Were you, were you?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Very surprised.
Libraries are supposed to be
quiet.
[ Chuckling ]
that's silly.
What kind of welcome party
would this be if it were quiet?
I mean, duh!
Boring!
You see, I saw you when you
first got here, remember?
You were all, "hello."
And I was all [gasps]
Remember?
You see, I never saw you before.
And if I never saw you before,
that means you're new,
'Cause I know everypony, and
i mean everypony, in Ponyville.
[ Groans ]
And if you're new,
you hadn't met anyone yet.
And if you haven't met
anyone yet, you must
not have any friends.
And if you don't have
any friends, then
you must be lonely.
And that made me so sad.
And I had an idea.
And that's why I went
[gasps]
"I should throw
a great, big, ginormous,
Super-Duper, spectacular
welcome party
And invite everyone
in Ponyville."
See? And now you have
lots and lots of friends.
Applejack: are you all right,
sugar cube?
[ Whistle blows ]
Aww!
She's so happy, she's crying.
Hot sauce.
Ooh.
[ Muffled ] what?
This is good.
[ Dance music playing ]
[ Clock ticking ]
Ugh.
Spike: hey, Twilight,
Pinkie Pie's starting
"pin the tail on the pony."
Want to play?
No!
All the ponies in this town
are crazy!
Do you know
what time it is?
It's the eve
of the Summer Sun Celebration.
Everypony has to stay up,
Or they'll miss
the princess raise the sun.
You really should lighten up,
Twilight.
It's a party.
[ Mumbling ]
Ugh! Here, I thought
I'd have time
To learn more about the elements
of harmony, but silly me.
All this ridiculous
friend-making
Has kept me from it.
Legend has it that on the
longest day of the 1,000th year,
The stars will aid
in her escape,
And she will bring about
everlasting night.
I hope the princess was right.
I hope it really is
just an old pony tale.
Spike:
come on, Twilight!
It's time to watch
the sun rise.
[ Music continues ]
Isn't this exciting?
Are you excited?
'Cause I'm excited.
I've never been
so excited.
Well, except for the time that i
saw you walking into town,
And I went [gasps]
But, I mean, really,
who can top that?
[ Birds singing ]
Fillies and gentlecolts,
as mayor of Ponyville,
It is my great pleasure
to announce the beginning
Of the summer sun
celebration.
[ All cheering ]
In just a few moments,
our town
Will witness
the magic of the sunrise
And celebrate this,
the longest day of the year.
And now, it is my great honor
to introduce to you
The ruler of our land,
The very pony who gives us
the sun and the moon
Each and every day,
The good, the wise,
The bringer of harmony
to all of Equestria...
ready?
...princess Celestia!
[ Birds singing ]
Huh?
This can't be good.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
remain calm, everypony.
There must be
a reasonable explanation.
Ooh, ooh!
I love guessing games.
Is she hiding?
She's gone!
[ All gasp ]
Ooh, she's good.
Aah!
[ All gasp ]
Oh, no.
Nightmare Moon.
Oh!
Oh, my beloved subjects.
It's been so long
Since I've seen your precious
little sun-Loving faces.
What did you do
with our princess?
Slow down, nelly.
[ Laughs evilly ]
Why?
Am I not royal enough
for you?
Don't you know who I am?
Ooh, ooh!
More guessing games.
Um, Hokey Smokes.
How about Queen Meanie?
No.
Black Snooty, Black Snooty!
[ Muffled speaking ]
Does my crown
no longer count
Now that I have been imprisoned
for 1,000 years?
Did you not recall
the legend?
Did you not see
the signs?
I did,
and I know who you are.
You're the mare in the moon,
Nightmare Moon.
[ All gasp ]
Well, well, well.
Somepony
who remembers me.
Then you also know
why I'm here.
You're here to...to...
[ gulps ]
[ Laughs evilly ]
Remember this day,
little ponies,
For it was your last.
From this moment forth,
the night will last forever!
[ Laughs evilly ]