No. Nope.
Thank you kindly, Twilight,
for helping me out.
No. No.
I bet Big Macintosh
I could get
All these golden delicious
in the barn by lunchtime.
No.
If I win, he's gonna
walk down stirrup street...
nope. No.
...in one
of granny's girdles.
No.
[ Laughs ]
No problem at all,
Applejack.
I'm glad the goal
is lunchtime.
All this hard work
is making me hungry.
I know, right?
Ohh-Eee, Spike.
You've been lounging on my back
all morning while we worked.
Exactly.
You two are taking so long,
I missed snack time.
[ Stomach grumbling ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
I guess we better
get some food.
Nope. Worm.
Aha!
Oh, Spike!
That looks delicious!
[ Chomp! ]
Spike!
[ Gulp! ]
What?
[ Gasps, burps ]
It's a letter
from princess Celestia.
[ Clears throat ]
"Hear ye, hear ye.
"Her grand royal highness,
princess Celestia of Equestria,
"Is pleased to announce
the Grand Galloping Gala
"To be held in the magnificent
capital city of Canterlot
On the 21st day of..."
[ Groans ]
yada yada yada.
"...Cordially extends
an invitation
To Twilight Sparkle
plus one guest."
[ Both gasp ]
The Grand Galloping Gala!
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
Gala-riffic ponies!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
The great Galloping Gala!
Hoo-Hoo!
Yeah!
[ Both giggling ]
[ Gasps, burps ]
Look -- Two tickets!
Wow! Great!
I've never been to the gala.
Have you, Spike?
No.
And I plan to keep it that way.
I don't want any of that girly,
frilly, froufrou nonsense.
Aw, come on, Spike.
A dance would be nice.
Nice?
It's a heap good more
than just nice.
I'd love to go.
Land's sakes!
If I had
an apple stand set up,
Ponies would chawing
our tasty vittles
Till the cows came home.
Do you have any idea
How much business I could
drum up for sweet apple acres?
Why, with all that money,
We could do a heap
of fixin' up 'round here.
We could replace
that saggy, old roof.
[ Poof! ]
And Big Macintosh could
replace that saggy, old plow.
[ Poof! ]
And Granny Smith could
replace that saggy, old hip.
[ Poof! ]
[ Up-Tempo music plays ]
Why, I'd give my left hind leg
to go to that gala.
Oh. Well, in that case,
would you like to --
Whoa!
[ Grunts ]
Are we talking
about the Grand Galloping Gala?
Rainbow Dash!
You told me you were too busy
to help me harvest apples.
What were you busy doing?
Spying?
No. I was busy...
napping.
And I just happened to hear
that you have an extra ticket?
Yeah, but --
Yes!
This is so awesome!
The Wonderbolts perform
At the Grand Galloping Gala
every year!
I can see it now.
[ Harp music plays ]
Everyone would be
watching the sky,
Their eyes riveted
on the Wonderbolts.
But then, in would fly...
Rainbow Dash!
[ Crowd gasping ]
I would draw their attention
With my super-Speed strut.
[ Cheering ]
Then I would mesmerize them
With my fantastic filly flash!
And for my grand finale,
the buccaneer blaze.
[ Zap! ]
[ Crowd cheering ]
The ponies would go wild!
The Wonderbolts would insist
That my signature moves be
incorporated into their routine
And then...
welcome me
as their newest member.
[ Electricity crackles ]
Don't you see, Twilight?
This could be my one chance
to show 'em my stuff.
You've got to take me!
Hold on just one
pony-Pickin' minute here.
[ Spits ]
I asked
for that ticket first.
So? That doesn't mean
you own it.
Oh, yeah? Well, I challenge you
to a hoof wrestle.
Winner gets the ticket.
[ Zip! Zip! ]
[ Both grunting ]
Girls!
These are my tickets.
I'll decide who gets it,
thank you very much.
Whoever has the best reason
to go should get the ticket,
Don't you think?
Drumming up business
for the farm?
A chance to audition
for the Wonderbolts?
Money to fix
granny's hip.
Living the dream!
Oh, my.
Those are all pretty good
reasons, aren't they?
[ Stomach grumbling ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
listen to that.
I am starving.
I don't know about you,
But I can't make important
decisions on an empty stomach.
So i'll, uh,
think about it over lunch
And get back
to you two, okay?
Okay.
[ Zip! Zip! ]
[ Both grunting ]
So, who are you gonna
give the ticket to, Twilight?
I don't know, Spike,
But I really can't think
straight when I'm hungry.
So, where should we eat?
[ Thud! ]
Aah! Bats!
Bats on my face!
Help! Wait!
These aren't...
tickets
to the Grand Galloping Gala?!
It's the most amazing,
incredible, tremendous, super,
Wonderful, terrifically
humongous party
In all of Equestria!
I've always, always,
always wanted to go!
* oh, the Grand Galloping Gala
is the best place for me *
* hip, hip, hooray
* it's the best place for me
* for Pinkie
With decorations like streamers
and fairy lights
And pinwheels and piniatas
and pincushions?
With goodies like sugar cubes
and sugarcanes and sundaes
And sunbeams and sarsaparilla?
And I get to play my favoritist
of favorite fantabulous games
Like pin the tail on the pony!
* oh, the Grand Galloping Gala
is the best place for me *
* 'cause it's
the most gala-Riffic *
* superly terrific gala
ever in the whole galaxy *
Whee!
Oh, thank you, Twilight!
It's the most wonderfullest gift
ever.
[ Blink! Blink! Blink! ]
Um, actually...
[ gasps ]
Are these
what I think they are?
Uh...
yes! Yes! Yes!
Twilight's taking me
To the Grand Galloping Gala
in Canterlot!
The gala?
I design ensembles
for the gala every year.
But I've never had
the opportunity to attend.
Oh, the society,
the culture, the glamour.
It's where I truly belong
[giggles]
And where I'm destined
to meet him!
Him!
Who?
Him.
I would stroll through the gala,
And everyone would wonder,
"who is that mysterious mare?"
They would never guess
That I was just a simple pony
from little old Ponyville.
Why, I would cause
such a sensation
That I would be invited
for an audience
With princess Celestia herself.
And the princess
would be so taken
With the style and elegance
That she would
introduce me to him!
Her nephew...
the most handsome, eligible
unicorn stallion in Canterlot!
Our eyes would meet.
Our hearts would melt.
Our courtship
would be magnificent.
He would ask
for my hoof in marriage.
And, of course,
I would say, "yes!!"
We would have a royal wedding,
befitting a princess,
Which is [giggles] what i
would become upon marrying him,
The stallion of my dreams!
Twilight!
I simply
cannot believe
You would invite Pinkie Pie
so she can party
And prevent me
from meeting my true love.
How could you?
Hmph!
Spike: hey!
[ Gasps ]
Angel, these are perfect.
Uh, listen, guys,
I haven't decided
who to give the extra ticket to.
You haven't?!
Um, excuse me,
Twilight,
I would
just like to ask --
I mean, if it would be
all right,
If you haven't given it
to someone else --
You?!
You want to go to the gala?
Oh, no.
I-I mean, yes.
Or, actually, kind of.
You see...
it's not so much
the Grand Galloping Gala
As it is the wondrous
private gated garden
That surrounds the dance.
The flowers are said to be
the most beautiful and fragrant
In all of Equestria.
For the night of the gala
and that night alone
Will they all be in bloom.
And that's just the flora!
Don't get me started
on the fauna.
There's loons and toucans
and bitterns, oh, my!
Hummingbirds
that can really hum
And buzzards
that can really buzz!
Blue jays and red jays
and green jays,
Pink jays and pink flamingoes.
[ Squawks ]
Gee, Fluttershy,
it sounds...
beautiful?
Rainbow Dash:
wait just a minute!
Rainbow Dash!
Were you following me?
No. I mean, yes.
I mean, maybe.
Look,
it doesn't matter.
I couldn't risk
a goody-Four-Shoes like you
Giving that ticket away
to just anybody!
Wait just another minute.
Applejack?
Were you following me, too?
No, I was following
this one
To make sure she didn't
try any funny business.
Still trying
to take my ticket.
Your ticket?!
But Twilight's
taking me!
[ All arguing indistinctly ]
Quiet!!
And then I said, "oatmeal?
Are you craz--"
Oh.
Girls, there's no use
in arguing.
But, Twilight!
Eh!
This is my decision.
And I'm gonna make it
on my own.
And I certainly can't think
straight with all this noise.
[ Stomach grumbling ]
Not to mention hunger.
Now go on!
Shoo!
[ All grumbling ]
And don't worry!
I'll figure this out!
Somehow.
Aw, Spike,
what am I gonna do?
All five of my best friends
have really good reasons
To go to the gala.
Applejack
or Rainbow Dash?
Pinkie Pie or Fluttershy?
Rarity?
Oh, who should
go with me?
[ Stomach grumbling ]
Waiter:
have you made your decision?
I can't decide!
Twilight, he just wants
to take your order.
Oh.
I would love
a daffodil-And-Daisy sandwich.
Do you have
any rubies?
No?
Okay.
I'll have the hay fries.
Extra crispy!
What do you think,
Spike?
I think we have to try
another restaurant.
I mean,
I like grass just fine,
But would it hurt anybody
to offer some gemstones?
I mean about the gala and the
ticket and who I should take.
Oh.
You're still on that?
Spike, listen!
How do I choose?
And when I do choose,
Will the other four
be mad at me?
I mean, I could give up
my ticket and give away two,
But that would still leave
three disappointed ponies.
What if I --
Ah, your food.
Oh, thank you.
This looks so good.
I'm sure everything will be
much clearer once I eat.
Um, madame?
Are you going to eat your food
in the rain?
It's not raining.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
What's going on?
Hi, there, best friend forever
I've ever, ever had.
Enjoying
the sunny weather?
Rainbow Dash,
what are you doing?
What do you mean?
I just saw the smartest,
Most generous pony
about to get rained on,
So I thought
I'd kick a hole in the clouds
To keep her dry so she could
dine in peace, that's all.
Rainbow, you're not trying
to get extra consideration
For the extra ticket
By doing me extra-Special
favors, are you?
Me? No, no, no.
Of course not.
Uh-Huh.
Seriously,
I'd do it for anypony.
[ Gulps,
laughs nervously ]
Rainbow, I am not comfortable
accepting unwanted favors,
So I'd appreciate it
If you'd close up
that rain cloud right now.
Ugh! Fine!
[ Zip! ]
That's better.
[ Groans ]
Twilight!
It's raining.
No, really?
Come with me
before you catch a cold!
[ Whiffle! Whiffle! Whiffle! ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
oops.
Sorry.
Oh, no!
It's quite all right!
After all, we are the best
of friends, are we not?
And you know what
the best of friends do.
Uh...
makeover!
[ Grunting ]
Rarity! Ow!
This really
isn't necessary.
I mean, thank you, but --
Ooh!
That's too tight!
[ Harp music plays ]
There!
Oh, you're simply darling!
Uh...
yeah, it is kind of pretty,
isn't it?
And you!
Oh, Spike, I have
a dandy little outfit
For the Dashing gent.
Whoa! Ouch! Oh! Hey!
Come on! Watch it! Whoa!
[ Harpsichord music plays ]
Oh, Spike.
Now you just need a hat.
Ugh!
I told you, I don't want any
part of this girly gala gunk.
See you back at the library.
[ Zip! ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
oh, who needs him anyway?
This is all about you
And how fabulous you'll look
at the Grand Galloping Gala.
Wait.
The grand --
[ Gasps ]
And, oh, my goodness.
What a coincidence.
I happen to have an ensemble
of my own
That matches yours
to a "t."
We would be the belles
of the ball, you and i.
Everyone would be clamoring
for our attention.
All eyes
would be on us.
And then everyone
would finally know
The most beautiful,
most talented,
Most sophisticated pony
in all of Equestria
Is Rarity the unicorn!
[ Giggles nervously ]
And Twilight Sparkle,
of course.
[ Giggles nervously ]
I see what's going on.
You're just buttering me up
so I give you the extra ticket.
Well,
it's not gonna work.
You're going to have to wait
for my decision
Just like everyone else.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've been trying all day
just to get some lunch!
Did somepony say "lunch"?
You've got
to be kidding me!
I got apple Pie,
apple fritters, apple tarts,
Apple dumplings,
apple crisp, apple crumblers,
And apple brown betty!
Uh, the dessert,
not my auntie.
What do you say there,
best friend?
[ Stomach grumbling ]
Is that a "yes"?
No. No!
I don't know
who I'm giving the ticket to!
And all these favors aren't
making it any easier to decide.
In fact, I'm less sure now
than I was this morning!
Ugh!
So, that's a "maybe"?
[ Sighs ]
I never thought
being showered with favors
Would be so aggravating!
[ Humming ]
[ Gasps ]
Fluttershy! Not you, too!
Oh!
Well, hello, Twilight.
I hope you don't mind,
But we're all doing a little
spring cleaning for you.
It's summer.
Oh.
Well, better late
than never, right?
It was Angel's idea.
[ Squeaks ]
You're not doing this
for the ticket, are you?
Oh, no!
I'm doing this because
you're my very best friend,
Right, Angel?
Oh.
Yes, we are just doing this
for the ticket.
[ Stomach grumbling ]
No! No! No!
Well, this was all
very nice of you and Angel,
But I'm not accepting
any extra favors
Until I've made
my final decision.
So I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Surprise!
[ Horns blowing ]
* Twilight is
my bestest friend *
* whoopee, whoopee
Pinkie --
* she's the cutest, smartest,
all-Around best pony, pony *
Pinkie --
* I bet if I throw
a super-Duper fun party, party *
Pinkie!
* she'll give her extra ticket
to the gala to me *
Pinkie!!
Yes, Twilight?
[ Blink! Blink! Blink! Blink! ]
At least
the other ponies
Tried to be subtle
about the ticket.
Wait, what ticket?
What gala?
Oh,
you didn't know?
Twilight has an extra ticket
to the Grand Galloping Gala!
All:
the Grand Galloping Gala?!
Have I ever told you
how much I love your mane?
I'll wash your dishes.
Would you like any help
with your gardening?
I have cartload
of extra carrots.
[ All talking over each other ]
What are we gonna do?
We're...gonna...
RUN!
[ All talking over each other ]
[ Ominous music plays ]
[ All gasping ]
Where is she?
Where did she go?
She's
disappeared!
[ Poof! ]
[ Groans ]
Warn me next time
you're gonna do that.
I didn't even know
it was gonna happen.
Now quick --
Lock the doors!
[ Blows ]
Whew.
[ Ominous music plays ]
Yah!
I can't decide!
I just can't decide!
It's important to all of you,
And I just can't stand
to disappoint any of you.
And giving me gifts and doing me
favors won't make any difference
Because you're all
my friends,
And I want to make
you all happy.
And I can't!
I just can't!
Twilight, sugar, I-I didn't mean
to put so much pressure on you.
And if it helps,
I don't want the ticket anymore.
You can give it
to somepony else.
I won't feel bad.
I promise.
Me too.
I feel just awful
that I made you feel so awful.
And me too! It's no fun
upsetting your friends.
Twilight, it was unfair of me
to try to force you as I did.
Yes!
That means the ticket is mine!
[ Laughs ]
* I've got the ticket,
I've got the ticket *
You know, I haven't
perfected my signature moves
For the Wonderbolts, anyway.
I don't need that ticket,
either.
We all got so gung ho
about going to the gala
That we couldn't see how
un-Gung ho we were making you.
Together:
we're sorry, Twilight.
Spike,
take down a note.
"Dear princess Celestia,
"I've learned that one
of the joys of friendship
"Is sharing your blessings.
"But when there's not enough
blessings to go around,
"Having more than your friends
can make you feel pretty awful.
"So, though I appreciate
the invitation,
I will be returning both tickets
to the Grand Galloping Gala."
What?!
"If my friends can't all go,
I don't want to go, either."
Twilight, you don't
have to do that.
Nope.
I've made up my mind.
Spike, you can
send the letter now.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Now you won't get to go
to the gala, either.
It's okay, girls.
I couldn't possibly enjoy myself
Without my best friends
there with me.
[ All giggling ]
So I would rather
not go at all.
[ Gagging ]
Well, wallop
my withers, Spike.
Isn't that
just like a boy?
Can't handle the least bit
of sentiment.
[ Burps ]
whoa, nelly!
[ Poof! ]
A letter from the princess?
That was fast.
"My faithful student
Twilight,
Why didn't you just say so
in the first place?"
Six tickets
to the Grand Galloping Gala!
[ All gasping ]
Now we can all go!
[ All cheering ]
[ Stomach grumbling ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
Allow us
to treat you to dinner.
What a great way
to apologize.
And to celebrate!
Come on, everyone!
The cupcakes are on me!
How come I don't get a ticket
to the gala?
[ Gasps ]
[ Burps ]
"And one for you, Spike."
[ Giggling ]
I mean, gross!
I have to go, too?
[ Zip! ]
[ Both laugh ]