Wow.
What a gorgeous day.
Rainbow Dash must have
gotten up early for once
And cleared
all the clouds away.
I bet all of Ponyville
Is gonna be out
enjoying the sunshine.
What?
Where is everypony?
Is it some sort
of pony holiday?
Not that I know of.
Does my breath stink?
Not more than usual.
Is it...zombies?!
Uh, not very likely.
Not likely,
but possible?
psst!
Twilight!
Spike!
Come here!
Hurry!
Before she gets you!
Who?
The zombie pony?
Z-Zombie pony?
Aah!
Spike, there are no
zombie ponies.
Pinkie, what are you doing
here alone in the dark?
I'm not alone
in the dark.
Okay, then, what are you all
doing here in the dark?
We're hiding from her.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Did you see her,
Twilight?
Did you see...Zecora?
Apple Bloom, I told you
never to say that name.
Well, I saw her
glance this way.
Glance e-E-Evilly
this way.
And then a bunch of you flip out
for no good reason.
No good reason?!
You call protecting your kin
no good reason?
Why, as soon as my sister
saw Zecora riding into town,
She started shaking
in her little horseshoes.
Did not.
So I swept her up
and brought her here.
I walked here myself.
For safekeeping.
Applejack,
I'm not a baby!
I can take care
of myself!
Not from
that creepy Zecora.
She's mysterious...
sinister...
and spo-o-o-oky.
Will you
cut that out?
Just look at those stripes.
So garish.
She's a zebra.
A what?!
A zebra.
And her stripes aren't
a fashion choice, Rarity.
They're what
she was born with.
Born where?
I never seen a pony
like that in these parts,
Except...her.
Well, she's probably
not from here,
And she's not a pony.
My books say that zebras come
from a faraway land.
But I've never seen her
in Ponyville.
Where does she live?
That's just it.
She lives in...
the Everfree forest.
Spike!
Uh, sorry.
The Everfree forest
just ain't natural.
The plants grow...
animals
care for themselves...
and the clouds move...
all on their own!
All on their own!
And that wicked enchantress
Zecora lives there,
Doing her evil...stuff!
Why, she's so evil,
I even wrote a song about her.
Here we go.
* she's an evil
enchantress *
* she does evil dances
* and if you look
deep in her eyes *
* she'll put you in trances
* then what will she do?
* she'll mix up an evil brew
* then she'll gobble you up
in a big, tasty stew *
* so watch out!
Wow. Catchy.
It's a work
in progress.
This is all just
a lot of gossip and rumors.
Now, tell me, what exactly have
you actually seen Zecora do?
Well...
once a month,
she comes into Ponyville.
Ooh!
Then...she lurks
by the stores.
Oh, my.
And then
she digs at the ground.
Good gracious!
Okay, I'm sorry,
but how is any of this bad?
Maybe she comes to town
to visit.
Yeah. Maybe she's just
trying to be neighborly.
And maybe she's not lurking
by the stores.
Maybe she's going to them,
lurk-Free, to do some shopping.
Yeah.
Everypony likes to shop.
You know what I think?
Apple Bloom, hush
and let the big ponies talk.
I am a big pony.
What about
digging at the ground?
You've got to admit
that's weird.
What if she's digging
for innocent creatures?
I am sure there's an explanation
for everything Zecora does.
And if anypony here
Were actually brave enough
to approach her,
She would find out
the truth.
Well, I'm brave enough.
I'm gonna find out myself.
You ponies
are being ridiculous!
Well, I heard
that Zecora eats hay.
Pinkie, I eat hay.
You eat hay.
Yeah, but I heard it's
the e-E-Evil way she eats hay.
Hey!
Where's Apple Bloom?
Fluttershy:
the door's open.
She went outside!
And Zecora's
still out there.
That silly
little filly.
I told her
to stay put.
Spike, you stay here in case
Apple Bloom comes back.
Will do!
Apple Bloom?!
You get back here
right now!
Beware! Beware,
you pony folk!
Those leaves of blue
are not a joke.
Y-You keep
your creepy mumbo jumbo
To yourself, you hear!
Yeah!
Ha! Was that
supposed to scare us?!
* she'll gobble
you up *
* in a big,
tasty stew *
Oh, brother.
Beware! Beware!
Yeah!
Back at you, Zecora!
You and your lame
curse are the ones
who'd better beware!
And you!
Why couldn't you just
listen to your big sister?
I-I...
who knows
what kind of nasty curse
Zecora could have just
put on you?
Just like in my song.
* evil enchantress!
* with the dances!
* and the trances!
You guys, there's
no such thing as curses.
Well, that's
interesting to hear
Coming from
miss magic pants herself.
My magic, real magic,
comes from within.
It's a skill
you're born with.
Curses are artificial,
fake magic.
It's conjured with potions
and incantations --
All smoke and mirrors
meant to scare.
But curses
have no real power.
They're just
an old pony tale.
Just you wait,
Twilight.
You're gonna learn that
some pony tales really are true.
* she's an evil enchantress!
* she does evil dances!
Beware! Beware!
* if you look deep in her eyes
* she will put you
in trances! *
Yeah, was that
supposed to scare us?!
Wicked, wicked zebra.
Curse.
* then what will she do?!
Just you wait, Twilight.
Some pony tales really are true.
* then she'll
gobble you up *
* in a big, tasty stew
Ohhh...watch out!
Ugh. What a dream.
Curses, schmurses.
Whoa.
Maybe Zecora cursed
my hair.
Or she cursed my horn!
No, no, no, no, no!
None of these books have a cure.
There has to be
a real reason for this!
An illness?
An allergy?!
A curse!
I said a real reason --
Something that points
to something real.
How about this one?
"Supernaturals"?
Spike, the word
"supernatural"
Refers to things like ghosts
and spirits and zombies,
Which are
as make-Believe as curses.
This book
is just a bunch of hooey.
But what if you're wrong,
Twilight?
What if this
really is a --
A pfurse!
A purse?
How could it be a purse?
Pinkie!
What happened?!
Pee pah pah pfurse pah!
Pee pah pah pfurse pah pah!
Hey, say it,
don't spray it, Pinkie!
Rainbow Dash: ow!
Oh!
She's --
Trying to say -- Ow!
Zecora -- Oh!
She slapped us all
with a -- Ow!
...curse!
I'm afraid
I have to agree.
Pftblblt!
I hate to say
I told you so, Twilight,
but I told you so!
It's a curse,
I tells ya!
But Fluttershy
seems just fine.
Yes.
There doesn't seem to be
a thing wrong with her.
Fluttershy?
Are you okay?
Is there something
wrong with you?
Would you
care to tell us?
So...
you're not gonna tell us?
"Yes, you're not,"
or "yes, you will?"
Good gravy, girl!
What's wrong with you?!
I don't want to talk about it.
This is hilarious!
Look at all of you!
We got hair-ity...
Rainbow Crash...
Spitty Pie...
Apple-Tini...
Flutterguy...
and...uh...
I got nothing.
"Twilight Sparkle" --
I mean, seriously,
I can't even work with that.
Ah-Ha-Ha-Ha.
This is no joke, Spike.
Now, start looking for more
books so I can find a cure.
I think we'll find a cure
to this curse at Zecora's place!
It's not a curse!
I agree with Dash.
We'll go to Zecora's and
force her to remove this hex.
It's not a hex either!
That woman's
got to be stopped.
This is all
my fault.
If I hadn't followed Zecora
in the first place,
None of this
would have happened.
I just got to fix this.
Now, where does she think
she's going this time?
I don't care what you say,
Twilight!
It's time to pony up
and confront Zecora!
Come on, girls.
Are you with me?!
I am-Pft!
And I, as well.
Oh, I don't know.
Seems awfully dangerous.
How about you,
Applejack?
pf-She's gone-Pft!
Aah!
Somepony stepped on her!
Or sat on her?
Rarity's hair!
Oh! Oh!
Pinkie, what are you doing?
Really -- Ow!
Ever hear
of personal space?!
Nope!
Apple Bloom
is gone, too.
I bet
they went after Zecora.
Well, we'd better
go find them.
Aah!
Come on, girls.
Let's go.
Oh, dear!
Oh, this
is so unseemly. Aah!
Hey,
a little help here?
Oopsie. Sorry.
Ow!
Uh, s-Spike?
A-Are you coming?
Nope.
Uh...
got to stay here
and look for a cure.
Twilight flopple!
Stop right there!
Turn around right now, missy!
No!
No?!
You can't ignore a direct order
from your big sister!
Sorry, Applejack,
but I'm the big sister now.
Apple Bloom, you come back here
right this instant!
I'm gonna tell
Big Macintosh on you!
Oh, pony feathers.
Come on, girls.
We've got to get to Zecora's.
Hurry!
Oh!
Easier said than done.
Hey! Wait for me!
Oof!
Rainbow! Thank Celestia!
There's no time to lose!
I need to get
to Zecora's pronto!
Giddy up, pony!
Excuse me?!
Yee-Haw!
What the...
no, Rainbow Dash!
Other way!
Oh!
I look horrible!
Plis place
plooks horrible!
Oh, my.
That place
really does look horrible.
Nice decorations --
If you like creepy!
Pfhe psole my psung!
Pshe spluh mm mm!
She stole your song?
Oh, Pinkie.
It doesn't sound
anything like your song.
Hmm.
* she's an evil
enchantress *
* and she does
evil dances *
* and if you look
deep in her eyes *
* she will put you
in trances *
* then what
will she do? *
* she'll mix up
an evil brew *
* then she'll
gobble you up *
* in a big,
tasty stew *
* so...
* watch out
You saw
those terrible things.
Now do you believe us,
Twilight?
Scary-Looking masks,
confusing incantations,
And a great, big
bubbling cauldron?
Oh, everything is pointing
to Zecora being...bad.
Or...what if Zecora's
just making soup?
Mmm!
The perfect temperature
for ponies, I presume.
Now, where is
that little Apple Bloom?
Or...what if she's making
Apple Bloom soup?!
What if she's making
I'm coming for you,
Apple Bloom!
Aaaah!
oof!
Whoa, there! Aah!
Heel, Rainbow Crash!
What have you done
with Apple Bloom?!
No! No!
Ponies,
what is this you --
No! You know not
what you do!
You've gone and spilled
my precious brew!
We're onto you,
Zecora.
I didn't want to believe
that you cursed us,
But the evidence
is overwhelming.
You made me look
ridiculous.
You made me sound
Pfe pfuh pfuh pfound
puh-Pluh-Pli-Plus!
You ruined my horn!
How dare you?!
You destroy my home,
destroy my work,
Then rudely accuse me
of being a jerk?!
You put this curse on us,
now you're gonna un-Curse us!
It is unwise to venture
down this road.
Your actions
will make my anger explode!
Where is Apple Bloom?
Zecora, I think I found
all the things you asked for.
What in Ponyville
is going on here?
Apple Bloom! You're okay!
Why wouldn't I be?
Because Zecora
is an evil enchantress
Who cursed us and was gonna
cook you up into soup.
Oh, Twilight.
Did those silly fillies
finally get in your head?
You know there's
no such thing as a curse.
Apple Bloom, sweetie,
You can't just stand there
and tell me this isn't a curse.
This isn't a curse.
If you
will remember back,
The words I spoke
were quite exact.
Beware! Beware,
you pony folk!
Those leaves of blue
are not a joke.
It was a warning
about that blue plant.
It's called "poison joke."
That plant
is much like poison oak,
But its results
are like a joke.
What in the hay
does that mean?
It means this plant
does not breed wrath.
Instead, this plant
just wants a laugh.
Will somepony
please talk normal?
I think
what she's saying
Is that when we ran in
to save Apple Bloom,
We ran into
the poison joke.
All our problems are just
little jokes it played on us.
Little jokes?!
Very funny.
Okay. Fine.
But what about the cauldron?
And the chanting?
And the creepy decor?
Treasures of the native land
where I am from.
This one speaks "hello,"
and this -- "Welcome."
Not welcoming at all,
if you ask me.
The words I chanted
were from olden times --
Something you call
a nursery rhyme.
But the cauldron,
the Apple Bloom soup?
Looky here, Twilight, that pot
of water wasn't for me.
It was for all these
herbal ingredients.
The cure for poison joke is
a simple, old natural remedy.
You just got to take
a bubble bath.
But I tried to find a cure
in all my books
And couldn't find
anything.
What book
has this natural remedy?
Here is the book. You see?
Sad that you lack it
in your library.
Actually,
I do have this book.
But I didn't look inside because
the title was so...weird.
"Supernaturals --
Natural remedies and cure-alls
that are simply super."
I...i...
I'm so sorry, Zecora.
I had the answer
the whole time,
If only I'd bothered
to look inside.
Maybe next time
You will
take a second look
And not judge
the cover of the book.
Zecora,
would you be kind enough
To mix up another batch
of the herbal bath?
Mix it up,
I certainly will.
Yet I am missing
an herb from Ponyville.
But whenever
Zecora comes to town,
All the shops
are mysteriously closed.
Oh, well, I think
we can help you with that.
Look, rose.
How awful!
The wicked enchantress
has cursed them all.
The horror!
Everypony get inside.
Run, ponies! Run!
Daisy,
we need to talk.
"Dear princess Celestia,
"My friends and I all learned
an important lesson this week --
"Never judge a book
by its cover.
"Someone may look unusual
or funny or scary,
"But you have to look past that
and learn who they are inside.
"Real friends don't care
what your cover is.
"It's the contents of a pony
that count.
"And a good friend,
like a good book,
"Is something
that will last forever.
Your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle."
Miss Zecora, I would love to get
the recipe for this bath.
It's simply luxurious.
Applejack!
Hey!
Where's Applejack?!
I'm right here,
little sis.
I ain't tiny no more.
Oh!
I have never felt so lovely
in all my life.
Oh, my gosh!
I never realized how horrible
it is not to be able to talk!
I mean,
I love talking so much,
And when I couldn't talk
anymore,
My tongue was all...
aaaah!
It was the worst!
Don't you agree, Fluttershy?
Yes.