[ Splash! ]
[ Otters squeal ]
[ Birds chirp ]
Ptoo! Ptoo!
Not too fast, now,
Angel bunny.
You don't want to get
a tummy ache.
[ Chuckles ]
You really should eat more
than that, don't you think?
[ Boing! Boing! Boing! ]
It's not playtime yet.
I know
you want to run,
But just
three more bites.
Two more bites?
One more bite?
Pretty please?
[ Sighs ]
[ Coughing ]
oh, goodness.
Are you okay?
Are you coughing
Because there's a carrot
stuck in your throat?
Because you need
some water?
[ Coughing loudly ]
[ Gasps ]
Because of that giant cloud
of scary, black smoke?
I'll take that as a...
yes.
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Help! Help!
Please?
Help!
There's -- There's a horrible
cloud of smoke.
It's headed this way,
and -- Aah!
Don't be such
a scaredy-Pony.
It's just me, future Equestria
ball-Bouncing record holder.
146, 147...
this calls
for a celebration!
Oh, no, Pinkie Pie.
This is no time for celebration.
This is a time for panic,
for --
Ooh!
I'm gonna need balloons!
One for every pony
in Ponyville.
There's -- There's smoke,
And -- And where there's smoke,
there's fire, and --
Let's see!
That's
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
154, 155...
no, wait.
7...
Pinkie Pie!
Now I have to
start over.
We're all gonna have to
start over
In a new village,
'Cause ours
is gonna be --
Hey, Rainbow Dash,
wait up!
Oh, please.
This is an emergency.
I-I need every pony
to --
Listen up!
Smoke is spreading
over all of Equestria.
What?!
Oh, no!
That's what i've
been trying to --
Pony:
but don't worry.
I've just received a letter
from princess Celestia
Informing me that it is not
coming from a fire.
Oh, thank goodness.
Pony:
it's coming from a dragon.
[ All gasp ]
A...d-D-Dragon?
Applejack: what in the name
of all things cinnamon swirl
Is a full-Grown dragon
doing here in Equestria?
Sleeping.
Huh?
Huh?Huh?
According to princess Celestia,
he's taking a nap.
His snoring is what's causing
all this smoke.
He should really see
a doctor.
That doesn't sound healthy
at all.
Well, at least he's not
snoring fire.
What are we meant to do
about it?
Rainbow Dash: I'll tell you
what we're meant to do --
Give him the boot!
Take that!
[ Tinkling ]
And that!
We need to encourage him
to take a nap somewhere else.
Princess Celestia
has given us this mission,
And we must not fail.
If we do, Equestria
will be covered in smoke
For the next 100 years.
[ Gasps ]
[ scoffs ]
Talk about getting
your beauty sleep.
All right, everypony, I need you
to gather supplies quickly.
We've got a long journey
ahead of us.
Let's meet back here
in less than an hour.
Okay, girls,
you heard her!
The fate of Equestria
is in our hooves.
Do we have
what it takes?!
Yeah!
You betcha!
We can do it!
Yeah, we can do it!
Um...actually...
rrarrr!
Hyah!
[ Cheer! ]
[ Giggles ]
Oh, I mean...
grrr!
Ew!
Much better.
Onward!
[Door hinges creak, door slams]
[ squeals ]
Let's go!
Um...
let's...not?
[ Squeals nervously ]
All right, girls,
listen up.
I'm mapping out
the fastest route,
But we've all got to keep
a good pace
If we expect to make it up
the mountain by nightfall.
M-Mountain?
The dragon is in that cave
at the very top.
Looks pretty cold
up there.
You bet it is.
The higher you go,
the chillier it gets.
Good thing
I brought my scarf.
Ooh! Pretty!
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, yeah.
That'll keep you
nice and cozy.
[ Gulp! ]
Fluttershy:
um, excuse me. Twilight?
I know you're busy,
but --
Uh-Huh.
Well,
we could go this way.
But if I could just have
a second --
Uh-Huh.
No, we want to avoid that.
So, um, i-I was thinking
that, um,
Maybe I should
just stay here in Ponyville.
Uh-Huh.
Oh, good!
I'll stay here and --
Wait!
You have to come.
Your way with wild animals
will surely come in handy.
I don't think I --
Oh, and don't worry
about your little
friends in the meadow.
Spike's got it covered
while you're gone.
You can count on me.
Ohh!
Hey! Hey!
Wait!
I don't really think
he's up to the task.
Maybe...
but...but...
[ squeals ]
Are you sure you want Fluttershy
to come along?
I mean, that pony's afraid
of her own shadow.
She's just gonna
slow us down.
Oh, she's just
a little nervous.
Once we get going,
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Fluttershy: oh!
[ Whiffle! ]
All right, girls.
Move out.
But...but...
[ squeals ]
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
[ Gasps ]
Whoa!
What was that?
That is what it sounds like
when a dragon snores.
It's -- It's so...
high.
Well,
it is a mountain.
I'm gonna fly up there
and check it out!
[ Creak! ]
[ Grunts ]
Hold on, now.
I think we should
all go up together.
Safety in numbers
and all.
Oh, all right.
I hear the only thing
that sparkles more
than a dragon's scales
Are the jewels they use
to build their nests.
Ooh!
If I play
my cards right,
I might be able to convince him
to part with a few.
"Welcome to my cave,
Rarity.
"Care for a diamond?
Rrarrr!"
[ Laughter ]
Girls!
This is no laughing matter.
Fluttershy, you're the expert
on wild creatures.
What do you think the dragon
will be like?
Fluttershy?
Hey, what are you waiting for --
An invitation?
Ooh! I think I have one
in my bag.
[ Cheer! ]
I-It's so...so...
steep.
Well, it is a cliff.
You could just --
Oh, I don't know -- Fly up here.
Come on, Fluttershy,
you can do it!
Flap those wings.
Uh...okay.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
Ohh! Uhh!
[ Groans ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ]
we don't have time for this.
What are you doing?
I'll need this
if I'm gonna take her
Around the mountain
another way.
Ohh!
Around
the mountain?
That's gonna take
them forever.
[ Squeals ]
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
Don't worry, twi.
We'll be there
lickety-Split.
Whoo-Hoo!
I win again!
[ Sighs ]
that's 35 games in a row.
Best of 71?
[ Applejack
breathing heavily ]
We...made...it.
Told you it was gonna
take them forever.
[ Gulp! ]
Your turn,
Fluttershy.
But it's so wide.
Come on, Fluttershy.
We should be
much farther along by now.
You could just
leap on over.
I --
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
I don't know.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
It's just
a hop, skip, and a jump!
See?
* it's not very far,
just move your little rump *
* you can make it if you try
with a hop, skip, and jump *
We don't have time
for this.
* a hop, skip, and a jump,
just move your little rump *
* a hop, skip, and jump,
a hop, skip, and jump *
* a hop, skip, and jump
Okay.
Here I go.
A hop...
that's it.
You got it.
Almost there.
Skip...
just don't look down.
Aah!
[ Wind howling ]
[ Groans ]
I guess
I forgot to jump.
Twilight Sparkle:
let's keep it down.
According to my map,
We're entering
an avalanche zone.
The smallest peep
could cause a huge rockslide.
An --
An ava-- Ava--
Shh!
[ Wind howling ]
[ Poink! ]
[ Echoing ] avala--
[ All sigh ]
[ Loud rumbling ]
Avalanche!
[ All screaming ]
Oh, no!
Help! Oh!
[ All coughing ]
Oh, my.
Everypony okay?
Thanks to you,
I am.
Ugh! Blech!
Whoo-Hoo!
Let's do it again!
[ Scoffs ]
This is why a girl
always packs extra accessories.
Oh, please tell me I brought
the tiara that goes with this.
Uh, I think we got
bigger problems
Than making sure our hair bows
match our horseshoes.
[ Sighs ]
sorry.
Ah, no big whoop,
sugar cube.
Yeah.
We'll just have to [sighs]
climb over.
[ All grunting, moaning ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Squeals ]
Aah!
[ Crash! ]
My apologies.
Not your fault.
Still think it was a good idea
to bring Fluttershy along?
We're about to
find out.
We're here.
Rainbow Dash, you'll use
your wings to clear the smoke.
Mm-Hmm.
Rarity and Pinkie Pie,
You create a diversion
to distract the dragon
If things get a little hairy
in there.
[ Squeaking ]
Applejack,
you're ready with the apples
In case he decides
to attack.
But it shouldn't come to that
because Fluttershy
Will do what she needs to do
to wake him up.
And between the two of us,
we should be able
To get him to understand
why he needs to go.
Is everypony ready?
Mm-Hmm!
Okay, then.
We're going in.
So...
what is the best way
to wake up a sleeping dragon
Without upsetting him?
Fluttershy?
Oh, come on.
Come on!
[ Grunts ]
We have to do this.
Now!
Every [grunts]
second longer
That dragon [grunts]
sleeps
Is another [grunts] acre
of Equestria
That is covered
in [grunts] smoke.
I...i...
I can't go in the cave.
[ All groan ]
Oh, great!
She's scared
of caves now, too.
I'm not scared
of caves.
I'm scared of dr...
what's that,
sugar cube?
I'm scared of drag...
what?
I'm scared of dragons!
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
[ Squeals ]
[ All coughing ]
But, Fluttershy,
you have a wonderful talent
Dealing with all kinds
of animals.
Yes, because
they're not dragons.
Oh, come on!
We've seen you walk right up
to a horrible manticore
Like it was nothing.
Yes,
because he wasn't a dragon.
Spike is a dragon.
You're not scared of him.
Yes, because he's not a huge,
gigantic, terrifying, enormous,
Teeth-Gnashing,
shark-Scale-Having,
Horn-Wearing,
smoke-Snoring,
Could-Eat-A-Pony-In-One-Bite,
Totally all-Grown-Up dragon.
[ Dragon snoring loudly ]
[ Whimpering ]
But if you're
so afraid of dragons,
Why didn't you
say something
Before we came
all the way up here?
I was afraid to.
Argh!
All of us are scared
of that dragon.
I'm not!
Almost all of us
are scared of that dragon,
But we've got a job
to do.
So get in there
with Twilight
And show her
what you're made of.
I...i...
I just...
can't.
Oh, Fluttershy.
I'm going in.
He probably just doesn't realize
what he's doing...
right?
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
Easy-Peasy.
Of course.
If you say so.
[ Laughs ]
Mr. Dragon?
[ Snoring loudly ]
Uh, excuse me?
[ Grumbles ]
Mr. Dragon?
Oh, good.
You're awake.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
My name is Twilight...
[ groans, roars ]
Ohh!
[ Groans ]
...Sparkle,
and my friends and i
Are residents here
in Equestria.
[ Snorts ]
Ponyville,
to be exact.
We've come here to ask
That you find another spot
to take your nap.
It's just that you seem to be
doing an awful lot of snoring,
And every time you do,
You send out a terrible cloud
of smoke.
[ Snorts ]
[ coughing ]
Equestria simply can't survive
100 years in a dark haze.
You understand,
don't you?
[ Groaning ]
So, you'll find
another place to sleep?
[ Snoring loudly ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Dragon snorts, all cough ]
So much for [coughs]
persuading him.
Now what?
[ Clears throat ]
Obviously,
this situation
Just calls for a little
pony charm.
Allow me, girls.
[ Singsong voice ]
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
[ Clears throat ]
Uh, but I couldn't possibly
head back home
Without mentioning
what handsome scales you have.
And those scales
have to be hidden away
In some silly cave
for 100 years?
[ Groans ]
Personally, I think you should
skip the snoozing
And be out there,
showing them off.
[ Chuckles ]
Obviously,
I would be more than happy
To keep an eye on your jewels
while you're gone.
[ Roars ]
Aah!
I was this close
to getting that diamond.
You mean,
"getting rid of that dragon"?
Oh, yeah, sure.
[ Party horn blowing ]
Applejack:
what in tarnation?
Darling,
you look ridiculous.
Exactly!
Sharing a laugh is a surefire
way to get someone on your side.
Hi!
[ Crash! ]
Apparently he doesn't like
laughing [chuckles]
Or sharing.
All right!
That's it!
We've tried persuasion,
charm,
Whatever it is
Pinkie Pie does.
[ Party horn blows ]
It's time to stop wasting time!
I'm going in!
Rainbow, no!
[ Zoom! ]
Get out!
Ah-Ah-Ah-Ah-Choo!
[ Growls ]
I'm...sorry.
[ Roars ]
Wh-O-O-O-Oa!
[ Strike! ]
[ Tweet! ]
Aah!
Whoa!
[ Growling ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Roars ]
[ All groaning ]
How dare you?
How dare you!
Listen here, mister!
Just because you're big
Doesn't mean you get to be
a bully!
You may have huge teeth
and sharp scales
And snore smoke
and breathe fire,
But you do not --
I repeat --
You do not hurt my friends!!
You got that?
[ Whimpers ]
Well?
But that Rainbow one
kicked me.
And I am very sorry
about that.
But you're bigger than she is,
and you should know better.
You should also know better
than to take a nap
Where your snoring can become
a health hazard
To other creatures.
But I --
Don't you "but i" me,
mister.
Now, what do you have to say
for yourself?
I said, what do you have to say
[ Sobbing loudly ]
There, there.
No need to cry.
You're not
a bad dragon.
You just made
a bad decision.
Now,
go pack your things.
You just need to find
a new place to sleep.
That's all.
[ All cheering ]
Fluttershy
to the rescue!
You did it.
I knew you could do it.
[ Spike exhales sharply ]
I said, come back here!
Ohh!
[ Creak! ]
How does Fluttershy put up
with you furry, little things?
Twilight Sparkle:
Spike?
Take a letter.
[ Sighs ]
with pleasure.
"Dear princess Celestia,
I am happy to report
"That the dragon has departed
our fair country
"And that it was
my good friend Fluttershy
"Who convinced him to go.
"This adventure
has taught me
"To never lose faith
in your friends.
"They can be
an amazing source of strength
"And can help you overcome
even your greatest fears.
Always your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle."
Applejack: Twilight,
you got to come see this!
She's just five away
from a new pony record.
347, 348...
Pinkie Pie:
rrarrr!
Dragon!
[ Bleats ]
[ Laughter ]
Why are you laughing?
That awful dragon is back!
Rrarrr!
Pinkie Pie,
you scared me!
I mean, uh...
you broke
my concentration.
It's okay,
Rainbow Dash.
Not eve pony
can be as brave as me.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Poink! ]
Aah!
[ Bleats ]
[ Laughter ]