Hmm.
Ha!
Perfect.
Just take the broken limbs down,
Rarity.
Don't y'all care about nothing
other than prettifyin'?
Somepony has to.
You are making
an absolute mess
Of the town square,
Applejack.
Yeah, well, the storm's gonna
make an even bigger mess
If we don't prune
all these loose branches
So they don't tumble down
on anypony.
I simply cannot imagine
why the pegasus ponies
Would schedule a dreadful
downpour this evening
And ruin what could have been
a glorious sunny day.
think more practical-Like,
will ya?
They accidentally skipped
a scheduled sprinkle last week,
So we need a doozy of a downpour
to make up for it, is all.
Oh, no!
My wonderfully styled mane
shall be ruined!
You should have hurried up
and finished the job already!
Ooh! Aah! Oh! Oh!
It's coming down too fast!
Aah! Oh! Oh! Aah!
Help me!
Uh...there.
Hunker down to your heart's
content whilst I finish things.
Oh, no, no! No!
What now?
I'd prefer not to get
my hooves muddy.
There is just
no pleasin' you, is there?
Everything's got to be
just so.
Oh, well, and how does
muddying my hooves
Serve any useful purpose?
Y'all wouldn't know useful
if it came up and bit you.
That doesn't even
make any sense.
Does so.
Does not.
Does so infinity.
Ha!
Does not infinity plus one.
What say
we go our separate ways
Before one of us says something
she will regret?
I reckon y'all are gonna say
something you'll regret first.
On the contrary, I believe it
shall most certainly be you
Who says something
you will regret first.
I'm not sayin' anything!
Nor am i!
Y'all just be on your way,
then.
After you!
Aah!
Perhaps we should stick together
for now
And find some shelter.
Uh-Huh,
perhaps we should...
and fast.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Nice and dry under here...
sort of.
Oh!
Unacceptable.
Applejack! Rarity!
Twilight?
Come inside, girls,
quick.
Whoa, nellie.
Is inside a tree
Really the best place to be
in a lightning storm?
It is if you have
a magical lightning rod
Protecting your home
like I do.
Come on in.
We are most grateful
for your invitation.
Thank you kindly
for your hospitality.
Uh, do be
a polite houseguest
And go wash up, please,
won't you?
If I got to spend
one more second
With that fussbudget Rarity
today,
I can't be held responsible
for what I'm gonna do.
Some storm, huh?
The pegasus ponies sure have
outdone themselves this time.
I hope you and Applejack
Don't have any trouble
getting home.
It may, indeed,
be a problem.
Well, you're welcome to stay
if need be.
Spike is away in Canterlot
on royal business.
I'm home all alone tonight.
You and Applejack should
totally sleep over!
We'll have a slumber party!
I've always wanted one of those.
Oh, goodness.
Uh, I do believe
I have another engagement
scheduled for this evening
That completely slipped my mind
until just now.
Oh, silly me.
I can't possibly stay here
all night...with Applejack.
"Slumber 101:
"All you've ever wanted to know
about slumber parties
But were afraid to ask."
My own personal copy.
It's a fantastic
reference guide.
You should see
the table of contents.
I've been waiting
for a chance to use it,
And today's the day.
This is gonna be so great!
Yes, uh, great.
What in tarnation?!
Now wait
just a goldarn minute!
You make me wash
the mud off my hooves,
But it's okay for y'all
to have mud all over your faces?
Silly.
This is called a mud mask.
It's to refresh
and rejuvenate your complexion.
We're giving each other
makeovers!
We have to do it.
It says so in the book.
"Slumber 101:
everything you..."
Oh, hey,
would you look at the time?
I got to skedaddle
on home quick.
I'm powerful late
for, uh -- For something.
Uh, good night.
Aah!
Or maybe I'll sit here
for a spell.
Hooray, slumber party!
blech!
What in the world
is this for?
To reduce the puffiness
around one's eyes, of course.
Puffiness, shmuffiness!
That's good eatin'.
Isn't this exciting?
We'll do everything
by the book,
And that will make
my slumber party officially fun.
Did you hear that,
Applejack?
You certainly would not want
to do anything
That would ruin Twilight's
very first slumber party,
Would you?
Of course not.
And you wouldn't, either,
I reckon.
So, do we have
an agreement?
You betcha.
Oh, gross!
You know, there's messy,
And there's
just plain rude.
You know, there's fussy,
And there's just plain
gettin'-On-My-Nerves.
Fortunately, I can get along
with anypony,
No matter how difficult
she may be.
Oh, yeah?
Well, i'm
the get-Alongingest pony
You're ever gonna meet.
That's not even a word.
This is gonna be the bestest
slumber party ever!
Yay!
Yay.
So...
how are you getting along
over there, Applejack?
Just fine, Rarity.
This is so awesome!
Makeovers -- Check.
Ooh! It says here
we have to tell ghost stories.
Who wants to go first?
Me!
I'd like to tell y'all
the terrifying tale
Of the prissy ghost
Who drove everypony crazy
with their unnecessary neatness.
Ooooh!
I'm sure y'all are familiar
with that one.
Never heard of it,
but I have a much better one.
It's the horrifying story
Of the messy,
inconsiderate ghost
Who irritated everypony
within 100 miles!
Ooooh!
That's not a real story!
You made it up!
It is a ghost story.
They're all made up.
Aah!
I've got one.
This story is called "the legend
of the headless horse."
It was a dark and stormy night
Just like this one,
And three ponies
were having a slumber party
Just...like...this one.
And just when the last pony
thought she was safe,
There, standing
right behind her,
Just inches away, was...
the headless horse!
Aaaah!
Ghost story -- Check.
Now, who wants s'mores?
Then you place
one marshmallow
On the top
of the chocolate.
And be sure it's centered.
That's critical.
And then carefully
put another
Perfectly square graham cracker
on the top.
And...done.
Ta-Da!
Ooh!
Nah, you just eat 'em.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
You could at least
say, "excuse me."
Oh, I was just about to,
but you interrupted me.
Pardon.
S'mores -- Check.
Now the next item of fun
we have to do is truth or dare.
I dare Applejack
To do something carefully
and neatly for a change.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I dare Rarity
to lighten up
And stop obsessin' over
every last little detail
For a change.
I think the truth of the matter
is that somepony
Could stand to pay a little more
attention to detail.
And I think the truth is
Somepony ought to quit
with her fussin'
So the rest of us
can get things done.
Um, I don't think this is how
the game's supposed to work.
You have to give
an honest answer to any question
Or do whatever anypony
dares you to do.
I dares you
to step outside
And let your precious tidy mane
get ruined again.
You have to.
It's the rule.
Ha!
Fine!
Okay, I dare Applejack
to play dress-Up
In a froufrou, glittery,
lacy outfit.
Happy?
Very.
Um, do I ever get a turn?
I dare you to enter the next
rodeo when it comes to town.
I dare you not to enter the next
rodeo that comes to town.
I dare you to not comb your mane
100 times before bed!
And I dare you to comb yours
just once!
I, uh -- I think we should check
off truth or dare and move on.
Let's see what our next fun,
fun, fun thing is, shall we?
Hmm, what does this mean?
"Pillow fight"?
Oh, please.
I am not at all interested
In participating
in something so crude.
Oh!
It...is...on!
Hyah!
Yah! Yah! Yah!
Oh, I get it.
Pillow...fight.
Fun!
Ugh! Aah!
uh, girls...
maybe we should take it down
a notch.
I will if she will.
She started it.
Maybe we should just call it
a night and get some sleep.
Keep your muddy hooves
on you side of the bed.
My hooves ain't muddy.
They were.
There might still be
a little on them.
There ain't. See?
Ew!
Now who's bein'
inconsiderate?
I have
to make the bed again
So the blanket
will be right.
Get up.
Hey!
Unh-Unh-Unh.
You'll ruin it.
You have to do it
like this.
Yeah.
That's not gonna happen.
Geronimo!
Hey!
Ahh.
You did that on purpose.
Um, yeah.
Get up
so I can fix it again.
Can't hear you.
I'm asleep.
Hmph!
I ain't budgin'.
You will
if you want any blanket!
Give it back!
I will not!
Yes, you will!
Won't!
Will!
Enough!
It says right here
that the number-One thing
You're supposed to do
at a slumber party is have fun.
And thanks to you two,
I can't check that off.
I've been tryin' my darndest
to get along.
No, it is I
who have been trying my best.
No, it was me.
No, it was I.
Me!
I!
I hope you're happy,
both of you.
You've ruined
my very first slumber party --
The makeover, the s'mores,
truth or dare, the pillow fight!
I mean, is there anything else
that could possibly go wrong?!
Sorry I asked.
You see?
That's why we needed
to take down
All those loose branches
in town, not spiffy 'em up.
But I --
Out of my way, missy!
Time's a-Wastin'.
Wait! Stop! Don't!
No waitin'! No stoppin'!
Doin'!
And that, my friends, is what
we call "gettin' her done."
Aah!
I tried to tell you it would
come crashing down in here!
Well, you should have
tried harder!
I'm mighty sorry, Twilight.
It's --
Well, it's not okay.
There's a giant tree branch
in the middle of my bedroom!
And the book
doesn't say anything
About having a giant tree branch
at your slumber party --
Or at least I haven't found
that entry yet.
What in tarnation
are y'all doin' over there?!
Cleaning up this mess
somepony made!
Who was that again?
Oh, right -- That's you!
We got to do something!
Baking, bffs, brothers.
There's nothing in here
about branches.
Rarity, for pony's sake,
stop sweatin' the small stuff
And help me get rid
of this thing!
I said hustle over here
and help me!
Look...i'm sorry,
all right?
What was that?
I said, "i'm sorry"!
I should have
listened to you
When you noticed where this here
branch would end up.
Your annoyin' attention
to detail
Would have saved us
from this whole mess.
But right now, you need to stop
bein' so dang fussy,
Pickin' up
all those little things,
And help me move
the one big thing in here
That actually matters!
Please!
Uh, uh,
but I'll get all icky.
Consarn it!
What the -- You --
I mean, yes,
Ickiness is often a side effect
of hard work.
But y'all need
to get over it
On account of I just can't
fix this mess I made myself.
I need your help.
Ohh.
Let's do this!
Well, they do have a section
about backyard slumber parties.
Is that what we're doing
right now?
Does this count
as camping?
Ohh.
I look awful.
Better?
Thanks.
Ooh, pretty.
Where did these come from?
They're not in the book,
either.
Is it bigger than a barn?
Nope.
Is it smaller
than a saddle?
no.
Only 3 of your 20 questions
left.
We're never gonna guess
what you're thinkin' of.
It could be anything.
Are we getting warmer?
Why?
Is it too cold in here for you?
I can turn up the heat.
She means, are we gettin'
any closer with our guesses?
Oh! No.
And that technically counted
as a question,
So only two more left.
Is it...
a 6-Legged pony
with a purple, polka-Dotted mane
And shootin' stars
comin' out of its eyes...
who flies through the air
all over the world
To hide magic,
sparkly eggs?
That's it!
It is?
No.
It's that.
But it was just so nice to see
you two finally getting along,
I wanted you to be able
to win together.
See?
We could have been having fun
like this all along.
If only somepony
hadn't been so persnickety.
Well, maybe she wouldn't
have been
If somepony else
hadn't been so sloppy.
Sorry for bein'
such a pain in the patootie.
Oh, no.
I'm sure I was much worse.
That's kind of you to say,
but I'm the one who's sorry.
Oh, I'm much more sorry
than you are.
Are not.
Are too.
I declare my first slumber party
a success.
Yeah!
Have fun -- Check.
Now take two steps
to your left.
Uh, no, my left.
Well, which is it?
Whoa!
That mess is your fault,
not mine.
Sorry.
"Dear princess Celestia,
it's hard to believe
"That two ponies who seem
to have so little in common
"Could ever get along.
"But I found out
that if you embrace
"Each other's differences,
you just might be surprised
To discover a way to be friends
after all."
So...
who's up for another
slumber party tomorrow night?
How about a week from thursday?
Ooh, how about two weeks
from saturday?
A month from now?