[ Rainbow Dash grunts ]
Whoo-hoo!
Ooh-whee!
Not a bad pitch
for a pony who works
with her head in the clouds.
Oh, yeah?
Think you can do better,
cowgirl?
I know I can.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Heh!
Looks like this pegasus can
pitch better than the workhorse.
The object of the game is
to get the closest to the stake.
All right, all right.
You got another throw there,
pony girl.
[ Crash! ]
Wow, rainbow.
[Chuckles]
You couldn't hit a barn door
with that kind of a throw.
Yeah, yeah.
I still have the closest throw,
apple smack.
Just try and beat it.
[ Neighs ]
Yee-haw!
It's a ringer.
That's how we do it
down here on the farm.
I lost.
Don't feel bad, rainbow.
It's all in good fun.
I hate losing.
Besides, you're
a mighty good athlete.
I'm just better.
[ Chuckles ]
All right, Applejack.
You think you're the top athlete
in all of Ponyville?
Well, I was gonna say
"in all of Equestria,"
But that might be
gilding the lily.
And I think I'm the top athlete,
so let's prove it.
Prove what?
I challenge you
to an ironpony competition.
A series
of athletic contests
to decide who's the best
once and for all.
You know what, Rainbow?
You're on.
* My Little Pony
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
* My Little Pony
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
This magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
[ Grunting ]
So, you two
are doing what, now?
An iron--
Ironpony competition!
See, we've set up
a bunch of events
To decide
which one of us is --
The most athletic
pony ever!
And I'm here to...
uh...I don't know.
Why is she here?
To be our judge
and keep score.
Right. Heh!
Somepony's got to record
my awesomeness
for the history books.
[ Grunting continues ]
Spike:
Hello, everypony!
and welcome to the first annual
Ironpony competition!
Uh, Spike,
who are you talking to?
Um...them!
[ Boing! Boing! Boing! ]
Let the games begin!
Yee-haw!
Ready, set, go!
[ Clock ticking ]
[ Gasps ]
Dag nabbit.
Twilight Sparkle:
Time, Spike?
17 seconds.
You're kidding.
That breaks my record
from last year's rodeo.
But you got a 5-seconds penalty
for nudging the barrel.
Nuts and shoes!
Still, that's 22 seconds.
Not too shabby.
Hey, don't be nervous.
Remember, it's all in good fun.
Now, get on up there.
Ready, set, go!
[ Clock ticking ]
Whew!
That was some fancy hoofwork
there, Rainbow.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Thanks, but I couldn't have been
as fast as you.
What was the time
on that, Spike?
18 seconds.
[ Both gasp ]
18 seconds?
Rainbow, are you sure you're not
secretly a rodeo pony?
Rainbow Dash
wins the barrel weave.
[ Fanfare plays ]
I can't believe I won.
Yeah, well, don't you
go getting used to it.
[ Bell dings,
cheers and applause ]
Mighty respectable.
But let me show you
how it's really done.
[ Grunts ]
[ Bell dings,
cheers and applause ]
Years
of apple-bucking.
[ Bell dings ]
[ Grunts ]
Whoo-hoo!
Yup!
Why me?
Go!
Whoa!
Whoa-oh!
Wh-o-o-oa!
Ouch.
Ready for
another pony ride?
No!
Go!
G-G-G-G-G-whoa!
Rainbow Dash
wins the bronco buck.
[ Bell dings ]
...and I lose.
[ All cheering ]
Whoa!
[ Grunts ]
How do I get roped
into these things?
[ Rainbow Dash grunting ]
Does this count?
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Bell dings ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Bell dings ]
Pbht!
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Bell dings ]
[ Both grunting ]
[ All gasp ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Bell dings ]
Fillies and gentlecolts,
at the halfway point, our
competitors are tied at 5 and 5.
Who are you
talking to?
Them!
[ Gasps ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
95.
96.
97.
98.
99...
100.
Yes!
[ Grunts ]
[ Bell dings ]
Be a good sport,
Applejack.
[ Screech! ]
[ Bell dings ]
[ Clucking ]
[ Chirping ]
[ Gasps ]
All right, you two,
this is the final event.
Give it all you've got.
Looks like the workhorse might
come out ahead in this one.
[ Muffled ]
That's not fair.
You can't use your wings
to help you win.
Huh?
You're cheating.
I can't understand you
with that rope in your mouth.
I said --
Uh-oh.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Bell dinging ]
Whoo-hoo!
I win by a landslide.
Or mudslide, in your case.
[ Laughs ]
I am the ironpony!
Only 'cause
you cheated!
What?!
You used your wing power
To help you win
over half those contests.
Sounds like
sour apples to me.
Are you saying
you didn't use your wings?
Well, no, but you never said
I couldn't use my wings.
I didn't think I needed
to tell you to play fair.
I still would have won
even without my wings.
Ha! Prove it!
Gladly! How?
Tomorrow's the annual
Running of the Leaves.
I challenge you
to race me in it.
Ha! Easy-shmeasy.
Hold on!
There is one condition.
The point is to run,
so no wings allowed.
No wings?
Aah!
No problem.
Pbht!
[ Both laugh ]
Twilight, hurry up.
We're gonna be late
for the race.
Why are you so excited
about the race?
It's only for ponies.
Yeah, but I'm hoping
I can be the announcer again.
Just listen.
Fillies and gentlecolts,
welcome to the annual
Running of the --
Pinkie Pie:
Welcome to the annual
Running of the Leaves!
This is Pinkie Pie,
Your official
"puh-ie-in-the-sky" announcer.
Sorry, Spike, I guess
that job's already taken.
As everypony knows, the run
is a very important tradition,
for without it,
the autumn leaves of Equestria
would never fall.
So get ready, ponies.
The Running of the Leaves
will begin in five minutes.
[ Applejack grunting ]
Pardon me! Excuse me!
Make way for the ironpony!
The iron phony,
you mean.
So, Applejack,
you ready to win...
second place?
I'm ready to run
a good, clean race.
Yeah, yeah.
You are not
allowed to use your wings.
I can win this race with
both wings tied behind my back.
[ Grunting ]
Trussed up like a turkey --
Well, a turkey
who can't fly, that is.
Very funny.
At least now we know
we're racing fair and square.
Pinkie Pie: Racers,
please take your positions!
Um, Pinkie Pie?
Hey, Spike! What's up?
Oh, wait -- It's me!
I'm up! [ Laughs ]
Uh, yeah, uh,
I know you're doing the
announcing today and stuff,
and I'm sure you're gonna do
a great job and all,
but I was just
wondering...
What?
Uh, forget it.
Spike, would you like to be
my co-reporter?
We could comment
on the action together.
We could?
Climb on up.
[ Tinkling ]
Twilight?
What in tarnation
are you doing up here?
I'm racing.
[ Laughing ]
Good one, Twilight.
I'm not joking.
What?!
You're not an athlete.
You're an --
Well, you're an egghead.
I am not an egghead.
I am well-read.
Egghead.
[ Chuckles ]
But h-have you ever
run a race?
Well, no. But I do know
a lot about running.
And you
know this from...
Books. I've read
several on the subject.
[ Laughing ]
What'd you read --
"The Egghead's Guide
to Running"?
[ Sighs ]
Did you stretch out
your eye muscles to warm up?
[ Laughing ]
Get it?
Eye muscles?
Scoff if you must,
Rainbow,
But the Running of the Leaves
is a Ponyville tradition.
And since
I'm here to learn,
I've decided I should
experience it myself.
Well, I think
that's just dandy, Twilight.
Good luck.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
See you
at the finish line...
tomorrow!
[ Both laughing ]
All right, ponies.
Are you ready?
Get set...
[ bell rings ]
And they're off!
Welcome
to the official coverage
of the Running
of the Leaves.
You know, Spike,
despite its name,
the leaves don't do
any of the actual running.
No, that's left
to my little ponies.
Why, yes, Pinkie.
It's the running
of the ponies
that causes
the leaves to fall.
Oh, those
lazy, lazy leaves.
But this year, the run is about
more than the weather.
It's about
the race to the finish
and the two runners
who want to win it --
Applejack
and Rainbow Dash.
You know, Pinkie,
these two ponies
have a bit of a grudge match
they're trying to settle,
trying to prove
who's the most athletic.
Yes, and "grudge"
rhymes with "fudge."
Yes, it...does.
What?
And I like fudge,
but if I eat too much fudge,
I get a pudge,
and then I can't budge.
So, no fudge?
Uh, no, thanks.
I had a big breakfast.
Let's check in with
our two competitive ponies,
Applejack
and Rainbow Dash.
Having come
fast out of the gate,
Applejack
and Rainbow Dash
are evenly matched,
running neck and neck.
But what's this?
Applejack is making a move.
She's now ahead
by a nose.
But Rainbow Dash
won't let Applejack have it
and takes the lead.
She's ahead
by half a nose.
Or maybe
three-quarters of a nose!
No, about
63.7% of a nose!
...roughly speaking.
Applejack sees this move
and plunges forth
with her strong, workhorse legs,
leaping ahead by 350 noses!
Not so easy
without wings, is it?
Come on, Rainbow.
Show 'em a little dash.
H-hold your horses,
Pinkie.
Rainbow Dash is catching up
to front-runner Applejack.
Pinkie Pie:
What an upset!
I thought Applejack
had this in the bag.
You didn't think i
was gonna let you off
that easy, did you?
Whoa!
[ Panting ]
I don't believe it.
I know.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Not the scenery,
Twilight.
Rainbow Dash
just tripped me.
She did not.
She did, too!
And if you slowed down
and looked
where you're going, like me,
you'd see that you tripped
over a rock.
What?
Oh, hayseed!
Now I've got a lot of ground
to make up to catch Rainbow.
Just be careful!
[ Squirrel chitters ]
See you
at the finish line!
Spike:
I don't believe it!
After a huge setback,
Applejack is back
at the front of the pack.
She's the head of the pack,
all right,
the pick of the litter,
the cat's pajamas!
Oh, wait.
Why would Applejack take
some poor kitty's P.J.s?
That's not
very sporting of her.
Okay...
Let's get back
to the race.
Not so fast, Applejack!
This race isn't over yet!
It is for you. Heh!
Whoa!
I don't believe it!
Applejack tripped me!
Twilight Sparkle:
Don't you ponies
ever look
where you're going?
You tripped
on a stump. See?
Oh, I see.
A big cheater is what I see.
Rainbow, Applejack
would never cheat.
It was just an accident.
Sure it was.
I mean, yeah.
I'm sure it was.
Remember, Rainbow,
this is just a game.
Yes, but the rules
have changed.
And two can play
at that game.
Welcome back, Ponyvillians.
It's me -- Pinkie Pie.
And Spike.
Looks like Rainbow's
doing her best to catch up.
I'm not sure how
"ketchup" is gonna help
her in this contest.
Now, in a
hot-dog-eating contest,
It can make them doggies
nice and slippery.
But personally,
I prefer mustard.
How about you, Spike?
Uh...I like pickles?
And...it looks like
Applejack has found herself
in quite a pickle,
as Rainbow overtakes her.
Look, ma. No wings.
Spike: As the racers enter
Equestria's Whitetail Wood,
Rainbow Dash
is back in the lead.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Grunts ]
Hey! Rainbow!
Pbht!
[ Gasps ]
Why, that little cheater
did that on purpose!
It's on!
Nice one, Rainbow.
Later!
Argh!
[ Gasps ]
A-a-a-ah!
[ Laughing ]
[ Twilight Sparkle gasping ]
Oh, my. Whitetail Wood
is just lovely.
Hey, Rainbow.
Shouldn't you be up ahead?
[ Laughs ]
I'm sure to win now.
Except that all the other racers
just passed you.
Oh, horse apples.
See ya!
Applejack,
what are you doing up here?
Spike: There aren't even
any trees.
I know, but the signs
pointed this way.
Rainbow!
Mind giving me a lift?
[ Gasps ]
What the hay?
You said no flying!
No, I said no wings.
Pinkie Pie: I must say, Spike,
that this has been
The most interesting
Running of the Leaves
in Equestria history.
Or the most interesting
announcing.
But it isn't the running
that's been fascinating --
It's the
lack of running.
[ Grunting ]
Whaa!
[ Snap! ]
Wh-o-o-oa!
Whoa!
[ Both shouting ]
Twilight Sparkle:
Forgive me, girls.
I know I'm not an athlete,
But shouldn't
the Running of the Leaves
actually involve...
running?
You know,
I think Twilight's right.
You do?
Yeah.
If you want to beat me,
you better...
run!
Pinkie Pie: once again,
Rainbow Dash and Applejack
are neck and neck,
jockeying for position.
Applejack inches ahead.
Now it's Rainbow.
It's Applejack.
It's Rainbow Dash.
It's Applejack!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Spike:
Oh, no, she didn't!
Oh, yes, she did!
Cut it out!
No, you cut it out!
You started it.
And now
I'm gonna finish it.
Oh, no, you won't!
[ Chomp! ]
Oh, yes, I will!
That's it!
All bets are off!
Oh, no, you don't!
Hey! Quit it!
No! Uhh!
It's Applejack!
It's Rainbow Dash!
[ Crash! ]
[ Panting ]
I won!
No! I won!
Spike: You tied!
Tied?
For first?
For last!
Last?!
Then who won?
You?!
Oh, no, but I did get 5th place,
which is rather good,
considering
I've never run a race before.
What?
How is that
even possible?
You ran so slow
and looked at the scenery!
Exactly. I paced myself,
just like my book said.
Then at the end, when all
the other ponies were worn out,
I sprinted to the finish.
I don't believe it.
Twilight beat us!
Well, with
all your horsing around,
it was quite easy.
You're right,
Twilight.
Our behavior
was just terrible.
We weren't
very good sports.
Princess Celestia:
Sounds to me
like an important lesson
was learned.
Princess Celestia?!
What are you
doing here?
Fall is one of my
favorite seasons,
So I came to celebrate
the Running of the Leaves.
I'm sorry
you had to see us
being such poor sports,
princess.
That's all right,
Applejack.
Anypony can get swept up in
the excitement of competition.
It's important to remember
that the friendship
is always more important
that the competition.
Exactly, Twilight.
Now, unfortunately,
because the two of you
were busy tricking each other
instead of
shaking down leaves,
many of the lovely trees
in Equestria are still covered.
Why, princess, I bet
we can knock those leaves down
for you lickety-split.
What do you say, friend?
Want to go for another run?
I'd love
to stretch my legs.
* My Little Pony
* Friends