Where
are you taking us?
We're almost there, youngins!
I've never been here
before.
Ouch!
Oh, sorry.
Are we there yet?
There? Where?
What?
I don't even know
what we're doing!
Here we are!
What are we
looking at?
I have no idea.
What is
that thing?
Cutie Mark Crusaders,
welcome to your new clubhouse!
Well, don't thank me
all at once.
This was my clubhouse
when I was your age.
Sure, it hasn't been used
in a while,
But it's empty
And on a secluded, private
part of the farm.
And it's all yours.
It just needs
a little, uh, TLC.
TLC as in "Tender Loving Care"
or "Totally Lost Cause"?
Applejack,
we're supposed to turn this
Into
our new clubhouse?
Well, maybe y'all will get
your cutie marks
When you discover
your talent for -- Aah!
Ugh.
House cleaning?
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Not so fast!
Whoa!
Hey, Scootaloo.
Back already?
You're amazing
on that scooter.
Thanks.
Wow, Apple Bloom.
You did all of this?
Yep.
I fixed the broken shutters,
sanded off the splinters,
Rebuilt the roof, painted.
That's so cool!
What's Sweetie Belle
up to?
* we are
the Cutie Mark Crusaders *
* never stop the journey
There you are, Sweetie Belle!
See?
I told you we could find her
By following
her totally awesome voice.
What's that sweet tune
you're singing?
Oh. I was just working on our
new Cutie Mark Crusaders
theme song.
Cool!
Teach us?
Well, I've only come up
with one part, but, okay!
* they all say
that you will get your mark *
* when the time
is really right *
* and you know just
what you're supposed to do *
* and your talent
comes to light! *
Well, I'll be,
Cutie Mark Crusaders.
You've done one fine job
with this place.
So, what's next?
Well, now that we have
a real-Life clubhouse...
and a map
of Ponyville...
and a Cutie Mark Crusaders
theme song...
theme song?
We're gonna go out in the world
And discover our talents!
A new adventure!
And earn
our cutie marks!
We'll leave no stone unturned!
No mountain unclimbed!
No meal uncooked!
No song unlearned!
Well, okay, then!
sounds like you have a plan.
I got to, uh,
leave no apple unpicked.
See y'all later.
Are we ready to get
our cutie marks, ponies?
Ready!
I had nothing to do
with this.
What is going on here?
Hmm.
Well, we sure aren't getting
our cutie marks
For being librarians.
Huh.
I should think not.
What?
Girls, I think you're going
about this the wrong way.
Instead of trying to do things
In areas
you're not familiar with,
Why not try doing things
in areas that you already like?
And I have the perfect place
to start.
Showcase your talents...
for all to see.
Perform in the Ponyville
school talent show!
There will be
all sorts of awards --
Best dramatic performance,
best comedy act, best magic act.
Surely you can find
your talent.
This would be the perfect place
to discover our talents!
Juggling!
Acting!
Magic tricks!
Square dancing!
Tight-Rope walking!
Tiger taming!
My little ponies,
you're missing the point.
Think about the things
you already enjoy doing.
Think about
what you're already good at.
Sure.
We could do that.
Yeah, sure we can.
Well, whatever we do,
we'll do it as...
the Cutie Mark Crusaders!
Sweetie Belle!
I told you not to touch
my things!
Come back
with my supplies!
We're just borrowing them
for the talent show.
Don't worry, sis!
I promise
we'll bring them back!
Thanks, mr. Breezy.
We're return the fan to you
real soon.
What do we need
this fan for?
Trust me on this one.
Okay, so that's six wooden
planks, 4x8 plywood,
A box of nails, four cans
of paint, and four brushes.
Anything else?
Yeah.
Instructions on how to use
six wooden planks,
4x8 plywood, a box of nails,
four cans of paint,
And four brushes.
Whoa!
"Ghosts, goblins,
and ghoulish figures"?
Good heavens, girls.
What do you need
a book like this for?
You'll see.
Thanks, Twilight.
We'll give it back as soon
as we're done with it!
What do you think
they're up to?
I have no idea,
And I don't know if I should be
excited or scared to find out.
I'm glad
we're doing this as a team.
Me too!
Um, so,
what are we doing again?
A super, awesome, dramatic song
for the talent show, of course.
Right!
With super-Cool scenery
and amazing costumes!
And mind-Blowing
dance moves.
This is gonna be
so amazing.
Sweetie Belle, I think
you should be the singer.
What?
No way I'm singing
in front of a crowd.
Twilight said to do something
we like to do,
And I'd like to be
like my big sister,
And she's a designer.
Fine, then. You can do
the costumes and the scenery.
Mm-Hmm.
And, Scootaloo, you're great
at maneuvers on your scooter,
So you should do
the choreography.
You know,
all those dance moves.
Nah.
I'd rather sing
a wicked rock ballad.
Why don't you come up with the
dance routine, Apple Bloom?
Hmm.
I'm not much of a dancer,
but I do like kung fu!
That's kind of like dancing!
Hyah! Hah!
Hah! Yah!
Then it's settled!
Let's get started!
One, two, three, oh!
Oh!
Ow, Apple Bloom!
What are you doing?
I feel like I have
four left feet.
I can't even spin right.
Don't be silly.
You just got to keep
your head forward
Until the very last minute,
like this.
See?
Easy peasy.
You just got to practice
a bunch, that's all.
Wow!
That does look easy!
Thanks!
Okay.
Let's try this again.
Oh! Ouch!
Ow!
I'm okay!
Keep practicing!
Will do!
* we fight the fight,
walk the walk *
* talk the talk, eat the, uh,
food like a celery stalk? *
Ugh!
I'll never come up
with anything!
Never, never, never!
Come back! Come back!
Dumb fabric.
Hey, scoot.
How's the song going?
Pbht!
Pbht?
Oh, my.
Sounds serious.
I'm just no good
at lyrics.
Coming up with words
is like...really hard.
Oh,
they can't be that bad.
"With our cutie marks
we'll rock Equestria.
We use our stomachs
to digestia"?
Um, well,
these are, um, good,
But how about
after "we fight the fight"...
* there is nothing
that we fear *
* we'll have to figure out
what we'll do next *
* till our cutie marks
are here *
Wow!
That's so awesome!
Did you just come up
with that now?
Yeah, kind of.
Thanks!
I'm totally using that.
Oh, no!
One, two, three, four, five?
Oh!
Ouch!
How's the spin
coming along?
I think I got to just stick
to punches and kicks.
You know
ponies only have four legs?
Unh.
I'll never be a designer
like my sister, Rarity.
Hey,
it's no big deal.
Why don't you use
the dress form?
It'll help you
with your patterns
And help you put all the pieces
in the right places.
Oh.
Is that what that's for?
Uh, maybe you should also clean
your paint brush
Between each color.
Oh, I was wondering why all
the colors looked like mud.
You're not using power tools,
are you?
The talent show's
just around the corner.
I wonder how the fillies
are doing.
Oh, sorry, Scootaloo!
That's okay.
Ugh!
Oops!
Sorry, Scootaloo.
Ouch!
Oh, my bad,
Sweetie Belle.
Let's sing
the chorus again.
Well, gosh.
Sure wasn't expecting that.
I think that sounded pretty good.
Me too.
You think we're ready?
Ready as we'll ever be.
Hey,
did you see us practicing?
Uh, yeah.
Well, how did we do?
How did we do?
Uh...
speechless!
See, girls?
I told you that's what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna leave them
speechless!
Yay!
Speechless is right.
And on the count
of three,
This rabbit
will disappear
And something tasty
will reappear in its place!
One, a-Two,
and a-Three!
Hey!
Where are they?
Snails,
where are the...
...carrots.
Snails!
Uh, how about a round of
applause for the S&S magic act?
And now for our next act,
We have Sunny Days
and Peachy Pie
Reciting their favorite poem
on roller skates!
Break a leg!
Sweetie Belle,
what a thing to say!
No, no, no.
You see, in the theater,
It's considered bad luck
to say "good luck,"
So you say
"break a leg" instead.
My little ponies,
how are you doing?
Nervous.
Don't worry.
You're gonna be amazing.
Remember -- Just stick
to what you know best.
I can't wait to hear you sing,
Sweetie Belle.
What does every pony
always think I'm gonna sing?
Actually, Twilight Sparkle,
I'm the main singer tonight.
Oh?
And I'm the main dancer.
Hyah!
Oh?
And I'm in charge of...
costumes?
And sets and props.
How'd you know?
Really, girls?
Are you sure?
Cutie Mark Crusaders,
you're on next.
Break a leg.
Break a le--
Ugh!
Uh, good luck!
* look here
are three little ponies *
* ready to sing
for this crowd *
* listen up
'cause here's our story *
* I'm gonna sing it very loud
* when you're
a younger pony *
* and your flank
is very bare *
* feels like the sun
will never come *
* when your cutie mark's
not there *
* so the three of us
fight the fight *
* there is nothing
that we fear *
* we'll have to figure out
what we'll do next *
* till our cutie marks
are here *
* we are
the Cutie Mark Crusaders *
* on a quest to find out
who we are *
* and we will never stop
the journey *
* not until we have
our cutie marks *
* they all say
that you'll get your mark *
* when the time
is really right *
* and you know just what
you're supposed to do *
* and your talent
comes to light *
* but it's not as easy
as it sounds *
* and that waiting's
hard to do *
* so we test our talents
everywhere *
* until our face is blue
* we are
the Cutie Mark Crusaders *
* on a quest to find out
who we are *
* and we will never stop
the journey *
* not until we have
our cutie marks *
* we are
the Cutie Mark Crusaders *
* on a quest to find out
who we are *
* and we will never stop
the journey *
* not until we have
our cutie marks *
Wow.
That did not go
as well as I expected.
I can't believe
they're laughing at us!
Was it that bad?
Back on stage, girls!
It's time for the awards!
Back on stage?
No.
They'll just laugh
some more!
Yeah.
What's the point?
Now, girls,
let's be good sports.
You made a great effort.
You should be proud.
Now, come on.
Let's hear it for all our
talented fillies and colts.
Our first award goes to...
Snip and Snails
for best magic act.
Hey!
My medal is shinier!
Well, mine's bigger!
Oh, yeah, well --
Well, mine, is, um, heavier?
The next award goes to
Sunny Days and Peachy Pie
For best dramatic performance.
And, finally, the last award
of the night goes to...
...the Cutie Mark Crusaders!
What?
For best comedy act!
Can you believe it?
We won!
I knew our act
was awesome!
You know
what would be the best?
If we won
and we got our cutie marks.
Congratulations, ponies.
Job well done.
Thanks, Twilight.
Hey.
You don't sound too excited.
We worked really hard
and won a prize,
But we still don't have
our cutie marks.
Which is the prize
we really wanted.
Oh, girls.
But we think
we know why.
Yes.
We know why.
Oh?
Tell me.
I'd love to make a special
report to the princess.
Well, maybe we were trying
too hard.
Yes?
And?
And instead of forcing ourselves
To do something
that's not meant for us...
yes? Yes?
We each should be embracing
our true talent.
And that is?
Comedy!
Apple Bloom,
you did it!
Did you see our award?
Weren't we funny?
One day.