* La la la la la la la la la
[ Squeaks ]
Thank you,
little squirrel.
But remember, these flowers
are for Princess Celestia.
Only the prettiest ones
will do.
[ Zip! ]
* La la la la
La la la la la *
[ Chortles ]
Aah!
[ Whoosh! ]
[ Sloop! ]
[ Chortles ]
Hello, little guy.
I've never seen
anything like you before.
[ Sniffing ]
Oh, are you hungry?
Here you go.
[ Creak! ]
[ Chomp! ]
[ Gasps ]
I guess
you were hungry.
[ Chortles ]
You're
the cutest thing ever!
I can't wait to show you
to my friends.
* My Little Pony
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
* My Little Pony
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
This magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
Twilight Sparkle:
Oh, hurry up, Spike.
This place
isn't gonna clean itself.
It also
didn't mess itself up.
Princess Celestia
will be here tomorrow!
I thought this was just
an unofficial, casual visit.
There's nothing casual
about a visit from royalty!
I want this place
to be spotless,
And you've barely made
a dent in the clutter!
Maybe you should...
start reading them...
one at a time!
Whoa! [ Groans ]
Everything's
got to be perfect.
No time
for fooling around!
You know, this would be
an awful lot easier
if there weren't
two of us here
getting under
each other's feet.
Great idea. You clean.
I'll go see how everyone else's
preparations are coming.
Well, maybe I should --
[ Groans ]
What happened
to the rest of her name?
We couldn't fit
it all in.
You can't hang a banner that
says "Welcome, Princess Celest."
Take it down,
and try again.
That looks perfect.
Keep up the good work.
Hello,
Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
How's
the banquet coming?
Uh, i-it would be coming
a little better i-if...
[ Slurp! ]
Pinkie!
What are you doing?!
Those sweets are supposed
to be for the princess!
I-I know.
That's why I'm tasting them.
Somepony
needs to make sure
that everything is tasty enough
to touch the royal tongue,
And I, Pinkie Pie, declare
that these treats
are fit for a king...
or a queen...
or a princess!
Twilight, Pinkie --
You won't believe!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, am I interrupting?
No, not at all.
Come on in,
and make yourself at home.
[ Chomp! ]
[ Ding! ]
What's going on,
Fluttershy?
You won't believe
what I found
at the edge
of the Everfree Forest.
Come on out, little guy.
It's okay.
[ All chortling ]
[ Gasps ] Three?
They're amazing.
What are they?
I'm not sure.
I'm also not sure where
these other two came from.
I'll take one
off your hooves.
I've never seen anything
so...adorable!
Besides, it'll be nice
to have a companion for Spike
So he won't bother me so much
while I'm studying.
Pinkie, do you want
the other one?
Ugh! A parasprite?!
Are you kidding?!
"Ugh"?
A para-what?
How could you
not like --
Ugh! Now I got to go find
a trombone!
A what?
A trombone. You know.
[ Imitates trombone ]
[ Sproing! ]
[ Sighs ]
Typical Pinkie.
[ Chortles ]
Stand still,
Rainbow Dash.
[ Grunts ] I can't!
[ Creak! ]
I need to fly!
This is way too boring for me.
Do you want to look nice
for Princess Celestia or not?
Wow!
Rarity, those outfits
are gorgeous!
[ Giggles ]
Thank you, Twilight.
Nice to know someone
appreciates my talents.
[ Groans ]
So boring!
[ Chortling ]
Huh?
What's that sound,
Twilight?
[ Chortles ]
[ Squeaks ]
Wow!
What are they?
The better question is,
where did they come from?
I only had one
a minute ago.
I-I'll take one!
Me too!
Oh, they're perfect!
Does anypony know
where I can find an accordion?!
[ All speaking gibberish ]
Gals, hello!
This is important!
[ Grunts ]
Thanks a lot!
[ Insects chirping, owl hoots ]
[ Tinkling ]
Oh, the decorations,
the banquet.
I really hope everything comes
together in time for tomorrow.
[ Both snoring ]
[ Yawns ]
What's there
to worry about?
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Snoring intensifies ]
Spike!
[ Whiffle! ]
Wake up!
What happened?!
Huh?
Aah!
What's going on?
[ Chortling ]
Where did they
come from?
I don't know.
The little guy got hungry
in the night,
So I gave him a snack,
But I have no idea
where these others came from.
[ Crash ]
Oh, no!
They're messing up
all my hard work!
The princess will be here
in a few hours!
[ Whiffle! ]
[ Tinkling! ]
Spike, help me round up
these little guys.
[ Grunting ]
What does it...
look like I'm...doing?
Aah! Aah!
[ Grunts ]
[ Whiffle! ]
I know. I know.
"Stop fooling around."
[ Snoring ]
[ Chortles ]
Huh?
Aaaaah!
[ Whiffle! ]
[ Grunting ]
Get off me!
[ Whiffle! ]
Aaah!
Not only are you adorable,
but you're also quite useful.
[ Chortles ]
[ Gags ]
Oh, are you okay?
Aah!
[ Gasps ] ew!
Gross, gross, gross!
No creature that behaves
so revoltingly
is allowed
in my boutique!
[ Gagging ]
Aah!
Look, Rarity, applejack
lent me a harmonica!
[ Plays harmonica ]
Isn't that great?
[ Chortling ]
[ Gasps ]
And not a moment too soon!
[ Grunts ] Pinkie,
I'm a little busy right now.
And I'm not?
Do you know how many more
instruments I've got to find?
A lot!
That's how many!
Now, if we split the list
between us,
We might just make it
in time.
Please, Pinkie,
I don't have time
for some silly
scavenger hunt.
I've got
a real problem.
You've got a real problem,
all right,
and a banjo
is the only answer!
[ Gasps ]
I see we're having
the same problem.
Rainbow Dash: Ditto!
[ Whip! ]
Fluttershy knows everything
about animals.
I'm sure
she can tell us
How to stop them
from multiplying.
[ Chortling ]
Or not.
Do something, Fluttershy!
Can't you control them?
I've tried
everything I know.
begging and pleading
And beseeching
and asking politely and --
[ Grunts ]
[ Fanfare ]
[ Gasps ] Aah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
If we can't get them
under control
before the princess arrives,
it'll be total disaster!
[ Gags ]
Ew!
If you ask me,
it's already a total disaster.
Here's all those apples
you wanted, Fluttershy,
But I still can't figure
why you need so many.
[ Buzz! ]
Hey!
What do we do?
[ Gasps ] I got it!
Nopony can herd like applejack.
Yeah! We can drive them
back into the forest!
I'll rassle them up,
but I'll need
everypony's help to do it.
Twilight, you and Rarity
wait over there.
I'll herd
the little critters
straight at you,
like a funnel.
Rainbow Dash, you and Fluttershy
stay on top of them.
Don't let them
fly away.
Aye, aye!
Yee-haw!
[ Chortling ]
[ All shriek ]
All right, y'all.
Here goes nothin'!
Look out, Rarity!
That one's fixin' to get away!
Keep a lid on them,
Rainbow Dash!
Hold on, girls!
We're almost there!
Pinkie!
Twilight,
we don't have much time!
You're telling me!
The princess could arrive
at any moment!
Exactly!
That's why I need you gals
to drop what you're doing
And help me find
some maracas!
Maracas?
Pinkie, we've got
much bigger problems
than missing maracas.
[ Gasps ] You're right!
Getting a tuba has to be
our number-one goal!
Follow me!
[ Patter! ]
I said "follow me!"
Pinkie Pie,
you are so random.
And you are all
so stubborn!
Forget her, ladies.
Focus!
Head them up
and move them out!
All right!
[ Bonk! ]
Ouch.
We did it!
Nice work, Applejack.
Couldn't have done it
without y'all.
Now, let's get back
and clean up the mess they made
before
the princess arrives.
Okay. Everyone knows
what to do, right?
We got to work extra hard
to make up for lost time.
[ Gasps ]
Ooh!
Where did they
come from?!
Well, I may have kept just one.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Pop! ]
I couldn't help myself.
They're just...so...cute.
We don't have time to keep
rounding up these things!
What do we do now?
We call in
the weather patrol!
[ Grunts ]
Aah!
Time to take out
the adorable trash.
Yaaaaa!
[ Zip! ]
[ Whoosh! ]
Way to go,
Rainbow Dash!
Looks like
our problems are solved!
They will be
with these cymbals!
[ Cymbals crashing ]
Hey!
Give me those back!
[ Zip! Zip! ]
Whoa! Aah!
[ Shing! ]
Aah! Aah!
Whoa!
I can't hold it!
She's breaking up!
[ Whoosh! ]
Pinkie Pie,
what have you done?
I've lost
a brand-new pair of cymbals!
That's what I've done!
Will you forget about your silly
instruments for one second?
You're ruining our efforts
to save Ponyville!
Me?! Ruin?!
I'm not the ruiner!
I'm the ruinee!
Or is it "ruiness"?
"Ruinette"?
Come on, girls. There's
no reasonin' with that one.
She's a few apples
short of a bushel.
Hey!
I'm trying to tell
you all
that the ruining
is on the other hoof!
If you'd just slow down
and listen to me!
[ Chortling ]
[ Creak! Whip! ]
[ Chomp! Chomp! ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Buzz! ]
What do we do?
They're eating
all the food in town.
My apples!
We've got to do
something.
[ Gasps ] I got it!
I'll cast a spell to make them
stop eating all the food!
[ Tinkling! ]
[ Plink! ]
Look! Tambourines!
If you could all just --
Aaaah!
[ Tambourines rattle ]
[ Sniffs ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Chortles ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Creak! Chomp! ]
[ Buzz! ]
[ Chuckles ]
Hey. It worked.
They're not eating
the food anymore.
Oh, no!
If they get inside my store...
Everypony
for herself!
[ Zip! ]
My outfits!
Go on! Shoo!
Get out! Naughty! Naughty!
[ Gags ]
Aaah!
Pinkie Pie:
I'll save you!
[ Blows horn ]
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
No woodland creature's gonna eat
the Apple Family's crop!
Brace yourselves, y'all!
Here they come!
[ Buzz! ]
[ Gasps ]
Didn't see
that one coming.
Help!
[ Gasps ]
They're eating the words!
Help.
[ Whiffle! ]
[ Grunts ]
Have you gone mad?
Zecora, these little guys
are devouring Ponyville,
and the princess
is on her way!
Can you help us,
please?
Oh, monster
of so little size.
Is that a parasprite
before my eyes?
I don't know! Is it?!
Tales of crops
and harvests consumed.
If these creatures
are in Ponyville...
[ gags ]
You're doomed.
[ Gulps ]
Oh, no!
Here she comes!
[ Ponies screaming ]
Aaah!
Okay, here's the plan.
Rainbow Dash, you distract them.
Aaaaaaah!
Good.
Everyone else,
we need to build
an exact copy of ponyville
right over there.
We've got
less than a minute!
[ Thud ]
Zecora was right.
We're doomed.
[ Horn music plays ]
Oh, no. The princess'
procession is here.
It's all over!
[ Squeak! ]
Pinkie, we're in
the middle of a crisis here.
This is no time
for your...
nonsense?
[ Music continues ]
[ Plink! Plink! Plink! Plink! ]
Look!
[ Pop! Pop! Pop! ]
Twilight Sparkle,
my prized pupil.
Hello, princess.
So lovely to see you again,
as well as your friends.
[ Cymbals crash ]
[ Music continues ]
[ Plink! Plink! Plink! Plink! ]
So [chuckles]
how was the trip?
Hit much traffic?
[ Gasps ]
What is this?
[ Chortles ]
[ Chuckles ]
These creatures are adorable.
They're not
that adorable.
I'm terribly honored
that you and the good citizens
of Ponyville
have organized a parade
in honor of my visit.
Parade?
Oh, yes! The parade!
Unfortunately, that visit
is going to have to wait
for another time.
I'm afraid an emergency
has come up in fillydelphia.
Apparently there's been
some sort of infestation.
An...infestation?
Yes.
A swarm of incredibly
bothersome creatures
has invaded the poor town.
I'm sorry, Twilight,
to have to put you all
through so much trouble.
Trouble? [ Chuckles ]
What trouble?
Before I have to go,
would you care to give me
your latest report on the magic
of friendship in person?
My...report?
Haven't you learned
anything about friendship?
[ Plink! Plink! Plink! Plink! ]
[ Music continues ]
Actually, I have.
I've learned that sometimes
the solution to your problems
can come from
where you least expect it.
It's a good idea to stop
and listen to your friends'
opinions and perspectives.
[ Cymbals crash ]
Even when they don't always
seem to make sense.
I'm so proud of you,
Twilight Sparkle,
and I'm very impressed
with your friends, as well.
It sounds like
you're all learning
so much from each other.
Thank you, princess.
[ Music continues ]
[ Music stops ]
Hey, what happened
to the princess?
Emergency
in fillydelphia.
Some sort of...
infestation.
Oh, no! Have they got
parasprites, too?
Well --
Have tuba, will travel.
I think the princess
can handle it.
So, you knew
what those critters were
all along,
huh, Pinkie Pie?
Well, duh!
Why do you think
I was so frantic
to get my hooves
on all these instruments?
I tried to tell you.
We know, Pinkie Pie, and
we're sorry we didn't listen.
[ All apologizing ]
You're a great friend,
even if we don't always
understand you.
Thanks, guys.
You're all
great friends, too,
Even when
I don't understand me.
You saved my reputation
with Princess Celestia.
And, more importantly,
you saved Ponyville.
Or not.
[ Wah-wah-wah-wah! ]
* My Little Pony
* Friends