[ Grunting ]
[ Tinkling ]
[ Poof! ]
[ Grunting continues ]
Eyes over here, Spike.
Uh, sorry.
For this to work,
it's crucial
we keep our concentration
totally on the --
[ Poof! Strike! ]
Ugh!
[ Tweet! ]
Spike...
This magic needs our full
attention to make it happen.
There's no other way.
I can't help it!
[ Zip! Zip! Boing! ]
Look!
[ Zip! ]
[ Patter! ]
[ Zip! Blink! ]
[ Sloop! Zip! ]
[ Zip! ]
[ Creak! ]
[ Sighs ]
Never mind her.
She's just being
Pinkie Pie.
Super extra Pinkie Pie
today.
[ Pitter! ]
[ Rattle! ]
[ Sighs ]
Twitchy-twitch,
a-twitch-a-twitch!
Pinkie Pie, what in the wide,
wide world of Equestria
are you up to?
Oh, it's my tail!
It's my tail!
It's a-twitch-a-twitchin'!
And you know
what that means.
Actually, Pinkie,
I haven't the slightest idea.
The twitching means
my Pinkie sense is telling me
that stuff's
gonna start falling!
You two
better duck for cover!
Oh, Pinkie,
it's not gonna rain.
Why, there's barely even
a cloud in the -- Ugh!
[ Croaks ]
He just said, "nice catch"
in frog.
[ Croaks ]
* My Little Pony
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
* My Little Pony
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
This magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
[ Croaks ]
Fluttershy:
Oh, I'm so, so sorry.
Are you okay,
Twilight Sparkle?
I just couldn't stand to see the
pond getting so overpopulated,
what with the frogs all hopping
into each other and all,
so I decided to fly
as many as I can
on over to Froggy Bottom Bog.
Of course you did.
[ Garbled ] Bye-bye!
Um, Twilight,
you got a little something
on your face there.
Oh, really?
Did your Pinkie sense
tell you that, too?
Nah, I could just see it.
* La-la-la la-la
La-la-la *
Ptoo!
[ Boing! ]
Come on, Spike.
Let's continue
our practice session
where there's a little less
commotion.
Wow!
That was amazing!
Pinkie Pie predicted
something would fall,
and it did!
Oh, come on.
She said
something would fall,
and a frog just happened to fall
right around the same time --
a coincidence --
nothing else to it.
My tail! My tail!
[ Rattle! ]
Twitch-a-twitch!
Something else
is gonna fall!
Oh, Pinkie, please.
Nothing else
is gonna fa-a-a-ll!
Unh!
[ Tweet! ]
Oh, no!
Twilight fell!
Is it safe
to go help her?
It's okay.
My tail stopped twitching.
[ Boing! ]
* La-la-la la-la,
La-la-la la-la-la *
[ Groans ]
[ Laughs ]
That was amazing!
Oh, please.
Applejack:
Uh, Twilight,
Why are you hanging out
in a ditch?
Because Pinkie Pie
predicted it.
Honestly, Spike,
she did not.
Two coincidences in a row
like this may be unlikely,
but it's still
easier to believe
than twitchy tails
that predict the future.
[ Gasps ]
Twitchy tail?
Pinkie sense?
Ohh!
Ugh!
Don't worry.
It's safe.
The prediction
already came true.
Oh, wait.
Don't tell me you believe
in this stuff, too.
I know it doesn't make
much sense,
but those of us who have been
in Ponyville awhile
have learned over time
that if Pinkie's a-twitchin',
you better listen.
My ears are flopping!
Aah!
What does that mean?!
I'll start a bath
for you.
Huh?
[ Laughs ]
A bath?
This thing keeps on getting
more ridiculous by the minute.
[ Splash! ]
Ugh!
[ Blows ]
So, basically,
it works like this --
I get different little,
miggly feelings,
and they mean
different things.
Like, when my back gets itchy,
it means it's my lucky day.
And when my knee
gets pinchy,
that means something scary's
about to happen.
Is your knee
pinchy now?
No, but my shoulder's
achy.
That means there's an alligator
in the tub.
Oh!
Aah!
How come your knee
didn't get pinchy?!
That isn't just scary --
it's downright dangerous!
No, it's not, silly.
This is my pet alligator
gummy.
He's got no teeth, see?
[ Laughs ]
Okay, okay.
I get it.
Well, I still
don't believe
all this
special-powers stuff.
It's just a bunch
of mumbo-jumbo.
What's not to believe?
You do magic.
What's the difference?
Huge.
For one thing...
[ Clears throat ]
...Magic is something
you study and practice.
It only happens
when you decide to do it,
and it's meant
to make something specific
that you choose to happen
happen.
With you, it -- it makes
no sense at all!
That's so not true,
Twilight.
Sometimes it's a bunch
of random things
happening to my body
at random times
that supposedly predict
the future.
I call 'em "combos."
Combos?
Sure.
You know, like ear flop,
then knee twitch,
then eye flutter --
that means the sky
is about to be graced
with a beautiful rainbow.
Yeah, sure.
Uh-oh.
I feel a combo
coming on.
Ear flop, eye flutter,
knee twitch.
[ Grunts ]
[ Beep! Beep! Beep! ]
[ Groans ]
You said that combo
meant beautiful rainbow.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no.
You're thinking of
an ear flop,
then knee twitch,
then eye flutter.
This was an ear flop,
then eye flutter,
then knee twitch.
That usually means
"look out for opening doors."
Are you okay?
I don't believe this.
You don't believe
because you don't understand.
Hmm.
[ Bubbling ]
[ Warbling ]
[ Tinkling ]
Okay. Now, when you get
another twitch,
we'll have all kinds
of scientific information.
Okey-dokey-lokey!
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Any twitches yet?
Nopey-dopey.
[ Music resumes ]
Now? Anything?
Wait! Hold on!
[ Music resumes ]
Uh, no.
Are you kidding me?
After a whole day
of nonstop twitching,
now that I've got you
all hooked up,
you're not getting
a single one?!
I don't control it.
They just come and go.
That makes no sense!
Sometimes you just have to
believe in things,
even when you can't
figure them out.
I will not believe in anything
I cannot explain.
Wait. Hold on.
I'm feeling something.
Oh, my gosh!
What?
What is it?!
[ Rumble! ]
It's my tummy!
That usually means I'm hungry.
Let's eat!
Ugh!!
You know what?
[ Machine powers down ]
Just forget it.
I don't need to know
if this is real or not.
I don't need to understand it.
I don't even care!
[ Zip! ]
Okey-dokey-lokey!
[ Boing! Boing! Boing! ]
[ Gasps ]
Uh-oh.
[ Shudders ]
Pinkie,
have you seen Twilight?
Uh-huh.
[ Creak! ]
Twilight, what are you doing
back there?
[ Groans ]
Did you two plan this?
Plan what?
Ugh!
This is ridiculous!
This can't be happening!
This makes no sense!
I have to figure this out.
[ Croaks ]
[ Frogs croaking ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Sniff! ]
Mmm!
[ Laughing ]
[ Tribal music plays ]
[ Boing! Boing! Boing! Boing! ]
[ Tinkling ]
Spike: Twilight?
Aah!
Whoa-oh!
Honestly, Spike,
don't you know better
than to sneak up
on ponies?
Oh, sorry.
But, um, well,
isn't that
what you're doing?
[ Gasps ]
No.
[ Grunts ]
I'm doing
scientific research.
I'm observing Pinkie Pie --
scientific name,
Pinkius Pieacus --
in its natural habitat.
Pinkius who-acus?
Aah!
There's something fishy
going on
with the whole
twitchy-prediction thing,
and I'm getting to the bottom
of it, so shh!
Come on.
Pinkius Pieacus
is on the move.
[ Humming ]
Hmm.
Itchy nose.
[ Gasps ]
[ Zip! ]
Aha!
That makes no sense.
See? She's hiding
like something's about
to fall from the sky,
but a twitchy tail
means something's gonna fall
from the sky,
not an itchy nose.
[ Buzzing ]
[ Gasps ]
This proves,
perhaps conclusively,
That --
Aah!
Spike,
where are you going?
I'm trying to teach you
the value of scientific obser--
Ow!
Ouch! Ow! Ohh!
[ Cows mooing ]
What's she doing now?
[ Sniff! ]
Smelling a flower.
Holy guacamole!
I wonder what that means!
Probably that the flower
smells good.
Wait.
I'm getting something.
Ear flop...
eye flutter...
knee twitch.
Hold on.
She told me that's the combo
that says,
"watch out
for opening doors."
[ Scoffs ]
You really, really believe
this stuff, don't you?
Here.
Let me show you
there's nothing to be afraid of.
You see?
I promise you, there's nothing
to fear from that --
Whoa!
Ow! Ow! Ohh! Ow!
[ Clang! Crash! Clang! Thud! ]
Applejack: Twilight! You came
to visit my new apple cellar.
How nice.
Twi? You okay?
Uh, Twi?
Here. Let me help you.
Okay.
Take this down.
[ Rattle! ]
Twitchy tail.
Twitchy tail?
[ Gasps ]
Twitchy tail!
Ohh! Hush, Spike.
We can't let Pinkie know
we're here, remember?
Something's gonna fall!
Run for your lives!
Whoa-oh-oh!
Ohh, Spike, honestly.
You're overreacti--
[ Clank! Clang! Crash! ]
Ugh!
[ Plong! ]
Ohh!
[ Gasps ]
[ Humming ]
Hey, Applejack.
What you doing?
Taking more apples
to my new apple cellar.
How about you, Pinkie?
What you doing?
Oh, letting Twilight
secretly follow me all day
without me knowing.
You mean
you knew all along?
Why didn't you tell me?
[ Laughs ] Silly.
That would have spoiled
the secret.
Uh...uh...
Ugh!
Tail...
still twitching?
All done.
Clear skies from here on in,
as far as I can tell.
[ Shudders ]
[ zip! ]
Oh, no!
What does that one mean?
Don't know -- never gotten
any like it before.
But whatever that shudder's
about, it's a doozy!
Something you never expect
to happen is gonna happen!
[ Shuddering ]
And it's gonna happen...
at Froggy Bottom Bog!
[ Gasps ] That's where
Fluttershy's headed.
Oh, no!
Is it about her?
Uh, I'm not sure.
We'd better go
and make sure she's okay.
[ Hoofbeats depart ]
Calm down, everypony.
All we know right now
is that Pinkie Pie
just got a case
of the shivers -- that's all.
[ Up-tempo western music plays ]
Huh?!
Hey, I thought you didn't
believe in this stuff.
I don't.
I just want to be there
to see the look on Pinkie's face
when we find out
nothing's wrong.
Okey-dokey!
[ Frog croaks ]
[ Music resumes ]
[ Music fades ]
[ Shuddering ]
Cold?
Need a jacket
or something?
No, thanks.
I'm fine.
[ Shuddering ]
So, what do you think happened
to Fluttershy?
I hope nothing.
I know, but what do you think
happened?
I'm trying
not to think about it.
Me too...
But I'm thinking about it,
anyway,
like...
what if she exploded?!
Just exploded
for no reason?
Yeah, like, boom!
Whoa!
I know.
What if --
what if she exploded
and then --
and then exploded again?!
Can you do that?!
Can you explode twice?!
Of course not.
But what if she exploded
and exploded again
and then --
[ Creak! ]
Will you two stop?
She's fine.
I'm sure of it.
I hope you're right,
for Fluttershy's sake.
Look!
There's Froggy Bottom Bog!
[ Buzzing ]
Fluttershy!
[ Owl hooting ]
[ Gasps ]
Fluttershy,
you're okay!
Of course.
Whew! What a relief.
I'm so glad
everything's all right!
Sorry.
I know it's not nice to gloat,
but -- Ha ha! --
Whoa!
I told you there was
nothing to worry about,
and I was right.
Pinkie Pie said whatever
she was shuddering about
was [coughs] a doozy,
and [coughs] --
and the only [coughs] doozy here
is how right I am.
Um [gulps]
Twilight...
Pinkie's made a lot
of predictions today, but...
[ coughs ]
Ugh,
what is that smell?!
...but what we've shown here
is that there is no point
in believing [coughs]
in anything
you can't see
for yourself.
W-well, then s-s-see what's
b-b-behind you, Twilight!
[ Creature growls ]
I see it...
but I don't believe it!
[ Roars ]
Pinkie Pie:
Is that a hydra?!
Applejack:
Who cares? Run!
[ Growling ]
Oh!
[ Gasping ]
Pinkie, come on!
[ Growls ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Panting ]
Oh, I'm so sorry.
[ Growls ]
[ Roars ]
Oh!
[ Laughs evilly ]
[ All screaming, panting ]
Everypony
up that hill.
Spike: Help!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Coming, Spike!
Hang on!
[ Footsteps pounding ]
[ Creak! Creak! Creak! ]
[ Roars ]
I think
we're gonna make it!
But Pinkie's
still shuddering!
[ Shuddering ]
[ Boing! ]
Oh, looky there.
It stopped.
[ Shuddering ]
Oh!
There...it...is...again!
[ Gasps ]
[ Footsteps pounding ]
[ All gasp ]
[ Growling ]
[ Gasps ]
He'll be up here in no time.
Quick!
One at a time, cross!
Aaah!
Uh, do you know
any spells
for turning a hydra
into a mouse?
No.
How about a squirrel?
How about --
No small rodents
of any kind!
That's too bad.
A hop, skip, and a [gasps] jump!
Whoa-oh!
[ Shuddering ]
Wh-o-o-oa!
[ Grunts ]
[ Growls ]
He's too close.
I'll distract him.
You two go -- now!
Oh, what would a brave pony
like Rainbow Dash do?
[ Poink! ]
Cha-a-a-a-rge!
[ Roars ]
[ Screeches ]
T-T-T-Twilight?!
[ Grunts ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Rattle! ]
[ All gasp ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Tweet! ]
[ Roars ]
T-T-T-Twilight!
You have to jump!
I'll never make it!
You'll be fine!
I will not!
[ Roaring ]
[ All screeching ]
It's your only h-hope!
[ Roaring ]
You have to take
a leap of faith!
[ Gulps ]
[ Growls ]
[ Roars ]
No!
[ Whiffle! ]
Oh, no!
Noooo!
[ Whistle! ]
Unh!
Wh-o-o-oa!
[ Boing! Boing! ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Tweet! ]
[ Rattle! ]
Ugh.
[ All cheering ]
I knew you could do it,
Twilight!
I don't know
how it happened --
coincidence, dumb luck,
or what --
but you said there'd be a doozy
here at Froggy Bottom Bog,
and I'd say
we just had ourselves
one heck of a doozy.
I mean, that hydra --
[ Shudders ]
Pinkie?
That wasn't it.
Huh?
What wasn't what?
What are you
talking about, Pink?
The hydra
wasn't the doozy.
Pbht!
I'm still getting
the shudders.
[ Shuddering ]
You see?
There it is again.
Whatever the doozy was
at Froggy Bottom Bog,
my Pinkie sense says
it still hasn't happened.
Huh?
But I -- What?!
The hydra
wasn't the doozy?
How could it not be
the doozy?!
What could be doozier
than that?!
Don't know,
but it just wasn't it.
[ Growls ]
Ugh!
[ Crackling, whooshing ]
Ohhh.
I give up.
Give what up, Twi?
The fight.
I can't fight it anymore.
I don't understand
how, why, or what,
but Pinkie sense
somehow...makes sense.
I don't see how it does,
but it just does.
Just because I don't understand
doesn't mean it's not true.
Y-y-you mean
you b-b-b-believe?
Yep.
I guess I do.
[ Shudders ]
[ Gasps ]
That was it!
That's the doozy!
[ Rattle! ]
What?
What is?
You believing!
I never expected that
to happen!
That was the doozy!
Oh, and, oh, what a doozy
of a doozy it was!
* La-la-la
La-la la-la *
[ Laughter ]
Twilight Sparkle: Oh, good,
Spike. You're here.
Take a letter.
With pleasure, Twilight.
"Dear Princess Celestia...
[ blink! ]
I'm happy
to report that --"
Spike, what have I been saying
about focus?
I know, but I --
Well...
What's wrong, Spike?
Never thought you'd see me
with an umbrella hat on?
Not really, no.
Pinkie's tail's a-twitchin'.
What else can I do?
[ Laughter ]
"I am happy to report
that I now realize
"there are wonderful things
in this world
"you just can't explain,
"but that doesn't necessarily
make them any less true.
"It just means you have to
choose to believe in them,
Aad sometimes it takes a friend
to show you the way."
Honk!
"Honk."
"Always, your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle."
[ Rattle! ]
There it goes again.
I wonder what's gonna drop out
of the sky this time.
You never know.
[ Gasps ]
[ Whistle! ]
Twitchy tail?
Holy guacamole!
* My Little Pony
* Friends