Perfect.
[ Bell dings ]
Coming!
Welcome to Carousel Boutique,
Where every garment is chic,
unique, and magnifique.
[ Gasps ]
Sapphire Shores!
The pony of pop!
Good afternoon,
miss Rarity.
[ Stammering ]
Y-You know my name?
Well, of course I do,
darling.
I make it a point
to know
All of the up-And-Coming
designers,
And clothes horse magazine
simply raved about you.
Oh, my stars.
If I'm dreaming,
do not wake me up.
How may I help you,
miss Shores?
Oh,
please call me Sapphire.
[ Giggles ]
How may I help you,
Sapphire?
Well,
as I'm sure you know,
I'll be touring all of Equestria
with my latest concert --
Sapphire Shores
zigfilly follies!
So I need to look
se-E-E-Nsational!
Oww!
I have
just what you need.
Sapphire Shores,
prepare yourself
For the pièce de résistance
de la haute couture.
I used every last diamond
I found on this one garment.
[ Gasps ]
And it is spectacular!
I'll take it.
Really?
Oh, yes.
And five more, each done up
in a different jewel.
Beg pardon?
Costume changes.
Ohh!
[ Chuckles ]
Yes, I do have that effect
on ponies.
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Oh, my gosh!
Sapphire Shores!
The pony of pop!
She is awesome!
I mean, she's gorgeous
and talented and...
[ chuckles ]
And -- Not even half the pony
you are.
I mean, you're 10 times more
gorgeous and talented and --
Spike,
a lady is never jealous.
O-Of course not.
But were you totally
flipping out or what?
Ladies do not flip out,
Spike.
However, I was quite in awe.
Ooh, I need to find more jewels
than ever before
To decorate her costumes.
Ooh! Aha!
Did you find some?
Yes, Spike!
Right there!
Ooh!
You look so...delicious.
Rarity: Spike!
I promised I'd give you gems
to snack on,
But we need to collect more
first,
Or I'll never be able to make
these outfits for Sapphire.
[ Groans ]
I will miss you, my sweets.
Come along, Spike.
We have many jewels to find.
At your service, my lady.
Spike!
[ Slobbering ]
You've been very patient today,
Spike.
And for that,
you get the finest reward.
This is from me to you.
Is something wrong,
Spike?
No.
It's perfect.
Ooh, bring the cart,
Spike.
There are more
over here.
For me, from Rarity.
Diamond dog:
glass gems!
Gems!
Where?
Precious gems.
He is the gem hunter.
With him, we can have
all those gems and more.
Let's get the dragon.
Rarity:
Spike, where are you?
Wait!
Who is that?
You know, it's terrible
to keep a lady waiting.
Coming!
I think we're really going to
strike gold this time.
So to speak.
Jackpot!
Diamond dog: ooh,
it's not the dragon we want.
It's the pony.
Yeah, pony.
Well, Spike.
I think that's all we can do
for today,
And these will certainly get me
well on my way
With Sapphire's outfits.
Why don't
we start heading --
[ Tinkling ]
ooh! What's this?
Another jewel!
Oh, oh, strange.
It's in the trees.
Ooh.
Aah!
Uh, good day,
gentle...fellow.
Uh, I am Rarity,
and this is my friend, Spike.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
And you are?
A diamond dog.
Oh, really?
Well, that explains
your fine taste in jewelry.
I mean, I-I-I know that diamonds
are a girl's best friend,
And now I know that they're
a dog's best friend, too.
[ Chuckles ] so, um...
[ clears throat ]
You're out hunting for gems,
as well?
Yes.
We hunt.
Uh, we?
We hunt for gems.
But you are a better hunter,
so now we hunt for you.
Unh!
Aah!
Run, Rarity!
Run!
Spike, come on!
Hurry!
Gotcha!
Aah!
Go on, Rarity!
I got him!
[ Laughs ]
nope.
Dogs sorry, skinny one.
W-Wait.
Rarity.
Unhand me this instant,
you ruffians!
Put me down!
You brutes!
[ Gasps ]
Rarity!
Spike!
Aah! Dirt!
Aah!
W-W-Where --
Spike!
Noooooo!
Spike,
can you breathe now?
[ Panting ]
yes.
I think so.
Good.
Now tell us what you now.
Yeah, 'cause all you said
earlier was...
[ panting ]
Rarity! Woods! Jewels!
Dogs! Hole! Taken!
Save her!
Not a whole lot to go on there,
sport.
Sorry.
Rarity and I were in the woods
looking for jewels
When these creepy guys
showed up.
Creepy guys?
They called themselves
the diamond dogs.
They grabbed Rarity
And disappeared down a hole
in the ground.
Well,
this sounds mighty easy.
Just take us to that there hole,
and we'll save Rarity.
[ Gasps ]
[ All gasp ]
Holy moley,
that's a lot of holeys!
Come on, girls.
Let's get started.
Hello?
[ Growling ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Coughs ]
Ugh!
Quick, we got to get down one
before they're all filled up.
O-Oh, my.
Ohh! Ohh!
[ Sproing! ]
[ Grunting ]
Aah!
We can't muscle through it!
We'll see about that!
Whew!
Heavens to betsy.
Now, I'm used to picking myself
up and dusting myself off,
But Rarity won't even touch mud
unless it's imported.
Oh, Rarity.
Oh, woe is me!
Whatever shall I do?
Aah!
Dirt! Dirt!
Get away, dirt!
Aah!
Make it stop!
Filthy, disgusting dirt.
It stings!
It burns!
Help!
Oh, somepony, save me!
Save me!
We got to save her.
But they blocked up
all the holes.
Don't mean
we can't dig them out.
Come on.
Ow!
Unh!
Get 'em!
[ Gasps ]
Whoa!
Come on!
[ Panting ]
All those scary monsters
popping up everywhere.
Oh, poor Rarity
must be terrified.
Ohh.
Give me the baubles!
Aah!
Give me the beads!
Where are the trinkets?
Aah!
Where's the treasure?!
Ohh!
Poor Rarity.
What are we gonna do?
Spike: I got it!
I'll save you, my sweet.
Huh?
Huh?Huh?
Spike,
it is very noble of you...
shh!
...to sacrifice the gem
Rarity gave you.
Oh, lady Rarity,
my damsel in distress,
I shall save you.
Show yourselves, you dogs!
You curs!
[ Growling ]
Ah, there you are,
you mangy mutts.
Who are you calling
mutts?
Unleash the hounds!
[ Dog whistle blows ]
Roar!
[ Barking ]
[ Yelping ]
Now,
where is lady Rarity?
[ Gasps ]
Spike!
I knew
you would save me.
Nothing could stop me,
my lady.
Ohh, Spike,
you are my hero.
[ Smooching ]
Whoa, there, loverboy.
Whoa!
W-W-W-Whoa!
I've got a bite!
[ Grunting ]
Hold on there,
little fella.
Applejack.
Twilight!
Oh, my goodness.
Wait for me!
Whee!
Aah!
[ Giggles ]
Ha ha!
It worked.
We're in!
Now we can finally save Rarity.
Um...
which way do we go?
Nooooo!
All these tunnels.
How are we ever
gonna find Rarity?
Guess we're just gonna have to
start going down them
One by one.
That could take
forever.
There's got to be a way
to narrow it down.
Spike: I know.
I bet they've taken Rarity down
the tunnel with the most gems.
But, Spike, Rarity's the only
one who knows how to find gems.
No, Twilight.
You can.
You can copy
Rarity's gem-Finding spell.
Oh, my gosh.
You're right.
Rarity showed me how she did it
awhile back.
If I can just remember...
That's it.
You did it, Twilight!
Come on.
We're coming, Rarity.
We'll save you.
Just hold on.
Oh, please,
diamond dogs.
Please let me go.
No!
You're
our precious little pony.
Forever!
[ Laughs maniacally ]
But whatever do you want
from me?
Gems!
Yes,
the gems, the jewels.
Find them.
Find them all.
Oh, is that all?
[ Tinkling ]
There, a lovely pocket of jewels
are right there.
Now, if you'll be so kind
as to show me the exit...
good.
[ Chuckles ]
Now, dig them up, pony.
What?
But you said you wanted me
to find the gems.
Yes.
Find and then dig.
Dig?
Yes.
Dig.
[ Groans ]
Ugh.
[ Squeaking ]
What are you doing?
We said dig!
Forgive me, but prior to you
so rudely dragging me
Into a dirt pit,
I had a ponypedi, and I am
not about to chip a hoof
Because you dislike
my style of digging.
Uh!
Oh, for goodness' --
Fine!
Just stop.
Stop!
Dig, dogs.
Dig!
And fast.
[ Barking ]
If she won't dig,
she pulls.
I beg your pardon, but what,
pray tell, are you doing?
Others will dig.
You will haul
the wagon.
Precious ponypedi
will be preserved!
Well, somebody certainly needs
proper nail care.
When was the last time
you two had a manicure?
You're scratching up my coat
with those jagged things.
Please be quiet!
Good heavens!
What is that smell?
Smell?
Ah, mystery solved.
It's your breath.
[ Sniffs ]
Phew!
Enough!
Search, pony!
Well, since you insist.
But I must say
the working conditions in here
Are simply dreadful.
Musty and damp -- It's going to
wreak havoc on my mane.
And this air is stifling,
suffocating!
And when I try to get
a deep breath,
The stench of all you dogs
makes me nauseated.
[ Crack, dogs yelp ]
You look and smell like
you haven't bathed in weeks.
Have you never heard of soap?
[ Sniffing ]
You could all do with a good
round of soap and water.
Oh, water.
Water!
I'm terribly thirsty.
Could I please have some water?
Good gracious,
I can't take this anymore!
Be quiet, pony!
And that's another thing.
I would appreciate it
if you'd stop calling me "pony."
I am a lady, and I wish to be
addressed as such.
So you may call me "miss,"
or "Rarity," or "miss Rarity."
Enough!
Y-Your whining --
I-It hurts!
Whining?
I am not whining.
I am complaining.
Do you want to hear whining?
[ Whining ]
this is whining!
Ooh,
this harness is too tight!
It's going to chaff!
Can't you loosen it?!
Ooh, it hurts,
and it's so nasty!
Why didn't you clean it first?
It's gonna leave a stain!
The wagon's getting heavy!
Why do I have to pull it?
Ugh, make it stop!
Stop whining!
But I thought
you wanted whining!
We'll do anything, pony.
Oh, uh,
we'll do anything, miss Rarity.
[ Panting ]
Anything?
[ Sighs ]
this water is hardly sparkling,
But I suppose
it will have to do.
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting ]
Wait,
why are we doing this?
To stop the awful noises
from the pony's mouth.
Remember?
[ As Rarity ]
my neck --
Yes, yes, I know.
This is ridiculous --
Letting a pony order us around.
What are we?
Mice or dogs?
Mi-- Uh, dogs?
Dogs?
Dogs do not pull.
Ponies pull.
Let her make
the awful noises.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Hey!
You spilled my drink.
Oh! [ Whining ]
not so tight!
Ha!
Make the noises all you want,
but move while you make them.
Hyah, mule!
Did you just call me
a...mule?!
Uh...
mules are ugly.
[ Voice breaking ] are you
saying that I, too, am ugly?
[ Sobbing ]
What are
these noises?
He called me ugly!
No! "Mule!"
I said "mule."
An old, ugly mule!
And it's true!
Just look at me!
I used to be beautiful.
But -- But now!
No, no, you're still beautiful,
po-- Miss Rarity.
You're just saying that!
No, you're still pretty and --
And --
Oh, nice!
Yeah.
I don't believe you.
You never liked me!
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, I've had just about
enough of this.
We're getting close.
I can feel it.
[ Rarity crying in distance ]
It's coming from down here.
Come on!
She must be
in there.
Let's go!
Aah!
Aah!Aah!
More workhorses.
Unh!
Whoa, doggies.
If you can take this bull
by the horns,
You better be ready for a ride.
Come on, ponies!
Kick 'em up, kick 'em out.
Buck 'em up, buck 'em down.
Aah!
Ooh!
Whoa!
Yeehaw!
Get along, little doggies.
[ Clanging, crashing ]
I'm coming for you,
my lady!
Heigh-Ho, Twilight!
Away!
And just what do you think
you're doing?
Please, Twilight.
Just give me this.
[ Sighs ]
fine.
[ Neighs ]
Lady Rarity,
I'm here to save you!
Please!
Save us!
Make her stop!
Excuse me?
So picky.
And critical.
She won't
stop talking.
And crying.
We, uh, give her back.
Yes.
Rarity,
you're safe!
Why, yes.
Hello, girls.
You arrived just in time
to assist me.
Uh,
assist you with what?
With those.
You're letting her leave
with all these...jewels?
Yes.
Take them --
And her with them.
Please!
I can't believe
you found all these gems.
you tricked all those dogs.
Just because I'm a lady
Doesn't mean I cannot handle
myself in a sticky situation.
I had them wrapped around
my hoof the entire time.
I can't wait to write
to princess Celestia
To tell her
what you taught me today.
Me?
What did I teach you?
Just because somepony is
ladylike, doesn't make her weak.
In fact, by using her wits,
A seemingly defenseless pony
Can be the one who outsmarts
and outshines them all.
Mmm,
outshines is right.
Now you have enough gems to
cover Sapphire Shores' costumes.
Not if you eat them all,
Spike.
[ Giggling ]