Oh, Opalescence,
can't you just picture it?
Moi stepping out
in a stunning new gown
at the Grand Galloping Gala
in Canterlot.
Meow!
Why, yes, I did make it myself.
Thank you so much
for asking.
Oh, oh, well, of course
you can help me.
Thank you.
Meow!
What's that?
You want to help me more?
Oh, aren't you
the sweetest thing?
Meow!
Careful now.
Don't move.
This shouldn't take long
at all.
* My Little Pony
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
* My Little Pony
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
This magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
Howdy, Rarity.
Shh!
Can't you see Rarity's
trying to concentrate?
What do you think
she's making?
Looks like a dress.
Well, that makes sense,
since this is
a dressmaker's shop and all.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Oh, so very sorry
to trouble you, Rarity,
but I need
a quick favor.
Could you please fix
a button for me?
It's my dress
for the Grand Galloping Gala.
Oh, no, no, no!
You can't wear this --
ugh -- old thing.
You need a glamorous new outfit
for the gala.
And I'll make it for you,
no problem at all.
It would be my pleasure.
Oh, that's really sweet of you
to offer, Rarity,
but I can't let you
do that.
It would be so much work.
This dress is fine.
Twilight Sparkle,
I insist on making you
a new dress.
But --
Not another word.
I won't take "no"
for an answer.
Well...in that case,
thank you
for your generosity, Rarity.
Knowing your handiwork,
I'm sure it will be
absolutely beautiful.
Let me guess, Applejack --
You don't want
a new gown, either.
Gown? Shoot.
I was just gonna wear
my old work duds.
You can't possibly be serious,
Applejack!
You absolutely must wear
formal attire.
Hmm...
nah.
What if I just spruce up
your, uh...duds
for you a little bit?
Oh, okay.
Sure. Why not?
Since you're offering
and all.
Just don't make them too,
uh, froufrou-y.
Deal!
Look out below!
Aah!
Sorry. New trick.
Didn't quite work.
Hmm.
Idea!
I'll make you an outfit
for the gala, too, Rainbow Dash!
Outfit for the what now?
I'll make one for you and you
and all of you.
Ooh! And, of course,
Pinkie and Fluttershy, too.
Oh, and when I'm done,
we can hold
our very own fashion show!
What a great idea --
If you're sure
you can handle it.
Oh, it'll be
a little bit of work,
but it'll be a wonderful boost
for my business...plus fun!
Oh, I love fun things!
Then it's settled.
We'll have a fashion show
starring us!
Yay!
Yay!Yay!
So, all you have to do
is make a different, stunning,
original, amazing outfit
for one, two, three,
four, five --
plus yourself -- six ponies,
and lickety-split?
Oh, Applejack.
You make it sound
as if it's going to be hard.
* Thread by thread
* Stitching it together
* Twilight's dress
* Cutting out the pattern
Snip by snip *
* Making sure
The fabric falls nicely *
* It's a perfect color
And so hip *
* Always got to keep in mind
My pacing *
* Making sure the clothes
Correctly facing *
* I'm stitching
Twilight's dress *
* Yard by yard
* Fussing on the details
* Jewel neckline
* Don't you know
A stitch in time saves nine? *
* Make her something perfect
To inspire *
* Even though
She hates formal attire *
* Got to mind
Those intimate details *
* Even though she's
More concerned with sales *
* It's Applejack's new dress
* Dressmaking's easy
* For Pinkie Pie,
Something pink *
* Fluttershy, something breezy
* Blend color and form
* Do you think
It looks cheesy? *
* Something brash
* Perhaps quite fetching
* Hook and eye
* Couldn't you
Just simply die? *
* Making sure it fits
For lock and crest *
* Don't forget some magic
In the dress *
* Even though it rides high
On the flank *
* Rainbow won't look
Like a tank *
* I'm stitching
Rainbow's dress *
* Piece by piece,
Snip by snip *
* Croup, dock, haunch,
Shoulders, hips *
* Thread by thread,
Primmed and pressed *
* Yard by yard,
Never stressed *
* And that's the art
Of the dre-e-e-e-ss *
That's it.
Keep them closed.
Don't look.
Okay, you can look now!
These are your new outfits.
What do you think of your
old duds now, Applejack?
Pretty swanky, are they not?
And, Twilight, I made this dress
for you,
and I designed each outfit theme
to perfectly look like
each pony's unique personality.
Oh!
It took me forever
to get the colors right on this
one, Rainbow Dash, but I did it.
Oh, and it turned out beautiful,
don't you think?
And I know you're going
to love yours, Fluttershy.
It just sings spring!
And, Pinkie Pie, look -- Pink!
Your favorite!
Aren't they all amazing?!
Wow!
They're...
Yeah, they're...
They sure are,
uh, something.
Yes! Something.
I love something.
Something is my favorite.
It's...nice.
Well, what's the matter?
Don't you like them?
They're very nice.
And we're plumb grateful 'cause
you worked so hard on them.
Mine's just not as cool
as I was imagining.
She asked.
I guess
what we're all saying
is that they're just not
what we had in mind.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Uh-huh.
That's okay.
Not a problem.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
They were only a first pass.
You're my friends, and I want
you to be 110% satisfied.
Not to worry.
I'll redo them!
Oh, Rarity.
You don't have to do that.
They're fine.
I want them to be better
than just fine.
I want you to think
they're absolutely perfect.
Are you sure?
I mean,
we wouldn't want to impose.
Oh, it's no imposition.
Really, I insist.
Well, in that case,
thank you again, Rarity.
What have I gotten myself into?
Hello?
You wanted to see me,
Rarity?
Fluttershy!
Your new
new gown's ready.
I completely revised it,
and I know
you're going to love it.
What do you think?
I...love it.
Oh, you're just
saying that.
No, no. I do.
It's...nice.
"Nice"?
Nice.
If you don't like it,
you should just tell me.
Ooh, but I do like it.
Like it or love it?
Um...both?
Which is it?
Uh, please stop
asking me this. I --
Well, just tell me
what you really think.
Uh, no, that's okay.
Tell me!
No.
I-it's fine.
Tell me.
I-I like it.
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
tell me, tell me!
All right,
since you really want to know.
The arm size -- tight.
The middy collar doesn't go
with the shawl lapel.
The hands are clearly
machine-stitched.
The pleats are uneven.
The fabric looks like toile.
You used a backstitch here
when it clearly called
for a topstitch
or maybe a traditional
blanket stitch.
And the overdesign
is reminiscent of prêt-à-porter
and not true french
haute couture.
But, uh, you know,
um, whatever you want to do
is fine.
Now, the stars on my belt
need to be technically accurate.
Orion has three stars
on his belt,
Not four.
* Stitch by stitch
* Stitching it together
* Deadline looms
* Don't you know
The client's always right *
* Even if my fabric choice
Was perfect? *
* Got to get them all done
By tonight *
* Pinkie Pie,
The color's too obtrusive *
* Wait until you see it
In the light *
* I'm sewing them together
Don't you think my gown
would be more me
with some lollipops?
Well, I think --
Balloons?
Well...
Do it!
* Hour by hour
* One more change
* I'm sewing them together
* Take great pains
* Fluttershy,
You're putting me in a bind *
* Rainbow Dash,
What is on your mind? *
* Oh, my gosh,
There's simply not much time *
* Don't forget,
Applejack's duds must shine *
* Dressmaking's easy
* Every customer's call
* Brings a whole new revision
* Have to pick up the pace,
Still hold to my vision *
That constellation
is canis major, not minor.
French haute couture,
please.
Eh...
What if it rains?
Galoshes!
More balloons!
Oh, no.
That's too many balloons.
More candy!
Oh, less candy!
Oh, wait, I know --
Streamers!
Streamers?
Whose dress is this?
Streamers it is.
What?
Aren't you going to tell me
to change something, too?
No. I just want my dress
to be...cool.
Do you not like
the color?
The color's fine.
Just make it look cooler.
Do you not like
the shape?
The shape's fine.
Just make the whole thing,
you know, cooler.
It needs to be
about 20% cooler.
* All we ever want
Is indecision *
* All we really like
Is what we know *
* Got to balance style
With adherence *
* Making sure we make
A good appearance *
* Even if you simply
Have to fudge it *
* Make sure that it stays
Within our budget *
* Got to overcome intimidation
* Remember, it's all
In the presentation *
* Piece by piece,
Snip by snip *
* Croup, dock, haunch,
Shoulders, hip *
* Bolt by bolt,
Primmed and pressed *
* Yard by yard,
Always stressed *
* And that's the art
Of the dre-e-e-e-es *
Oh, Opal.
These are the ugliest dresses
I've ever made.
Okay. I did exactly
what each of you asked for.
Now, don't hold back.
Let me know
what you really think.
Oh, my!
It's...perfect!
It's cool!
Wow.
They're the best duds
I ever did see.
It's exactly
what I asked for!
Thank you, Rarity.
Are you as happy with them
as we are?!
Huh, huh, huh?!
Well, I'm happy
that all of you are happy.
I'm just relieved
to finally be done.
You are never
gonna believe this!
You've heard of Hoity-Toity?
The bigwig fashion hotshot
in Canterlot?
Uh-huh.
He heard
about your fashion show.
Well, maybe I happened
to mention it to him.
He's coming here
all the way from Canterlot
to see your work, Rarity!
Whoa, nelly!
You could sell a ton of dresses
to this guy.
Your business
will be booming!
That's so cool!
I can't believe it!
Amazing!
H-Hoity-Toity?
He's coming here...
to see these dresses?
Yep. Get ready for all
your dreams to come true.
Oh.
There he is.
Okay.
Relax, Rarity.
Your friends like their outfits,
and so will he.
Aaah!
What's wrong with the lights?!
Aah!
Oh, yes.
That means the show's starting.
Good.
Since the beginning of time,
The elite of Equestria
have longed for pony fashions
that truly express the essence
of their very souls...
Patiently waiting decades --
no, centuries --
for the perfect pony gown.
Today, at long last, Equestria,
your wait is over.
Let's hear it
for the breathtaking designs
of Ponyville's own Rarity!
Blech!
Why is everypony
looking at us like that?
Oh, dear.
Y-you think
we overdid it?
Nah.
Okay.
Maybe a little.
Oh, those amateurish designs
look like a piled-on mishmash
of everything
but the kitchen sink.
It's a travesty,
is what it is.
Those outfits are the ugliest
things I've ever seen!
Oh, for shame.
Who is responsible
for subjecting our eyes
to these horrors?!
Not to mention wasting
my valuable time?
Oh! Hide me.
Come on out and take a bow,
Rarity.
You worked really hard
for this.
Yes! All right!
Hoo-hoo! Go, Rarity!
Rarity,
you okay in there?
You haven't come out
for days.
I'm never coming out!
I can't show my face
in Ponyville ever again!
I used to be somepony.
I used to be respected.
I made dresses --
beautiful, beautiful dresses.
But now everypony
is laughing at me.
I'm nothing but a laughingstock!
You're not
a laughingstock, Rarity.
She kind of is.
Shh!
Come on out
and talk to us.
Leave me alone!
I want to be alone.
I want to wallow in...
Whatever it is that ponies
are supposed to wallow in!
Do ponies wallow in pity?
Oh, listen to me!
I don't even know
what I'm supposed to wallow in!
I'm so pathetic!
Now what do we do?
Panic?
That's your answer
for everything.
Well, we can't just
leave Rarity like this.
She'll become
a crazy cat lady!
She only has one cat.
Give her time.
Hmm.
Exile.
I guess, technically,
I'd have to move away
to live in exile.
Where would I go,
and what would I pack?
Oh, it's gonna take me forever
to do all of that packing.
What are you supposed to pack
when you go into exile?
Are you supposed to pack warm?
Huh? Opal?
Opal, how did you
get up there?
Hang on, you poor dear.
Mama's coming!
Rainbow Dash?!
How dare you strand
my poor Opal in a tree!
Well, how else were we gonna get
you out here to show you this?
What is it?
It's m-- y--
We all finished
your dress for you!
Thanks to Fluttershy's
freaky knowledge of sewing.
Do you like it?
Like it?
Uh-oh.
She doesn't like it.
No.
I don't like it.
Oh!
I love it!
Yay!
Yay!Yay!
You ponies
did an amazing job!
It's exactly the way
I imagined it.
We just followed
your brilliant design.
Like we should have let you do
for our outfits.
Those first dresses you designed
were perfect.
We're so
supersorry.
You worked really hard
to make our dresses
exactly the way we wanted them,
and we all saw how well
that turned out.
Oh, I forgive you.
Well,
that's mighty big of you.
But my whole career
is still ruined!
Oh. Right. That.
Maybe not.
All right.
I haven't got all day.
Take two.
Hello.
Oh, this can't be
the same designer.
Simply magnificent!
And I suddenly have
a fierce craving
for some dutch apple pie,
candied apples on a stick,
apple turnovers,
apple cobbler...
Brilliant!
Oh! Spectacular!
Now, this is a fashion show!
Oh, these dresses
are absolutely amazing!
Who is responsible?
Step forward. Show yourself!
Brava! Brava!
Magnifico! Encore!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
Oh!
Thank you so much!
Dear Princess Celestia,
This week, my very talented
friend Rarity learned
that if you try
to please everypony,
you oftentimes end up
pleasing nopony,
especially yourself.
And I learned this --
when somepony
offers to do you a favor,
like making you
a beautiful dress,
you shouldn't be overly critical
of something
generously given to you.
In other words, you shouldn't
look a gift horse in the mouth.
Rarity,
my congratulations to you
on a most impressive
fashion debut!
Would you do me the great honor
of allowing me
to feature your couture
in my best of the best boutique
in Canterlot?
Now, I'll need you to make
a dozen of each dress for me
by next tuesday.
* My Little Pony
* Friends