[ Train whistle blowing ]
Applejack:
"And that's when the yellow
birdie thought to himself,
"'Hmm.
My favorite little tree
"isn't such
a little tree anymore.'
"So she sang her song
big and strong,
"and they all lived
in that great, big tree
"happily ever after.
The end."
Applejack!
Were you reading
a bedtime story to...
an apple tree?
[ Chuckles ]
Uh...
Well, you know, being replanted
in a whole new place
is very upsetting
for a tree.
And Bloomberg here
is one of my favorites.
No fair, Applejack!
You've got a luxurious private
sleeper car for a tree,
while I am crowded and cramped
in the same car
with all the other ponies.
How am I supposed to get
my beauty sleep?!
But Bloomberg's the whole reason
we're making this trip.
He needs his rest
so we can give him as a gift
to my relatives
in Appleloosa.
Hmm!
You talk about it as if
it's your baby or something.
Who you calling a baby?
Bloomberg's no baby!
Don't let widdle Rarity
make you all saddy-waddy.
Bloomberg's
a big and strong apple tree.
Yes, he is.
A-coochie-coochie,
coo-coo-coo!
It's widdle Rarity
who's all saddy-waddy!
Ugh!
* My Little Pony
Hard of Hearing subtitles
by YayPonies
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
* My Little Pony
* I used to wonder
What friendship could be *
* My Little Pony
* Until you all shared
Its magic with me *
* Big adventure
* Tons of fun
* A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong *
* Sharing kindness
* It's an easy feat
* And magic
Makes it all complete *
* Yeah, My Little Pony
* Do you know you're all
My very best friends? *
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Oh, man!
We're going fast!
Oh, my gosh!
This is so exciting!
I can't even wait!
[ Sighs ]
For crying out loud
in the morning!
I can't wait!
Yeah!
[ Groans ]
Do you guys mind?
I was up early
fire-roasting those snacks
you're all eating,
and i'm pooped!
Uh, speaking of --
Some of these popcorn kernels
didn't get popped.
Okay, fine.
[ Whoosh! ]
[ Pop! ]
Good night!
Uh...
Maybe it's time we all got
a little shut-eye.
We've got a big day
ahead of us tomorrow.
[ Squeak! ]
Aww!
[ Snoring, mumbling ]
Rainbow Dash: Psst!
Pinkie Pie, you asleep yet?
Pinkie Pie:
No. Are you asleep yet?
If I was sleeping,
how could I have asked you
if you were asleep?
Oh, yeah.
[ Giggles ]
When we get to Appleloosa,
you think we'll have to carry
that heavy tree
all the way from the train
to the orchard?
What tree?
You mean Bloomberg?
[ Sarcastically ]
No. Fluttershy.
Fluttershy's not a tree,
silly!
What's going on?
Rainbow Dash
thinks Fluttershy's a tree.
I do not think she's a tree.
I was just --
Did you say
she was a tree?
No!
Well, yes,
but not exactly.
You know she's not a tree,
right?
She's not a tree,
Dashie.
I'd like to be a tree.
Oh, for Pete's sake!
[ Boing! ]
[ Footsteps depart quickly ]
[ Door creaks, slams ]
Well,
that was kind of huffy.
Huffy the magic dragon.
[ Both giggle ]
[ All giggling ]
Would you all
be quiet now?!
Aaah!
Aaah!Aaah!
[ All blow ]
Bloomberg?
[ Grunts ]
Sorry, but I tend to snore
a bit.
Good night.
[ Sighs ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Hoofbeats rumble,
tracks clacking ]
[ All snoring,
rumbling continues ]
[ Thud! ]
Huh?
Who gets what now?
[ Sloop! Sloop! Sloop! ]
[ All gasp ]
A buffalo stampede!
Oh, wow!
So noble,
all of them together.
Rarity: I just love
their accessories.
They're getting awfully close
to the train.
Aah!
Aah!Aah!
[ All shouting indistinctly ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Creak! ]
[ Squeak! ]
[ Tweet! ]
Ooh! Looky!
Now they're doing tricks!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Now do a back flip!
[ Thud! ]
Or just jump?
Hmm.
Something tells me
this isn't a circus act.
Hey, there!
[ Gasps ]
Where you headed
in such a hurry?
[ Grunts ]
Wow.
You're pretty quick
for someone so...bulky.
No offense.
Huh?
I just want to know --
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
[ Whirl! Whirl! Whirl! ]
Whoa!
[ Grunts ]
[ Screech! ]
I've got you now, you --
[ Thud! Twang! ]
[ Zip! ]
[ Groans ]
[ Whistles ]
[ Applejack gasps ]
They've got Bloomberg!
He-e-e-e-lp!
And Spike!
[ Groans ]
Spike: He-e-e-e-lp!
Dragon-napping Spike.
I'll show her!
[ Twang! ]
Ow.
[ Brakes screech, steam hisses ]
[ All panting ]
Hey, there!
Welcome to A-A-Appleloosa!
Braeburn, listen --
Cousin Applejack,
mind your manners.
You have yet to introduce me
to your compadres.
Shame on you!
Braeburn, listen!
Something terrible's happened!
"Terrible" is right.
Your train is a full
seven minutes late.
That's seven minutes less
for you to delight
in the pleasures and wonders
of A-A-Appleloosa!
[ All grunt ]
Boggles the mind we
settler ponies built all this
in just the past year,
don't it?
And as you can see, we have
all of the finest comforts.
Like horse-drawn
carriages.
Okay.
You pull now.
Aw, we just switched.
And those there are horse-drawn
horse-drawn carriages.
Listen, Braeburn,
I -- Oof!
And here's our local
watering hole, the salt block.
Pony:
That's enough salt for you!
Can't I at least get
a glass of water?
Over there's the office
of Sheriff Silverstar.
And here's where we have
our wild west dances.
our mi-west dances.
But, Braeburn, we --
And here's
the most wonderful sight
in all of A-A-Appleloosa --
Our apple orchard.
Braeburn!
First harvest
should be any day now.
Braebur--
Good thing, too.
Brae--
'Cause we need
that grub to live on.
Braeburn!!
Uh, yes, cuz?
You have a very nice town
and all,
but we have
a huge problem!
Some of our friends
are missing.
A stampede of buffalo.
They took Spike!
Rainbow Dash
went after them!
And we can't find
Pinkie Pie.
And we had an apple tree with us
for your orchard,
but they took that, too!
Did you say buffalo?
[ Sighs ]
Them buffalo,
they want us settler ponies
To take every single tree
you see here off this land.
They sure as hay don't want
any new ones added in.
But why?
Beats me.
We put a lot of hard work
into this land
so we could feed our town,
our families, our foals,
and now they're saying
all these trees have to go?
T'ain't fair.
[ Bird screeches ]
[ Sloop! Slump! ]
[ Pitter! ]
[ Sloop! Whip! Slump! Zip! ]
Oh, I can't wait to get my
hooves on that little buffalo.
[ Twang! ]
Ow!
Nobody tricks Rainbow Dash
and gets away with it.
Boo!
Yah!
Pinkie Pie!
Oh, you caught me.
Looks like I tricked you and
didn't get away with it, either.
You're good.
Shh!
What do you think
you're doing?!
You got to
get out of here!
I do?
You're gonna blow
my cover!
I am?
I'm trying
to save Spike!
Oh, my gosh!
So am i!
And the more of us
there are out here,
The more chances
of us getting...
[ Rumbling, snorting ]
...caught.
Run, Pinkie! I'll hold them off!
Save yourself!
Spike: Stop!
Dash, Pinkie, 'sup?
Hey, no worries.
I know those guys.
They're cool.
If you say so, Spike.
Catch you later, bro.
Seems they took me
by mistake,
and they feel awful
about it, too, poor guys.
Fortunately,
they totally respect dragons,
so they treat me
like an honored guest.
Still don't like ponies much,
though,
Ugh!
but you're with me,
so it's cool.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, I still don't trust them.
I say we turn tail
and bail while we still --
Mmm!
[ Munching ]
Before we finish eating?
Are you loco in the coco?
Can I please have more
of that mushy stuff,
whatever it was?
Certainly.
And, Mr. Spike,
you like gemstones, yes?
Turquoise! Mmm!
[ Munching, chuckles ]
This here's
Little Strongheart,
and these are my friends
Pinkie Pie and Rainbow Dash.
[ Snorts ]
[ Poing! ]
You!
That's it!
We are out of here!
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Ooh!
Wait!
Please accept my apologies
for what happened on the train.
We didn't mean
for anyone to be hurt.
Yeah, right.
We only wanted
the tree.
The settler ponies
have overtaken the land
and have planted an orchard
all over it.
Because of
their thoughtlessness,
we can no longer run over our
traditional stampeding grounds.
Huh?
I think it's time
they met Chief Thunderhooves.
We have a long and winding
stampeding trail
that we have run upon
for many generations.
My father stampeded
upon these grounds
and his father before him
[ Snoring ]
and --
I think they get the idea,
Chief.
Hmph.
It is a sacred tradition
to run the path every year,
but this year,
these settler ponies,
these...
[ snorts ]
...Appleloosians...
[ snorting ]
they planted apple trees
all over it
without asking
our permission.
Well,
that's not very nice.
Right,
Rainbow Dash?
Hmph.
The ponies
refused to move their trees,
so we are stuck here,
and it is not fair!
See, Rainbow Dash?
They had
a good reason to --
[ All gasp ]
I'll say
they had a good reason.
Come on.
We have some apple-picking
Appleloosians to talk to.
Ow!
[ Groaning ]
Gently, please.
Sorry, Rarity,
but our friends are out there,
and we have to be
ready for a long hike
into buffalo territory
if we're gonna
save them.
Let's go!
[ Screech! ]
Hi, guys.
Pinkie!
[ Thud! ]
We're so glad
you're safe.
Oh, there you are.
Thank goodness.
How did you escape
from the buffalo?
We didn't.
[ All gasp ]
Rainbow Dash: We promised
the buffalo a chance to talk.
Oh, yeah?
About what?
We brought our new pal
Little Strongheart here
to explain
to the Appleloosians
why they should move
the apple trees
off buffalo land.
That information
will be quite help--
That's weird. 'Cause
my cousin Braeburn here
wants to explain
to the buffalo
why they should let
the apple trees stay.
That would be
a useful thing to --
The land is theirs!
You planted the trees
not knowing that.
Honest mistake.
Now you just got to move them.
That's all.
Well...
[ Chuckles ]
They busted
their rumps here.
And now they're supposed to
bust their rumps again
just 'cause some buffalo
won't stampede someplace else?
Plant the tree
somewhere else!
Where?
It's the only flatland
around these parts.
The buffalo had it first!
The settler ponies
need it to live!
Come on, Applejack!
I put my hoof down!
You're being unreasonable!
Look...
both the settlers
and the buffalo
have good reasons
to use this land.
There must be something
we can do.
Hey!
I've got an idea!
[ Thud! ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Piano plays ]
* We may be divided
* But of you all, I beg
* To remember we're all hoofed
* At the end of each leg
[ Zip! ]
* No matter what the issue
* Come from wherever
you please *
* All this fighting
gets you nothing *
* But huff-and-mouth disease
* Arguing's not the way
* Hey, come out and play
* It's a shiny, new day
* So what do you say?
* You got to share
* You got to care
* It's the right thing to do
* You got to share
* You got to care
* And there'll always
Be a way through *
* Both our diets,
I should mention *
* Are completely vegetarian
* We all eat hay and oats
* Why be at
Each other's throat? *
* You got to share
* You got to care
* It's the right thing to do
* And there'll always be a way
Thro-o-o-o-ugh *
[ Clapping ]
All right, Pinkie Pie!
That was fantastic!
What a great song!
You're right on!
It appears
that Sheriff Silverstar and I
have come to an agreement.
We have.
That was the worst performance
we've ever seen.
Abso-tively.
The time for action
is upon us.
Our stampede will start
at high noon tomorrow.
And if the orchard
is still there,
we'll flatten it
and the whole town!
[ All gasp ]
But, Chief!
And we Appleloosians say
you'd better bring your best,
'cause we'll be ready
and waitin'.
But, Sheriff...
[ indistinct shouting,
moaning ]
Oh, that wasn't the message
of my song at all.
[ Indistinct shouting ]
I want my kin to have
what they need to live,
but a storm's a-brewin' here,
and I don't like the look of it.
We've just got to talk
some sense into them
before somepony
gets hurt.
Listen, maybe if you would
just reconsider, we --
About the trees --
Now, if you could --
[ Gasps ]
If we could just sit down
and talk, we could --
[ Growls ]
[ Gasps ]
Why won't anybody
be rational and reasonable?!
Sheriff,
if we could only --
[ All cheer ]
[ Snorting ]
[ Grunting ]
Isn't there some way
to stop this?
Unless the settlers
remove those trees,
I do not think so.
[ Sighs ]
[ Munching ]
I know you don't want to
do this.
But they have taken
our land.
What would you have me do,
Rainbow Dash?
I don't know.
But it's never too late
to think of something.
At noon,
it will be too late.
[ Rumbling ]
Come on. Think.
Think, think, think, think,
think, think, think!
[ Bell tolls ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Gasps ]
He's not gonna do it.
[ All sigh ]
Pinkie Pie: * ...say?
You got to share *
* You got to care
* It's the right thing to do
* You got to share
Cha-a-a-a-rge!
Whoa! Whoa!
Who-o-o-o-a!
[ All screaming ]
Ready...
Aim...
Fire!
[ Gasps ]
[ Rattle! ]
[ Tweet! ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Sproing! ]
[ Snorts ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Distorted ] No-o-o-o!
[ Thud! ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Laughing ] Yum!
Hey!
I've got a much better idea.
[ Whistles ]
Chief Thunderhooves: We will
allow the apple orchard to stay
in exchange for a share
of its fruit --
those delicious apple pies.
I'd rather eat turquoise
any day of the week.
[ Chomp! ]
Ahh.
Applejack: Bloomberg,
this is your special day.
Mama's so proud of you.
Twilight Sparkle:
"Dear Princess Celestia,
"Friendship is a wondrous
and powerful thing.
"Even the worst of enemies
can become friends.
"You need understanding
and compromise.
You've got to share.
You've got to care."
Hey!
That's what I said!
* My Little Pony
* Friends