Oh, are you sure
about this, Scootaloo?
I've never even heard
of a pony zip-Lining before.
Neither have i,
But Spike
told me it was awesome!
Aah!
Whoa!
Oh!
See anything?
Tree sap and pine needles,
but no cutie mark.
Plan B?
Yeah.
You know where we can find
a cannon at this hour?
It's no use.
No matter what we try,
We always end up
without our cutie marks,
And, surprisingly often,
covered in tree sap.
Maybe we should do something
less dangerous,
Like pillow testing
Or flower sniffing.
This town is full of ponies
who have their cutie marks.
Why don't we ask them
how they did it?
That's a great,
safe idea.
Yeah, and we can start with
the coolest pony in Ponyville.
Applejack!
Rarity!
Come on, guys.
I said cool.
You know
who I'm talking about.
She's fast, she's tough,
she's not afraid of anything.
Pinkie Pie?
No! The greatest flyer
ever to come out of cloudsdale.
Fluttershy?
No!
Rainbow Dash!
Oh, yeah,
that makes much more sense.
Of course.
Let's do it.
Let's find out how Rainbow Dash
earned her cutie mark.
Yeah!
Ah!
Ah! Unh!
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
we have muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Get back here,
you thievin' varmints!
Thievin' what, now?
Whoa!
Apple Bloom?
Hey, sis, how'd you get
your cutie mark?
I never told you
that story?
Hey, I thought we were
gonna ask Rainbow Dash.
We need all the help
we can get.
Ugh! Fine.
Why, shoot,
I was just a little filly --
Even littler than y'all.
I didn't want to spend my life
on a muddy old apple farm.
I wanted to live
the sophisticated life,
Like my aunt and uncle orange.
So I set out to try my luck
in the big city -- Manehattan --
The most cosmopolitan city
in all of equestria.
Hey, out of the way! You rube!
I knew I'd find out who i
was meant to be in manehattan.
Aunt orange, uncle orange,
Thank y'all so much
for letting me stay.
"y'all."
Isn't she
just the living end?
How quaint.
Don't worry,
we'll have you acting
Like a true manehattanite
in no time.
And how are you finding
good old manehattan?
Oh, it's simply divine.
Very well said,
my dear.
Although, I must admit
The city noise
took some getting used to.
Where I'm from,
nights are so quiet,
You seldom hear a peep
until the roosters wake you.
The what?
I say, my dear, what
in the world is a...rooster?
What's he talking about?
What do I say? I don't
want to look like a fool.
Dinner is served.
Thank goodness.
Being a city pony
is hard work.
I'm so hungry,
I could eat a...
Cock-A-Doodle-Doo.
Oh, I wonder what Granny Smith
and Big Macintosh are up to.
I'll bet they're
Apple-Bucking their way
Through
the red delicious trees.
Oh, what I wouldn't give
for just one bite.
I never felt so homesick in all
my days as I did right then.
It was amazing.
A Rainbow,
pointing right back to home.
In that moment,
it all became clear.
I knew right then
just who I was supposed to be.
That's when this here
appeared.
I've been happily
working the farm ever since.
Ppbbhhtt!
There they are! Get back here,
you thievin' varmints!
Aww, that was
such a sweet story.
Sweet? Try sappy.
Come on, we've got to find
Rainbow Dash
And hear the cool way
to get a cutie mark.
Ohh!
Aah!
All right, little ones,
this way.
This way.
You really should be
more careful.
Somepony could get hurt.
Why are you
in such a hurry, anyway?
We're trying to find
Rainbow Dash
So we can hear how
she earned her cutie mark.
Oh? That would be
interesting.
You know, I wouldn't have gotten
my cutie mark
If it weren't for her.
Rainbow Dash?
Really?
Oh, yes. It all started
at summer flight camp.
You'd never guess,
but when I was little,
I was very shy
and a very weak flyer.
Ooh!
Aah! Yah!
Oh!
Nice going, cluttershy.
They ought to ground you
permanently.
Ha! My baby brother
can fly better than you.
It was the most humiliating
moment of my life.
And then,
out of nowhere...
leave her alone!
Ooh, what are you gonna do,
Rainbow crash?
Keep making fun of her
and find out!
You think
you're such a big shot?
Why don't you prove it?
What do you
have in mind?
You're going down.
In history maybe.
See you boys
at the finish line.
Ah, ah, aah!
Yaah!
Ah! Aah!
Huh?
I had never seen
such beautiful creatures.
Butterflies don't fly as high
as my cloud home,
And I had never been
near the ground before.
* what is this place
filled with so many wonders *
* casting its spell
that I am now under? *
* squirrels in the trees
and the cute little bunnies *
* birds flying free
and bees with their honey *
* hone-E-E-E-Y
* oh, what a magical place
* and I owe it all
to the pegasus race *
* if I knew that ground
had so much up its sleeve *
* I'd have come here sooner
and never leave *
* yes, I love
everyth-I-I-I-Ing *
Shh.
It's okay.
You can come out.
Everything's okay.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Somehow, I had the ability
To communicate with the animals
on a different level.
Wait, wait, wait.
What happened to Rainbow Dash?
What about the race?
Oh, well,
I wasn't there,
So I don't really know
what happened.
Come on, crusaders.
We've got to find her.
Besides, I can't take
any more singing.
Maybe my sister knows
where she is.
Bye, Fluttershy!
Bye, girls.
How did we
get roped into this?
We'll never hear
Rainbow Dash's story.
Are you girls still obsessing
over your cutie marks?
Of course.
Most of the fillies at school
already have theirs.
I know how you feel.
For the longest time,
I couldn't figure out
why I didn't have mine.
Well done, Rarity.
Your costumes are very nice.
Nice?!
They need to be spectacular!
And the performance
is tomorrow!
I tried every trick
I could think of,
But nothing seemed to work.
The costumes just weren't right,
and the play opened that night.
Maybe I'm not meant to be
a fashionista after all.
Aah!
What's going on?!
I had no idea
where my horn was taking me,
But unicorn magic doesn't happen
without a reason.
I knew this had to do
with my love of fashion --
And maybe even my cutie mark!
I knew that
this was my destiny!
A rock?!
That's my destiny?!
What is your problem, horn?!
I followed you all the way
out here for a rock?!
Hmph!
Dumb rock!
Aah!
Ooh!
Whoa!
Whoa!Whoa!
Ugh!
These namby-Pamby stories
Aren't getting us any closer
to our cutie marks!
They're all about finding
who you really are
And boring stuff
like that!
Yes, Scootaloo,
that's exactly --
Come on, girls,
we need action!
We need Rainbow Dash!
As a young filly in Canterlot,
I always wanted to go
to the Summer Sun Celebration,
Where princess Celestia
raises the sun.
And I saw the most amazing, most
wonderful thing I've ever seen.
I poured myself into learning
everything I could about magic.
My parents decided
to enroll me
In princess Celestia's
school for gifted unicorns.
It was a dream come true...
except for one thing.
I had to pass an entrance exam.
Well, miss Sparkle?
Well,
miss Sparkle?
We don't have
all day.
I knew it was the most important
day of my life,
That my entire future
would be affected
By the outcome of this day...
and I was about to blow it!
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Aah!
Twilight Sparkle...
I'm so sorry.
I didn't --
...you have
a very special gift.
I don't think I've ever
come across
A unicorn
with your raw abilities.
Huh?
But you need to learn
to tame these abilities
Through focused study.
Huh?
Twilight Sparkle,
I'd like to make you
My own personal protégé
here at the school.
Huh?!
Well?
Yes!
One other thing,
Twilight.
More?
My cutie mark!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes!
Okay, okay.
We're happy for you,
Twilight.
Yeah, thrilled.
Let's get out of here
while we still can.
Yes, yes! Yes!
Are you okay?
Um...yes.
Aw, why don't we ever
smash into Rainbow Dash?
You're looking for
Rainbow Dash?
If I was her,
I'd be at sugar cube corner.
Of course, if I was anyone,
Hey!
I have an idea.
Want to go
to sugar cube corner?
Well, we're sort of looking
for Rainbow Dash
So we can hear
how she got her cutie mark.
Cutie mark!
Come with me, and I'll
tell you how I got mine.
Why not?
All right!
My sisters and i
were raised
On a rock farm
outside of Ponyville.
We spent our days
working the fields.
There was no talking.
There was no smiling.
There were only rocks.
We were in the south field,
Preparing to rotate the rocks
to the east field,
When all of a sudden...
I never felt joy
like that before.
It felt so good I just
wanted to keep smiling forever.
And I wanted
everyone I knew to smile, too.
But Rainbows don't come along
that often.
I wondered, how else
could I create some smiles?
We better harvest the rocks
from the south field.
Pinkamina Diane Pie,
is that you?
Ma, I need you and dad
and the sisters
To come in here quick!
Surprise!
Do you like it?
It's called a party.
Oh, you don't like it.
You like it!
I'm so happy!
And that's
how equestria was made.
Wha-- Huh?
Look, we're here.
Maybe
on the way home
I can tell you the story
of how I got my cutie mark.
It's a gem.
Oh, come on.
She's just being Pinkie Pie.
Ugh.
Rainbow Dash!
You're here!
I hear you're looking
for my cutie-Mark story.
You have no idea
what I've been through today
To hear that story.
It all happened
during the race at flight camp
Where I stood alone
against all odds
To defend
Fluttershy's honor.
Ah, ah, aah!
I'd never flown like that
before.
The freedom was unlike anything
I'd ever felt.
The speed, the adrenaline,
the wind in my mane!
I liked it a lot!
Whoa!
Ha!
Later, Rainbow crash.
Hey!
Turns out the only thing I liked
more than flying fast...
whoa-Oh-Oh!
...was winning.
Most people thought
That the sonic rainboom
was just an old mare's tail.
But that day,
the day I discovered racing,
I proved
that the legends were true.
I made the impossible happen.
And that, little ones,
is how you earn a cutie mark.
Whoa!
Wait a second.
I heard that explosion,
and I saw the Rainbow, too.
Rainbow Dash, if you hadn't
scared the animals,
I never would have learned
I could communicate with them
And gotten
my cutie mark.
I heard that boom,
and right afterwards,
There was this amazing Rainbow
that taught me to smile.
When I got my cutie mark,
I saw a Rainbow
that pointed me home.
I bet it was
your sonic rainboom.
There was an explosion
I could never explain
When I got my cutie mark.
This is uncanny.
If that explosion didn't happen
when it did,
I would have blown
my entrance exam.
Rainbow Dash, I think you helped
me earn my cutie mark, too!
Whoa!
We all owe
our cutie marks to you!
Do you realize
what this means?
All of us had a special
connection before we even met.
We've been BFFs forever,
and we didn't even know it!
Come here, y'all.
Oh!
I love you guys.
Aww!
Ew!
Give me a break.
Come on, crusaders.
Maybe we just need to try
zip-Lining again.
Hey,
how about a song?
Yes!
Definitely!
N-O-O-O-O-O!
Dear princess Celestia,
Today I learned
something amazing.
Everypony everywhere
Has a special magical connection
with her friends,
Maybe even
before she's met them.
If you're feeling lonely
And you're still searching
for your true friends,
Just look up in the sky.
Who knows? Maybe you
and your future best friends
Are all looking
at the same Rainbow.
Gross.
When did you get so cheesy?
Just write it, Spike.