Aah!
I! Can't! Believe! The grand!
Galloping! Gala! Is! Tonight!
Pinkie,
please stop shouting.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Pinkie Pie,
stop that right now.
It's time to prepare
for the gala,
And I refuse to let you
put on your new dress
When you're all sweaty.
[ Screech! ]
[ Tinkling ]
What's Twilight doing?
She's got an awesome
magic spell
She's been working on
for the gala.
Where are the others?
It's getting late.
Hold your horses, girl.
We're here.
Perfect. I'm ready.
For what?
All right, Spike.
An apple!
Are we having Pie?
Shh! Watch.
[ Tinkling ]
[ Whoosh! ]
Awesome!
Lovely!
Ooh!
Thanks.
But that's
just the start.
Fluttershy,
did you bring your friends?
Yes.
Will they be safe,
Twilight?
You have my word.
[ Mice squeaking ]
[ Tinkling ]
[ Whoosh! ]
Ta-Da!
Oh.
Uh...
[ squeaking ]
Interesting.
Neat, huh?
And don't worry.
They'll be mice again
at midnight.
Opalescence, no!
[ Yowls ]
[ Neighing ]
Wait! Come back!
Those horses were supposed to
pull our carriage.
How will we get to the gala?
Whatever shall we do?
[ Slurping ]
Uh...
[ clears throat ] excuse me.
Uh, would you boys mind pulling
our carriage to the gala?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
we have muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Ooh!
[ Whirring ]
[ groans ]
Aw. Come on, you guys.
Let me in!
Sure thing, Spike.
Heavens, no!
We're getting dressed.
Dressed?
Uh, beg your pardon,
Rarity,
But we don't normally
wear clothes.
[ Groans ]
[ tinkling ]
I'm sorry, Spike.
Some of us do have standards.
I still can't believe
We're going to be at Canterlot
tonight, our hometown, Twilight.
And the best part is
That we all get to hang out
together all night long!
I don't know, Spike.
[ Tinkling ]
[ Blink! Blink! ]
We'll just have to see.
[ Spits ] we're gonna be
a might busy.
Busy having fun!
[ Boing! ]
Oh. Okay.
Don't worry, Spike.
We'll all get to spend
some time together.
Great!
'Cause I planned out
my insider's tour of Canterlot.
I've got to show Rarity
the crown jewels
And Applejack the princess'
golden apple tree.
And, Pinkie, we got to go
to my favorite doughnut shop.
All right!
Sounds good, Spike.
Show me around.
Then let's get moving.
Hyah!
Excuse me?!
Um, I...
if you weren't friends
with our neighbor Rarity...
hmph!
[ Boing! ]
Whoa!
You all look...amazing.
I can't believe
we're finally here.
With all that we've imagined,
The reality of this night
is sure to make this
The best night ever!
* at the gala
* at the gala,
in the garden *
* I'm going to see them all
* all the creatures,
I'll befriend them at the gala *
* at the gala
* all the birdies,
and the critters *
* they will love me,
big and small *
* we'll become good friends
forever *
* right here at the gala
* all our dreams
will come true *
* right here at the gala
* at the gala
* it's amazing
* it will sell them
all my Apple-Tastic treats *
* hungry ponies,
they will buy them *
* give me some
* caramel apples, apple sweets
* and I'll earn a lot of money
for the Apple family *
* all our dreams and our hopes
from now until hereafter *
* all that we've been wishing
for will happen at the gala *
* at the gala
* at the gala, all the royals,
they will meet fair Rarity *
* they will see I'm just
as regal at the gala *
* at the gala
* I will find him,
my prince charming *
* and he'll guarantee we'll be
* he will treat me like a lady
tonight at the gala *
* this is what we've waited for,
to have the best night ever *
* each of us will live our
dreams tonight at the gala *
* at the gala
[ Fanfare ]
[ Whooshing ]
* been dreamin',
I've been waitin' *
* to fly
with those great ponies *
* the Wonderbolts,
their daring tricks *
* spinning 'round
and having kicks *
* perform for crowds
of thousands *
* they'll shower us
with diamonds *
* the Wonderbolts will see me
right here at the gala *
* all our hopes and all our
dreams, our Happy-Ever-After *
* finally they'll all come true
right here at the grand gala *
* at the gala
* I am here at the grand gala,
for it is the best party *
* but the one thing
it was missing *
* was a pony named "Pinkie"
* for I am the best at parties
* all the ponies will agree
* ponies playing, ponies dancing
with me at the grand gala *
* happiness and laughter
at the gala *
* at the gala
[ Twinkling ]
* at the gala,
with the princess *
* is where I'm going to be
* we will talk all about magic
and what I've learned and seen *
* it is going to be so special
as she takes time just for me *
* this will be
the best night ever *
* into the gala we must go
* we're ready now,
we're all aglow *
* into the gala, let's go in
and have the best night ever *
* into the gala,
now's the time *
* we're ready
and we look divine *
* into the gala
* meet new friends
* sell some apples
* into the gala
* find my prince
* true, fine prince
* and the Wonderbolts
* to meet
* to sell
* to find
* to prove
* to whoop
* to talk
* into the gala
* and we'll have
the best night ever *
[ Boom! Boom! Boom! ]
* at the gala
Yeah! This is gonna be
the best night ever.
You know why?
'Cause we're all gonna spend
time at the gala to--
Whoa!
[ Rattle! ]
--Gether.
Or not.
Princess Celestia.
Twilight.
It is so lovely
to see my star student.
Oh, I'm so excited
to be here.
We have so much
to catch up on.
Well, I want you right
by my side the entire evening
So we'll have plenty
of time together.
[ Zip! ]
That's just what I was hoping
you'd say.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Squeals ]
Hurry, Rarity.
But not too fast.
I don't want to lose him.
[ Gasps ]
have to play it cool.
Oh, but don't be cold!
I can't lose him! I can't!
He's everything I imagined!
[ Wind whistles ]
Even better than I imagined.
[ Bird tweeting ]
Oh, my.
A meadow lark.
[ Bird tweeting ]
[ Gasps ]
I think she's calling to me.
It's exactly what I wished for.
* ah-Ah-Ah-Ah-Ah
[ Bird tweets melody ]
Howdy, partner.
You hungry?
As a horse!
Well,
what you hankerin' for?
Carmel apple? Apple Pie?
Apple fritter? Apple fries?
I'll take
that big apple Pie!
Well,
thank you kindly, sir.
Yee-Haw!
In the first minute,
I made my first sale,
just like I expected.
Always hungry after a show,
eh, soren?
[ Chuckles ] yeah!
[ Gasps ]
My Pie!
[ Zoom! ]
You saved it. Thanks.
Hey, no prob.
Hey, I know you.
You're the pony that saved us
in cloudsdale
And won the best-Flier
competition.
Hey, yeah.
Name's Rainbow Dash.
Well, Rainbow Dash, looks like
your skills saved us again.
Well, at least,
they saved Soren's apple pie.
[ Munching ] yeah!
[ Slurps ]
Want to come
hang out with us?
Sure. Why not?
[ Ting! Ting! Ting! ]
I'm hanging
with the Wonderbolts!
[ Squeals ]
[ Laughs ]
Oh! The shiny dance floor!
The pretty party ponies!
Ooh! The fancy band!
Shiny, pretty, fancy!
[ Whimpers ]
Got to dance!
* I'm at
the grand galloping gala *
* it's all I ever dreamed
whoo-Hoo! *
yippee! *
* I'm at the grand galloping
gala-A-A-A-A-A-A *
[ Cough ]
* it's all I've ever dreamed?
Well, hello.
I am prince Blueblood.
I am Rarity.
Oh, my,
what a lovely rose.
You mean...
this rose?
Thank you.
It goes with my eyes.
[ Groans ]
* ah-Ah-Ah-Ahh
[ Bird tweets melody ]
[ Gasps ]
My little meadow lark
is right around this bend.
[ Whistles melody ]
Was that you?
Yep. I love whistling
while I work.
[ Whistles melody ]
Oh. Yes, well, excuse me.
[ Monkey screeching ]
Oh, I see a toucan.
And a spider monkey.
And, oh, is that a wallaroo?
Oh, Fluttershy,
you're such a loudmouth.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Hey!
Have you ever done a rain cloud
double back flip?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Have you ever
swerved past lightning?
It's awesome!
Welcome to
the grand galloping gala.
Princess, I've been so excited
to spend time with you, and --
Yes, me too, twi--
Oh, good evening.
Welcome to the gala.
Which is why I --
Ladies.
Lovely to see you again.
[ Sighs ]
Looks like getting a chance
to talk to the princess
Is gonna be
a magic trick in itself.
First minute, first sale.
Second.
Fourth.
Sixth.
60th minute, no sales.
[ Sighs ] this ain't
what I expected at all.
* I'm at
the grand galloping gala *
And it's not what I dreamed.
This isn't at all
what I imagined.
Good evening.
Welcome.
This isn't
what I hoped.
This isn't hanging out.
[ Birds chirping ]
This isn't what I wished for.
No.
I waited all my life...
for this moment.
And I'm not going to...
let it slip by.
If it's the last thing I do...
I'm gonna make this...
all: the best night ever!
I just have to be more bold,
like Twilight says.
I'm so sorry to have scared you,
my friends.
But I'm leaving now,
so you can all come out.
[ Whip! ]
[ Munching ]
Gotcha!
It's okay.
I promise not to hurt you.
I just want to be your --
Friend?
Mmm!
Sounds good to me.
Come on, Rainbow.
If they don't notice you, you
got to make them notice you!
[ Whistling ]
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
Just give him a chance,
Rarity.
His princely side is sure to
come out if you're just patient.
Miss Rarity, stop!
Oh!
Prince blueblood,
how chivalrous.
One would hate to slip.
Yes, one certainly would.
One's cloak should take care
of the problem.
Oh, of course it will.
[ Gasps ]
[ Whispering ]
And then...
and then I want you to do this.
[ Horn blows ]
[ Feedback ]
Come on, everypony!
I know what'll make you
shake those groove things!
* you reach your right hoof in
* you reach
your right hoof out *
* you reach your right hoof in,
and you shake it all about *
* you do the pony pokey, meeting
lots of folks with clout *
* that's what
I'm talking about *
* you step your left hoof in
* you pull it right back out
* you step your left hoof in,
but you better help him out *
* you do the pony pokey,
but you find a different crowd *
* that's what it's all about
* you kick your back left in
* you pull your back left out
* you reach your back left in
* just be brave
and have no doubt *
* you do the pony pokey
* feeling like
you're gonna pout *
* that's what
I'm singing about *
* you tilt your head in
* you tilt your head out
* you tilt your head in,
then you shake it all about *
* you do the pony pokey,
even though your date's a lout *
* you're better off without
* you stomp your whole self in
* you stomp
your whole self out *
* you stomp your whole self in,
and you stomp yourself about *
* you do the pony pokey,
and you give a little shout *
Come out!
* that's what
I'm talking about *
* you do the pony pokey
* and that's what
it's all about *
Yeah!
Young lady, this is not
that kind of party!
Oh-H-H-H-H.
They don't want to party.
These ponies
want to pa-A-A-Rty!
Two apple fritters,
please.
Two apple fritters
coming right up.
That'll be 4 bits.
Ahem.
I'm going to have to pay,
aren't i?
It's okay, Rarity.
I got you covered.
Thank you, Applejack.
At least some pony here
had good manners.
Blech! Ugh!
Fritters! Dumplings!
Caramel apples!
My royal lips have touched
common carnival fare!
I'm going to the buffet
for some hors d'oeuvres.
Well, no wonder
no pony wants my food.
They're filling up on all those
fancy-Schmancy vittles.
Well, my down-Home apples
Are plenty good enough
for this crowd.
I'll just dress them up a bit
and prove it to them.
I'll catch you yet,
my pretties. Oh, yes.
As soon as one of you little
birds or monkeys or bears
Touches this net,
you'll be mine.
Mine! [ Laughs maniacally ]
[ Thunder crashing ]
Wha--
[ Dance beat plays ]
come on, everypony!
You wanted a part-Ay?
Now let's party!
Yeah! Unh!
Now, that's a beat! Yeah!
Come on! Dance!
Yeah! Whoo-Hoo!
Okay,
all you high-Class ponies.
Here's a highfalutin
apple cake
For all your
hoity-Toity taste buds.
Stage dive!
Aah!
[ Squish! ]
[ Growls ]
You, sir, are the most
uncharming prince
I have ever met!
In fact, the only thing
royal about you
Is that you are
a royal pain!
Ew! Stay back!
I just
had myself groomed!
Afraid to get dirty?!
Aah! Aah!
[ Grunting ]
Whoa!
Aah!
[ Metal creaking ]
This is my chance!
[ Zoom! ]
Yes!
Whoa!
[ Crashing ]
Well,
it can't get any worse.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Animals screeching ]
You're going to love me!
Oh. Uh...
[ gasps ]
Run.
[ Whistles ]
Ooh! Rarity,
your glass slipper!
Now your prince
is sure to find you!
[ Shrieks ]
[ Grunts ]
Let's go!
[ Zip! ]
Hey, Pony Joe,
another doughnut.
Don't you think
you've had enough?
Another doughnut!
Extra sprinkles!
[ Bell chimes ]
Twilight Sparkle.
[ Chuckles ]
Long time, no see.
Hey, how was the gala?
How was your best night ever?
That sounds like
the worst night ever.
It was!
[ Laughter ]
I just hope princess Celestia
isn't upset with us
For ruining the gala.
Celestia: that was the best
Grand Galloping Gala ever!
All: princess Celestia.
Pardon me, princess,
but tonight was just awful.
Oh, Twilight, the Grand
Galloping Gala is always awful.
It is?
That is why
I was thrilled
You were all attending.
I was hoping you could
liven things up a bit.
And while the evening may not
have gone as you planned,
I'm sure you'll agree
that in the end,
It didn't turn out so bad
for this group of friends.
You're right, princess.
Friends have a way of making
even the worst of times
Into something
pretty great.
Yeah!
Hanging out with friends.
Talking.
Laughing!
You mean doing exactly what
I wanted to do the whole time?
Yes, Spike.
You were right.
As horrible
as our night was...
being together here
has made it all better.
In fact, it's made it...
all: the best night ever!
[ Laughter ]