Here? I get to stay here?
Twilight Sparkle said you were
coming to Canterlot for a visit...
...and asked if
I might accommodate you.
Thank you so much, princess.
You're very welcome.
No, really. This is so nice of you.
It's nothing, really.
Oh, but it isn't nothing.
It's everything.
I-I just don't know what to say
but thank you, thank you!
Thank you... Thank you...
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
-You are very welc...
-Thank you!
Your luggage, mademoiselle?
I'll leave you to get settled.
Your highness...
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you!
Where would you like me to put these?
That's perfect.
Opal, do you know what
I love about Canterlot?
Everything!
I may have been born in Ponyville,
but I am a Canterlot pony at heart.
Now I know that we are here
to pick up some fabrics for the shop...
...but Twilight was such a dear
to get me that suite at the castle...
...I simply must make her something
to express my gratitude.
Ooh!
An outfit for her birthday party
this weekend! Perfect!
Don't you just love it
here, Opalescence?
Please excuse our interruption.
I'm Jet Set and this
is my wife, Upper Crust.
We saw you from across the café
and just have to find out...
Where did you get that
simply marvelous chapeau?
Huh, this old thing?
Oh, it's just something I...
Rarity!
Hey, Rarity!
It's me! Hayseed Turnip Truck!
We met at the big hoedown
in Ponyville last month.
Oh... Yes... Of course. How are you?
Good! Real good!
You're from... Ponyville?
Well, ye... yes, but...
She sure is! She's a real big time
fancy pants dressmaker there.
Probably made that real purty
thing she's got on her head.
I thought it looked a little... country.
I told you it wasn't something you
could get here in Canterlot, dear.
Well, they seemed real nice.
"Looked a little country."
"Not something you could
get in Canterlot."
I'll show you something
worthy of Canterlot!
I have to get started right away.
This new design is very ambitious...
...and I've already written
to Twilight to let her know...
...she'll have something beyond
fabulous to wear to her party.
Fancypants?
I say, that's one way
to make the introduction.
Oh, goodness!
I am so sorry. I didn't see you there.
I've just got so many bags...
...and I was trying to get back
to my suite at the castle and...
You're staying at the castle?
Wh... The princess invited me
to stay in one of the suites.
You know the princess?
Hmm... A pony with
expensive taste, I see.
Oh... It's for an ensemble
I'm making for a friend.
Her birthday is in a few days.
Again, I am really sorry
I bumped into you.
I'm not.
You are obviously somepony
worth bumping into.
Uh, listen. I have a VIP box reserved
at the Wonderbolts Derby this afternoon.
Would you... Would you be so kind...
...as to join me and a few
of my companions there, hmm?
Me?
But of course, my dear.
Well, I'm... uh... I'm not sure.
We'd love to see you there, uh...
Rarity.
...Rarity.
Pro: seeing the derby from a VIP box
is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Con: going to the derby cuts
into the amount of time...
...I have to finish Twilight's outfit.
Pro: Fancypants is *the* most
important pony in Canterlot.
His stamp of approval could
mean big things for me here.
Con: Twilight's party might not be
as sophisticated as a derby...
...but that doesn't mean
I shouldn't put all of my energy...
...into creating her birthday ensemble.
My Ponyville friends will appreciate
my hard work more than anypony.
I hate to let them down.
And I won't.
Opal, I am going to the Wonderbolts
Derby as a guest of Fancypants.
Pardon me.. Excuse me... Excuse me...
Rarity! Jolly good to see you!
So glad you could make it.
Everypony, this is Rarity.
She is staying at Canterlot Castle.
Fillies and gentlecolts!
Welcome to the Wonderbolts Derby!
The competitors are taking their
places at the starting line...
...and the race will begin momentarily.
I'll be rooting for Rapidfire, of course.
He's sure to take home the grand prize.
I don't think he has
a chance against Fleetfoot.
And it's Fleetfoot by a nose!
Bravo, Rarity!
I say, how did you know
Fleetfoot would be victorious?
My friend Rainbow Dash
talks about her all the time.
She says what Fleetfoot lacks
in size, she makes up for in speed.
And who is this Rainbow Dash?
Why... she's...
She's the... the Wonderbolts'
trainer, of course.
Staying at Canterlot Castle AND she knows
the pegasus training the Wonderbolts!
I told you all this was
an important pony.
Three cheers for Rarity,
my new favorite party guest.
Hip hip, hurray! Hip hip, hurray!
Hip hip, hurray!
...and then I said: "Please,
that isn't a hat, darling."
"That's a natural disaster, that
somehow landed atop your head!"
Oh, you are a delight, Rarity.
An absolute delight.
You simply must attend my
art gallery opening this evening.
Oh. I'd love to, but I...
And let's not forget my charity
auction tomorrow morning.
That sounds wonderful, but I...
And of course there's a seat for you
at my dinner party tomorrow night.
I'm flattered. Really.
It's just I have a project I really
need to get started on and...
Oh, but Rarity!
I may as well close down the whole
gallery if you can't attend!
My auction is for charity,
dear. For charity!
And my dinner party will be
a disaster if you don't come.
Of course I'll be there.
-Wonderful!
-Disaster averted.
Looks like we'll be spending a few
more days here, Opalescence.
Turns out bumping into
Fancypants like that...
...was the best thing that's
ever happened to me.
Of course finishing
Twilight's dress in time...
...for her birthday party
is still my top priority.
But I can't possibly disappoint
the Canterlot elite...
...by rejecting their
invitations, now can I?
I'll be the toast of the town,
the girl on the go
And the type of pony
everypony, everypony should know
I'll be the one to watch,
the girl in the flow
And the type of pony
everypony, everypony should know
Becoming as popular
as popular can be
Making my mark, making my mark
in high society
I'm the belle of the ball,
the star of the show, yeah
And the type of pony
everypony, everypony should know
See how they hang on
every word that I speak
My approving glance
is what they all seek
I'm the crème de la crème,
not just another Jane Doe
And the type of pony
everypony should know
At home, at the opera,
on a fancy yacht
Becoming the talk,
the talk of all of Canterlot
I'm the crème de la crème,
not just another Jane Doe, yeah
And the type of pony
everypony, everypony should know
Because I'm the type of pony
Yes, I'm the type of pony
everypony should know
Oh, I hope I haven't forgotten anything.
Me... too...
We better get going.
I must get back to Ponyville...
...with enough time
to finish Twilight's ensemble.
For me?
"Dearest Rarity, your
presence is requested..."
"...at the Canterlot Garden
Party tomorrow afternoon."
"Yours, Jet Set and Upper Crust."
The Canterlot Garden Party!
Why, next to the Galloping Gala that is
*the* premier event of Canterlot!
Ooh. But if I go,
I'll miss Twilight's birthday.
But if I don't go, my new
reputation in Canterlot...
...as a Very Important
Pony might be ruined!
I might never be invited to another
high society event again!
Friend's birthday – Very Important Pony...
It's just too important.
"My dear Twilight. I am afraid..."
"...I won't be able to make it
to your birthday party tomorrow..."
"...because..."
Because poor Opal is quite ill!
And she is in no condition to make
the long journey back to Ponyville.
"I do hope you understand.
Your friend, Rarity."
I suppose this means you don't
need me to bring down your bags?
No.
But I will need some
help unpacking them.
What do you think? Too much?
You're right. Too little.
Garden party, here I come!
SURPRISE!
And SWOOSH! And right before
she hit the ground, SHOOM, she...
Hi again!
W-What are you...
How did you... Why are you...
Listen to her. She's so excited
to see us, she can hardly talk.
What I mean to say is,
what are you all doing here?
When I got your letter saying
you were stuck in Canterlot...
...I asked Pinkie Pie if it
wouldn't be too much trouble...
...to move my birthday party here,
so you wouldn't have to miss it.
Balloons are super easy to pack.
Wow. First you get me a suite
at Canterlot Castle and now this...
I don't know what to say, Twilight.
How about you start by saying what
you're doing in that fancy getup.
This? Uh.. Well, I...
I always put on something a little fancy
when Opal's feeling under the weather.
Cheers her right up.
Oh, poor Opal.
Where is the sick darling?
Oh, uh... she's...
Hold on a minute.
I am so sorry about this.
She's resting on the bed.
Poor baby. She looks awful.
Is that my dress?
Yes...
It's so simple. So practical.
So... ME!
It's the perfect dress
for my birthday party!
I love it!
You don't know how glad
I am to hear you say that.
When I told the princess that I was
moving the party to Canterlot...
...she was kind enough to offer us
the Canterlot Castle ballroom.
Isn't it fancy pants?
Fancypants!
Where?!
I... mean...
...where did you find the time
to put up all these decorations?
Oh, I never leave home
without my party cannon!
Ta-da!
I thought about having
my birthday outside...
...but they're having another party
on the castle grounds today.
LET'S PARTY!
No reason I can't at least
make an appearance.
I'm here!
Darling, I'm so glad you made it.
Rarity! So happy to see you here.
I wouldn't have missed
this for the world.
I say, what is that
scent you're wearing?
It smells like...
Is that cake frosting?
Yes, I always dab a little frosting
behind my ears before I go out.
After all, who doesn't like
the smell of cake frosting?
I know I do.
Well, all this talk about cake
has made me hungry.
Think I'll go and see what's
on the hors d'oeuvre table.
If you'll excuse me...
-I must say, you do look like a...
-Oh, yes, darling.
I think I left the bath water
running in my suite.
I really should go check on Opal.
Is that Princess Celestia?
I need to use the little filly's room.
Can I get anypony more punch?
I... have to go to do the...
...thing with the... stuff, you know.
Uh... What's with the croquet mallet?
-[What croquet mallet?]
-Duh! The one in your mouth.
Oh, that croquet mallet.
I... well, I... you know,
the truth is... the truth is...
Were you at that other
party in the garden?
I... I... I...
Rarity, I'm surprised at you.
Twilight, let me explain! I...
I hadn't realized you were
such a savvy businesspony.
You must understand! I...
All of those ponies look so posh.
And with the Grand
Galloping Gala coming up...
...I bet you could totally get
some of them to buy your dresses.
Very smart.
Wh... wwwhyyy, yes! Uh...
I didn't want you to think
I was being rude...
...so that's exactly
the reason I didn't tell you.
The one and only reason.
Oh, well. You didn't have to do that.
You should totally go
over there and mingle.
Twilight, you really are the best
friend a pony could ever ask for.
I don't know why I ever thought
you wouldn't understand.
Understand what?
Nothing!
See you girls later!
Hey, wait up!
We're your friends. I'm sure they won't
mind if we check out the party too.
Come on, you guys! Let's show 'em
how to party Ponyville style!
Oh no!
How come y'all aren't
doin' any gardenin'?
This is a garden party, isn't it?
Can you believe what
that pony is wearing?
It's just so plain.
Yeah...
Excuse me. Might I ask where
you got you ensemble?
Why, yes. Yes, you may.
A very, very close friend of mine
from Ponyville made it for me.
Ponyville? You don't say.
I do say. Her name is...
Fancypants! Come with me.
I'd like to show you...
this thing that's over there.
On the other side of the room.
In a moment, my dear.
This lovely filly from Ponyville
was just about to tell me...
...who made her charming dress.
That dress? Oh, come now.
Who cares? It's just a plain old...
Oh, don't be so modest.
This dress you made is beautiful.
We all think so.
You know these ponies?
Yes. Yes, I do know them.
They may not be as sophisticated
as some of you Canterlot ponies...
...but they are my best friends
and they are without a doubt...
...the most important ponies I know.
"Important ponies"? These ruffians?
Don't make me laugh.
I, for one, find them charmingly rustic.
And I think the dress you made
for your friend is lovely.
I dare say every mare
in Canterlot will be wanting one.
Oh, I'd like to place my order right now.
I think you should get two, hmm?
Uh, yes. Now then...
How about you introduce me
to your friends?
With pleasure.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"I wanted to tell you about the important
lesson I learned during my visit."
Now that I would like to hear.
I learned that no matter
where you go in life...
...you should never forget that you are
the product of your home and your friends.
And that is something always
to be proud of, no matter what.
A very valuable lesson to have learned.
It certainly is...
...but might I ask that
we hurry things up a bit?
Oooh nooo!
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000