Who could that be?
It's still dark!
C'mon, Fluttershy! Cider
season's about to start!
Oh, where are we?
What's the rush?
The rush? Don't you remember
what happened last year?
Or the year before that?
Or pretty much any cider season ever?!
Um, well...
Pinkie Pie!
She always ends up ahead of us in line,
and then they always run out of cider!
- I guess I...
- Well not this year!
This year, I'm gonna get there before sunrise...
...so I can drink all the cider I want,
and laugh when she doesn't get any!
It's the perfect plan.
I might even buy some cider and hold onto it for a while...
...drinking it drop by drop in front of her...
Gee Rainbow Dash, it looks like a few
other ponies had the same idea.
Oh, gosh Pinkie, I love your new style.
Who are all these ponies?!
Isn't this great?
I couldn't sleep last night 'cause
I was so excited about cider season...
...and I had this brilliant idea
to come gather and camp out...
...so I told a few others about it and
they all thought it was a great idea too...
...and now it's just a big old cider party! Woohoo!
Oh gosh, that's a lot of ponies.
Hope they don't run out before you get any.
Subbed and Synced by GrayJeager
http://grayjeager.blogspot.com
GrayJeager@gmail.com
Isn't this exciting, Spike?
Opening day of cider season!
Yeah! That means it's only thirty
more days to sapphire season!
Attention, everypony! Cider
season is now officially open!
Sorry everypony!
That's it for today!
Surprise, surprise...
You ran out again!
Yeah, you always run out!
For the record, I don't mind...
Why can't you make enough cider for all of us?
Or at least for me!
Hold on everypony, we've done
our best to improve supply this year.
You always say that!
And it's always true.
But Apple family cider is made
with love and integrity...
...and only the highest quality apples in Equestria.
Sorry, but that recipe takes time.
If y'all just be patient, we'll
have plenty more tomorrow.
She's right, y'know!
You can't rush perfection!
And this year's batch was perfection!
Uh, Pinkie Pie...
I'll never forget the cider I just drank!
It was a moment in time that will never exist again...
What in Equestria is that?
Well, lookie what we got here, brother of mine,
it's the same in every town
Ponies with thirsty throats, dry tongues,
and not a drop of cider to be found
Maybe they're not aware that there's
really no need for this teary despair
And the key that they need to solve the
sad cider shortage you and I will share
Well you've got opportunity
In this very community
He's Flim, he's Flam
We're the world famous Flim Flam brothers
Travelling salesponies nonpareil
Non-pa what?
Nonpareil, that's exactly the reason why, you see
Nopony else in this whole place will give you
such a chance to be where you need to be
And that's a new world, with tons of cider
Fresh squeezed and ready for drinking
More cider than you could drink
in all your days of thinking
I doubt that.
So take this opportunity
In this very community
He's Flim, he's Flam
We're the world famous Flim Flam brothers
Travelling salesponies nonpareil
I suppose by now you're wondering,
about our peculiar mode of transport
I say, our mode of locomotion
And I suppose by now you're wondering,
where is this promised cider?
Any horse can make a claim
and any pony can do the same
But my brother and I have something
most unique and superb
Unseen at any time in this great new world
And that's opportunity
Folks, the one and only, the biggest and the best
The unbelievable
Unimpeachable
Indispensable
I can't believe-able
Flim Flam brothers' Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000
What d'you say, sister?
Oh, we got opportunity
In this very community
Please Flim, please Flam, help us out of this jam
With the Flim Flam brothers'
Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000
Young filly, I would be ever so honored if
you might see fit to let my brother and I...
...borrow some of your delicious, and might I add...
...spell-bindingly fragrant apples for
our little demonstration here?
Uh, sure, I guess.
Opportunity, in our community
- Ready Flim?
- Ready Flam.
Let's bing-bang zam!
And show these thirsty ponies
a world of delectable cider!
Cider, cider, cider, cider, cider, cider...
Watch closely, my friends!
The fun begins!
Now, here's where the magic happens.
Right here in this heaving roiling cider
press boiling guts of the very machine...
...those apples plucked fresh are right now as we speak...
...being turned into grade-A top-notch five-star
blow-your-horses-off one-of-a-kind cider!
Feel free to take a sneak peek!
Now wait, you fellas, hold it!
You went and over-sold it!
I guarantee that what you have there won't compare
For the very most important ingredient
Can't be added or done expedient
And it's quality, friends, Apple Acre's quality and care!
Well Granny, I'm glad you brought that up,
my dear, I say I'm glad you brought that up
You see that we are very picky when
it comes to cider if you'll kindly try a cup
Yes, sir, yes ma'am this great machine,
it's just the very best
So whaddaya say then, Apples
Care to step into the modern world
And put the Super Speedy Cider
Squeezy 6000 to the test?
What do you think, folks?
Do you see what the Apples can't?
I see it clear as day!
I know she does! So does he!
C'mon Ponyville, you know
what I'm talking about!
We're saying you've got
Opportunity
In this very community
He's Flim, he's Flam
We're the world famous Flim Flam brothers
Traveling salesponies nonpareil
Yeah!
You got a deal!
Not so fast!
No way no how that machine matches up
with the care we put in our cider!
But if it really does work, we could
make everypony in town happy!
I just don't know, y'all. We've
always made cider the same way.
Eeyup.
We'll sweeten the deal.
You supply the apples...
We supply the Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000.
Then we split those sweet sweet profits...
Seventy five...
- Twenty five.
Deal!
Hold on, who gets the seventy five?
Why us, naturally.
And, we'll throw in the magic
to power the machine for free.
Cider sales keep our business
afloat through the winter.
We'd lose Sweet Apple Acres if we agreed to this.
So? What'll it be?
No deal.
Very well, if you refuse our
generous offer to be partners...
...then we'll just have to be competitors.
You wouldn't dare.
Oh no?
Don't you worry, everypony!
There'll be plenty of cider for all of you!
Once we drive Sweet Apple Acres out of business.
Still worried about Flim and Flam?
Granny Smith says they were just blowing hot air.
I'm not so sure.
They sounded mighty serious when they
threatened to run us out of business.
That's it! Last cup!
Oh for Pete's sake!
C'mon back tomorrow, everypony!
*Tomorrow?*
What seems to be the problem here?
Oh my oh my, out of cider again?
What have we here?
Who'd like a cup?
Don't worry, everypony, we've got the Super Speedy
Cider Squeezy 6000 to make more in an instant!
You can't sell that cider!
That's made from Apple family apples!
Is this some kind of cruel joke?
Don't worry, everypony, there are
plenty of apples in Equestria.
We'll find some others and make more
cider than all of Ponyville can drink!
We'll make more cider than you could ever imagine!
Now, it ain't about the speed,
young'un, it's about quality.
Who cares how good the cider is,
if I never get to drink any?
Oh, look at these poor, dissatisfied ponies.
Ponyville is Sweet Apple Cider country!
Our cider speaks for itself!
Let's put it to the test!
Anywhere, anytime!
Well, that's enough, now.
With our machine, we can make enough cider
in one hour to satisfy this entire town!
We'll do it in 45 minutes!
Easy, Apple Bloom, easy.
What's the matter, Granny Smith? Chicken?
What did you call me, sonny?
If you're so confident in your cider,
then what's the problem?
Tomorrow mornin', right here!
But I'm afraid we haven't any... apples.
You can use our south field...
...and it'd be worth it to teach you
all a thing or two about cider making!
Excellent, we have a bet.
Whoever produces the most barrels in one hour,
wins the exclusive right to sell cider in Ponyville.
And after we beat ya, I don't never want to
see you bimbahoozalers around here again!
Until... tomorrow.
Don't worry, Applejack,
I know you'll win tomorrow!
We'd better, 'cause if we don't,
we're gonna lose our farm!
Applejack? Are you sure
this is such a good idea?
Me and the family are...
a hundred percent confident...
...in our cider making capabilities.
And besides, nopony calls Granny a chicken.
Attention everypony!
Well, good luck.
Thanks Twilight.
We'll need it.
The teams have one hour to produce
as much cider as they can.
After which, the barrels will be counted...
...and the winner will be named the
sole cider provider for all of Ponyville!
Are both teams ready?
Ready!
Then let's...
...go!
Bad 'un. Good 'un!
Bad 'un...
Great job, y'all!
We've already filled an entire barrel!
I'll bet you those guys don't even have...
C'mon, Apple Bloom, focus!
We gotta forget those guys if we're
gonna have a chance of winnin'!
Sorry, sis! Better keep up, Granny,
we're fallin' behind!
Good 'un... bad 'un...
Rest when it's over, Big Macintosh!
Ride! Ride!
This is just dreadful.
Even at top speed, the Apples are only
making one barrel to the twins' three!
Miss Mayor! Are honorary family members
allowed to help in the competition?
Well, I'm not sure...
Flim, Flam, would you object to
honorary family members helping?
Are you kidding?
We don't care if the whole
kingdom of Canterlot helps.
It's a lost cause.
I guess it's okay.
Applejack? What do you think?
I think I'd love to have the
rest of my family helpin' out.
All right!
Okay everypony, we're not gonna let those
smooth talkers take our friend's farm.
Yeah!
Fluttershy, help Applejack with the trees.
Got it.
Pinkie Pie, you're on apple catching detail.
Yes sir, ma'am, sir!
Rarity, you've got a discerning eye.
Help Granny Smith at the quality control station.
Of course.
Rainbow Dash, do you think you
can help Big Macintosh press?
In my sleep!
Alright everypony, let's save Sweet Apple Acres!
All right!
Over there, Apple Bloom!
Don't miss them!
Right behind you, Pinkie Pie!
Good 'un, bad 'un, bad 'un, good 'un...
Lovely, horrid, horrid, lovely...
Based on these figures, we're making
five barrels for every three of theirs!
Keep it up, everypony!
We're back in this!
Come on, brother, we've gotta pick up the pace!
Right, double the power!
We gotta try something else!
I've got it, brother of mine.
Well done, Flam!
We're at top productivity!
C'mon, Rainbow Dash, keep grinding!
We don't have time for quality control,
if we wanna win this thing!
Get back, you!
One bad apple spoils the bunch!
Applejack, help me!
There's no point in winnin' if we cheat!
We'll just have to work harder!
C'mon, everypony!
All right then, double time!
Time's up!
I'm proud of you, Applejack.
Thanks.
Integrity like that, will always be... rewarded.
Flim and Flam win!
We... lost?
Too bad, Apples.
Guess you'll just have to find a new line of work
that doesn't match your names quite so... perfectly.
Now should we tear down all these tacky
old buildings and put up new ones, brother?
I don't see why not, brother.
After all, this isn't Sweet Apple Acres anymore.
How about 'Flim Flam Fields'?
I ought to press you into jerk cider!
No, Rainbow Dash.
A deal's a deal.
Congratulations to y'all.
The cider business in Ponyville... is yours.
C'mon, Apples. Let's go pack up our things.
Fear not, everypony. There's more
than enough cider to go around.
Go ahead, everypony.
Go on, y'all. It's okay.
Drink up, Ponyville!
Down the hatch!
I can't get the taste off my tongue!
Mine's got rocks in it.
I wouldn't pay one cent for this dreck!
You wouldn't pay even one cent?
No!
How about two cups for one cent?
Two bits for a barrel?
No!
It looks like we've encountered a slight...
...problem here, in Ponyville.
Nopony wants our product. Next town?
Next town.
- Let's go, Flim!
- Let's go, Flam!
They're gone.
That means Sweet Apple Acres is still in business!
Plus we can have high quality Apple family cider!
Because of this silly competition...
...we've made enough of our
cider for the whole town!
"Dear Princess Celestia..."
"...I wanted to share my thoughts with you. "
"I didn't learn anythin'!
I was right all along!"
"If you take your time to do things the
right way, your work will speak for itself."
"Sure, I could tell you I learned something about
how my friends are always there to help me..."
"...and I can count on them no matter what..."
"...but truth is, I knew that already too."