Hey Rarity, hey Pinkie Pie.
What are you looking at?
Rainbow Dash!
Isn't she the most daring devil?
I mean, the most devilish darer?
I mean...
She's dazzling!
Oh yeah, that's a good word.
- Oh no, oh no, oh no!
- Ayayayayay!
So much for dazzling...
Is she gonna be okay?
I'm so worried!
Is her face gonna stay that way?
- How is she, doctor?
- She's going to be fine.
Luckily, she has friends like you
who got her over here in a jiffy.
How long do I need to lie here?
I've got things I need to do!
Well, that all depends on your recovery.
But I'd say a few days minimum.
You guys have gotta get me out of here!
I'm gonna climb the walls!
Just like a spider!
Did the crash somehow give her
super-duper spider powers?
No.
Nor did it give her amazing
healing powers.
She needs to stay in bed for a few days.
Few days? Might as well be
a few months, or few years!
It's not so bad, Rainbow Dash.
I bet the chow in here
is hoof-lickin' good!
And the hospital gowns,
they match the curtains!
And look!
You have a roommate!
What's this?
"Daring Do and the Quest
for the Sapphire Stone."
This is the first story in the series.
I own all of them.
No thanks.
I so don't read.
I'm a world-class athlete.
Reading's for eggheads like you,
Twilight.
No offense, but I am not reading.
It's undeniably, unquestionably, uncool.
Is she serious?
Who doesn't like to read
a bang-up tale from time to time?
A good book is almost as magnificent as
silk pajamas on a Sunday morning.
Reading is for everypony,
Rainbow Dash!
Yeah! I love reading.
And my head isn't even close
to the shape of an egg!
It's more the shape of an apple,
or maybe an orange!
But a big orange,
more like a grapefruit really...
All right, my little ponies.
Rainbow Dash needs her rest.
You'll have to come back tomorrow.
I think you'd like Daring.
She's a lot like you.
Adventurous, fierce and undeniably,
unquestionably, unstoppable.
...to get to the other side!
Get it?
Nevermind...
As Daring-Do trekked through
the tropical jungle, the wet heat
sapped her energy and
slowed her every step.
If only she could escape
this oppressive atmosphere
and fly up into the cool blue sky...
But her crash landing in the jungle
had injured her wing
and she was grounded for a few days.
Few days... it might as well be
a few months, or a few years!
I'm right there with you, sister.
The mosquitoes buzzed loudly.
The macaws cried from the high trees.
Yet, all of these distracting noises
were not enough to cover the sound
of the predators following her every step.
Safely landing on the other side, Daring finally
allowed herself a moment to breathe.
She turned around to find herself
face to face with the long lost temple
that she had sought tirelessly
for over sixty days and nights!
I hate to admit it to myself, and would
really hate to admit it to my friends
but... I love this story!
I love reading!
I'm an egghead.
The smell of decay and danger
hit Daring-Do as she peered into
the dimly-lit entrance
of the ancient temple.
Hi Rainbow Dash!
Uh, hey, guys...
We thought we'd come and cheer you up!
We brought your favorite board game!
We know how much you like to win!
You go first, Rainbow Dash!
No no, you first.
Alright... cloud three.
Aw,shucks, you... rained on my cumulus.
Go again!
Sky five?
You found my seagull!
- Cloud two?
- You zapped my weather pony!
You stung my bumblebee.
Oh, my thunderbolt.
And that's my last cloud.
You found it.
Guess you guys win, I lose.
But Rainbow Dash,
you didn't even get a turn.
You win some, you lose some.
But you don't lose some.
I don't think you've
ever lost a game of...
Thanks for coming!
But yesterday you were
desperate for things to do!
Do? Who said anything about Daring-Do?
I told you I'm not interested in reading.
It's nap time for me!
Glad we could... cheer you up?
Alright then.
Daring-Do stood at the entrance
to the central temple chamber.
At last, she was face-to-face with
the legendary sapphire statue!
There must be a pattern here.
What do all these animals have in common?
These animals are all predators!
Except... rats!
Hello, Rainbow Dash!
How's our patient doing today?
We need to get some fresh air in here.
You're lookin' sweatier than a pig
wrangler on a summer's day.
Well, guys, thanks for visiting, but...
Okay, now, dinner time for Rainbow Dash.
Just in time.
I am so hungry.
Don't mind us, Rainbow Dash.
Yeah, just go ahead and eat up.
On second thought...
We'll see you tomorrow, Rainbow Dash.
"You thought you could evade me
and capture the relic for yourself."
"But you are sadly mistaken, Miss Do."
And now, you shall meet your doom!
Who is this dude?
You won't get away with this, Ahuizotl!
But I already have...
Not again...
Quicksand!
Rainbow Dash?
Rainbow Daaaash?
- Oh, good evenin...
- Morning.
...morning, Doc.
Have you been up all night?
Of course not.
Well, I'll be quick.
Congratulations, Rainbow Dash,
we're checking you out of the hospital.
What?
Later today?
No.
Right now!
Right now?!
Right now, right now?
Right now, right now.
But I don't feel better!
Now take it easy, Rainbow Dash.
Remember to stay off
that wing for a week.
How will I ever find out
what happened to Daring-Do?!
Is Ahuizotl gonna get away
with the statuette?
What's gonna happen to Daring?!
Twilight has a copy of the book!
But I can't ask her after
I called her an egghead and all...
This is making me sick all over again!
The pain... the pain!
Rainbow Dash, what are you doing here?
Anything wrong?
My wing!
It's still hurting, Doc.
Ouch!
Right there.
I was touching your good wing.
Uh, right.
Well, I think that one's hurting now too.
I think I know what the trouble is.
A severe case of lazy-itis.
But, you got me all wrong, Doc!
I'm not being lazy!
You're fine, Rainbow Dash.
Give it some time and you'll be
right back in the swing of things.
Good day, Rainbow Dash.
Take care!
What am I gonna do?
I'll never get to sleep without knowing
what happens to Daring-Do!
Which may not be such a bad thing...
Feels like the harder I struggle,
the tighter the ropes get!
Burglar, burglar!
Someone's trying to steal my slippers!
I'm not trying to steal your slippers,
I'm trying to steal this book!
Stop, thief!
Hey, nopony invited me!
Hasn't anypony heard of beauty sleep?
Rainbow Dash,
what in the world is going on?
Why are you stealing slippers?
Hey, get back to the hospital!
What's all the ruckus?
I'd say it's more of a fracas
than a ruckus.
What's going on, Rainbow Dash?
I'm an egghead.
Pardon?
See, I was trying to get back into
the hospital to finish the last chapter of...
"Daring-Do and the Quest
for the Sapphire Statue"!
You got me.
I knew the book was good,
but I didn't know it could drive
a pony to petty theft!
Good? Try awesomely amazing.
That book is undeniably,
unquestionably, un-put-down-able!
But then I had to put it down.
I was sent home before I could finish it.
Well, I'm glad that's all this is about.
There's no reason to go
around causin' a ruckus...
Fracas!
...causin' a fracas,
just because you like to read.
Like I said, I have
every book in the series.
And you can borrow them all,
any time you like!
Thanks, Twilight.
I'm sorry I made such a big deal
about all of this.
I thought reading was just
for smart ponies like you.
Rainbow Dash, just because you're athletic
doesn't mean you aren't smart!
Yeah!
Just look at me!
Reading is something everypony can enjoy,
if they just give it a try.
Yeah, I get it.
I shouldn't knock something
until I've tried it.
That's a great lesson.
And it would make a great letter
to the Princess.
- Did you get all that?
- Yeah...?
Great!
You write the letter,
I've gotta finish this book!
Another day, another dungeon!
With Daring-Do out of the way,
the world will suffer mightily at my hands.
I am victorious!
I'll take that!
Wha...?
Noooooooo!
Better luck next time, Ahuizotl!
Curse you, Daring-Do!
And so, with Ahuizotl defeated,
and the sapphire statue secured...
...the world was safe and sound,
once again.
Thanks to Daring-Do!
Daring-Do and the Griffon's Goblet...
Awesome!