I just don't feel like
it's quite finished.
I know what you mean.
It's for Miss Cheerilee,
it needs to be perfect.
Hearts and Hooves Day only
comes once a year after all.
I say we add a little more ribbon!
Yeah.
And just a tiny bit more lace.
A few more hoof-prints.
Glitter!
It could definitely use
just a little more glitter.
Now that'll show Miss Cheerilee
how much we care about her.
Just have to get it to the
Hearts and Hooves party at school.
I think we're gonna need
a bigger envelope...
It's lovely.
And so...
...big!
We just wanted to let you know that
we think you're the best teacher
in the whole wide world!
And we think you're super!
And that we love you so so much!
And we want you to have
the best Hearts and Hooves Day...
...ever!
Thank you so much, girls.
I love it, I really do.
I'm sure it's nothing compared to
the gifts you've gotten from your...
...very special somepony!
I don't have a very special somepony
at the moment.
Really?
How could somepony as amazing as you
not have a very special somepony
in Hearts and Hooves Day?
It's alright, Sweetie Belle.
I have lots of good friends
and wonderful students
who care about me very much.
I'm gonna have an absolutely terrific
Hearts and Hooves Day!
Alright everypony,
who's ready to play
"pin the heart on the pony"?
If anypony deserves
a very special somepony,
it's her!
You alright?
I'm more than alright,
I've just come up
with the best idea ever!
We're gonna find Miss Cheerilee
a very special somepony...
- That is the best idea ever.
- Told you!
So, what are we waiting for?
Hearts and Hooves Day
is almost over!
Let's get out there and find
somepony special for Cheerilee already.
- Yeah!
- Let's do it!
Now it can't be just any pony.
Miss Cheerilee is one of
the best mares in Ponyville.
She deserves to have
one of the best stallions
as her very special somepony.
Cheerilee is sweet and kind
She's the best teacher we could hope for
The perfect stallion you and I must find
One to really make her heart soar
But...
This one's too young
This one's too old
He clearly has a terrible cold
This guy's too silly
He's way too uptight
I say!
Well, nothing's wrong with this one
He seems alright
His girlfriend sure thinks so...
How 'bout this one?
He's much too flashy
He might do
If he weren't so splashy
Too short
Too tall
Too clean
Too smelly
He's strangely obsessed
with tubs of jelly
I don't think that we're mistaken
It seems all the good ones are taken
I really feel that at this rate
We'll never find the perfect date
Don't wanna quit and give up hope
Doing anything special
for Hearts and Hooves Day?
Oh please oh please oh please say...
Nope.
We did it girls, we've found the one
Who will send our teacher's heart aflutter
Wait a minute, let me get this straight.
Are you talkin' about my brother?
Sweetie Belle is right.
Big Macintosh is the perfect match
for Miss Cheerilee.
He's really nice, super hard-working...
But he's also pretty shy!
He's never gonna ask Miss Cheerilee
to be his very special somepony.
Maybe he doesn't have to.
If we can get Big Mac and Miss Cheerilee
in a really romantic setting,
I bet she'll ask him!
Sounds like a plan to me.
So? What are we waiting for?
Let's get out there
and create the perfect date.
Flowers.
Don't forget the flowers.
Oops.
I'm on it!
They're coming!
This is gonna be perfect.
Miss Cheerilee is gonna have
the best Hearts and Hooves Day ever.
With her new very special somepony.
Hi, girls!
Hi, Miss Cheerilee!
So, you three said you needed
help identifying a tree
you found here near the gazebo?
That's an apple tree.
Is it?
Sorry, big brother.
We went and fixed up
the gazebo all on our own.
See?
As long as you're here,
why not have a bite to eat
from this romantic-looking picnic?
Oh gosh, seems like
there's only room for two!
I guess we'll just be going, then.
You really think this'll work?
Of course it will work,
they're perfect for each other.
Beautiful day we're having.
Eeyup.
Any big plans for tonight?
Nope.
Oh, come on Miss Cheerilee!
Ask him to be your
very special somepony.
Oh my gosh, look.
Big Mac...
Eeyup?
You have something
stuck in your teeth.
OH, COME ON!
Well, this has been... strange.
Eeyup.
I need to get going.
But it's always great running
into a good friend.
Eeyup.
Do you think it just wasn't
romantic enough?
Maybe it was too romantic.
Either way, we failed.
There's gotta be something else we could...
Oh my goodness,
I didn't even see you there.
I'm so so sorry.
It's okay Twilight,
it was an accident.
I've just been reading the most
fascinating book about
Hearts and Hooves Day.
Did you know that
this holiday got its start
because of a love potion?
Did you say... a love potion?
That's right.
It even has the recipe.
I don't suppose we could borrow
that book for a little while, do ya?
Of course you can.
I have another book here,
that I think you'll...
Take a tuft of cloud.
A bright rainbow's glow.
Stir with a Pegasus feather.
Fast, not slow.
Serve to ponies
who aren't in the know.
I feel kinda bad tricking my brother
and Miss Cheerilee this way...
What's the problem?
We all agreed these two
are perfect for one another.
Yeah, they just need a little nudge.
And what can make them happier
than being together, right?
Right!
Here they come!
Hi, Miss Cheerilee.
Hello again, girls.
Hello, Big Mac.
Would you three like to tell us
why it was so very important
- ...that we meet you here?
- Punch!
Excuse me?
Punch!
We made punch.
We were gonna set up a stand
and try to sell it, but,
we needed some pony
to taste test it first.
Yup.
We thought you two
would be perfect together...
To test it...
...together.
So, we'll just leave you two alone...
Together, to test it.
I'm very sorry about this.
I mentioned to the girls that
I don't have a very special somepony.
And I believe they're putting us
in these awkward situations
because they've decided it should be you.
I suppose we should just
humor them for a moment.
This punch does look delicious.
Eeyup.
I think they're gonna drink it!
To good friends!
They're drinking it.
They're drinking it!
They're looking into each others' eyes.
They're about to be in
for a big surprise!
- Big Mac?
- Yup?
Will you be my very special somepony?
Eeyup.
YES!
He's her special somepony.
She's his special somepony.
He's my special somepony.
Eeeeeya.
He's my shmoopy-doopy
sweedy-weedy pony pie.
You're my shmoopy-doopy
Did he just say...
You're my cutie-patootie
lovie-dovie honey-bunny.
You're my heartie-smartie
smirchy-wirchy baby-waby.
Big Mac!
Hey! Hello!
What's going on?
Miss Cheerilee, are you alright?
I have a special somepony.
A kissy-wissy
snuggy-wuggy sugar bear.
I think we may have given them
too big of a nudge.
You're my cuddly-wuddly
boopsie-woopsie pumpkin pie.
Ya think?
What have we done?!
My brother's acting like
a grade-A goofball!
Maybe we added too much rainbow.
Or maybe not enough cloud.
Or maybe... Uh oh.
What do you mean "uh oh"?!
We might not have given Big Mac
and Miss Cheerilee a love potion...
We may have given them a love poison!
What?!?!
Apparently, some prince who
long time ago whipped up this recipe
and gave it to this princess he liked.
He meant it to be a love potion,
but things didn't turn out so well.
How "not so well" did things turn out?
Well, there's something here
about a dragon...
Kingdom falling...
Chaos reigning...
Okay, apparently it was all because
the prince and princess
were so lost in each others' eyes,
that they couldn't perform
their royal duties.
Great!
We've not only turned
Big Mac and Miss Cheerilee
into a couple of nonsense-spouting
nincompoops,
we may have put all of
Ponyville in jeopardy!
Come on, Apple Bloom.
Miss Cheerilee and Big Mac
don't have any royal duties.
But they still got responsibilities.
If we don't fix this, Miss Cheerilee
won't be able to teach.
Big Mac won't be able to
harvest any apples.
And before you know it...
Ponyville will be overrun with uneducated
little ponies starving for apples.
It'll be chaos, it'll be chaos!
There's an antidote!
Well, why didn't you say so?
Didn't you see me gettin'
all panicked back there?
If we can keep Miss Cheerilee and Big Mac
from looking into each others' eyes
for one full hour,
the love curse will be broken.
Only an hour?
We can pull that off in a second.
You take the first sip,
snuggle-wuggles.
Nope, you take it, sugar lump.
No, you, shnooky-lumps.
No, you, pooky-pie.
I'm all for romance,
but this has been going on for hours.
What's happened to these two?
Who knows?
Well, these love birds will probably
be planning a wedding soon.
I can always use the catering business.
A wedding!
That's it!
Miss Cheerilee and Big Mac
should get married!
How is gettin' hitched
gonna keep them apart?
They aren't really gonna get married.
They're just gonna get ready
to get married.
No you, biscuit-wiscuit bear!
Nope you, huggy-wuggy
snuggy bunny!
Hi Miss Cheerilee, how are you?
I have a very special somepony.
Yeah, we noticed.
Gosh, you two are so in love,
the next thing you know,
you'll be getting married.
Married?
That's right. Married.
Married.
'Course, if you're gonna get married,
you wanna pick out a really nice
diamond for your...
...shmoopy-doopy-pookie-pie.
Diamond!
Shmoopy!
Don't you think you should start
looking for your wedding dress?
You'll wanna look your best for your...
honey-bunny snuggle-baby.
Dress!
Now we just need to keep them apart.
I'll keep Miss Cheerilee occupied.
You two do the same with Big Mac.
No problem.
Meet me back at the clubhouse in an hour,
when this whole mess is over.
This one looks nice.
Better try it on now.
Ten minutes down,
fifty minutes to go.
No.
Not that one either.
Too... shiny.
No.
You know, something less... shiny.
Miss Cheerilee deserves the best.
How much time is left?
I'm running out of ways
to make diamonds sound bad.
We still have twenty five minutes.
Where's my brother?
He made his purchase
and departed out the back.
Said something about needing to see his...
...shmoopy-shmoop.
Okay, I'll see what I can do
to slow him down.
You go on to Carousel Boutique
and warn Sweetie Belle.
What's wrong? Where's Apple Bloom?
Where's Big Mac?
On... his... way.
Gotta... keep him... out of Boutique.
Move away!
He'll get to her!
He's still strong!
Let him go!
Shmoopy-doo!
I sure am glad we found those shovels.
One more minute
and the spell will be broken!
Shmoopy-doo!
Sweetums?
Please be normal, please be normal!
Am I wearing a wedding veil?
Eeyup.
Are you sitting on a feather bed,
in a hole in the ground?
Eeyup.
Girls! Can you explain why I look like
I'm getting married at the bottom of a pit?
We may have given you
the teeny-tiniest bit of love potion...
...that may have turned out
to actually be a love poison.
And you may have gone
just a teeny tiniest bit nutty.
Well, we only did it because we thought
you and Big Mac would be really happy
if you could be each other's very special
someponies on Hearts and Hooves Day.
Our hearts and hooves
were in the right place.
We appreciate that you care about us
and want us to be happy, but...
But no matter how good
our intentions might have been,
we shoulda never meddled
in your relationship.
Nopony can force two ponies
to be together.
It's up to everypony to choose that
very special somepony for themselves.
We're sorry.
And you can think about
how sorry you are
while you're doing all of Big Mac's chores
at Sweet Apple Acres.
Does that seem like
a fair punishment to you?
Eeyup.
Hey there, Miss Cheerilee!
What are you doing here?
Since you three are doing
all of his chores,
Big Mac and I thought we'd
have a picnic at the gazebo.
Ready, sugar bear?
Eeyup, pumpkin pie.
NOOO!!!