Can you believe the new baby is finally here?
Cup Cake and Carrot Cake must be so proud!
I wonder if it's a filly or a colt?
I wanna see the new baby pony!
I wanna see! Which one is it?!
Meet our son, Pound Cake.
And our daughter, Pumpkin Cake.
Two new foals for me to play with?
That's two, two, two times the fun!
This is the greatest day ever!
We need to celebrate your birthday, babies!
'Cause you were just born today!
Shhh. The babies are trying to sleep.
- But I was just...
- Shhh.
- But...
- Shhh!
Happy happy birthday,
to you and you today!
Now, how in thunderation is one of them twins a pegasus...
...and the other one a unicorn?
Easy. My great great great great
grandfather was a unicorn.
And Cup Cake's great aunt's second cousin
twice removed was a pegasus.
That makes sense, right?
Aw yeah, just you wait!
Once little Pound Cake gets his wings going...
...he'll be all over the place!
And be careful around Pumpkin Cake.
Baby unicorns get strange magic
surges that come and go.
Quick! Make a wish and
blow out your candles!
Which is easy, 'cause there are zero candles!
- You are zero years old, after all!
- Shhh!
Happy monthiversary
to you and you today!
I can't believe you're already
a month old time sure flies...
...it seems like only yesterday you weren't born!
But now you're a month old today, hey!
Are you ready for your favoritest
game in the whole wide world?
Where's Pinkie Pie...?
Here I am!
Everything okay in there?
Who needs a diaper change?
Don't worry, they're fine!
I mean...
I got it.
Is anypony hungry?
No thanks.
I just had a big breakfast.
I'm on it.
You're making funny faces!
I have one!
No, you see, Pinkie, the babies need to be burped.
All set now?
Everything good?
Okay, who wants to play again?
Pound Cake, no pounding things.
We don't chew on things, Pumpkin Cake.
Except food.
Food! Great cinnamon sticks,
I completely forgot!
No, you just fed them bottles, remember?
Not the babies' food!
The food for the enormously big catering
order we have to deliver today!
With the new twins, we've been so distracted!
Quick, honeybun!
We need to find a babysitter to watch
the foals while we take care of this.
I could do it!
I wanna do it!
The babies love playing with me, I'll do it!
Wonder who would be available
on such short notice...
Me! Me!
Pick me!
I would love to babysit!
But I can't today, sorry.
I promised Angel we'd go on a picnic.
You understand, don't you?
You're not mad at me, are you?
Please don't be mad at me!
I'll do it!
Pick me!
I have to finish this report for the Princess...
...summarizing all my other reports to the Princess.
I wanna babysit!
Pick me!
Babysit?
Now?
When there's a swarm a' hungry
caterpillars headed this way?
I gotta get all these apples picked
before they get swarmed on!
I wanna do it!
I got tickets to the Wonderbolts
airshow this afternoon.
Gotta dash!
Ask me!
Mememememememememe!
Moi?
Babysit?
Nononononono.
I'm flattered that you would think about me though.
Pinkie Pie, how would you like to babysit for us.
I dunno.
I'll have to check my schedule.
Now, Pinkie, are you sure you really understand
the responsibility of watching over two babies?
I can be responsible.
Why, responsibility is my middle name.
Pinkie Responsibility Pie!
But this time you need to take care of them.
Not just play with them.
You have to be responsible.
Yes, I know.
I will, I am.
Here you are, dearie.
All your responsibilities are on this list.
That's a lot of responsi...
Consider it done.
We'll frost it when we get there!
C'mon, sugarplum, tick tick!
Take good care of our two precious little ginger snaps!
No problemo, Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
Everything is under control.
Don't cry, little friends!
Look, look!
Where's Pinkie Pie?
Oh no... I'm right here, see!
Think, think, think...
Hey guys, watch this!
Hey, you're a wonderful crowd here tonight!
Where y'all from?
Well, that's great.
Y'know, I used to have an ant farm,
but I had to get rid of it...
...because I couldn't find tractors that small!
Get it?
Tractors that small?
The other day, I spilled spot remover on my dog.
And now I can't find him!
Gee, tough crowd.
Tell me about it.
Fine, I wasn't gonna pull off a show stopper...
...but you're a lovely audience and I think you deserve it!
First you wiggle your tail, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your snout, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your rump, oink oink oink
Then shout it out, oink oink oink
First you wiggle your tail, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your snout, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your rump, oink oink oink
Then shout it out, oink oink oink
First you wiggle your tail, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your snout, oink oink oink
Then you wriggle your rump, oink oink oink
Then shout it out, oink oink oink
There, see?
Nothing to this babysitting business!
Snack time.
That's easy enough.
Okie dokie!
Eat up!
Like this!
No, Pumpkin Cake.
We eat food, not tablecloths.
Hey guys, look at me!
Yeah.... I think I can see
where this is going.
Towels are not food, Pumpkin Cake!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Look guys, bubbles!
Don't cry, look, look, floating things!
Don't make me do it, guys.
You know what happens when you
mix flour and water, don't you?
Smells like somepony needs me
to changie-wangie their...
...diaper-wiper right now-ow-ow!
Easy... easy...
Stand still, I've almost...
You've gotta be kidding me.
Thank goodness they're home!
Hi!
I finished up the work I had to do...
...so I thought I'd stop by and
see if you needed any help.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you for coming!
I can't begin to tell you what my day has been like...
...I mean, these babies just won't listen to reason!
And don't even get me started on
their taste in stand-up comedy.
It's okay, Pinkie.
I figured you'd need some help.
That's why I stopped by.
Excuse me?!
Babies take a lot of work.
And some ponies are just not cut out
to handle the responsibility.
Is that so?
Well, thanks for stopping by, Twilight.
Sorry, I don't have time to visit.
I'm very very busy with
my 'responsibilities' here.
I'm happy to help!
It's no trouble.
Well, she thinks I can't handle things on my own!
Maybe because I haven't handled things on my own.
Well, I can handle things on my own!
Pound Cake.
This is a crib.
It is only to be used for napping, sleeping...
...and on occasion with permission...
...as a pretend old-timey Western fort.
It is not a trampoline.
So stop your jumping right now, mister!
And you, young filly.
We do not put anything in our mouth...
...that we cannot safely and properly digest.
So stop slobbering on that toy, this instant!
Now, we've all had a very exhausting afternoon...
...and it's time for all good little foals to take their nap.
So, fall asleep!
Sleep tight.
Now that's what I call handling things.
Oh, nononono.
Not good, not good, not good!
Pound? Pumpkin?
Where are you?
Come out, wherever you are!
You be a good little girl now, Pumpkin-wumpkin...
...and stay in your crib for your pal Pinkie-winkie!
Pound Cake?
Here, Pound Cake!
You can fly?!
Get down here, this instant, young colt!
I'm responsible for you!
No no no, Pumpkin.
No no.
No.
I am the responsible one, and I said no.
That goes for you too, Pound Cake!
Gotcha!
I think?
Mhh, raspberry.
I'm not letting go!
I'm responsible!
Oh, not you too!
There!
Now who's the responsible one?
Y'know, you're right.
That is funny.
"Dear Princess Celestia..."
"I've always had fun playing with little kids..."
"...and I thought babysitting
meant just more playtime, right?"
"Wrong!"
"Being a caregiver is way more responsibility..."
"...than just being a playmate."
"And today I learned that sometimes,
our desire for responsibility..."
"...can outrun our actual ability to handle it."
Pinkie Pie!
We're back!
How did everything go?
Are we in the right place?
Shhh!
Pinkie!
This is just... just...
...amazing, is what it is!
We had no idea how responsible you really are.
Would you be interested in becoming our
go-to babysitter on a permanent basis?
Let me check my schedule!
I should be available a week from... never!
- Pinkie...
- Pie...
I have some free time next Tuesday.