Let's do this.
Happy! Sad.
Open, shut.
Nailed it!
Morning, Daisy Jo!
You here to pick up some cookies
to go with your milk?
Oh ya, Pinkie, don'tcha know?
Well, Mrs. Cake just baked a fresh batch
of your favorite oatmeal.
Sounds delightful!
Rose, your calla lilies look even better
than last year!
I bet you'll take first prize
at the flower show again.
Thanks, Pinkie.
Would you like one?
Absolutely!
Looking fit as a fiddle, Mr. Waddle.
And you're wearing my favorite tie!
Aw shucks Miss Pinkie,
you flatterer you.
Well, happy birthday, Cheerilee.
Thank you, Pinkie.
Happy day-after-your-birthday, Zecora!
What a lovely hi, Miss Pinkie Pie!
And Miss Matilda, happy birthday to you...
...in one hundred and thirty two days!
Pinkie Pie, how do you remember
everything about everypony?
'Cause everypony's my friend
and I love to see my friends smile!
My name is Pinkie Pie
(Hello!)
And I am here to say
(How ya doin?)
I'm gonna make you smile
And I will brighten up your day!
It doesn't matter now
(What's up?)
If you are sad or blue
(Howdy!)
'Cuz cheering up my friends
Is just what Pinkie's here to do!
'Cuz I love to make you smile, smile, smile!
(Yes I do!)
It fills my heart with sunshine all the while!
(Yes it does!)
'Cuz all I really need's a
smile, smile, smile!
From these happy friends of mine!
I like to see you grin!
(Awesome!)
I love to see you beam!
(Rock on!)
The corners of your mouth turned up
Is always Pinkie's dream!
(Hoof bump!)
But if you're kind of worried
And your face is made of frown
I'll work your heart and do my best
To turn that sad frown upside down!
'Cuz I love to make you grin, grin, grin!
(Yes I do!)
Busted out from ear to ear, let it begin!
Just give me a joyful
grin, grin, grin!
And you fill me with good cheer!
It's true, some days are dark and lonely
And maybe you feel sad
But Pinkie will be there to show you
that it isn't that bad!
There is one thing that makes me happy
And makes my whole life worthwhile
And that's when I talk to my friends
and get them to smile!
I really am so happy!
Your smile fills me with glee!
I give a smile, I get a smile
And that's so special to me!
'Cuz I love to see you beam, beam, beam!
(Yes I do!)
Tell me what more can I say to make you see
(That I do!)
It makes me happy when you
beam, beam, beam!
Yes, it always makes my day!
Come on everypony, smile, smile smile!
Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine!
All I really need's a
smile, smile, smile!
From these happy friends of mine!
Come on everypony, smile, smile, smile!
Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine!
All I really need's a
smile, smile, smile!
From these happy friends of mine!
That's the perfect gift for me!
(Come on everypony, smile, smile, smile!)
It's a smile as wide as a mile!
(Fill my heart up with sunshine, sunshine!)
To make me happy as can be!
(All I really need's a smile, smile, smile!)
(From these happy friends of...)
Smile! Smile! Smile! Smile! Smiiiiiile!
Come on and smile!
(Smile!)
I've never seen you before.
Kid, you're smarter than you look.
Thanks! I'm Pinkie Pie.
What's your name?
"Property of C.D.D."
I'm guessing that last "D"
is for Donkey.
Quick as a whip, kid.
Now, how about that C...
Calvin? Calhoun? Caleb? Carl? Carmine?
Carlo? Charlie? Chester? Chico?
Claudio? Cleetus? Clifford? Coraline?
Cornelius? Cortez? Crank? Christopher?
Cranky! It's Cranky, alright?!
And your middle name?
Doodle.
- I'm sorry?
- Doodle.
One more time!
Doodle.
So you're a Cranky Doodle Donkey?
You're a Cranky Doodle Donkey guy
A Cranky Doodle Donkey
I've never met you,
but you're my new friend
And I'm your best friend Pinkie Pie!
C'mon now, Doodle. Give a smile!
Nopony calls me Doodle!
What just happened?
Meet somepony new, check.
Introduce myself, check.
Sing random song outta nowhere, check.
Become instant best friends... uncheck.
I don't get it, how can somepony
not become instant best friends with me?
Was it something I said?
Was it something I sang?
This is no time for the blame game,
Pinkie!
There's somepony new in town,
and you need to win him over!
"Try everything you can to make
Cranky smile and be your friend".
Check!
Alright, Pinkie.
If you're gonna win Cranky's friendship,
you're gonna have to bring your A game!
Let's do this.
Howdy doody, Cranky Doodle!
So... are you moving to Ponyville,
Cranky?
What gave you the hint there, kid?
The cart full of stuff, maybe?
Well, I'd be happy to show you around.
It's the least a new friend can do.
Listen, kid, I traveled around Equestria
my entire life.
I've made many friends.
I don't need any more.
Gosh! I could never have
too many friends!
Well, why don't you go
and make some more?
But I don't need to go,
when I can stay and make friends...
...with you.
Look, kid...
Oh, Cranky, you can call me Pinkie.
All of my friends do.
Look, kid,
I came to Ponyville for some peace
and quiet and privacy,
to be alone with my memories.
All I want is to get to my new home
and unpack my stuff.
What does this bauble do?
Don't touch that!
What's this?
Please, don't!
Look at these!
Pinkie! Keep your hooves off my wagon!
Okay, Cranky.
I promised not to touch your wagon
so I brought one of my own!
I use it to welcome folks!
Who'da guessed...
Maybe we can be wagon buddies?
Well, you've gotta at least let me
give you the special welcome
that comes with it...
Let's get this over with.
That's the spirit!
Welcome welcome welcome
A fine welcome to you
I say how do you do?
Welcome welcome welcome
I say hip hip hurray
to Ponyville today!
Wait for it!
Oh, silly me!
I must've put the confetti in the oven
and the cake in the confetti cannons!
Again!
Still delicious!
Try some, Cranky.
It's sure to make you smile.
Where is it, where is it?
Where is what?
Spider! Big hairy spider!
Stop, stop, stop!
Was that your wig?
I can fix this, I can fix this!
Hey, everypony!
Does anypony have a toupee?
This donkey is really, really, bald!
What's so funny?
This is serious business, everypony!
Cranky needs a new wig
to cover his hairless head!
I have had enough!
You're losing him, Pinkie.
Wait, Cranky, please!
Let me make it up to you...
No!
Please! Please please please...
Ladies, this is a spa emergency.
Cranky needs help, STAT.
Hi, Cranky, I have a gift for you!
The spa treatment was gift enough.
It's not going to
explode or anything, promise.
Just open it!
It's a new toupee!
I had my friend Rarity make it.
She calls it the "dreamboat special".
This is wonderful.
Thanks, kid.
He's starting to warm up,
but still no smile.
Hey! Whatcha doing there,
ol' buddy ol' pal?
What's it look like?
Looks like a yard sale.
I'll give you two bits for this!
I'm not selling, kid.
I'm unpacking.
Why didn't you say so?
I thought I had.
This is so pretty!
Where'd you get it?
Manehattan, now put it down, gently.
Really? What were you doin' there?
Trying to find a friend...
I'm always trying to find friends,
and today I found you.
See how good I am at it?
This was a special friend.
- Like me?
- No, you're extra special, kid.
Yes, I'm in!
Where in Equestria did you get this,
Cranky?
Fillydelphia.
It's awfully pretty.
Yes, she was.
I mean, it was. I mean, it is.
Yes, it's pretty, now put it down!
I wonder where Cranky got this.
Will you look at that?
Hey, Cranky!
Can I ask you about...
Oh no!
What did you sa-yayayayay!
What have you done?!
There!
All better?
No, not all better, all soggy!
I'm sorry, Cranky!
Oh, you're sorry, well, then,
everything is fine!
- It is?
- No! It isn't!
Listen to me, kid,
I will never be your friend!
Never, or never-ever?
Never, ever, ever, ever, ever!
That's four "ever"s.
That's like... forever!
I just can't believe it.
Cranky said he would never forever
be my friend.
It was horrible.
I know this is hard for you, Pinkie.
Seeing that you're friends with everypony.
But you just have to accept that Cranky
is gonna be an exception.
He just... doesn't want to be bothered.
Yeah, he doesn't want to be bothered
by your over-the-top super-hyper antics.
Rainbow!
No, no, it's okay, Twilight.
I get what you're saying.
What you're both saying.
And I guess... I can leave Cranky alone.
Right after he accepts my apology!
Cranky!
No! No!
Leave me alone!
Wait!
I understand that you don't want me
as a friend!
No, I don't!
So I just wanted to say "I'm sorry"!
Fine! You said it!
But do you accept my apology?
No!
Oh Cranky! Please accept my apology!
Please!
No!
But I'm really, really, really...
Really, really...
Really, really, really...
Really, really, really,really...
Really. Really. Really. Really.
Really. Really. Really. Really...
Sorry!
Cranky, please, please accept my apology!
I'd do anything to make it up to you!
But there's nothing you can do!
You ruined my book!
You destroyed all I have
to remember her by!
Her?
Her who?
The special friend?
Go away, Pinkie!
Cranky? It's me again.
I understand that you don't wanna
be my friend or accept my apology...
Before I leave you alone forever,
I have something to at least try
to make up for ruining your book.
No, I don't want it, kid!
Anything you would give me is sure
to lead to some sort of disaster!
Goodness, you really are cranky.
It can't be... is it really you?
It can, and it is.
Matilda! But how?
Pinkie.
But... I never told you about her!
You didn't have to.
I put two and two and two together
and it added up to Matilda.
What?
Well when you were talking about
your souvenirs,
you said something about trying to find
a special friend!
And y'know, I wasn't just born yesterday.
My birthday isn't for
another seventy five days!
And then, in your scrapbook,
there was a flower, an old ticket,
and a menu from the Grand Galloping Gala!
And I knew I recognized all these things.
But how could you have
ever seen them before?
Because I also have them in my scrapbook.
And I'd seen them in Matilda's book!
Oh, Matilda.
The night we met at the gala
was the most magical night of my life.
I couldn't wait to see you again.
But when I came to your room
the next day, you were gone.
Didn't you get my note?
No, I never got it.
Ever since that day,
I've gone from town...
to town... to town...
Searching all over Equestria for you.
Until finally I gave up.
I came to Ponyville
to retire from my search.
I was living in Ponyville
the whole time.
I always hoped that some day
you would come and find me.
Doodle.
Matilda?
Nopony calls him Doodle...
Nopony... but Matilda.
Doodle, I'm so happy to see you.
So does this mean
that you accept my apology?
Yes, Pinkie, I accept your apology.
And, I am honored to call you my friend.
This is just fantastic!
Now we can hang out together,
and chat, and sing songs, and...
party!
I can throw you guys a big party!
It'll be called "Welcome to Ponyville,
I found my lost love...
I'm BFF's with Pinkie Pie" Party!
Or maybe something less over-the-top
and not so super-hyper.
Pinkie, we're eternally
grateful to you, but...
Matilda and I just want to spend some
time together in peace and quiet.
But we're still friends?
Pinkie, you went way, way, way
out of your way to make me happy.
Of course we're friends.
Great!
Dear Princess Celestia,
there are many different kinds of friends,
and many ways to express friendship.
Some friends like to run and laugh
and play together.
But others just like to be left alone,
and that's fine too.
But the best thing about friendship
is being able to make your friends smile.
He had a Cranky Doodle sweetheart
She's his Cranky Doodle joy
I helped a Cranky Doodle boy, yeah
I helped a Cranky Doodle boy
Pinkie!
Oops, privacy, sorry.