Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness.
You've really outdone yourselves,
Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
This is sure to be the winning entry
of this year's National Dessert Competition!
Oh, thank you Pinkie!
And thanks for transporting it
all the way to Canterlot for us.
Absolutely! It's my honor and I-
Beg pardon but,
could we maybe move things along?
This here cake's a mite heavy,
right Big Macintosh?
Eeyup.
All righty then, Big Mac!
To the train depot!
That's it Big Mac, nice and slow.
This is precious cargo you're carrying.
Yes, it took months
of planning and testing.
I would hate for it to-
Fall!
Don't worry, Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
Rainbow Dash, Fluttershy,
a little pegassistance?
I'll get it there safely, you'll see!
Of course, Pinkie.
We never doubted you.
Twilight, can I see you a second?
A nice protective spell
as extra insurance...
Better safe than sorry.
AJ, Rarity, one last thing?
All right everypony,
we're in the home stretch here.
See, Mr. and Mrs. Cake?
I got it here without a hitch!
Now all we have to do is get it...
in?
Thank you all for helping me get
the cake safely on the dessert car.
Thank you for inviting us all
to go with you to Canterlot
for the National Dessert Competition.
I'm sure the festivities
will be just lovely.
Fooey on the festivities,
I can't wait to try
all those tasty treats!
Well, the tastiest treat
of all is sure to be the Cake's
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness.
All that rich creamy goodness
of the marzipan,
combined with the tart tanginess
of the mascarpone,
blended perfectly with the smooth,
silky sweetness of the meringue...
That's why I call the
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness
the "MMMM".
Exactly.
It's the most delicious delectable
delightful de-lovely cake in Equestria.
And it's sure to win first prize.
This is not so.
For I, Gustave Le Grand,
do challenge your crude cake
to a duel of delectable delacacies
against my exceptionally exquisite éclairs!
They will undoubtedly strike down
all the competition,
winning first prize and crowning me...
le champion!
Not a chance, Le Grand.
Doughnut Joe!
What are you doing in Ponyville?
Picking up the final all-important
ingredient for my contest entry...
"Doughnutopia"!
And with these super-sprinkles,
my doughnuts are gonna dunk all
the other lousy desserts steal first prize,
and make my doughnut shop famous...
forever!
Oh, Joe... your dippy doughnuts
could never outrun me.
Hello. What's your name?
I am Mulia Mild.
Behold, my chocolate mousse moose.
It will trample all your treats,
be given first prize,
and make me the greatest chef
in Equestria...
Madame Mild, you and your
mousse moose are mistaken.
Your frou-frou éclairs
will never defeat my doughnuts!
The Cakes'
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness
is going to win!
Your simple cake could never
take my moose.
Well, it sure looks like we're in
for a delicious competition tomorrow.
Maybe we should all settle in
for a good night's sleep.
I gotta admit I'm pretty beat.
Yeah, I'm gonna hit the hay myself.
Wait! Didn't you hear those chefs?
We have to protect "MMMM".
Mmmm?
Mmm hmm.
I know for super sure that "MMMM"
is the best dessert in all of Equestria.
And I know that they know it too.
So...
So... one of them is going to
sabotage the Cakes' cake tonight!
You have to help me stand guard!
Pinkie, you're overreacting.
Yeah, those chefs aren't gonna
do your cake any harm.
But they are! I just know it.
Fine!
If you wanna stand guard, go for it.
We're going to bed.
I'll show them.
I'll stay up all night and protect you.
Nothing and nopony will stop me
from keeping you safe.
Stop, you saboteur!
I have you now!
Thank Celestia, you're okay!
But one of those bakers
is mixing up something bad.
So I'm not leaving you again,
no matter what.
Who turned out the moon?
Don't go near that cake, thief!
Stop, thief!
Oh, are you okay thief?
Overreacting my hoof.
I knew I was going to have
to keep a close eye on you.
And that's just what I'm gonna do.
The cake!
You look mmmm-marvelous.
I know. I think some congratulations
are in order for a job well done.
You better hold off on giving yourself
an award just yet Pinkie... look!
Look at what?!
What is it?
What happened?
It's the
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness.
It's been... mutilated!
Now, we just need
to find out who done it.
You mean, who "did it".
Exactly. Who did-done-dood it.
Well, having read many mystery novels,
I know that the only way to
discover the culprit is to investigate.
Exactly.
And as chief detective,
that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
- You're investigatin'?
- Yes!
And Twilight shall be
my lowly assistant
who asks silly questions
with obvious answers.
Fine, Pinkie.
Should we start looking for clues?
Perfect silly question,
my dear Twilight.
Because the obvious answer is...
Yes?
No! 'Cause I know who did it.
Pinkie, how could you possibly know?
How could I possibly not know?
Clearly, this dastardly deed
was done by the baker
who knew their dessert
could not measure up
to the mastery of the
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness.
I guess you feared
your éclairs lacked flair...
Gustave!
Thus, destroying the cake,
and the Cakes' chance
of winning the
National Dessert Competition.
But it makes no sense!
What do you mean, lowly assistant?
Well first, if you were tied
to the train tracks,
how are you now here?
Guess that isn't
a totally silly question.
And second, the cake hasn't been sliced,
it's been bitten.
Just look at the teeth marks!
You're right, my fine fellow.
Gustave Le Grand
is clearly in the clear.
Which means the "MMMM"
was destroyed by another baker.
A baker whose doughnuts are do-nots.
That's right, it was Joe!
Or as he's known in the spy world,
Mane. Con Mane.
Crushing the Cakes' chances to win!
Pinkie!
There is no laser beam security system.
And Joe is not sleek, stealthy Con Mane!
He's big, gruff, and messy!
Although, you would look
rather dapper in a tuxedo.
You may be right, lowly assistant.
May be?
Now that I'm taking
a closer look at these desserts,
I see that one simply cannot
look me in the eye.
Pinkie... that moose is a mousse!
Yes!
And the mule behind the moose panicked
when she saw the mastery of the "MMMM".
So you're saying that the culprit is...
Mulia Mild!
Putting an end to the Cakes'
dreams of taking first prize.
I hope you're proud of yourself, Mulia.
Pinkie, stop! This is ridiculous!
Look at her!
I guess you're right...
Thank you!
But I was so sure that it was
one of the other bitter bakers
that destroyed the "MMMM".
That way, their delicious dessert
would reign supreme.
I mean, just look at Joe's Doughnutopia.
It's a spectacular city
of doughnutty delight,
topped temptingly
in sprinklicious sprinkles.
And Gustave's éclairs look incredibly
edible, with glistening glaziness.
But then, there's
Mulia Mild's Mousse Moose.
Why, this mouth-wateringly marvelous
mousse moose tempts the taste buds
with this silky, smooth, yummy-nummy,
chocolateyness.
So, why did this criminal devour the
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness
while leaving this trio
of tasty treats untouched?
Now I have no idea who do-doned it!
This mystery gets more mysterious
every minute.
Well, you have to stop the wild
accusations and get to the truth.
Everypony go back to your cars
while we do a little investigating.
Okay Pinkie, in order to
really solve this mystery,
we're going to have to find clues.
Now you were here,
at the scene of the crime all night.
You're not accusing me, are you?
No!
But maybe you saw something
that will help us.
I saw a silhouette in the moonlight!
Good... let's retrace your steps.
Then, I chased the culprit down
the train towards the caboose.
But when I got there, he was gone.
Our first clue.
I think I know who did it, Pinkie.
- Already?
- Yes.
But I need more evidence to confirm.
Tell me what happened next.
I heard somepony else in the dessert car,
and chased them up to the engine.
But, when I got there, all I saw
was the conductor shoveling coal.
The conductor, huh?
But, that doesn't make any sense.
What happened next, Pinkie?
Well... I went back to the dessert car.
Yes?
The curtains mysteriously closed,
all on their own.
Interesting. Anything else?
I heard hoofsteps, a loud thud.
And then they were gone!
When I opened the curtains,
I saw that the portrait by the door
was all crooked.
Oh my, what is that?
What next, Pinkie?
That's it. I was here guarding
the cake the rest of the night.
I mean... I slept by the cake
the rest of the night.
And when you woke up,
half the cake was gone?
Exactly.
By Jove, I think I've got it.
Call everypony back.
We have a cake culprit to catch.
Why are we all here again?
I bet you're wondering
why you're all here again.
She's good.
We have discovered the true culprit
of this cake carnage.
But how?
Well you see, when committing a crime,
it's crucial that one
never leaves behind clues.
Especially an obvious clue like... this.
A blue feather.
I knew it was you, Gustave Le Grand.
Pinkie, Gustave doesn't
have blue feathers.
No, 'cause he's been dying them!
No, Pinkie.
Remember how when you chased
the suspect to the caboose,
they suddenly disappeared?
That's because they flew away.
But the thief did leave
a little something behind...
didn't you, Rainbow Dash?
I don't even like cake!
So Rainbow Dash did it! Case solved!
Case not solved, because
when we went to the engine,
I saw the conductor's hat.
And inside the hat was... this.
So it was you, that pink hair came
from your rainbow colored mane!
I don't have pink in my mane, Pinkie!
So you're wearing a wig?
Cut it out!
Pinkie, remember?
You chased a pony to the engine,
where you thought you saw
the conductor shoveling coal.
But that wasn't the conductor at all.
It was... Fluttershy.
You're going down, Fluttershy.
Pinkie!
But then another clue
confounded my suspicions.
You were guarding the cake
when the curtains mysteriously closed.
But that's no mystery, that's magic.
But when the thief tried
to make their great escape,
they left a little addition to the portrait.
Has anypony else noticed
that Rarity is wearing
her hair rather differently today?
What? Is it a crime to change
one's style every now and again?
Why, I think it's a crime not to.
Really?
Fine, I'm guilty!
I wear false eyelashes.
Oh, and I took a bite of the cake.
So did I.
Oh nuts, so did I.
You just made it sound
so delectable.
So tasty.
And boy was it!
I only meant to take a little,
lady-like bite.
And it was so good.
Yeah, I just dove right in!
But I'm really really sorry.
Terribly sorry.
Sorry, Pinkie.
That's okay.
At least this mystery
is finally solved.
But it isn't.
We figured out who ate the
Marzipan Mascarpone Meringue Madness,
but we still don't know who devoured
the other bakers' goods.
You're right, Twilight.
You know what we have to do?
Well, yes I do. Do you?
Look for clues!
Well, Pinkie. Did you find
the devourer of the desserts?
I most certainly did.
It was, none other than...
the bakers!
First of all, Gustave has mousse
in his moustache.
And Joe has éclair in his hair.
And Mulia has sprinkles
in her freckles!
What do you say, bakers?
Oh I am so sorry, Mulia.
But Pinkie made your
mousse moose sound...
très magnifique.
And Pinkie's description of your éclairs
really did make 'em sound scrumptious.
And the way she spoke
of your Doughnutopia,
it was too delectable to resist.
Well everypony,
we finally have the mystery solved.
Yes, but now we don't have any desserts
to enter into the contest!
I think we can fix that. Come on!
Dear Princess Celestia,
today I learned that it's not good
to jump to conclusions.
You have to find out all the facts
before saying somepony did something.
If you don't, you could end up blaming
somepony for something they never did.
This could hurt their feelings,
and it can make you look really foolish.
So from now on, I'll always
make sure to get all the facts.
How's that for a lesson,
Princess Celestia?
Care for a bite?
I don't mind if I do.