I made it for you, Rarity.
Why yes, it is an ice cream house.
Chocolate fudge shingles...
Rocky road garage...
Twilight?
Oh, hi Spike.
It's the middle of the night!
Why are you pacing like this?
Frankly, I don't know how you
can sleep at a time like this!
Three AM?
It's awful, it's horrible, it's tragic!
I don't understand.
What's wrong?
Here.
Now do you see what's wrong?
You forgot to celebrate Arbor Day?
No, the problem is I just finished
planning my schedule for the month,
but I forgot to leave time to plan
for next month!
Don't you see?
There's no time in my schedule
to put together another schedule!
I could move my meeting with
the Ponyville Hay Board
to the following Tuesday,
but then I have to reschedule
my lunch with Pinkie Pie.
And you know what a nightmare
she is with scheduling.
This is an absolute disaster.
My whole year could be thrown off!
And I woke up from
an ice cream dream for this...
Oh my gosh, I think I did it!
If I can find a way to read
The Art of Invisibility Spells,
and Farmhill's A Brief History of Canterlot
at the same time,
that could leave me
a half-hour scheduling window!
What's going on?
Twilight,
you've got to listen to me!
Who are you?
I mean, you're me, but I'm me too.
How can there be two 'me's?
It's not scientifically possible.
You are not scientifically possible!
Twilight, please!
I have a very important message
for you from the future!
You're from the future?!
That's right, now listen-
What happened to you?
The future must be awful.
Please! I don't have much time!
Is there some sort of epic pony war
in the distant future or something?
Actually, I'm from next Tuesday morning.
But that's not important right now!
I can't believe
time travel's really possible!
How did you, I mean, I
figure it out?
The time spells are in
the Canterlot archives.
- But that's not-
- Really? Where?
I've never seen them.
They're in the
Star Swirl the Bearded wing.
- Now, you have to listen to me.
- Is time travel fun, or does it hurt?
I have so many questions-
I have something extremely important
to tell you about the future.
I only have a few seconds,
so you've got to listen!
Whatever you do, don't-
Future Twilight? Oh no!
What was she trying to warn me about?
Her clothes, her mane, that scar...
What a mess she is!
I mean, I am... or I... will be...
She must want me to prevent whatever
horrible thing happens in the future!
C'mon, Fluttershy! The party can't start
until the party supplies get there!
Happy to... help... but...
Can I carry... the balloons next time?
Listen, everypony! I've got
something really important to say!
This is no laughing matter!
We have a crisis on our hooves!
I've just been visited
by myself from the future!
This isn't a joke!
My future self tried to warn me
about a horrible disaster,
that's gonna occur sometime
before next Tuesday morning!
What kind of disaster?
I don't know!
I got sucked back into the future
before I could explain!
Run for your liiife!
Whatever should we do, Twilight?
How do we stop a disaster
if we don't know what it is?
We'll just have to work together
to make sure we're safe.
Rainbow Dash, you and the other pegasi
spread out over Equestria
and look for any kind of problem
that could lead to a disaster.
And I mean anything.
You got it!
Everypony else...
Anypony else wanna panic with me?
No?
Everypony else,
time to disaster proof Equestria!
Eeyup.
Done, and done, and done.
Applejack,
what about the Everfree Forest?
The perimeter's clear.
Great.
And my team gave the all clear
from Fillydelphia to Las Pegasus.
Excellent.
Well, we've done everything on the list.
But still...
Future Twilight looked like
she'd been through a horrible ordeal.
I just have this nagging feeling
we should be looking for something bigger
than loose bolts and leaky pipes.
Okay, everypony.
Follow my lead.
- What is that thing?
- That's Cerberus!
He's supposed to be guarding
the gates of Tartarus.
But if he's here, then all the ancient evil
creatures that have been imprisoned there
could escape and destroy Equestria!
- Destroy Equestria?!
- Yeah, isn't it great?
Hey, Cerberus! You look like
you could use some obedience training!
Magic obedience training!
Who's the cute widdle three-headed dog?
Wow, I knew you were good with animals,
but this is amazing.
Aw, he's just a big furry guy
who got out of his yard, that's all.
Right, Cerberus?
Who's a good boy? Who's a good boy?
- Pinkie.
- Yes, Twilight?
Do you have a ball I can borrow?
I have balls stashed all over Ponyville.
In case of ball emergency.
Hey, Cerberus!
Look what I have!
I'll be back as soon as I've returned him
to the gates of Tartarus.
Once he's back at home,
there'll be no disaster.
I wish Twilight would go on
epic adventures more often.
Best night's sleep I've had in weeks.
Hey Twilight.
How'd it go with Cerberus?
Great! I got him back before any
of the evil creatures could escape.
Oh no!
What's the big deal,
it's just a 'lost dog' flyer.
I guess the Princess hasn't heard
we found Cerberus yet.
It's not that,
it's this!
A paper cut...?
Come on, Twilight,
you really need to toughen up.
Just clean it out and you'll be fine.
The cut's in the exact same spot
as the scar on future Twilight's cheek!
We haven't changed the future at all!
The disaster is still coming!
If the disaster wasn't caused
by Cerberus getting loose,
then what could it possibly be?
I dunno, but maybe you ought
to give the pacing a rest.
You've worn a groove into the floor!
I don't have time for another one
of your lectures, Spike!
This is serious!
My lectures?
I did everything I could think of
to change the future.
But it didn't work.
So maybe it's not what I do...
Maybe it's what I don't do!
If I stand right here and don't
move a muscle until next Tuesday,
I can't possibly do whatever it is
that future Twilight wanted
to warn me not to do!
Really?
So... no matter what happens,
you're not gonna move a muscle, huh?
Then maybe you won't mind if I...
eat an entire tub of ice cream!
So good!
Spike, stop!
Think of the stomach ache!
Stomach ache, huh?
That's future Spike's problem.
Hey, Twilight!
Another pegasus just got back
from Baltimare with an all-clear and-
What's going on?
Aren't you gonna stop him?
She sure isn't!
In fact, she's not gonna move
'til next Tuesday!
She thinks it'll prevent
the disaster from happening!
Oh, this is too rich.
Hey Twilight!
There's a mouse right behind you!
Wait, wait, wait, let me try!
Oh no!
What happened?
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean to!
It was a total accident!
Show me.
I'm not so sure that's a-
Show me!
Oh no! This is the same
mane cut as future Twilight!
Y'know...
It really doesn't look too bad...
I don't care how it looks!
It's just another sign
that the future hasn't changed!
Not doing anything didn't work either!
I wish there was a way to know what
was going to happen so I could stop it!
You wanna see the future?
I might know somepony who can help!
What's this?
It's Madame Pinkie's place.
Madame Pinkie?
Come... enter the chamber
of Madame Pinkie Pie...
For the answers you seek, let us consult
the mystical orb of fate's destiny...
Do you like
my mystical orb of fate's destiny?
I just got it. Cool, huh?
Yeah, uh... best one I've seen.
Look deep into the crystal ball...
For soon it will reveal all!
Ah yes, I see something...
It's a vision of the future...
I see you, Twilight.
You will get...
a really cool birthday present next year!
Yes, and?
That's it.
Are you sure?
Yep. Cool birthday present.
Pinkie, I need your Pinkie Sense
to tell me what the impending
disaster is that future Twilight
was trying to warn me about!
Oh, my fortune telling has nothing to do
with my Pinkie Sense, silly.
It's only good for vague
and immediate events.
Like that, see?
Where did that even come from?
Gosh, I haven't seen Twilight
since the flowerpot incident.
Hope she still isn't mad.
Off by point zero two from yesterday.
Carry the fifteen...
Negative azimuth on the fourteenth moon...
Hey Pinkie.
Twilight's really serious about finding out
about that cool birthday present, isn't she?
Who cares?
As long as I can keep eating ice cream.
Sorry, future Spike.
Are you okay?
Ah, Pinkie, I'm glad you're here.
Can you help me recalibrate the apertures
on the nine and quarter
catadioptric telescopes?
Sure!
So I was thinking...
After I came to see Madame Pinkie
and the flowerpot landed on my head,
see the bandage, just like
the bandage from the future...
Nice.
I had an epiphany after that flowerpot.
Doing things didn't work,
not doing things didn't work.
And I couldn't predict the future either,
so I only had one other choice...
Monitor everything.
Makes sense to me!
That way no matter what happens
in the future, I'll be ready!
I thought I saw something last night
in the Horsehead nebula.
But after staring at it
for three straight hours,
I realized I was wrong!
Three hours? But when did you sleep?
Oh I didn't sleep. I haven't slept
since future Twilight was here.
There are only three days
left until next Tuesday,
I can sleep all I want after that!
You've been awake too long, Twilight.
Yeah. Tuesday's not three days from now.
Tuesday's tomorrow!
Pinkie, did you finish
recalibrating the apertures
on the nine and quarter inch
catadioptric telescopes?
I have no idea!
Ah! My eye!
Don't worry, Twilight,
I have eye patches stashed
all over Ponyville,
in case of eye patch emergency.
There! Now you look like a pirate.
A sleepy pirate,
with a really weird mane cut.
The eye patch...! Another sign!
Nearly all the signs have come true!
I haven't done a thing
to prevent the catastrophe!
If Tuesday's tomorrow,
and the disaster happens
by Tuesday morning,
then there's only one solution.
I'll just have to...
stop time!
Okay, the Canterlot archives
are right over there.
Let's move!
I don't think we need
to sneak around, Twilight.
It's not illegal
to walk around Canterlot.
Guard!
C'mon, you guys!
That was close.
I dunno why we have
to wear these things, either.
Aren't we wearing them for fun?
No, there's nothing fun about this!
- Are you sure?
- Focus, guys!
The only way to prevent this disaster
is to stop time!
Time spells are kept in
the Star Swirl the Bearded wing,
the most secure section of the archives.
That's why we're sneaking around!
Awesome!
That sounds fun!
No, it's not fun!
I still don't understand
how sneaking into the archives
is gonna help her find out
about her birthday present.
The coast is clear.
Now slowly lift me into the window
so we can- AH!
Let's get this over with.
Okay, if my calculations are correct,
the Star Swirl the Bearded wing
should be right... here.
Uh, Twilight?
What is it, Spike?
Isn't this where we came in?
Cool! Can we climb in the window again?
That was super fun!
I don't understand.
It's supposed to be right here...
How are we supposed to find it now?
Maybe we should ask somepony
in the Star Swirl the Bearded wing?
Huh. How'd I miss that?
Look at all those
priceless magic scrolls...
There are more than I ever imagined!
Twilight, the guard!
What do we do, what do we do?!
Hey, Twilight,
haven't seen you in a while.
Let me open that for ya.
Thanks!
Oh no!
Look! I look just like future Twilight.
The last sign has come true!
And that's bad, right?
Come on!
It's almost Tuesday morning!
The disaster could happen at any moment!
But how do we find
the time-stopping spell?
There must be a million scrolls here!
I. Don't. Know!
Twilight, it's over!
It's officially Tuesday morning!
No!
Tuesday morning, the disaster!
Incoming!
I dunno, Twilight.
I don't see any disasters.
It looks like a pretty nice day.
Good morning, Twilight,
love the new hairstyle.
Well, happy Tuesday!
Why isn't anypony surprised
to see me sneaking around in here?!
Is it possible
there never was a disaster?
That I've just been making myself
frantic over nothing?!
I don't get it.
If future Twilight wasn't
warning you about a disaster,
then what was she trying to tell you?
I don't know. But I do know one thing.
I look ridiculous!
Yeah, you do!
And it's all because
I couldn't stop worrying
and let the future handle itself!
Well, not any more.
From now on, I'm gonna
solve problems as they come.
And stop worrying about
every little thing!
That's great!
Does that mean there won't be
any more late night pacing?
No more late night pacing.
If only I had learned
this lesson a week ago,
we wouldn't have had
to go through all this.
Twilight, Twilight, I found something!
It doesn't stop time,
but it lets you go back in time.
It says you can go back once,
and it only lasts for a few moments.
Does that help?
Pinkie, you're a genius!
Now I can go back and tell past Twilight
that she doesn't need to go berserk
with worry about a disaster
that's never gonna come!
Twilight,
you've got to listen to me!
Who are you?
I mean, you're me, but I'm me too.
How can there be two 'me's?
It's not scientifically possible.
You are not scientifically possible!
Twilight, please!
I have a very important message
for you from the future!
You're from the future?!
That's right, now listen-
What happened to you?
The future must be awful.
Please! I don't have much time!
Is there some sort of epic pony war
in the distant future or something?
Actually, I'm from next Tuesday morning.
But that's not important right now!
I can't believe
time travel's really possible!
How did you, I mean, I figure it out?
The time spells are in
the Canterlot archives.
- But that's not-
- Really? Where?
I've never seen them.
They're in the
Star Swirl the Bearded wing.
- Now, you have to listen to me.
- Is time travel fun, or does it hurt?
I have so many questions-
I have something extremely important
to tell you about the future.
I only have a few seconds,
so you've got to listen!
Whatever you do, don't...
waste your time... worrying... about...
I can't believe I just did that.
Did you tell her about
the cool birthday present?
Remember last week when future Twilight
came to warn me about something?
That was me trying to warn myself
not to worry so much!
Now I'm gonna spend the next week
freaking out about a disaster
that doesn't even exist!
Don't worry about it.
It's past Twilight's problem now.
Huh, I guess you're right, Pinkie.
Oh... my stomach...
I think it's all that ice cream...
I thought the stomach ache
would be future Spike's problem...
But now I am future Spike.
Come on, future Spike.
Let's get you home.