Calling all pegasus ponies!
Meeting tonight!
Mandatory meeting
for all Ponyville pegasi.
Library, tonight.
Be cool, or be mule.
No offense.
None taken.
Alright, go on in, find a seat.
You too, Fluttershy.
Come on, let's go.
Every living thing depends on
the life-giving nourishment of rainwater.
And it is up to Cloudsdale
to provide rain-filled clouds
to every corner of Equestria.
But how, one pony might ask,
does Cloudsdale gather all this extra water?
Tornado power!
That's right, pegasi-driven tornado power.
A team of pegasi combine their wing power
to create a jumbo tornado,
powerful enough to pull water
out of the local reservoir,
and funnel it all the way up to Cloudsdale.
Remember, pegasi,
your jumbo tornado
must reach a minimum of
eight hundred wing power
to lift that water up to Cloudsdale.
So, the next time you're wondering
"Where does all that extra
rainwater come from?"
just rememb-
Uh... intermission?
So, here's the scoop.
Cloudsdale has chosen
our own highland reservoir
as a source of the rainwater
they need for all of Equestria.
And you know what that means.
It means it's up to Ponyville's pegasi
to bring that water up to Cloudsdale.
Not only that, but Spitfire,
captain of the Wonderbolts,
will be here to oversee the water transfer
and record our top tornado windspeed.
Now last year, Fillydelphia
broke the windspeed record
with a top speed of
nine hundred and ten wing power.
But I think we can do better.
I think we can get a top speed
over a thousand!
IF each and every pony trains,
and trains hard
to get their wing power numbers up.
That coughing better be from
a popcorn kernel, Thunderlane.
Nopony's getting sick on my watch.
So, are we gonna train hard?
Yeah!
Are we gonna be strong?
Are we gonna be fast?
Yeah!
Record-smashing fast?
Who's with me?
Fluttershy!
Stretch those glutes, Flitter!
Nice flexibility, Cloudchaser.
A little too much flexibility,
Blossomforth.
Somepony give Blossomforth a hoof.
Let's see some faster trotting,
Thunderlane!
Good pace, Silverspeed!
Keep it up!
We're gonna need all the wing power
we can get to break that record!
Yeah!
Good work, everypony!
Everypony except Fluttershy.
Fluttershy? I know you're in there!
You're avoiding tornado duty
and I want to know why!
Fluttershy, open-
Hi, Rainbow Dash.
Fluttershy, what happened to you?
Oh, I...
I think I have the pony pox.
I'm sorry, I really, really wanted
to come to training day today...
But this pony pox has really
knocked me for a loop.
Oh, you poor thing.
You know, there's only
one cure for pony pox.
I know, plenty of bed-
Cold water!
Those pony pox are clearing right up.
Y'know, all of a sudden I'm,
I'm starting to feel better.
I'll just get out of these robes and-
My wing, oh ow, it's hurt.
I guess I can't fly after all.
Messed up wing, huh?
Stop horsing around, Fluttershy.
We've got a lot of training to do.
Come on now, what's going on?
Well, y'see, uh, well...
Rainbow Dash, I just can't do it!
I can't fly!
What are you talking about?
Just last week you went into
that wicked nose dive
to save that falling baby bird
right before it hit the ground!
But that was different,
that was an emergency!
This whole tornado thing,
it's more like a performance.
And you know how I hate performing
in front of others.
Don't you remember flight camp?
I couldn't gallop hard, or fly fast.
Not with everypony looking at me!
It wasn't that bad.
You're right, Rainbow Dash,
it wasn't bad.
It was horrible!
All the other foals
used to tease me
a lot!
Fluttershy, Fluttershy,
Fluttershy can hardly fly!
I just can't risk that
sort of humiliation again.
Suck it up, Fluttershy!
This is no time for-
I mean, confidence or no confidence,
I'm gonna need every pegasus
to break the record, including you.
I need every ounce of wing power
I can get.
I don't think so, Rainbow Dash...
Thanks anyway.
Wait.
I'll do it.
- You will?
- I will.
- You're game?
- I'm game.
Alright!
What exactly does this machine do?
This is an anemometer.
It measures your accelerative velocity
and translates it into wing power.
Thus gauging your cumulative H2O
anti-gravitational potential.
Any other questions?
Yeah.
What exactly does this machine do?
It tells you how fast you're flying
and how strong your wings are.
Is that you again, Thunderlane?
Please, we need to have
a germ-free environment.
It wasn't me, it was Blossomforth.
Don't worry, Twilight.
Thunder Lane is just cooking up an excuse
to spend tornado day in bed.
Why don't you get over here
and be our first test flier, Thunderlane?
We have 9.3 wing power.
Wow! That's fast!
Yeah!
Not bad...not bad.
16.5 wing power!
Now listen up!
If each of you can get your numbers
up to at least 10.0 wing power
by the end of the week,
we'll no doubt set
a new tornado speed record.
We'll be number one!
Impressive.
Fluttershy, your turn.
Fluttershy, Fluttershy,
Fluttershy can hardly fly...
- Tell her!
- No, you tell her!
No, you!
Great job, Fluttershy!
You measured... point five.
Point five? Isn't that like...
less than one?
Fluttershy, Fluttershy,
Fluttershy can hardly fly!
Fluttershy, wait!
So some punks poked a little fun at you
and you got stage fright, big deal.
You aren't gonna go quit
just because of that, are you?
Yes!
But I need you!
I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash, I just
don't have the courage right now...
Oh, thank you, but I'm afraid
a couple of little acorns won't solve
my big flying problem.
I tried, but you should've seen
those ponies laughing at me...
I know it's important
to have confidence in myself...
Yes, yes, I do remember.
The river was swelling...
... and you were scared.
Yes, I did tell you to never give up
and to believe in yourself.
You're right, my friends.
I shouldn't give up.
I will get my confidence up and show
everypony that I am a good flyer!
A great flyer!
That's wonderful, Flitter.
Much better than yesterday.
This is crazy awesome!
We're gonna smash that record!
What'd he say?
Do I look like I speak squirrel?
What's that?
Two point three? Two point three?!
That has to be some kind of mistake!
I worked so hard!
Fluttershy, that's a huge improvement!
You did awesome, Fluttershy.
No I didn't. I thought I'd
gotten over my nerves,
but they still got the best of me!
There's no way I'll fly with
10.0 wing power tomorrow!
So you won't fly with 10.0 wing power.
Every bit counts!
How would you feel if everypony
else was flying with 10.0 wing power
and you were flying with 2.5?
Actually, it was only 2.3, and- ow!
Well, uh... I'd feel...
Exactly! Humiliated!
I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash,
I just can't do it!
It's okay, Rainbow Dash.
You've still got plenty of
wing power for your tornado.
You'll be able to lift tons of water up
to Cloudsdale!
If only there was a way to lift
Fluttershy out of the dumps...
Are we ready to do this?
Look!
Lazy Thunderlane!
Where is he?!
He's been trying to get out
of tornado duty the whole time
with his fake coughing and all.
Rumble, where's your lazy brother?
He's got the feather flu.
He's down at Ponyville hospital.
But he's not the only one.
Let's see, with those eight sick pegasi
out with the feather flu...
Oh no!
Don't tell me we won't be able
to break the windspeed record?
No...
You might not have enough wing power
to create a tornado powerful enough
to lift the water to Cloudsdale!
Well, should we pack up?
No. Of course not.
Forget the record.
Cloudsdale still needs water!
Okay, everypony,
let's give it all we've got!
On the sound of the horn, we take off!
You think they're gonna make it
to eight hundred wing power?
I sure hope so!
One hundred and fifty wing power.
Two hundred and fifty wing power.
Five hundred wing power!
Seven hundred and fifty wing power!
Twilight!
Fluttershy! What are you doing here?!
I figured, if I couldn't help
Rainbow Dash with the tornado,
the least I could do
was offer moral support!
She could sure use it,
considering eight pegasi
are sick with the feather flu!
Oh no! That's terrible news!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
You were so close to the
eight hundred wing power minimum!
I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash.
We've got to try again!
But you've pushed your crew
to their limit already!
If you break apart again,
somepony could get hurt!
You should quit, it's not safe!
No! One more time!
I've gotta know we gave it our all!
If I'm going down, I'm going down flying!
C'mon, ponies, let's make this happen!
Yeah!
Okay, here we go...
One hundred wing power!
Two hundred... five hundred!
Stay in position!
Flap those wings! Faster!
Seven hundred!
Seven hundred and fifty wing power!
They fell apart right after this!
I'm too nervous to look!
C'mon! Just a little harder!
I can see the water
trying to funnel through!
Seven ninety five! We are so close!
Fluttershy, they need you up there!
I won't make a difference!
You can make a difference!
My measly 2.3 wing power
is still too little!
It's sticking at seven ninety five!
I don't know if they've got
any more in 'em!
Do it for Equestria!
Do it for Rainbow Dash!
Do it for yourself!
It's moving!
She's doing it!
Seven ninety eight!
She surpassed her best
wing power number!
Fluttershy, Fluttershy,
Fluttershy can hardly fly!
No!
What was that?
I think it was Fluttershy!
She did it! She did it!
They all did it!
Whoa, girl, take it easy!
Whuh, what? Did we do it?
Yeah, we did it!
You did it!
Great job, Fluttershy,
that was awesome!
Yeah, we couldn't have done it
without you.
Nice job, Rainbow Dash.
You may not have set a new record,
but you showed a lot of guts.
Thanks.
But if you wanna talk guts,
then you've gotta give it
to my number one flyer,
Fluttershy!
Let's hear it for Fluttershy!
Fluttershy! Fluttershy!
Fluttershy can really fly!
Dear Princess Celestia,
sometimes you can feel like
what you have to offer
is too little to make a difference.
But today, I learned that
everypony's contribution is important.
No matter how small.
If you just keep your head high,
do your best, and believe in yourself,
anything can happen.