♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another,
whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Hey, this is Tom!
I can't get
to the mirror right now.
Leave a message
after the shriek.
[cat meows]
Hi, dude! It's me, Star.
Anyway, just, uh, just wondering
what you were up to.
Glossaryck. No! Down!
Glossaryck!
I thought-- I thought we could
meet up for that corn shake.
So, give me a call.
[knocking on door]
Hey, Pony Head-- Ooh!
Sweat much? [laughs]
What, me? Oh, I mean,
that's ridiculous!
Uh... so...
Anyway, I don't mean to dive
straight into hot goss,
but Tom is acting
super weird.
I thought things
were going great,
and then all
of a sudden he--
Are you okay?
You're ruining the carpet.
Okay, what is going on?
What? Ha ha ha! Oh!
You know, that is so funny
that you would think
to say a thing such as that,
because I most definitely
did not run into Tom,
and definitely
he did not tell me
to not tell you
what's going on.
Pony, what's going on?
Tom's getting a demoncism,
and he told me you can't know!
[gasps] Oh, no!
I'm unreliable.
-What?
-Okay, I gotta go now!
Oh, no, you don't!
[shouts]
A demoncism?
Aren't those,
like, the worst?
[spits] Yeah!
They are!
He's gonna ruin himself.
We gotta stop him!
His demoncism is happening,
like, right now!
Wait, what? Where?
Those things are,
like, super secret!
Like, you gotta get invited.
You do realize you were
not invited, right?
I'm not trying to rub that
in your face, but...
[grunts]
This is not helping.
Look, we can go ask my ex.
He got demoncized.
Which ex? Sorry.
That sounded way more judgy
that I wanted it to.
Oh, Bessie, are you
talking right now?
My big bad ex, Seahorse?
You know, he's the one
who wrote that song about me.
-Blech.
-[heavy metal shouting]
Aw, yeah!
You're all trash! Aah!
Aw! He was
such a romantic.
Yeah, I-I tried that.
What kind of dummy
do you think I am?
This mirror's garbage!
I'm sorry.
That's disappointing.
Can I help you
find a replacement?
No. No!
Get out!
Thank you for choosing
Reflecticore.
Have a mirror-ific day!
Oh, what a nerd!
Look how much water
he needs now!
He's a seahorse, Pony.
Yeah, well, he used to be
all dry, like a cool horse.
Well, hello! Welcome
to Reflecticore Mobile.
Can I help you find
a compact mirror?
Mm, I'm just dropping by
to, like, see how you've
been doing and stuff.
[whispers] And to ask
about the demoncism!
Yeah, and that too.
Please take your time
browsing our collection.
Uh, what?
Please take your time
browsing our--
Yeah, I got that!
Don't you even have
anything else to say to me?
Can I interest you
in a three-year
interdimensional plan?
Seahorse! Hello!
Wake up! It's me, Pony Head!
[groans] Can't we even talk
like normal horsepersons?
Well, you can talk
to anyone
with Reflecticore
Mobile Technology.
Okay, you know what?
You're broken, Seahorse.
You're not the man
you used to be.
That's disappointing.
Can I help you
find a replacement?
[crying]
It's so horrible!
It's like he doesn't
even know me!
And I'm the best person
anyone could know!
I'm like a gift!
Oh, Pony, I am so sorry.
I'll take care of it.
A friend of ours
is going to get
a demoncism tonight,
and we need to know
where it's happening.
Can you give
us directions
using Reflecticore
Mobile Technology?
[squish]
You can go anywhere
with Reflecticore
Mobile Technology.
We just want a map,
you corporate turd!
[sobs]
I'll print a--
I'll print a map now.
[squish]
[buzzing]
[Pony Head whimpering]
[gong ringing]
You distract them.
I'll find Tom.
Oh, yeah, I got you, girl.
Watch this.
Excuse me!
Some last-minute announcement!
So, as all of you know,
fall is coming up.
Okay, so let's take a vote
on our new spooky robes.
The first color
we're gonna vote on is maroon.
Yea or nay?
All for yea,
show your hands.
O-Okay, so we
just not a hot ticket.
That's fine.
We just have one for yea. Okay.
All right, Tom, just what
do you think you're do--?
-Oh, you look so nice!
-What are you doing here?
I'm here to stop you from making
a terrible, terrible mistake!
If this is just another way
to get my attention, you--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
I don't know
what Pony told you,
but it's
not what you think.
I genuinely want this.
What?
[sighs]
I need to change.
You're here being
the best princess
you can be,
and it's
really inspiring.
It's time for me
to be a better prince.
Yeah, but whatever's
going on out there
looks creepy
and dangerous.
I'm the prince
of the underworld, okay?
This is gonna be
an easy procedure
for a guy like me.
In and out!
All this stuff--
the robed guys,
the skulls, the fire--
it's just for show.
So, you're just gonna zap
all your personality away
so you can feel good
about yourself?
No! I have problems,
and this is the only way
to get rid of them!
Ow! See? Problems!
You don't have to be
like this, Tom!
Yeah, well, I've
already made up my mind,
and you're not
gonna stop me.
Fine, be that way!
But I am not gonna stay here
and watch you
do this to yourself.
I didn't invite
you, anyway, so...
-Great!
Gah! Of course!
Also, who is bringing
what to the potluck, okay?
Because I don't wanna see
nothing but chips.
Come on,
we're outta here.
All right, y'all, thank you
so much for your time!
[gong ringing]
Brethren, this world
is in danger.
There is a blight
that plagues it.
Of course, we dream
of a world pure
as a piece of sweet corn,
but if one kernel
is infected,
then the entire harvest
is at risk.
Bring forth the son
of the blight.
Son of the blight
has arrived!
Thanks for coming out,
everybody.
Whoa! Tight grip there.
That fool
is so frustrating!
I just wanna--
I just wanna--!
Like, punch a tree
or something?
I need to punch a tree!
Girl! You know
I hate trees.
[snapping]
Hey, hey! Thanks
for the ride, guys!
Love
the massage table.
Commence
the purification ritual.
[sneezing]
Okey-doke.
Let the ceremony begin.
[reciting
in foreign language]
[responding in foreign language]
[crows cawing]
Oh. That's a nice touch.
[reciting
in foreign language]
[responding
[zaps]
Wow! Magic manacles.
Magicals.
The cauldron!
Close your eyes.
Okay, but no tickling!
Hey. Hey, man, this is
real ceremonious and stuff,
but it seems kind
of flim-flam to [hiccoughs]--
[zapping]
[screams]
It begins!
[Tom growling]
Hold him!
[screaming continues]
[reciting in foreign language]
Aah!
[indistinct yell]
[grunting]
Harder! Harder!
Yah!!!
[flames explode]
Dang, not that hard.
[men screaming]
What? That's weird.
Something's wrong.
Huh? Where are you going?
No!
You're just gonna leave him
up there like that?
He'll be fine.
Magical mach ten blast!
[gasps]
Tom, it's okay.
I'm-- I'm here.
I'm right here.
[groans]
Star?
Tom? Oh, my gosh,
are you okay?
I'm... [excitedly]
in tremendous pain!
[demoncist] Congratulations,
Master Lucitor.
The procedure
was a success.
[growls]
Wow. Hard to believe
that one little demon
was the source
of so much rage!
What? No, no.
No, no, no.
You still got thousands
of these little guys inside.
We're gonna have to start you
on a 13-year plan.
-What?
-Yeah, this is all gonna be
a long and painful process
for all of us,
but you were
such a good boy today,
you can help yourself
to just one toy
from the toy chest.
Oh, no. No!
No, no!
I'm gonna be
an evil demon forever!
The important thing is that
you want to improve yourself!
You can still do that
with a bunch of those
little guys inside of you.
So, should we go again
next weekend?
No. This is not worth it.
Well, if you're
not coming back,
you'd better make
that one toy count.
So, still up
for that corn shake?
Yeah, that'd be cool.
[gasps] You two have got
to be kidding me.
Oh, no.
Hey, there, big guy.
Hey, Mama!
So, you're ready
for the new school year?
Yep. Still getting used
to Earth life, though.
[slurps ]
Hmm. I see you're still
wearing your cape.
Of course.
I'm a knight!
Did I ever tell you
about my friend
who spent a summer
in France?
In France,
everything was better--
the arthouse films,
the fashion, the croissants.
She said it just like that--
"croissant."
Who does that?
Wow, your friend
sounds annoying.
It was me, Marco.
"Croissant."
Oh! [chuckles]
But... come on!
I'm not annoying.
I just wear a cape.
Look, I'm sure everybody
on Moony wore a cape.
Mewni.
It's pronounced "Mew-ni."
Marco,
I'm just trying to help.
And I'm just trying to help
you properly say "Mewni."
Croissant! Croissant!
It's pronounced "croissant!"
Hey, no!
No, no, no!
I'm not the croissant girl!
I earned this cape,
and by golly,
I'm gonna wear it!
Good for you, Marco.
The cape looks cool.
Thanks, Dad.
You are chained to the wall
of Azgorth's dungeon
surrounded by his feral imps,
and only one holds the key
to your freedom.
-What's in our surroundings?
-Nothing.
I try and break the chains.
The imps eat your hands.
Aah!
I cast a healing spell!
-The imps eat your hands.
-Marco!
Oh, um...
use the butter.
What? There's no butter!
Didn't you hear
what she just said?
There's nothing
in our surroundings!
Put it on the chains,
slide your hands out,
hide in the vents!
This isn't Mewni, Marco!
It's not going to work.
It worked.
You're free.
Oh! Oh! Next we go
find Ludo,
say the Whispering Spell,
destroy Toffee!
No! This
isn't Mewni!
Yeah, you destroy Toffee,
save Mewni.
Congratulations!
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
It's okay, Ferguson!
It's just a game!
No. On Mewni,
this actually happened!
They made me a knight!
[door slams]
Where-- Where did Ferguson
and Alfonso go?
They left.
What? Why?
Oh, they just get annoyed
when you talk
about Mewni all the time.
It's no big deal.
What?
All right, sensei,
just be straight with me, man.
Am I annoying when I talk
about Mewni?
Of course not, Marco.
You had a life-changing
experience on Mewni,
and it changed you.
Yeah,  that's right.
And it changed me too.
[chortling]
Look at it!
Look at it, yeah!
Ohh, ohh, it's a--
it's a cape.
We're cape bros now, dude.
Oh, that's--
that's great.
Marco,
you're making a face.
What face? This face?
It's just my face.
Hey, hey, hey. No secrets.
We're cape bros now.
Oh, well, it's no big deal,
but I-I earned my cape.
Earned? Is that...
a word you made up?
I just went through a lot
to get my cape.
I mean, I helped
save Mewni, you know?
Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
I keep forgetting,
you have to earn things.
[laughter]
[sobbing]
[sniffling]
You're right, Marco.
I guess I didn't earn this.
No, sensei.
I mean, did I really
earn my red belt?
[grunts]
Or my green belt?
I guess I didn't earn
any belts.
[chortles] You know,
I expected this
from my mother
and my probation officer,
but I didn't expect this
from you.
[Marco] You know,
first Ferguson
and Alfonso were weird,
and then sensei was weird.
[sighs]
I-I hate to say this,
but it's like
my best friends
are jealous of all
that I've accomplished.
[sighs]
Look, I get it.
Earth and Mewni
are totally different.
It must be hard to readjust.
No, Jackie,
you don't get it.
This isn't about me,
this is about them
not being able to accept
what this means.
How long has it been
since you took off your cape?
Pshh.
That's not relevant.
But it kind of feels like
you went to Mewni
and you never really
came back.
I'm not trying
to make you feel bad,
but you haven't even asked
about my summer.
You've just been talking
about yours.
Oh, no.
I'm the Croissant Girl.
-What?
-Oh, Jackie, I'm so sorry.
Wha-what are you
talking about?
-Jackie, I'm going
to make this up to you.
-Make what up?
You're never going to hear me
say "croissant" again.
[laughing]
-What?
-You look so... fancy.
Okay, okay.
[clears throat]
Jackie Lynn Thomas,
I'm here to take you
on the ultimate date.
Wait, seriously?
I'm done with Mewni, see?
No cape.
I'm back,
and I'm here for you.
Me, huh?
Well, can you guess
what I want to do right now?
Oh, Jackie, you know
I'm not good at this game.
Read my mind, Marco.
Uh...
Okay.
You want to go to
Seashell...ville...?
Shell Town? Shellville?
Necklace Land.
Necklace Land?
Necklace Land!
Shells?
Seashell?
Seashell Land?
Shelly.
Mike and Shelly.
You want to go to
Mike and Shelly's house.
No, dude, we're here.
Ohh, the pier!
Okay, see, I-I never
would have gotten that
from a seashell.
So, what exactly are you
supposed to do
on the ultimate date?
Ohh!
How about...
I win you
this cute dog thing.
Ha! Yeah, these guys
kind of look like you.
One dozen balls, please.
What?
[grunts]
This thing is rigged.
Let me try.
[bell ringing]
-Sweet!
-How did you do that?
Grand prize
for the lady.
This is the best day
of my life.
Marco.
[bird squawks]
Can you believe
this is almost our
three month-a-versary?
Yeah, we're like
an old married couple.
But we were doing long distance
for, like, half the time.
Don't think I wasn't jealous
of that cute lady mime.
Hey! Oh, n-- Aww.
Here,
have some of mine.
Aw, thanks.
That's amazing of you,
but I could actually go
for some real people food.
How much cash
do you have on you?
I don't know--
$650?
[both laughing]
Whew, okay.
Is there
anything on the menu
we haven't ordered yet?
There's that guy.
[gurgling]
No, I can't eat him--
he looks so sad.
[comical accent]
Hey! What do you a-think
you are doing-ah?
Run!
[both laughing]
Hey! Give it back here-ah!
Ohh!
[both panting]
Wow, he didn't even
say goodbye.
Not even a little
claw wave or something.
Dude, it's a lobster.
Oh.
-What are you thinking about?
-Lobsters.
We saved one, but we
could have saved them all.
Do you want
to go back for them?
I kind of do, though.
Freedom to lobsters!
Death
to fancy restaurants!
Oh ho ho! Yeah!
Whoo!
[laughing]
I finally feel like
I'm back on Earth.
Is that a good thing?
It's a great thing.
[soft grunt]
There's no place
I'd rather be.
Take off your shirt.
-Huh?
-What? Just do it.
[nervous chuckle]
But now? Why?
It's just a--
Huh.
What?
How did that
get in there?
Let's talk.
Okay, I know
this looks bad,
but I'm fine.
I can take it off
anytime I want.
[sighs]
Look, today was awesome,
and it's really sweet
that you're trying,
but if you're forcing
yourself to stay in Echo Creek
just so I'll be happy,
then we'll both end up
miserable.
You do see that, right?
So, I figure
now's a good time
to give you an out.
I want to make this work.
You're my best friend,
Jackie.
Mmm.
Oh, Marco.
[kiss]
We both know
that's not true.
Stay amazing, okay?
Well, I now release you
from the bonds of academia.
Be free. Uh... uh...
something like that.
We've never sent a kid
to another dimension before.
Sure you have.
It's just like what started
when she did her
exchange program--
just, you know,
in the opposite direction.
Well, I hope
I'm not sending you
off to your death.
Marco, hold on!
You can't leave  yet!
We want to say sorry for
how we acted the other day.
No, guys, I'm the one
who needs to say sorry.
I-I really haven't
been around much, and...
Dude, it's okay.
Look, we-we
brought you something.
It's our lucky die.
It'll grant you
good fortune
on your travels.
Aw.
Thanks, you guys.
For the record,
I'm still mad at you.
I know.
But I got you something.
[weeping] I'm gonna
miss you so much!
[chuckles] I'm gonna
miss you too, man.
I also got
something for you.
Wha-- what?!?!
How long have you had this?
Don't ask questions
you don't want the answer to.
[sighs]
What a creep.
Well, I guess this is
goodbye, guys.
I don't understand.
We're just letting
Marco leave school?
Is this even legal?
Shh. Marco needs to have
his own French summer.
What? What is happening?
-Bye-bye, Marc!
-Bye, Marco!
-Bye!
-Bye-bye!
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪