♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't
from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another,
whoo-hoo ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪♪
[sighs]
[both scream]
Mama! I need to talk to you.
I can't believe it!
-Star, I'm in the middle of--
-It's blowing my beautiful mind!
Okay, I have been meaning
to talk to you, as well.
We need to discuss
what happened at the temple.
Right? Isn't it
bonkers that Heinous
is Eclipsa's daughter?
Mina told me everything!
Mina! What are you
talking about?
Listen, I won't have you
making up ridiculous stories
to distract
from the real issue here!
The little party you threw
at the Monster Temple?
I told you
that it was dangerous
to rush the Mewman
and monster relationship.
You should have checked
with me first!
What? No, that's not
what I'm talking about!
Besides, you should've
checked with me
before you sent Rhombulous
in to storm the whole place!
Rhombulous? I didn't
send Rhombulous!
-Lies!
-You barge in here
with ridiculous claims
about Heinous,
make a mess in my office,
and then call me a liar?
I don't have time for this!
What? Hey! No, no, no, no!
I am not finished
talking about this yet!
What are we gonna do
about Heinous?
How could you do this
to your precious baby girl?
You're not a baby,
so stop acting like one!
[grunts]
I'm not a baby?
I'll show you a baby!
No! I came here
to talk about Heinous,
and that's just what
I'm gonna do. Ugh!
There you go,
rushing into things again!
Ugh! Dad, now is
not the time!
I really need
to talk to Mom!
Agh, you don't know
what you need!
-I'm sorry?
-But I do.
-Hunting trip!
-What?
Just like my father
did with me,
whose father did
with him,
and his father
did with him!
Just right after I talk
to Mom about this--
Ha ha! That's what I said
to my father before me,
and what he said
to his father before him
and his father before him
and his brother...
Uh, Dad!
[grunting]
Dad, what are we
doing here?
We have a royal family crisis
on our hands!
[grunts] There's
always a crisis.
Okay, I'm just gonna
call Mom and--
No, you don't.
[dial tones beeping]
Papa, what are you doing?!
[swallows] Ahh!
[Moon] Hello? Hello?
Star is that you?
-[beeps]
-She's busy.
Starship, listen to me.
This is a very important hunt,
and I want you here for it.
Once it's over, you can return
to your little crisis,
but until then,
you're all mine. Deal?
Fine... Can we please
hurry, then?
As soon as we
find Eddie.
-[New Zealand accent]
I'm right here!
-[both startle]
That's me, Eddie!
I have the markings
of a plant,
but in fact
I'm just a regular fella.
Oh! [laughs] Eddie,
you old bottom dweller!
Ha ha! True, I am
a bit of a creeper.
Yeah, you are.
So, what brings you
to this neck of the parks?
The Bogbeast of Boggabah!
Wowee! Is it
that time already?
Bogbeast?
Sounds easy enough.
Ah, you're
a first-timer, clearly.
This is no trifle matter!
The last thing you want
is to face the beast
ill-prepared.
I remember
my first Bogbeast hunt.
It did not go well.
Well, I'll alert the others!
You better get prepped!
How long is this
gonna take?
It takes as long
as it takes!
Listen for the Bogbeast song.
That's when you know it's near.
[River] Come, Star!
[groans] Coming.
[drumbeats]
[River] Okay,
the first ritual
is to cleanse
our minds of fear!
The beast can smell your fears
before you're even afraid.
Uh-huh. Okay, yeah,
so what do we do first?
We sweat!
Oh...kay.
Look, look!
I got one!
Ugh, forget this!
Summoning cloudy charm!
[thunder rumbles]
We good here?
[spits] It's time to learn
how to be one
with our surroundings.
[grunting] A voila!
The ancient skill
of camouflage!
But before you start,
you must check
every leaf carefully.
Yeah, I have
a better idea.
No! You'll accidentally
pick up the baby bog dragons
that live there!
Huh?
[squeaking]
Easy, little dragon babies!
-[flames whoosh]
-[Star screams]
[squeaking]
[sighs] Next task!
Mewman hair-braiding
is very important.
Oh.
It teaches focus
and attention to detail!
Ugh! Dad!
[humming]
[laughing]
Ah, yeah...
There!
Ooh!
Now do me.
[growls]
[deep tones]
The Bogbeast song!
Let's go get it!
Honey, we must finish
the rituals!
-But--
-Make me pretty!
Wait, wait,
wait, wait. Done!
Thank you, pumpkin.
Next ritual!
Dad!
Okay, the last ritual
is to teach focus.
To protect ourselves,
we must cover our bodies
with ancient markings!
Ahh! Like tattoos?
No! Ancient markings!
That doesn't seem hard.
And kinda cool.
Dip the stick--
Careful, uh, slowly.
There we are!
Way ahead of you!
Fascinating! Can we
start the hunt now?
Yes! Just 100
more scrolls to go.
[gasps, groans]
Make sure you get
the curve.
Don't forget
the curve at the end.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Got the curve.
There, done!
Very good, milkshake!
Now, let's see what you--
"Boy Beatz"?
[laughs] That's supposed
to say "Bogbeast"!
Ha! I'm afraid we'll
have to start all over.
What? Oh, no.
All right,
I'll get the ink and then--
Oh, no,
I mean all over,
from the very beginning!
Tallyho!
What? Ugh.
♪♪
Ugh, okay! We sweated,
we camouflaged,
we braided,
and we protected
our bodies
with ancient scroll thingies!
I am ready!
Wait! I'll tell you
if you're ready or not.
Look into my eyes.
Hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yes.
You are ready! Ack!
My back!
Don't worry!
This happens
all the time.
Just...
need to sit down.
But I'm ready!
Actually, no, you're not.
I lied, just as
my father lied to me,
and his father lied to him
and his father lied--
He was a liar.
Now, come lay down,
and we'll start over fresh
in the morning-- [snores]
What, you're asleep?!
Ugh! Okay.
[wind whistling]
[deep tones]
He's here.
That's it! Bogbeast,
I'm coming for you!
[screaming]
The Bogbeast! Yow!
Ugh! Oh!
Are you kidding me?
I don't have time
for this!
[deep tones]
What the--?
-[deep tones]
-Geh!
Aah! [groans]
Uh... hello?
Hello?
Who is there?
Oh!
[grunts] Bogbeast,
is that you?
Uh... no!
Don't-- don't--
Don't come any closer!
[screaming]
What? Huh?
Greetings, all!
[laughing]
I present you
the Bogbeast of Boggabah!
[all cheering]
♪♪
[deep tones]
Huh?
Congratulations, pumpkin!
-[laughs]
-Ah, what?
Me--? I am not
the Bogbeast!
Of course you are!
We've all been the Bogbeast
at one point or another!
Old Eddie here has even
been the Bogbeast twice!
Ha ha! I never learn!
Being impulsive
and running into situations
headfirst without thinking
is your specialty, dear,
but it's also what makes
a Bogbeast.
You have
so much greatness in you,
I don't want anything
to stand in your way,
especially yourself.
Please remember
this hunt always.
I will, Dad.
[man]
Bog party, everybody!
Sorry, not this time.
I promised Star
we'd go home.
She has stuff
that she needs to do.
[all groan]
You know what? My stuff
can wait till morning.
I think I can squeeze
a little bog party in.
Bog party!
[cheering]
♪♪
[sighs] Okay.
How could you do this
to your precious baby girl?
You're not a baby,
so stop acting like one!
[groans] Trying...
[chair squeaks]
Try already,
and she doesn't think...
Whew...
Baloo, balee,
baloo, below.
I let you go,
I let you go.
I don't even know
my own family.
[groans] Fine.
[rock music playing]
Eclipsa? I...
[gasps]
Oh, hey.
Queen Moon, hi.
You're in my room.
[sounds]
[squeaks]
Did you make a guitar...
out of a skeleton?
I work with what
I'm given.
This should be quick.
Star just stormed
into my office
with some crazy idea
about who your daughter is.
Okay.
Look, I just need you
to identify her
from a picture.
Can you do that?
Hmm.
What is it?
It's just...
I haven't seen my daughter
in 300 years.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have...
No, it's fine.
I'm fine.
Is this your daughter?
Festivia? No.
What? Are you sure?
Oh, I'm sure.
My daughter
was Meteora.
Well, the name
may have been changed.
But that's not her.
My daughter had
pretty little clovers
on her cheeks
and the cutest tail
in all of Mewni.
I-I'm sorry, a tail?
She got it
from her daddy.
But how is that possible?
Well, when a queen
and a monster love
each other very much...
I mean, how could this
not be your daughter?
This is the complete history
of the Butterfly family!
If this isn't your daughter,
then who is she?
I wish I could
tell you!
The Royal Archive
would have the truth.
The Archive?
In the Bureaucracy of Magic?
Where they keep lunch receipts
and office supplies?
Don't judge a room
by its supplies.
The Archive has
the real history,
beyond what's
in your book.
Well, I don't have access
to the Archive,
don't even know
how to get there.
I could come with you.
No, no, no.
That, uh, won't be possible.
I'd never hear the end of it
if I took you out of here.
Well, good luck.
If you find out
what happened,
please let me know.
I had a daughter.
I'd like to know
what happened to her.
[sighs] Fine. Let's go.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Well, think of it
as a girls' night,
if that makes you
feel better.
It doesn't.
♪♪
Sean, you little pig.
You made a mess.
Who's gonna clean this up?
Ah...
-[Moon] Hello, Sean!
-Huh?
-Queen Moon!
-Just, uh, just grabbing
something from my office,
like a normal person!
[klaxon blares]
Sorry, Queen Moon.
Looks like I'll
have to scan ya.
Yeah, that's
a great idea, Sean.
Why don't you scan me!
Uh, no, it's...
I don't need to!
Uh, it's probably fine.
[quavering]
I can't believe I'm doing this.
What am I doing?
Get out of there!
Now, where's the Archive?
I don't know.
You said you knew
where you were going!
Last time I was here,
the Archive was just
a stone cottage.
Wait, did you say stone?
Oh. It's a coat closet.
Don't judge a room
by its supplies.
Tah-dah.
Well, would you
look at that.
Let's see if I remember...
-[tones play]
-Duh... duh...
Mmm...
♪ Duh-duh-duh-duh
buh-bah! ♪
-[hissing]
-Ooh!
[heavy grinding]
Aren't you just
full of secrets!
Did it again, Sean.
Is that how you want
to live your life?
Those cupcakes
weren't even for you!
Oh.
Hey, Queen Moon.
Sean!
I see you brought, um...
you brought a friend,
and you opened
a secret door.
-It's not--
-[static clicks]
What are you doing?
I think I gotta report this,
don't I?
Put that down, Sean!
Right now.
I'm sorry,
I can't do that.
-[static clicks]
-[grunts]
[chuckles]
[worried moan]
No, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, the other members
of the High Commission,
they won't understand!
Why don't you
wipe his memory?
-[both] What?
-Oh, use your magic.
You know, just point and say
"mind eraser!" Pew-pew!
What? You can't do that!
Well, of course she can.
She's magic.
I am not wiping
his memory, Eclipsa!
-Eclipsa!
-Well, I can't do it.
I never learned magic
without a wand.
Yeah, please don't.
Is this how you
used magic?
When there's a problem,
you just "mind eraser, pew-pew"?
[groans]
[gasps] What've I done?
Oh, come on, you did
that on purpose.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I must be crazy!
Let's see.
♪ Dark is the hall ♪
♪ Beyond the pitch,
oh, where could
there be light? ♪
What are you doing?
Oh, just singing
a little song
I wrote to help me
remember my way.
Wait, Eclipsa,
don't run!
♪ Dark is the hall ♪
♪ Beyond the pitch ♪
♪ Oh, where could
there be light? ♪
It's this way.
♪ Not up nor down
but three steps round ♪
Hey, slow down!
Two doors down!
♪ Her torch
shall steer you right ♪
[sighs] Tah-dah!
Locked. Hmm.
Have you got
a hairpin?
That's better!
Okay, right, so we're going
to use the rat hole.
What rat hole?
Rat hole.
I am not getting
in a rat hole!
[giggles]
It's so dirty in here!
Isn't there--
isn't there another way?
[groans]
Oh, I think I'm stuck!
Yeah, I think so, too.
Looks like
your gown is stuck.
I'll have to go round to
pull you through, okay?
How long will it be
before you're on the other side?
Not long at all.
No worries!
♪♪
[grunts]
[tinkles]
What are you... doing?
[Moon gasps]
Hey, drop that!
[sighs] How long have
I been out?
Oh, no. Eclipsa!
Eclipsa!
Hello?
[sighs] I trusted her!
I can't believe
I trusted her!
Knock, knock!
What took you so long?!
I came as fast
as I could.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I just needed a little-- agh!
It's-- it's incredible!
I had no idea
this was here.
No, no, no!
Watch your step.
You'll set off
the alarm.
I haven't seen these little guys
in forever. Hello!
They've been recording
everything that's ever happened
to the royal family.
"7:59, King River reveals Star
to be the Bogbeast of Boggabah"?
What? You know, this stuff
would've made it a lot easier
to build a case
against you! Sorry.
There's so much stuff here,
it's impossible
to find anything,
unless you know
where to look.
[grunting]
Of course, I know
where my scroll is.
[screams]
Ah, here it is!
And so the daughter
of Eclipsa and King Shastacan,
Princess Festivia,
was crowned queen
upon her mother's
imprisonment.
They took her out!
They erased all record
of my daughter completely!
Who's Festivia?
Don't worry, we'll get
to the bottom of this.
-Unh!
-Oh!
Once we're back
at the palace, we can put--
[stone grinds]
I told you
to watch your step!
[klaxon blares]
-Run! Run!
-It's not the easiest thing
in this dress!
-[tinkles]
-Mmm!
Aah! Go!
Oh, dear. Unh!
[groans]
-You incorrigible--
-Moon, hurry!
Ha ha!
[quavering]
All right, so it's clear
someone's orchestrated
a cover-up,
and I think I know
who it was.
They erased my daughter.
I'm the one on trial.
Eclipsa, I believe your daughter
may still be alive.
-What? But how?
-[knocking]
-Hey.
-[both] Hey.
♪ She's a princess ♪
♪ Winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry
when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she would keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪