♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Oh, burrito ♪
♪ Burrito ♪
♪ I'll never let you go ♪
♪ My little burrito ♪
♪ Burrito, burrito, burrito ♪
♪ We've got such a long way
to go ♪
♪ For me to eat you ♪
MARCO: Hey Star!
- ( screams )
- Ow!
Marco! What did I
tell you about...
Wait... Marco!
Hi.
Oh, my goodness!
It's so good to see you.
Um, what are you doing here?
I missed it here,
so, I decided to come back
permanently.
- ( toilet flushes )
- TOM: ♪ Burrito, burrito ♪
- ♪ I'll never let... ♪
- Tom?
- Marco!
- Tom!
- GUARD: Intruder!
- ( Marco groans )
KNIGHTS: Hup, hup, hup.
Uh, wait, wait, wait,
wait a minute.
Guys, guys, hey guys,
it's all right. It's just Marco.
I'm not an intruder.
King River said
I could be a knight.
See?
I got the cape and everything.
( laughs )
- Look, he's got a cape.
- ( all laughing )
Ugh, River.
I'm so confused here.
You told Marco
he could be a knight?
Well, uh, yeah.
I never actually thought
we'd see him again. Ha ha!
I'm sorry, Marco, but I'm afraid
that's not how it works.
But King River
gave me a knight's cape.
M for Mewni.
No, my boy,
that's my meat blanket.
- Meat blanket?
- Yes.
- I also have a cheese doily.
- ( sighs )
But I wore this thing
every day.
For weeks. Weeks...
I'm sorry, Marco,
but becoming a knight
is no easy task.
Yes. It takes years
of intense training, dear.
Yeah.
Years of intense training.
- He hasn't even been a squire.
- A squire?
Hey, I can do that.
River, are any of our knights
in need of a squire?
Wait, I've got it.
How about we set him up
with Sir Pop Lock and Dropeth?
Hmm?
That old scamp!
( whispering ) Um, actually,
he "pop, locked, and dropped".
You mean...?
Oh, my.
Star, why don't you
have Marco stay with you?
It will give you two
a chance to catch up
while we figure this out.
Wait, wait, wait.
I know a knight
he can squire for.
Man, Star. I'm sorry.
I feel like I just
crash landed into your life.
Well, we figured it out.
Yeah... um, cool.
Wow, heh. Check out
all these stairs.
Sure are a lot.
So, what does Jackie
think about all this?
Oh, well, she wasn't
really into it, but you know me.
Ain't nobody telling me
what to do. ( chuckles )
That-that was a joke.
Actually, yeah,
she-she broke up with me.
Well,
I'm very sorry about that.
So, are you and Tom--
Yep!
Oh, look, here's that door
we were walking to.
( Lavabo laughing )
Found you!
Ah, here's our guy,
Sir Lavabo. Hi!
Ah, princess.
I will be with you shortly.
I have a job to finish.
There. Every sock in the kingdom
now has its mate.
How may I be of service?
Well, I...
I got you a squire.
( gasps )
My own squire?
What do you call him?
- Marco Diaz.
- What?
I'm squiring
for the laundry guy?
Yeah. This is Sir Lavabo.
He's super cool.
But I'd be way down here
in the basement.
Actually, sub-basement.
So moody.
You're gonna love it.
Yeah, but, just the same,
how about you princess me up
something a little closer,
like, say,
something in the castle?
Marco, just 'cause
I'm a princess
doesn't mean
I can do anything I want.
Yeah, but if I'm
all the way down here,
we're never even
gonna see each other.
( growls )
You don't appreciate
anything I do!
Star, wait. I didn't mean...
Marco Diaz, are you ready
for your first quest?
Yeah... sure.
What are we doing?
You must empty
the lint catcher.
( mocking Marco )
"Oh, hey Star!"
"I just showed up
out of nowhere."
"Why don't you give me
a job to do?"
Okay, Marco, here's a job.
"No, not that job!
Another job--" ( groans )
Hello.
Eclypsa.
They're giving you
some outdoor time.
That's great.
I know.
And real dragon chains,too.
( sighs ) They make a lady
feel so free.
Oh, yeah, that's, uh,
that's really awesome.
Can I sit?
Sit, like, right there?
( grunts )
( exhales )
Thanks.
Here, take a load off.
Feed the birds.
Always makes me feel better.
I don't get how some people
think it's okay
to just drop into your life
without so much
as a head's up.
You know what I'm saying?
And then you try
to help him out,
no appreciation.
So, what's his name?
Huh? What?
No, no, no, no, no,
it's not like that.
Well, well, not anymore.
- It's just Marco.
- Well, Marco.
So, that's it.
Marco thinks that
just because
I'm a princess,
I can get him
whatever job he wants.
Well, can't you?
No... yes.
But that's not the point.
Well, now that he's here,
do you want him to stay?
Uh, yeah... no.
Ugh, I don't know.
Doesn't matter anyway.
I already made him
a laundry squire.
He's squiring
for the knight of the wash?
Well, then your problem
will take care of itself, dear.
What's that supposed to mean?
No squire has ever survived
more than a day
in the laundry room.
It's the most dangerous place
in the castle.
( gasps ) Marco! I got to go.
Thanks for the popcorn.
That wasn't popcorn.
Lavabo, where's Marco?
On his first quest,
cleaning out the lint catcher,
mi' lady.
Oh, no.
Sparkle slushie juice blast!
Wait, princess!
Marco?
Whoa!
( blows raspberry )
That was weird.
Marco! There you are.
No, don't.
You're gonna wake it up.
- What?
- No, I said.
Don't. You're gonna wake it up.
What?
( sighs ) I said,
you're going to wake it up.
( slithering )
( screeching )
- Whoa!
- Ugh!
Whoa! Aah!
Aah!
Rolling thunder lightning blast!
( grunts )
( shrieks )
No!
( Star screaming )
( grunts )
Marco!
( belches )
Huh?
( both grunt )
Marco, are you okay?
We gotta get
that fan moving.
( monster rumbling )
( Marco grunting )
Hiya!
( grunts )
It won't budge!
Wiggle harder!
( rumbling )
I'm coming, Marco.
- Ha, gotcha!
- Whoa!
( monster screaming )
Fantastic exit beam!
- Aah!
( both grunt )
LAVABO:
Bravo!
Fantastique!
Only one other squire
has survived the lint catcher.
Me!
Marco Diaz, you will make
a fine squire
for the knights of the wash.
( chuckles ) Great.
Thanks, I guess.
Uh, Lavabo, can you
give us a sec?
I need to talk
to Marco alone.
As you wish, Princess.
Long live the wash.
( sighs )
Okay, listen, Marco.
Here's the thing.
A lot has changed
in my life since you left.
It's complicated,
but I finally figured out
that I just need to be
the best princess I can now.
And with you here
it's really hard to--
Yeah, yeah.
I totally get it.
It was a crazy bad idea
for me to do this
without giving you
a heads up.
I'll go back to Earth.
That's not what I meant.
Okay, can I, uh,
take my hands
off my face, please?
I feel like I'm gonna
run into something.
Okay, stop.
This is the place.
Sparkle glitter bomb expand.
Okay, you can look now.
Wow.
Is that... ( gasps )
What?
No way!
I can't believe it!
( puppies whimpering )
My room!
( gasps )
All my stuff!
My galactic kung fu doll.
( gasps )
This is so great!
Marco, kneel.
( chuckles )
Uh, what?
Marco, sit.
What are-are you doing?
( clears throat )
Head down, please.
I hereby declare that you,
Marco Ubaldo Diaz,
shall henceforth
be my royal squire,
to stay by my side
in times of peace
or danger,
as my most trusted
confidant and advisor.
To go clubbing with me
even when he's too tired,
to share his
late night nachos,
but most importantly
to be my very best friend
so long as we both
shall live.
Amen.
Do you accept?
I do.
Wait, do princesses
even have squires?
I'm a princess.
I can do what I want.
Attention, Quest Buy shoppers,
Quest Buy is proud to host
Quest Buy's 10,000th annual
Squire Blowout, or whatever.
Marco, this is gonna be
so much fun!
Just a squire and his knight
shopping, pop-locking,
shop-locking.
You know,
you feel me, bro.
I know that looked like it hurt.
Oh, it did,
but I'll feel better
as soon as we find
this little beauty
from the Quest Buy catalog.
I've always wanted one!
Sorry, Star, but that's
not on the list.
Boom!
BABY-MAN:
Wow, that's so organized.
Look, it's got coupons
attached to it.
I like a coupon.
( chuckles )
Hey, guys.
Oh, hey, man.
I dig your list.
Thanks.
It's every sale item
of the Squire Blowout
grouped together
by aisle and availability.
I called ahead to check
the inventory on each item.
That's cool.
A great squire is
an organized squire.
That's what I always say.
Uh, great.
Squire!
I'm Higgs.
That's Baby-Man.
- Hey!
- And the old guy
- is Old Guy.
- I'm old!
- I'm M--
- He's Marco.
This is his first blowout.
Really? Huh.
I would've thought
you a veteran
with that fancy
list of yours.
Nope.
I don't know anything at all.
Heh, nice.
Well, welcome to the
community, Marco.
- I'm honored.
Oh, uh, just a little
squire to squire advice,
equipping your knight
and making them look good
is gonna be your
most important task.
So you wanna get to
the good stuff fast.
The shelves
clear out quickly.
I plan on it.
So, where are
y'alls knights at?
Oh, they're over there.
That's Lady Whosits.
Baby-Man's knight.
( growls, laughs )
And Old Man's knight,
Sir Dashing of Muzzleton.
( gasps )
Call me.
And this is my knight,
Sir Stabby.
( growls )
Higgs, I am in need
of a wet wipe.
Oh, cool.
Duty calls.
See you at the starting line.
- Nerd.
- Okay.
Did she just
call me a nerd?
( chuckles )
No.
Endearing nerd
or something.
You know.
I don't know.
Come on,
let's get a cart.
My lady, choose your steed.
No. No.
Oh, in your dreams.
( gasps )
Giddy up, horsey!
Whee!
All right, here we go, boy!
Hi-ho, rainbow!
( PA beeps )
( clears throat )
Attention, Quest Buy shoppers,
the 10,000th annual
Squire Blowout
is starting in... now minutes.
- Wait, what?
- Go!
Go, go, go!
Marco, giddy up!
- Whee!
- Aah!
Marco, I think
something's wrong
with the wheels!
Whoa! Ah.
( knight laughing )
Here's my bolt, losers!
( laughs )
Thanks for the head start!
What?
That old guy
sabotaged our cart.
( gasps ) They're gonna get
all the good items before us!
Marco, it's all good.
We'll get the good stuff.
Let's just try to have fun.
See, fun!
Now, let's go!
I am buying everything!
Whoo-hoo!
Okay, what is
item number one?
Item number one is,
uh, a chest plate.
We need a chest plate.
It's on aisle
eight point nine.
Eight point nine,
got it.
Yee-haw!
Got mine!
( grunts )
I got mine.
I goo-goo got mine.
Hey, there's one left.
Almost forgot.
Have fun wearing my face.
Ha ha!
That Baby-Man ruined
the last chest plate.
I knew those squires
were up to something.
They don't want me
to have the good stuff.
- Marco, I don't--
- Yes, I see it now.
I think you're making them out--
I've got it!
We'll outsmart them.
We'll just go out of order.
That way we can get ahead.
Marco, chill.
I don't even wear chest plates.
I just wanna
salvage my plan, that's all.
A great squire
is an organized squire.
Yes! We've beat
the other squires to it.
( gasps )
I want that one!
Uh, oh, uh.
Actually, Star, I did
the research on these guys,
and it came down to these two.
They each ranked highest
in their class
on safety, growth rate,
a knight horse power.
This one comes with an airbag.
So either of these
should be good.
Oh, okay.
Well, I guess the airbag one.
- Good choice.
- ( horse squeaks )
Okay, since we're right near
the dragon repellant,
I think we should--
Hey, that's our
starter horse!
What?
I didn't take your horse.
I just saw you take it.
Now give it back.
Higgs, did you take
their starter horse?
No, siree.
Unh-unh.
Are you calling my squire
a liar?
Uh, yes?
If you're calling
my squire a liar...
- Oh, whoa!
- Then you're calling me a liar!
Ugh, whatever, stabby dude.
Take the horse.
We don't need it.
Very well.
( blows raspberry )
Can you believe her?
It's all right, Marco.
I'll just pick out
another... one.
Ha ha!
Peace!
Are you serious?
It's okay, Marco.
Listen, let's just
get back to your list.
Look, look, look, look, look.
There's the dragon repellant.
We need that, right?
( sighs )
Yeah.
Ugh, yep,
that's the stuff.
HIGGS:
Yoo-hoo!
- ( dragons growling )
- Oh, no.
( dragons growling,
Marco screaming )
Apparently, we've got dragons
on aisle 14.2... again.
Shoo. Shoo.
( sighs )
This is not my department.
( coughs )
Uh, please get off.
( coughing )
Uh, whoopsie.
Did you mean to get this one?
Easy mistake.
They look so similar.
( growling )
You wanna tell me why
you're being such a jerk?
Listen, wannabe, you think
it's easy being a squire?
All of my waking hours
I'm weaving chain mail,
sharpening swords.
I'm always at my knight's
beck and call.
I've even learned how to
polish armor in my sleep.
But what did you do
to earn this job?
Oh, nothing.
It was handed to you
because you're the
princess' boyfriend.
What? I'm not her boyfriend.
Interesting.
Guess it was handed to you
out of pity, then, huh?
( growls )
Star!
- Marco!
- I'm here, Star.
- Under the dragon butt.
- Oh.
Scram, lizard.
Sk-Sk-Skidaddle!
Well, I think
that's enough fun
for one squire.
What say we call it
a day, Marco?
The sale's almost over,
anyway.
No! There's still
one thing left
on my list, Star.
Armor wax.
There's just one bottle left.
I called ahead to check.
We have to get it
before those other squires.
Uh, Marco, no offense,
but you're looking
kinda sweaty.
Like sweatier than usual.
Hey, maybe let's just,
you know--
- Mount the cart!
- Okay!
( gasps )
Don't let them get that!
( both laughing )
( shrieks )
Marco!
Aah!
Oh, that's it!
( laughs )
Yes!
( groaning )
- Marco!
- What?
( groaning )
Oh, I didn't trip her
that hard.
What? She's faking it.
( sighs )
Here.
Ha, ha-ha!
Thanks for the wax, losers!
Let's check out.
Dude, you have
got to chill.
What? Why?
I'm just trying to get you
the best stuff.
I'm sorry.
I just really wanted
to show everyone
that I was truly worthy
of being your squire.
But maybe I'm not
cut out for this.
Why did you appoint me
as your squire
in the first place?
I'm terrible at it.
I didn't get you any gear,
and you're gonna
look like a joke
in front of all
the other knights.
Okay, first of all,
I am a princess.
So I'm gonna look great
no matter what.
Second, I knew how excited you
were about coming back to Mewni
so I bent the rules a little.
I'm a princess,
not a knight.
I don't need the stuff
actual knights need.
I've got, like,
a magic wand.
The whole point
of making you my squire
was so we could
hang out again
and just do silly stuff.
Attention, Quest Buy shoppers,
only one minute remains
in this year's
Squire Blowout sale.
All right, come on.
Huh? But wait, wait, wait.
Marco, I just told you
I don't need the--
I know, I know.
Come on.
( indistinct chatter )
Got you this
really shiny shield.
Not shiny enough.
( gasps )
It's beautiful!
Hey, Marco, I challenge you
to a duel...
A duel of silliness!
I accept your challenge!
( both exclaiming )
Hey, what do they think
they're doing?
That's not knight gear.
That's just silly,
random, fun stuff.
- Ugh.
- Clever squire.
Salami.
I'd never see that coming.
( groans )
Uh, did you really mean to grab
two of these defective
happy gnomes?
BOTH: Yes, yes, we did.
( both laughing )
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her
No, sir ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪