♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah! Hoo-hoo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Seriously, Star,
there's nothing
to be excited about.
- It's just--
- The best day of my life!
We're going on
a field trip!
Cork it, princess.
I can't believe
we're actually doing this.
( gasps )
He's so cute!
I just wanna
gobble him up.
I hope Jackie likes it
as much as you.
Ooh. Conversation starter.
Sh. She's right there.
Yeah, she's right there.
You go talk to her.
More than just hello?
Too risky.
I might say
something dumb.
This way, I let
the kitty pics
do the talking
for me.
Ooh. ( gasps )
Oh, I love it!
She sent me an LOL.
We're communicating.
- ( brakes squeal )
- We're here!
( shivering )
Amazing!
What is it?
It's a paper clip.
Yuck. Luckily,
I got my phone.
No distractions,
Mr. Diaz.
And for
the rest of you,
no monkey business!
This is the Echo Creek
Museum of Paper Clips.
We're gonna spend
the next eight hours
learning about the genius
of this little--
Miss Skullnick!
Stop. This hurts.
So boring!
( clamoring )
BOY: Why must she
torture us?
Well, you know what?
Life is boring!
Miss Skullnick,
life is supposed to be fun.
I used to think that,
but now I'm 50,
and all my dreams
are in the rearview mirror.
The best thing in my life
is teaching you kids,
and I hate teaching you.
That's 'cause you're
doing it all wrong.
You think you can lead
this trip better than me?
I was born to lead.
Literally.
( raucous laughter )
Okay, go ahead then.
When you fail,
those brats might
actually appreciate
me for a change.
Who wants to go
somewhere not boring?
- I do, I do.
- Yeah!
Let's go to
the morgue.
Welcome to the Dimension
of Wonders and Amazements!
( all cheering )
What is this place?
Just a planet full
of the most odd
and unbelievable
things in the universe.
No running,
no yelling,
no horseplay, no--
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You put me in charge,
so rule number one:
no rules.
No rules leads
to anarchy.
When you give people
the freedom
to do whatever
they want...
I get more bars here
than I do on Earth.
...they might just
surprise you.
Try to have a little fun,
you big old meanie.
Okay.
Walking With Trolls.
I heard, once
you go in,
you never come out.
Wait, that's cows at
the hamburger factory. Huh.
Can we jump through
this light-ray thing?
You don't have
to ask my permission.
Fly free, my curious
little sparrows.
Yeah!
Being a leader is easy.
Just say yes
all the time.
Take my hand, bro.
BOTH: Yeah!
Trolls are one of
the universe's
few ultra super
centenarians,
which means they live
a really, really, really
really long time.
I'm gonna live
to be 400?
And here I thought I was
going through the big change.
Turns out
I'm a teenager again!
( imitates gun firing )
The cat is in the bag.
GIRL: Yeah!
( laughing )
Uh, guys, I don't think
you're supposed to ride
a Dermathian stingray
like that.
Miss Star, may I jump into
this ominous-looking
vortex?
Francis, please
stop where you are
and ask yourself,
is this something
you really want to do.
Justin, no!
Um, yes, I really
wanna do this.
I really didn't
think this through!
Oh, stop. You guys knew
this would happen.
That's not a good idea.
Sabrina!
Hey, Star,
isn't this great?
Real great, but you might
wanna come down.
Justin!
Human expansion during
the industrialization period
of the third
Nebulic Millennium
gave rise to
the Fierce Troll warrior.
Trolls are abnormally strong,
able to lift 100 times
their own body weight.
Oh, please.
There's no muscle here.
Did that just happen?
No LOL, no smiley face?
Nothing?
Jackie.
Time to drop
the A-bomb of cute.
A for adorable.
( laughing )
No, no, no,
don't jump on that.
I gotcha.
Why did you let me
do that, Star?
- Star!
- Sabrina!
Oh, ow, ow!
Don't worry. I... I...
I don't even know
how to help you.
"Universe's Most Deadliest
Creature"?
Whoa, I told you
these weren't gumballs.
( purring )
What a tease.
Star, can I get
super powers?
Star, we're hungry.
I brought snacks.
Stinks to be you.
Star, can I touch it
with this?
( shuddering )
Star. Star, meet
my new BFF.
( guttural voice )
BFF.
( stammering )
- Star!
- Star!!
- ( all calling Star )
Can you guys just
be quiet for one second?
Ah, that's better.
Francis?
Justin?
Sabrina?
Where'd everybody go?
Star. Star, guess what.
Wait. Where's the rest
of the class?
Fine, Jackie.
I get it.
I know when
I'm not wanted.
( phone clatters )
No, no, no!
Please work.
Please work!
H-E-L-P?
What's that
an acronym for?
Jackie's text said
they'd been captured
by some monster.
Marco and I can totally
handle this.
We fight monsters
all the time.
I trusted you
with the class
for five minutes,
and you lost them.
They're not lost.
We just don't know
where they are.
They're wherever
this is.
Wait. I remember seeing
a trail of socks
right after
the class disappeared.
That's where I'm
starting my search.
This is it.
( kids yelling )
Kids, don't worry.
You're gonna
be home soon.
( ferocious growling )
Okay, we have to hurry.
Jump. I'll catch you.
Come on, jump.
I can't do this!
Take my hand, bro.
( both yelling )
Hurry. Next.
- Marco!
- Jackie!
Hi. Hey, yeah.
Uh, hey, uh...
Marco?
I'll take care of Jackie.
You free Janna.
- Yeah, Marco,
help me.
- Gaaah!
Relax. They weren't
real fangs.
Unless you
want them to be.
Quiet.
It's coming.
( whistling )
( screaming )
- All right,
string monster--
- No!
I'm back in charge,
and I need you
to get those kids
to safety.
- Wow!
- What did I say?
Go, go, go!
What did I say?
Skullnick's really
got some moves.
You bet your tuchus I do.
Get ready to eat magic!
Get that bus moving.
( cheering )
That's how you do it.
Hey, Marco, is someone
sitting there?
( stammering )
Huh, uh...
Yeah, you are.
Star, hurry up.
I'm coming.
( panting )
Hey, Cloudy,
can you put me down?
Sure thing, Star.
Thanks, guys.
You're the best.
We love you, Star.
Love you, too.
( screaming )
Can you do anything
without magic?
Sunshine Locker Slap!
- Love you, Star.
- ( neighs )
Hmm.
"You use too much magic."
- Blah blah blah blah!
- ( blows raspberry )
Hey, Marco.
Hey, Mike.
Sweet beard.
Thanks, Jackie.
I grew it last night.
JACKIE: So full.
One night?
I've been working on
mine for weeks.
You know what the quickest
way to grow a beard is?
Is it magic?
It's magic!!
I'll stick with
my peach fuzz, thanks.
This may not be much,
but it's mine.
Marco, I've got
a magic wand.
I might as well use it.
Sometimes there's a sense
of satisfaction
in doing things yourself.
Let me put
a beard on you!
MARCO: No, don't touch it!
I did it.
I grew a beard!
USA, USA!
Congratulations, Marco.
It looks really
good on you.
Star, why are you
making that face?
What face?
I don't make face.
You used magic
on me, didn't you?
( shuddering )
No.
Oh, come on, Star.
Oh, you come on.
You look so good
in your little beard-y.
I wanted to grow it
myself!
Star, my face...
Wow. That is
a lot of hair.
Don't you worry
your pretty little face, Marco.
It's nothing a little
magic can't fix.
Sparkle Razor Shave!
Oh, that's a taquito.
Hm. Where's my wand?
It's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Where is it?!
Wand? Wand!
I must've dropped it
in the bathroom
when Marco's face exploded.
Okay, think, Star.
What would a normal person
without a wand do?
Work, work, work, work,
work, work, work, work.
That's no help.
One second. I got it!
Normal person.
I'm comin' for
you, Marco.
Oh, man, this would be
a lot easier
if I had the wand.
But at least I got you,
Mr. Hedge Clippers.
( as hedge clippers )
Yeah, you don't need
no stinkin' wand.
I wanna cut more!
I have location
on the wand.
It's inside the house,
and it's ours for the taking.
That's a house?
It's covered in hair.
Maybe we should
come back another time.
Of course.
It's just, the wand
has never been
unattended before.
( all exclaim )
Fine.
But you idiots
are going to carry me.
I don't want
a single hair touching me.
Hold still,
you dumb bird.
Hurry up.
Protect me.
( muffled yelling )
Man, not having a wand
isn't so bad.
I bet I'm
all the way to...
I'm still in
the living room?!
Mr. Hedge Clippers!
Avenge me!
Keep moving.
What's the hold-up?
Master Ludo,
can't we take a break?
I'm dehydrated.
( clucking )
No breaks.
This is taking forever.
Let's go.
Do your job.
The wand
is that way.
We're close.
Clear the path
and move it, you idiots.
Here.
I'm stuck.
( crying )
I wish I had my wand.
( barking )
Oh, there, there,
little guy.
You stuck here, too?
Oh, I'm so tired,
and his hair
is so soft.
Maybe we should take
a little nap together.
Star? Star Butterfly?
Hello. Who's there?
It is I, Laser Puppy.
I thought you couldn't
get any cuter,
but look at you.
Thank you.
I wag my tail humbly.
You must not give up.
Marco needs you.
But it's just
so hard without my wand.
Let me remind you of
a time before your wand,
when a precocious pre-teen
got mixed up with snakes,
goblins and ghouls,
all while looking
super cute.
Oh, my gosh,
I was adorable.
You never needed
your wand before.
Why do you need it now?
Also, I'm a puppy that
shoots lasers out of my eyes.
The choice is yours,
Star Butterfly.
Either rise up and conquer
or wither here and die.
( voice echoing )
( gasps )
- Ludo. What are
you doing here?
- It's the girl.
Wait. The wand
is that way.
Don't take her.
Get the wand.
( speaking indistinctly )
Uh, yeah, the bathroom
is occupied.
Master, the wand is yours.
( screaming )
We've got someone
who wants to wish you
a very giggly
birthday, Ludo.
Here comes
the tickle monster.
Tickle, tickle, tickle.
( laughing )
( sobbing )
It tickles.
It's my birthday.
Hey, where is she?
Normally, I'd blast you guys
with narwhals right now,
but hey, you don't need
magic for everything.
( car alarm chirps )
Oh, my gosh, Marco.
I was looking
everywhere for you.
( muffled ) I'm so itchy.
Please help me.
You're right. I was
using my wand too much.
But I am Star Butterfly,
an independent woman
with fists like hammers.
( muffled ) I don't care.
Just get rid of the hair!
And now, I shall shave
this beard off of you
with this tiny razor,
just like a normal person.
Thank you, Marco,
for teaching me
such a valuable lesson.
( Marco screaming )
What a pathetic
display back there.
You guys make me sick!
No more milkshake
privileges for you.
( all grumbling )
I want you to
use that time
to think about
what you've done.
Perhaps they should
use that time
to think about
what you've done.
Exactly.
Wait, what?
Let me ask you
a question.
What kind of leader
throws you into a pit of hair,
makes you do all the work,
and shows you no appreciation
for your sacrifices?
Are you talking about me?
What kind of leader
has all the power
in the universe
at his fingertips,
and gets tickled
right out of it?
Toffee, what are
you doing?
Your soldiers
deserve better.
( sputtering )
You are fired!
Let's put it
to your soldiers.
Who's the better leader,
Ludo...
or me?
( all talking at once )
You guys belong to me.
Three-eyed
potato baby,
I am like
a father to you.
Beard deer, I took you
in off the streets.
Are you stupid imbeciles
really going to listen to him?
You can't do this.
This is my castle.
Those are my monsters.
Not anymore.
Toffee.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪