♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( slurping )
Huh.
Authentic Mexican horchata
isn't supposed to have
dairy in it.
So what?
It isn't illegal
to make horchatas
with milk.
Are you sugaring
your burrito?
Food is anarchy, dude.
Live by your own rules.
Ugh.
( muffled )
Want some?
Keep your sacrilege
off my taco.
Mmm.
Whoo! Do I feel alive!
You sure you don't
want a bite?
Definitely sure.
Who's up for fireworks?
I can't see how that'd be
a good idea.
'Cause I totally
wanna make fireworks.
Bright-Glow Pyro!
Sparkling Spiral Noodle!
Radical Rainbow Blast!!
Rainbow glitter unicorn!!
Star, might wanna
tone it down a notch.
( siren blaring,
distorts, then stops )
( gasps )
Ooh!
( panting )
What the heck
was that?!
I thought rainbows
were made of light.
My rainbows are
made of stuff, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
You just smashed
a police car.
Oh, man.
This is fine, this is fine.
What's the big
deal, Marco?
I've done this
a thousand times.
I'll just have my dad
give them some crowns.
Call it even.
Things don't work
like that on Earth.
Here, you'll
go to prison.
- You mean like Saint O's?
- It's worse than Saint O's.
They give you
one bar of soap,
and you have to make it
last a whole year.
You gotta get up
every day at 4:00 a.m.
and make hash browns
you're not allowed to eat.
And they force you
to wear orange jumpsuits
- every single day.
- Orange?!
Ai. I don't know.
You tell me.
They noticed
the dent.
I guess I could
visit you in prison
or whatever.
There's only one thing
left for me to do.
I'm gonna run away.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, that's not...
Running is worse.
You can't stop me,
rule boy.
Star, wait.
I'll contact you when
I find a place to lay low.
Look, if you can't read,
you can't do a crossword.
Whoa!!
Oh!
No one'll find me here.
Okay, first day in hiding.
Where to start?
Shelter.
Okay, maybe something
less conspicuous.
Not too shabby,
if I do say so myself.
Good enough.
( shivering )
( squawks )
( all squawking )
Well, what are you doing
down here, sunshine?
Uh, nothin'.
Just takin' a stroll.
( stomach growling )
Well, sounds like
someone's hungry.
I'm about to make
some pancakes,
if you'd like to join.
I do like pancakes.
Well, then, my house
is right through hair.
Wait a second.
Did you just say hair?
Of course not,
my dear.
( bird squawks )
Okay. Mm, pancakes.
Welcome to 80 square feet
of my own personal paradise.
Oh, your home
is so cozy.
A radical tapestry.
Would you like
one pancake or two?
Five, please.
Wow!
- Cool loft bed.
- Pancakes are ready.
So you gonna tell me
what you did?
What do you mean?
Oh, hon, come on.
Folks don't come down
to the river
unless they broke
some of the rules.
Your secret's
safe with me.
Well... okay.
So, like, I was with Marco
at Britta's Tacos,
and we were eating,
and he was all, like,
"Star, you can't put
sugar on your burrito."
But what does he care,
ya know?
So then I ate the burrito
and I wanted to
see some fireworks.
Again, he's, like, "Star,
don't fireworks your burrito,"
- and it's all like,
don't do this, don't do that.
- ( humming )
Hey. My eyes are down here.
Oh. I'm sorry, dear.
Go on and finish
your story.
So anyway, my rainbow
smashed a cop car.
Jumped a fence and fell asleep
in some garbage by the river,
and now I'm here.
So... what did you do?
Oh, you know.
I steal hair.
Oh, why would you do that?
Oh, no, no, no,
sweetie.
It's not like that.
I don't take hair
from people.
No, no, no.
It's more of like
a back-alley kind of thing.
You know, dumpsters,
behind hair salons,
dog kennels--
discarded hair.
So you do, like, witchy stuff
with the hair, right?
Is that what this is?
You some kind of witch?
Oh, goodness no, dear.
You can do
lots of things with hair.
I wove it into that tapestry
you like so much.
Stuff your bed with it.
Heck, you can even make
pancake batter from it.
( laughs )
I'm just playin' with you.
But seriously,
my favorite thing
to do with the hair
is to weave it into nests for
all my wounded forest friends.
Aww!
You can make
anything from hair.
Well, anything...
but love.
Star, your family
loves you.
Let's call them
and tell them you're okay.
No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
Just let me stay
here with you.
I can sleep anywhere.
Look. ( snoring )
But this is no life
for a little girl.
Let me help you.
- No, thank you.
- Star!
Wait. Come back.
Hello. Operator.
Whoa, whoa, stop.
Stop right there.
I said stop.
( dog barks )
Who's walkin'
who here?
( gasps )
( yawns )
( knocking )
- Whoa.
- Excuse me.
What is going on?
I'm fishing, hamster pats.
What does it look like?
Now go on.
Hidin' out here.
You're gonna
blow my cover.
Whoa, you, too?
I, too, am hiding out, too.
Why didn't you say so?
You've come to
the perfect place.
♪ An underwater hideout
to hide your princess face ♪
♪ You can make a shelter ♪
That's the pinkest thing
I've ever seen.
♪ Anything you want to ♪
♪ Sweet and savory
together ♪
Sugarritos!
♪ Nothing 'cause
you got to ♪
- ♪ You want to run a race ♪
- I love sea horses.
- ♪ But you want to
take a nap too ♪
- Actually, I just did.
♪ You never have to ♪
♪ Unless you really want to ♪
♪ Pilot submarines ♪
A sandwich!
♪ Anything you want to ♪
♪ Stay dirty,
stay clean ♪
How do you take
a bath underwater?
♪ I bet you really
want to ♪
♪ You can learn le France ♪
♪ Decorate a cake ♪
♪ Trash the economy,
turn someone to bones ♪
♪ You can make a scrapbook ♪
Wait. What was the thing
before scrapbook?
♪ Anything you want to ♪
Whatever. This is perfect.
I can hide out here
forever.
♪ Only if you want to ♪
Can he stop
singing now?
♪ Anything you want... ♪
Oh, it's cool.
Now I just gotta let
Marco know I'm okay.
What's this
missle-massle?
You can't go doing
that now.
But he'll be
so worried.
No, no, no,
you're hiding out.
You gotta lay low.
Lay low?
Yeah. You're
on the lam.
You can do whatever
you want down here,
so long as you never
see your family and
friends again.
Never ever?
Not even a bit.
So I'd have to spend
the rest of my life
here with just you?
( scoffs )
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not real.
I'm just your brain
trying to convince you
you haven't made
a big mistake.
Oh, no.
So I wrote that song?
Enjoy the inside
of your mind.
- Bleh-bleh-bleh.
- MAN: See anything?
- What's over there?
- WOMAN: Are those footprints?
Okay, I surrender.
Just lock me up
and put me in orange.
Seeing Marco once a month
is better than never again.
Marco.
You mean him?
Star? You're okay!
We were so worried.
How'd you find her?
We have our ways.
You know, you shouldn't
run away like that.
You really worried
your friend here.
Lucky for you, we were gonna
smash that old squad car anyway.
What? We were?
At the annual police car
demolition derby.
I was really looking
forward to smashing it.
Phew! Well, if you
won't be needing me....
I'll just see myself out.
Just a moment.
You're not getting off
that easy.
Uh...
You really can pull off
jumpsuit orange.
I know, right?
But enough of
this manual labor.
It's magic time.
Star, isn't that what
got you into this mess
in the first place?
No, Marco. That was
the rainbow glitter,
unicorn gnome hat, kitty bacon,
Hawaiian nightmare spell.
Super geyser windstorm!
Yeah, that was
totally me.
My bad.
Nobody panic.
I'll put it back.
I'm glad you're open.
I'm starving.
I'd like some
porridge, please.
( snaps fingers )
No!
This is mud.
That's not funny.
You messed with
the wrong bird, rat.
Face-melting death ray!
Huh?
( shrieks )
Ow!
( growls )
( humming )
Star!
It's your turn
to take out the garbage.
Marco, you've ruined
my Mewni battleship.
Don't you think you have
enough ships in a bottle?
Enough? I don't
even know you.
Come on. We told Mom
and Dad we'd have
the place cleaned up
before they got home,
and garbage is all yours.
Oh, fine!
Summoning cloudy charm.
Cloudy, could you
take out the gar...
( wheezing )
Cloudy?
( rattles )
Oh, hey, Star.
Uh, are you okay?
Yeah. Perfectly fine.
Okay.
Could you take out
the garbage?
Sure can.
I guess princess hands
are too delicate
to touch garbage.
- What?
- Oh, nothing.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
I got a mouthful
of garbage.
I don't know, girls.
Maybe this isn't
what it looks like.
It looks like
a magic wand.
What did I say?
Follow three feet
behind me.
Three!
Yeah, anyway, I don't know,
maybe it's just a baby rattle.
What are you doing?
No. No, put it down.
Let go, you nasty,
nasty thing.
You let go of my thing!
( gasps )
What?!
Do it again.
Not you, you stupid...
( shrieks )
I said not you, bird!
Do it again.
( evil laughter )
It's working, girls.
Oh, no, no. No, no!
I was kidding.
Please, let me go.
Let me go!
Don't let me go!
( screams )
( groaning )
Oh, no.
What happened?
( groaning )
I had an accident.
( loudly ) Glossaryk!
- Inside voices, please.
- Oh, sorry. Yeah.
Uh, Glossaryk, there's
something funky happening
with my wand.
Oh. What's wrong with it?
It's acting weird.
It's not doing what
it's supposed to.
Star, maybe there's
something wrong with you.
You ever think about that?
What's that supposed
to mean?
Uh, I'm not 100% sure.
I guess it means
there's something wrong...
with everyone.
I mean, look at me.
I did magic
on my own face.
- You know?
- No help as usual.
It hurts everywhere!
MARCO: Star, you're taking
care of the garbage, right?
Yeah. I got Cloudy to do it.
Uh, about that...
( giggling )
I don't know why
I have so much energy today.
Must be all that iced tea.
No, girls,
it's gonna get ugly.
( mice squeaking )
( Ludo humming )
A bowl of your
finest mud, sir.
Mm, I can taste it already.
( snaps fingers )
Ah!
All done.
Do your worst!
( laughing )
Ah! Whoopsie!
What's with him?
Cloudy, you stop this
right now.
Giddy-up!
- Are you listening to me?
- Whee!
Stop playing around
and clean all this up.
Uh-oh. Looks like
someone's allergic
to good vibes.
( Cloudy laughs )
Okay, that's enough.
Sunshine friendship.
( mocking )
Oopsie.
My Mewni battleships!
( growling )
Sunshine friendship spell!
Hey! That was sooooo rude!
No, girls.
I'm fine.
Come on, hit me
like you mean it!
Now you're really
starting to tick me off.
Run.
( evil cackling )
Cloudy, you're
out of control!
That's it!
Enough!
Hey! You poked
my fluffies!
I think you're
making him worse.
You gotta stop!
Star!
Marco!
Raspberry ribbon lasso!
Sunshine friendship spell!
Oh! ( giggles )
- You okay?
- Yeah, thanks to you.
( Cloudy giggling )
Whoa! What a mess!
What happened?
Yeah, what was up
with your wand?
I have no idea.
Kids, we got you ice cream
for cleaning the house.
Oh, Star, it is always
exciting with you around.
This'll take us
all weekend to clean.
Oh, no, no.
I've got this.
Tidying up tidal wa...
You know what?
Give me that thing.
Oh, that's way better!
Now...
give me some porridge.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪