♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ I just called back to say ♪
♪ Happy birthday
on your birthday day ♪
♪ Happy birthday on
your birthday day! ♪
And there's
a special delivery
comin' right your way.
- Your favorite.
- Wow!
Only the best for
the best bestie
a best bestie could have.
Oh, my goodness!
Thank you so much,
B-Fly.
I mean, a princess
such as myself
could never indulge in
such confections.
But would you please
donate them
to the starving Bartindles
of Galafamor on my behalf?
Did you bump
your uni-horn again?
Girl, you know we can't
receive packages here at
St. Olga's School
For Wayward Princesses.
( shrieks )
Get out, get
out, get out!
B-Fly?
I can't even stand
to hear the name
of that place.
( shuddering )
Oh, please, you gots
to be chill, B-Fly.
I'm the one doing
hard time here.
I know, but if you
weren't there,
we could totally
party it up.
Rainbow tea at
the Dowager Room,
sliding down the twisty
slopes of Zalla Mountain,
then dancing all night long
at the Bounce Lounge.
Oh, heck yeah, girl.
That would be the best
birthday day ever! Boom!
- ( metallic creaking )
- Oh, no.
I expressed my individuality
and publicly showed an emotion.
And that's my third strike.
Oh, no, no, please.
No, no!
They're sending me to
the solitary conforment chamber.
Pony Head!
Oh, you don't
deserve this!
Ready to take out
life's frustrations
on some ill-intentioned
monsters?
( loud sobbing )
This is terrible!
Best friends don't let
best besties
have bad
birthday days.
( blows loudly )
And Pony Head is having
the worst one ever.
Pony Head?
Yeah, I'm outta here.
Marco, we have to get her
out of that prison.
Oh, a breakout.
Why didn't you say so?
- Wait, isn't St. O's--
- ( shrieks )
St. O., St. O., St. O.!
Uh, we haven't even
left yet.
Sorry.
What's that
under your rug?
I have no idea.
But I do know one thing.
Never, ever step on it.
Let's get back to
that breakout thing.
But no one's ever
escaped from there.
I've seen every
prison escape movie made.
We only need three things.
Patience, brains,
and the ever-famous,
multi-faceted
bobby pin.
Or we use my dimensional
scissors to go
straight to her cell and get her
the heck outta there.
Uh, this isn't
Pony Head's cell.
Huh. I'm usually
pretty accurate
with these things.
- ( horses whinnying )
- ( exclaiming )
Ah, yes, the newbies
have arrived.
Welcome to St. Olga's
School For Wayward Princesses.
( thunder crashing )
- ( screaming )
- New arrivals?
If we could just
blend in somehow,
we could sneak in
unnoticed.
All we need is a--
Radiant shadow
transport!
Whoa! Do me.
Do me.
Radiant shadow
transport!
You couldn't turn me
into one of those guards
with the cool masks?
I don't know.
Pink is definitely
your color.
Single file.
Miss Heinous
is eager to start
the reformation process.
( squealing )
Marco.
Try not to blow
our cover.
MAN: Don't allow your noble
lineage to be thrown away.
Here at the tried
and trusted St. Olga's...
...we have a plethora
of foolproof security measures.
No dimensional scissors,
no magic, no boys...
...and etiquette
are the main focus for...
...your troubled,
wayward princess.
( woman whispering )
Wayward princess.
We turn undisciplined
behavior
into perfection.
That free-thinking,
one-in-a-million brat
will become
a one-of-a-million
emotionless rubber stamp
that your bloodline
can count on.
Every one of you
is here for a reason.
Too wild.
Too opinionated.
Too bubbly.
As part of a noble
lineage,
you don't have the luxury
of being an individual.
So by the time
I'm done with you,
you'll all be fixed.
Every last one of you,
whether you're
from Pixtopia,
or Mewni.
And don't even think
about escaping.
These are useless.
We have a Tramorfidian Crystal
in Tower 3.
No rift can sustain itself
within our walls.
So you might as well cough up
the scissors you smuggled in.
( all groaning )
It's totally hopeless.
Once we get Pony Head
and disable that crystal thing,
those are our ticket
outta here.
That concludes
your orientation.
I'm confident that
you'll all become
perfect princesses.
One way or another.
Now to get everyone
checked in
so we can start sucking
the individuality out of you.
( high-pitched voice )
I hear the first one
checked in
gets her own room.
( all exclaiming )
Respect the queue.
Respect the queue!
- This place isn't
what I thought--
- Sh!
Yeah, breaking out
Pony Head
is gonna be a breeze.
It's just a high-surveillance
prissy finishing school.
No, Marco, it's worse
than I imagined. Look.
♪ When your heart
is filled with sunshine ♪
♪ And you're feeling
oh so free ♪
♪ All of life
is just divine ♪
♪ And the world
is full of glee ♪
( whistling )
You know the kind
of girls who get sent here.
They can totally
benefit from this.
( bird continues
whistling )
No, no, no.
You're not leaving
until you get this right.
You know, this place has
some seriously luxurious digs.
Have you gone mad?
Come on.
Look at the intricate
floral ornamentation
on that armoire.
( gasps )
The rich mahogany
of the canopy bed.
And there's enough velvet
on that bedspread
for me to swim in.
- Don't you see what's
going on here?
- Dancing?
Let's just find Pony Head
and get outta here.
There she is.
Let's blow down the door
so we can get outta here.
No. We gotta do this
quietly,
without drawing
any attention.
( loudly ) ♪ I am here
'cause I have to say ♪
♪ Happy birthday
on your birthday day ♪
Do you wanna
get us caught?
Sorry. Pony Head.
Hey, it's us,
here to break you out,
so we can party.
- Ah!
- My deepest apologies,
but I must abstain,
as partying is for
the unrefined.
That's not the Pony Head
I know and love.
I got this.
Hey, Pointy Head.
It's Earth Turd.
Such language belongs in
the gutters of Galafamor.
You know, I kinda
like her better this way.
Snap out of it,
Pony Head.
Snap out of it!
( laughs )
Would you care
for some crumpets?
See, Marco, this is what
they do to you here.
Relax. Once we disable
that crystal thing
and get her outta here,
she'll finally be
a benefit to society.
What are you doing?
I saw this
in a prison movie.
Escape From
Jail Mountain.
Trust me, this'll
save our hides,
just like it saved
Hank Innocent.
It's clear.
Oh, escaping
is inappropriate.
Guards.
Guards!
Yoo-hoo, guards.
Hey, stop!
Keep your pinkies
at 90 degrees.
More tea, please.
Keep your pinkies
at 90 degrees.
More tea, please.
Keep your pinkies at...
This is worse than
my worst nightmare.
Yeah. I see
what you mean.
Keep your pinkies
at 90 degrees.
Why are you
saying that?
You don't even
have pinkies.
- Come on.
- ( chanting continues )
More tea, please.
He's right on us.
Are we gonna
blast our way
out of this?
No. That'll only
increase the heat on us.
We need some kind
of distraction.
Well, they are not
getting my individuality.
That's it.
It's not criminal
to be an individual.
Come on.
It's not criminal
to be an individual.
ALL: It's not criminal
That should
buy us some time.
( chanting continues )
Tee-hee. He got scolded.
She's laughing at
an authority figure.
I think the real
Pony Head's still in there.
An uprising?
In my institution?
Put St. O.'s on
full lockdown
and find the free thinker
who initiated this.
We will quell this uprising
in its infancy.
Quell, quell.
Is that right?
Someone get
a thesaurus.
Wrong way.
Quick. Find
a place to hide.
There she is.
Get her.
Oh!
We've stifled
the uprising.
Soon we'll find
those responsible
and stifle them in
a solitary conforment chamber.
Here's our latest
success story.
The once-wayward
Princess Pony Head
is now a model student,
reborn.
Yes. I'm glad
we stifled the uprising.
You know, stifled
isn't working for me either.
Prepare the chamber.
I'm leading this
princess hunt myself.
MARCO: What is this place?
STAR: I don't know.
( dogs barking )
We gotta move.
There. I'll see you
at the bottom.
My poufy dress
won't fit.
Marco!!
Something's got
my stockings.
( screaming )
( laughing )
Marco. You gotta
help me save him.
I can't do this alone.
A princess who misbehaves
will be saved
in the solitary
conforment chamber.
Why can't you remember
who you are?
( door slams )
Really? What?
The proper hat
for the event
lest you be
a malcontent.
Everyone will admire
the princess who
does not perspire.
'Tis better to be fussy
than to be called
a hussy.
Ugh. I can smell
her free spirit
through the safety glass.
Full power.
So this is how it ends.
On a cold checkered floor
by a pile of soiled linens,
wearing an eye patch.
"Embrace a princess
mentality.
Wash away
your individuality"?
Embrace this!
( sobbing )
( laughing )
Yeah. That feels
so good! Whoo!
Pony Head?
You're back!
Oh, you know it.
Now let's go destroy
something else.
I don't even care
what it is.
( Marco screaming )
Ooh, hold it.
I'd recognize that
girly scream anywhere.
That's Earth Turd.
Yep. Heinous got him.
Well, what are we
waiting for?
Isn't he your best bestie?
- Yeah.
On Earth. I'm still
your best bestie overall, right?
- Come on.
- ( Marco screaming )
Open that vent.
Keep screamin', Marco.
Proper throne posture.
( screams )
Yes. We are extinguishing
that rebellious spirit.
Make it stop!
( screaming )
I'm blasting our way
outta here, Marco.
You cool with that?
Where did she get
that wand?
( screams )
Gotcha, Marco.
Now let's get
the heck outta here.
Are they gonna let me
keep the dress?
Shoo. Shoo, shoo,
shoo, shoo.
- Go away!
- Your cheeks.
No. Stop it, stop it.
You saw nothing.
A princess always
maintains her poise.
I'm glad you're
back to normal, by the way.
Aw, you too.
Now I can make fun
of your ugly dress.
It's not criminal
to be an individual.
ALL: It's not criminal
Man, I can't believe it,
but you sure worked
some turd magic
on these girls.
They are in it.
Yeah, you really
started something.
My work here
is not done.
My fellow wayward sisters,
I'll show you the way.
They want you to be
a rubber-stamp princess.
I saw we stamp on them!
( yelling )
There's the tower.
Raspberry Panzerfaust!
Looks like that
did the job.
Let's get outta here.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Time's a-wastin'.
If we hurry, we can
still catch DJ Jump-Jump's set
- at the Bounce Lounge.
- Girl, I ain't goin' nowhere.
The Bounce Lounge ain't got
nothin' on this party.
But it's your birthday day.
You gave me
the best gift ever,
and it's called,
getting me
my groove back.
Look at me.
It's back, babe.
BOTH: Hugs.
So you wanna stay here?
Oh, I gotta.
I can't let what
happened to me
happen to anyone else.
Right, Princess Turdina?
Get on with your bad self,
my wayward sister.
Yeah! I'm gonna go bite
some of those robot guards
- on their faces.
- Bite one for me.
Okay, Marco, I conquered
my biggest fear,
I grew as a person,
yada yada yada.
Let's get outta here
and never come back.
If your elbows
are on the table,
you belong
in a stable.
There.
All better.
Hmm.
I will find
the rabble rousers
responsible for this
and annihilate them!
Annihilate.
That's the verb
I've been looking for.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪