♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( beeping )
( snoring )
Huh?
What is going on?
Star, wake up.
Marco, we're late for school.
- I'm not Marco.
- Where am I?
Oh. Oh, no.
The High Commission.
Leave it.
There's no time.
There's no way out.
What are you doing?
Escape route blast!
Magic is not supposed
to do that.
I'm not sure
what that was.
But my magic's gone.
- Rats.
- It will be okay.
No, rats.
We gotta hide.
- Narwhal--
- Star, no.
Mom, you can't take
my wand.
It was mine first.
No more magic until
we find a way to stop this.
I've got an idea.
Let's go destroy
Toffee.
Come on, Mom,
let's just go.
- Let's go kill him.
- Star, no.
Well, then,
what's the plan, Mom?
'Cause I ain't
seein' one.
Oh, Star.
I don't have
a plan.
I'm just trying
to keep you safe, okay?
Okay.
Well, can't stay out here.
It's creepy.
We need
another hiding place.
Ribbit.
( gasps )
I think I have an idea
where we can go.
But you have to trust me.
Buffrog!
Star Butterfly!
Oh, my little sweet potato.
It's been too long.
QUEEN MOON: Ahem.
Oh, Queen Moon.
Greetings.
Mom, this is
Yvgeny Bulgoyaboff.
Please, call me
Buffrog.
- He used to work for
Ludo, but he's cool now.
- What?!
Hey, Buffrog, can we
crash with you
for a night?
Of course. I owe you
for all that tadpole-sitting.
Star, can I
speak with you?
We cannot
stay with him.
He's a monster.
Mom, get with the times.
Not all monsters are bad.
- ( twig snaps )
- What was that?
Well, it seems we have
no other choice.
Uh, welcome to my...
home.
Boop.
You're in luck.
It's rainy season.
Ah, so good
for the skin.
Oh, uh, no shoes in house.
I am, how you say,
germophobe.
I feel so free.
Buffrog, wonderful home.
Oh, thank you.
Is a bit of a mess
right now.
Please take a seat.
Oh! Are those...
slugs?
Slugs keep
furniture clean.
I thought everyone
knew that.
I'll stand.
Yo, Buffrog,
where them babies at?
Oh, I just put them
down for nap.
Babies!
( laughing ) Oh, I missed
you little baby faces so much.
Oh, my gosh,
you have little baby arms!
Yes, all except
little Katrina.
She is
late bloomer.
Oh, you little special
snowflake.
Babies, say hello to
Queen Butterfly.
That really isn't--
( all ribbiting )
Star, I have been
so worried about you.
Why? I'm good.
Well, when Ludo
took your castle,
I thought, you know...
( makes slicing sound )
Whoa, wait.
Toffee has our castle?
Toffee is dead.
Ludo in castle.
Ugh! Toffee not dead.
Toffee inside Ludo.
Oh, I see.
So creepy.
Papa! Dad's still
in the castle!
We have to go save him.
No.
( gasps )
He is your husband!
Star, I've made
my decision.
We stay here.
Excuse me.
Where is your wash room?
Uh, wash room?
Yes. I'd like to
freshen up a bit.
She needs to
make boom-boom.
Oh! The wash room
- is out back.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
My mom's got...
monster issues.
Yes, I'm getting
certain vibe from her.
Yeah, we all are.
But Buffrog, I came here
for a favor.
Of course.
Anything for you.
I need you to
hang out with my mom.
keep her busy
while I go find Toffee.
Star, Toffee
is very dangerous.
Do you have plan?
- I have plan.
- You have plan?
I have plan.
Okay. When Moon returns,
I will distract her.
Distract me
from what?
Uh, from this.
I didn't want you
to see it.
Bad choices in past.
Oh. Thank you.
So what do you monsters
do for entertainment?
Uh, we could smash bugs.
We could play board game.
Great idea, Buffrog.
And I will hang out
with the babies
in their room.
Your daughter
is very strange.
Thank you.
We have many option
of board game.
( reading titles )
Monster Conquerors,
Castle Crushers,
Kill the Queen,
Mewman Versus Monster,
or my favorite,
Puddle Defender.
Mmm, interesting.
I like babushka monster.
I don't know why,
but I'm drawn to this one.
Okay, the rules of
Puddle Defender are,
uh...
Um...
the rules are...
Yes?
Uh, rules are simple.
The evil bloodthirsty Mewman,
that's you,
must try and sneak past watchful
Monster parent, that's me.
Break into daycare,
explode helpless monster babies,
and turn them into
stew for eating.
( gasps )
That is horrible!
( snapping sound )
Hey, here is dice!
You roll first.
QUEEN MOON: Seven.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
"You are filthy Mewman.
Use teeth-sharpening spell
for better eating of
monster babies." Really?
Is this fun?
Who will get to
daycare first?
Suspense is killing me.
"Congratulations."
Oh.
"You set a Mewman camp
on fire.
Collect four corn pieces
from bank."
Come on.
Oh, you land in
mud puddle.
You get nothing.
Tough break.
This game seems
a tad biased.
Really? I never noticed.
Yay! I get more corn.
( coughing )
Did you hear something?
I hear nothing.
You know, it's monsters
that eat Mewman babies.
Oh, really?
Can you name a time
when monsters have
ever done such a thing?
Well, no, but
when I was a child,
we played a game called
Castle Defender
about Mewmans protecting our
babies from ravenous monsters.
That idea had
to come from somewhere.
Because it was in
a children's board game?
I just think that monsters
would have less of a reputation
if they didn't act
so bloodthirsty all the time.
Monsters only act that way
to protect
their babies from Mewmans.
You may not understand,
but monsters will do
anything for our children.
Don't talk to me about
what I'm willing to do.
Why do you think
I'm here in this swamp?
To protect Star from Toffee!
Don't you think I'm worried to
death about my husband?
But I have to keep my child
safe at all costs!
Something you probably
wouldn't understand,
because you're a monster.
You insult me,
Queen Moon.
My buffbabies,
they are my life.
And that is why,
Star Butterfly...
I will not
help you escape.
- Star!
- Buffrog!
Star will be safe here.
Keeps babies in,
and dangers out.
I should have
realized.
But of course.
You're a parent, too.
I can't believe
you're taking her side.
BOTH: Go to your room!
- ( door slams )
- Kids.
Scared ol' mama.
Two-timing Buffrog.
What's their plan, huh?
Just avoid your problems
to death.
Great plan.
It's a terrible plan.
I've got plans.
I've got big plans.
But no, they stuck me
in here.
We can help you.
Not now. I'm thinking.
Who said that?
It was me, Katrina.
You guys can talk?!
Just me so far.
I haven't told my dad yet.
There's something else
I haven't told him.
Holy moley!
Sometimes we gotta
sneak out to the club
- and go dancing.
- I feel ya, girl.
All clear.
Wow. We made it.
- So what's the big plan?
- What plan?
The plan for
beating Toffee?
Oh, right.
I don't have one.
What?
Yeah, planning's
not really my thing.
I kinda just go for it.
That is a terrible plan.
Oh, my precious
little ribbit babies.
Don't you worry.
I'm very worried.
I'll see you
after I destroy Toffee.
She's gonna die.
Get it out,
all of it!
This is my castle.
I don't want to see
a single Butterfly face.
Move it!
Wait, wait, wait.
What am I looking at here?
No Butterflies.
Get that out of here.
Is that the last
of it?
And with that, everything
in my kingdom is in order.
Corncobs here.
Get your corncobs.
No, no, not again!
These rats have eaten me
out of house and home.
Right, they will do that.
Okay, a few kinks
to work out,
but overall, the citizens
of Mewni love me.
Hey, merch vendor,
how are the King Ludo
T-shirts selling?
Very, very,
very not good.
Not good at all,
Your Majesty.
What about the masks?
Those especially.
Here, I'll show you.
Greetings,
young man.
Might I interest you
in a King Ludo mask?
- ( shrieking )
- Run, baby, run!
Maybe it's the beard.
No, my lord, they just
don't like you.
Oh, honey, look at
all that great stuff.
Wow, we should load up.
Finally,
someone with taste.
Let me just...
This will look great
in our foyer.
How much for
this handsome fella?
Oh, well...
It's not for sale.
Come on.
You know what? That's it.
Levitato!
There. All that terrible
Butterfly stuff is gone.
Now, how about a nice
King Ludo coffee mug,
- or a bobblehead?
- We don't want your stuff.
Yeah, we don't
like you; nobody
likes you, dude.
See what I'm
dealing with here?
I am your king.
I command you to like me.
No.
( frustrated yell )
( straining )
Checkmate.
I'm bad at everything.
First rule
of chess, Marco:
you must always
protect your king.
( keys jingling )
- What do you want?
- You're coming with me.
No way. I'm not
going anywhere with you.
That's too bad.
It's urgent royal business.
I need you to command
the people to like me.
( laughs )
Why would I do that?
I don't even like you.
Shuffling about
and talking to
that wand hand of yours.
It's weird.
Fine. If you won't help me,
then you can just
rot in this cell.
Say good-bye
to your freedom.
Come on,
you stupid chain.
Ha ha!
Ho ho. Ludo.
Butter.
Change of plan.
I'm giving you 24 hours
to figure out a way
to make the people
of Mewni like me,
or I'll...
I'll levitato you
into the sky forever.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Twenty-four hours.
Dude, Ludo's gone
completely nuts.
You're telling me.
He left behind
a perfectly good
stick of butter.
Oh, I can...
almost taste it.
River, now is no time for...
butter.
Yes, you're
young and limber.
Reach out for it, boy.
Excellent!
Ha ha!
Careful. Save some
for the gruel, boy.
Nice work, Marco.
Here. Butter yourself up,
and I'll see if I can
figure a way out of here.
Try the AC vent.
The dungeon has
air conditioning?
It's a dungeon,
not a torture chamber.
Nice. How are those
shackles coming?
I don't think
this is going to work.
River, did you
eat the butter, River?
I used to be king.
Okay, okay, I'll go
steal that key from Ludo,
and then we'll both
get out of here.
You should just go.
This isn't your fight.
Marco, listen to your king.
Whoa. The royal bedroom.
Ludo.
- Sh.
- Ruberiot?
Quiet, dude.
You're gonna
get us caught.
Whoo, how'd I ever live
without a solid gold toilet?
What the heck
is going on here?
Since Ludo took over,
we've been hiding in
the vents.
When he's not around,
we eat his royal leftovers.
And bathe in
his royal bubble bath.
And sleep in
his royal bed.
She was miming that
we sleep in his royal bed.
LUDO: Those villagers
are so ungrateful.
And end scene.
I don't get it.
How are these things
not flying off the shelf?
It can't be for my lack of
devilishly good looks.
I've got that whole
levitatoing King River to do.
Being a king is
simply exhausting.
Now's our chance.
If we can get
that key from Ludo,
we can free the king and--
Whoa. I'm gonna have
to stop you right there.
You see, as artists,
our job is to comment
on the world around us,
not "doing stuff."
A heavy burden, yes,
but that's what it means
to be an artiste.
Oh, please.
You, an artist?
- You're nothing but
a jingle scribbler.
- And you're a buffoon.
The buffoon is merely
the facade
for my pointed
social commentary.
That's what makes me
a true artist.
Not as much of an artist
as the mime.
Obviously. We all know
the mime is an artistic genius.
- BOTH: Genius.
- Guys, look.
I'm not a soldier either,
but there's a time
when you have to get
off the sidelines
and get involved.
If the four of us
work together,
we can save
the true king of Mewni.
Now who's with me?
Now, see, I wouldn't
use that hand gesture.
It's just been
done to death.
And you never want to
end a sentence with a pronoun.
You all
make me sick.
No. I don't want
to shave the corn.
What? Who's here?
Who's in
my royal bedroom?
A guy in a mask.
We're here to...
entertain you,
my lord.
What?
In the middle
of the night?
Oh, yeah, because, uh...
And we wrote
this song about... you.
You wrote a song
about me?
♪ Ohhh, he... ♪
♪ Came on bird and spider ♪
♪ Uh, shone his grace
upon us all ♪
I did do that,
didn't I?
♪ And brought
the rats here ♪
♪ To protect us ♪
♪ And now
we'll never fall ♪
Get the key.
♪ And we say ♪
♪ Great King Ludo
is great ♪
♪ He's so great, great, great,
great, great, great, great ♪
♪ And Mewni
has never been better ♪
♪ Been better, been better,
been better ♪
♪ Oh, great King Ludo
is great ♪
♪ He's so great, great, great,
great, great, great, great ♪
You guys are really good.
What do you call your band?
Three Artists
And A Buffoon.
Okay, that's it.
- What?
- I'm the buffoon?
You're the buffoon.
You make fart jokes.
I make art.
You call that
noise art?
Your rhymes are whack!
Yeah, well, yours
are hack.
Oh, good one.
- Hey, hey.
- Hey!
Stop.
You're all hacks,
except for the mime.
She's a genius.
Get them!
I can't believe this.
I almost had the key.
Can't you two get along
for just one minute?
We like not
getting along.
Yeah. We're good at it.
Wow! You guys
really had me fooled.
No, we really do
hate each other.
Ah!
Marco!
Hey, king, we're
busting you outta here.
What are you doing?
I won't abandon
my people.
What?!
Sometimes, you've got
to let the king go.
Time's up.
So, um... ready to...
Where's my key?
I must've dropped my key
right in front of you,
and you didn't
even notice. What?!
You could have been running free
by now, prancing in the fields.
Must make you
feel pretty silly.
Ha ha. Spider!
So are you going to force
everyone to like me,
or is it levitato time?
You may have the crown,
but you will never be king.
We'll see how you feel
once you've been levitatoed.
No, River!
Come on!
Welcome to the reign
of King Ludo.
This is what happens
to anyone
who doesn't show respect
and adoration for their king.
You have any last words?
People of Mewni,
I am not afraid.
Blah blah blah.
Levitato.
( people gasping )
What are we
gonna do now?
Now?
We fight.
Uh, you know that's
not mud, right?
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪