♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Hold on to my hands.
They'll keep you safe.
Hey, Mr. Muscles,
just keep driving.
Just lookin' out
for your safety.
Then look out
for that cliff.
[both screaming]
Ha ha!
Oh, man, I was
not payin' attention.
Nice save, Nachos.
- Marco!
- Sorry.
So, uh, what are
we lookin' for again?
Oh, uh, that thing.
Follow me.
[screaming]
Why did you
punch him in the eye?
- Where else was I
supposed to punch him?
- Just don't punch it.
Whoa!
- Just drive, muscles.
- Yes, ma'am.
Another portal closed.
Man, I missed this.
Punchin' monsters,
crazy adventures.
Eat weird things.
Hey! Who you
callin' weird?
I'm quirky.
I just wish more portals would
open in your dimension, Hekapoo.
I look so awesome there.
Yeah, it's
a real shame.
- [watch beeping]
- Oh, I gotta go.
Already?
We just sat down.
I'll sit with ya.
No, thanks, weirdo.
Nachos!
Oh, buddy, it's getting
harder and harder to leave ya.
Hey, muscles,
you comin' back tomorrow?
Yeah, if you need me.
I could use a hand.
Cool. Can't wait.
Marco.
Hey... oh.
Oh... what happened
to your face?
I tried to take
Glossaryck for a walk today.
It did not go well.
I really could've used
some help from my squire,
who was mysteriously
not around.
Yeah, sorry.
I was, uh...
fishing.
You went fishing
in the middle of the night?
- Yep.
- Well, did you
catch anything?
I caught a mackerel.
A big old mackerel.
You caught a mackerel?
Where is it?
I ate it.
Okay. Well, I gotta
help my dad clear out
the castle sewers tomorrow.
Fuuuuun!
So could you just
keep an eye on Glossaryck?
Yeah. I can do that.
Oh, great.
Things have been
pretty busy around here.
Well, your squire
is here to help.
Thanks, squire.
[screeching]
Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew!
This is
a meow-trage, I say.
Can you hurry up?
I'm trying.
[screaming]
Shiver me timbers,
we're all gonna die...
Hekapoo, hey.
I'm here.
Oh. Nice of you
to show up.
Star needed me
to watch Glossaryck,
but it's cool,
I handled it.
Great story. Now can you
give me a hand with this?
Oh, right.
[all] Huh?
[screaming]
Captain, what were
those strange creatures?
Angels, me boy.
They be but angels.
Fur-tastic.
You two make
a purr-fect team.
Meow-velous.
Well, I hate it here.
So... tavern?
- [watch beeping]
- Oh, no. I gotta go.
Star needs me.
She says it's urgent.
But the same time tomorrow?
Ah, you bet.
Please stop doing that.
Not until you're bald.
Hey, Star, what's
the emer... gency?
You had one job.
Sorry, I was
fishing again.
Wait a minute.
Greasy pants.
Dimensional scissors.
Scorched bald spot.
You haven't been
fishing at all.
You've been hanging out
with Hekapoo again.
Uh, uh, just for, like,
a second.
Marco, I need you here.
Glossaryck needs
constant surveillance.
[blows raspberry]
I know it's not as glamourous
as dragon cycling.
I've been really
overwhelmed lately,
and I need your help.
You're right.
No more moonlighting.
Here.
You can watch
these for me.
Thanks, Marco.
I'm at your service,
milady.
Ha ha ha.
Don't ever call me that.
Now get some sleep.
Tomorrow, we're gonna be
waist deep in sewer sludge.
Can't wait.
Let's ride.
[snoring]
Okay, this is
just for tonight.
[blows raspberry]
Don't look at me like that.
Hey, sorry.
I'm late again.
Where are we
riding today?
This next job's
pretty big,
so I hired Talon Raventalon
for some extra muscle.
Who's Talon Raventalon?
I'm Talon Raventalon!
[electric guitar
riff plays]
One glass of worms.
Extra wiggly.
Hekapoo, we don't
need this bro.
Actually, we kinda do.
You've been so busy,
I wasn't sure you
were gonna show,
and I can't do
this job alone.
I guess that's fair...
but him?
( loud chewing )
So what's the job,
anyway?
Dragon cyclers
don't ask questions.
Dragon cyclers ride!
- Follow us, okay?
- [yells]
So what are we
doing today?
- Something fun.
- Ooh, like what?
Like closing up
these portals for good.
Wait, so... what?
There's a pattern to where
these portals have been opening.
And the next one should
open right over there.
Whatever comes out of it,
we're takin' it down!
Oh, yeah!
With this!
Doesn't this seem
like overkill?
Talon likes
overkill.
[electric guitar
riff plays]
H-Poo, can we chat?
So it's just that
closing these portals
with you
has been the highlight
of my time on Mewni.
Do we really
have to stop?
Marco, this has been fun,
but I've got a job to do.
Yeah, just
don't do it.
My job is to stop whatever
comes out of that portal.
[Talon] Incoming!
There it is!
Oh, yeah!
Stop!
Marco, what are you doing?
I'm not sure,
but you need to stop.
Oh, I'm just gettin' started.
Ba-kaw!
Marco, it's my job.
Star?
Oh, I love harpoons.
No! You idiot!
Ha ha!
Star!
[relieved sigh]
That was some great
riding, Hekapoo.
You knew?
You knew that Star
was the one opening
these portals,
and you didn't
tell me?!
Okay, okay,
hear me out.
I'm reporting this
to the high commission.
Okay, yeah, I lied
to you about Star,
but not about
anything else.
Working with you
has been incredible,
and I don't want it
to end.
Please don't report this
to the high commission.
Star needs to figure out
her new powers on her own.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous that is?
I'm her squire;
I can make sure she's safe.
Haven't I earned
your trust by now?
No!!
[sighs]
[adult voice]
Pretty please, H-Poo.
Oh, you know I can't
resist your adult voice.
Fine. I won't report
this, for your sake,
but us working
together is over.
- Hekapoo.
- Here.
You're gonna
need this.
Star's lucky to have
a squire like you.
Yah!
You wanna hang out?
[electric guitar
riff plays]
Uh... hello?
- [screams] Creepy blast!
- [Marco yells]
[Marco groaning]
Marco?
What are you doing?
And what are you doing
with your scissors?
Okay, okay,
I can explain.
First you're lying,
and now you're stealing.
- What are you doing?
- I've been closing
your portals.
Uh, you've been opening them
in different dimensions,
and I've been closing them,
with Hekapoo.
Wha-wha-what?
Does Hekapoo know about...
Yeah. Yeah, she knows.
She's not happy about it.
Oh, no. Oh, no,
oh, no!
Star, I like
adventures,
but I like keeping
you safe more,
so I can stop
doing this.
Can you stop
doing that?
Whoa, what is it?
I think it's
what you've been
looking for.
Okay, I thought it was
a dream,
but then, it was like,
"Oh, no, you ate
all these goblin dogs,"
but it was not a dream.
And then I brought
the goblin dogs truck
into my bedroom,
and then, I crushed
my bed with it,
and I had to turn my bed
back into a bed,
and then I told
my mom about it,
and then my mom
was, like, "That
shouldn't be happening."
And I was like...
Jenna.
Stop blowing in
Marco's hair.
That was you?
Sorry. Got a little bored.
No offense.
Yeah, Star, can you just
get to the point, please?
[sighs]
Okay, I'm sleep-portaling.
In my sleep, every night,
I hear this sound.
It's like...
[high-pitched screeching]
No, no, that's not it.
[high-pitched whining]
Okay, Star, we get it.
Can we just get to
the point, please?
I've been following
this sound
to the same location
every night,
but I never make it there,
because I wake up,
and that's where you
come in, Janna.
You've gotta hypnotize me
so I can stay asleep.
What? Hypnotize you?
Star, shouldn't you leave
that to a trained professional?
You doubt my skills?
Yeah, actually,
I do.
Chickenbutt.
What the heck?
What happened?
You guys, stop messing
around and get over here.
Hey, check it out.
I linked my compact phone
to my mirror,
so you'll be able to see
whatever I see.
Marco, you've got
the scissors.
If anything goes wrong
out there, you come get me.
You're my lifeline.
What if you get lost,
or go so far out
that we can't find you?
Marco, we've dealt with
much worse stuff than this.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, Star, take
a nice, deep breath.
Now, focus on my watch.
Hey, that's
my watch.
- Dude, this is about Star.
Get over yourself.
- [grunts]
Keep your eyes
on the watch.
You're feeling light
as a feather.
And now we wait.
So what exactly
does it look like
when she portals?
Like that.
We have lift-off.
I'm here for you.
Your lifeline.
Uh, what's all that?
Spiritual chromatograph,
magic wave scope,
energy oscillotron,
and a jigsaw puzzle
for when things get slow.
But most importantly,
the map.
Uh... uh...
where is she?!
Here she is,
she's here.
No, no, maybe
Or here. No.
Forget this.
I'm goin' in.
Dude, relax. She's got
a long way to go.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
So...
Janna.
Been a while since
we hung out one-on-one.
- We never really--
- Chickenbutt.
[snoring]
[high-pitched whining noise]
What the...
Hey, Sleeping Beauty.
Huh... what?
Janna?
What did you--
Shut up and look.
Wait. Where is that
on the map?
I don't know.
She's off the map.
[Marco] Star.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't go in there.
No! That's it.
I'm goin' in.
What happened?
Where is she?
I can't get to her
with the scissors
if I don't know
where she is.
You're here.
I'm here.
Stop it, stop it,
stop it.
[soft whinnying]
You're here!
Okay, okay,
I'm here.
But where is here?
You don't know?
You're in the realm
of magic.
Wow!
It's like Toffee
was never even here.
It's been reborn-ded.
That's not a word.
That sound.
The song of the firstborn.
She's been calling to you.
[high-pitched whine
continues]
[high-pitched whining]
Okay, stop, please.
And thank you.
So who are you?
Do you not recognize
your own creation?
[loud gasp]
I made you?!
I did good.
So you're the one
that called me here?
I can only call one
who wishes to be called.
I don't understand.
Why would I wish
to be called?
I don't know.
Perhaps the answer
rests here,
in the realm of magic.
Oh, I can't stay.
- I have to go home.
- Do you?
[whinnying]
I guess I could stay.
- Plug your nose.
- Oh, okay.
- Your call cannot
be completed as dialed.
- [frustrated groan]
...try again.
- Call Star.
- Calling Star.
Aaaaahhh!
What am I gonna do?
Oh, what about Glossaryck?
Maybe he can...
[screaming]
You're a disgrace to magic.
Magic.
Oh, that's a bad idea.
And that's coming from me.
- Oh, you're gonna die!
- Ooh!
Huh.
Nothing happened.
It's like our souls
are bonded--
[screaming]
And there.
Now it has your mole.
Whoa. The All-Seeing Eye.
Spying leads to crying?
Just hold it up
so I can read it.
Okay.
I summon
the All-Seeing Eye
to tear a hole
into the sky.
Reveal to me
that which is hidden.
Unveil to me
what is forbidden.
[Star] Salmon.
Stromboni.
Strawberry.
Sal... Sally!
What are you doing?
I can't remember
my name.
- What's a name?
- [Marco] Star!
That's it.
That's my name. Star.
Thanks, strange boy.
Star, you have to come home.
I am home.
We've gotta get
her out of there.
Just give me your hand.
Marco.
Marco?
Marco!
Wait.
Where are you going?
Don't go.
Sorry. I have to.
Janna? Janna?
Marco?
Where are you?
Janna! Marco!
[Marco] Over here.
[gasps]
Are you okay?
Better now without
that table on me.
My wand.
What did you do?
Well, I was kind of
out of options.
Oh, Marco,
that was incredibly
stupid of you.
That's a little mean.
Thank you.
Ew, gross.
Get a portal.
Janna!
- No rush.
- Gotcha.
This is the coolest thing
that's ever happened to you.
Agreed.
Oh, check this out.
Huh, huh?
Huh? Huh?
I can do it...
♪ At will ♪
So are you still hearing
that sound?
I...
I guess I'm not.
And does that mean you're
going to quit sleep-portaling?
I guess...
it does.
I don't know.
I'm not convinced
that this is--
[both] Chickenbutt.
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪