♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Star, let's go.
We've been here for hours.
No. We are not leaving until
the old donuts get thrown out.
( whistling )
- Evening, Marco.
- Evening, Pete.
Ah!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Star. Some lady
just got your donuts.
What?
( shuddering )
Mina.
You're Mina Loveberry.
You caught me.
Are you a cop?
That's Mina Loveberry.
I have no idea
who that is.
Marco, she's
the greatest warrior
- to ever live.
- Uh, her?
I lost my bag.
Has anyone seen
my bag?
That's a lady who's
lost her marbles.
No, she's
Mina Loveberry.
- Hello.
- Mewni's greatest
protector.
At least, I think
that's her.
Well, why don't you
see for yourself?
No, no, no.
Marco, no!
- Hello, Mina.
- Hello.
What are you doing
on Earth?
I'm on vacation.
Doctor's orders.
What are you gonna do
on your vacation?
I will let the soul
be my guide
and wander off
to the depths
of this unseen planet.
Wow!
That's what you say
when you've lost your marbles.
Marco, just...
There is actually
a really great park
across the street.
Fantastic!
The perfect place
to view humanity
at its most docile.
I will leave
in two seconds.
Boy, what a weirdo.
Star?
Oh, no.
Wait. Wait, Mina.
Wait.
Teach me your way,
O great warrior.
Hmm. Yeah. Okay.
Really?
O great Mina,
you will not be disappointed.
But ain't nothin'
for free.
You're gonna have to do
something for me.
Anything.
Get this bag
off my head.
Ooh, ow.
A, E, I, O, U!
Welcome to the Echo Creek
Mud Pits.
Here, we will answer
all of your questions
about mud.
Finally.
Today, I go
where Mina goes.
Look at us; we're already
basically best friends.
Inseparable.
Boy, are you guys in for
a real educational treat today.
Lesson number first.
In becoming
a great warrior,
one must cleanse
their mind
from sinking thought.
So... just don't think?
Don't think.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh!
We are mud sisters.
Wait a second.
Where's my camera,
where's my telescope,
where's my sketch pad?
What the heck is that?
Observe the wooly mammoth,
who may or may not have
walked through these mud pits
19 million years ago.
We're not really sure.
Ride, my great beast.
Ride to the cloud city
of Cloudlandia!
Get down, ya weirdo.
Come on, big boy.
Let's get to movin'.
Uh, ma'am, you leave
that mammoth alone.
I command ye to move.
That's it. I'm comin' in
to get you, ma'am.
Sorry, you can't
be doin' that.
Whoa, goin' down.
What a cruel
twist of fate.
Star, she's
clearly lost it.
I am the conqueror
of the beast.
No autographs.
Lesson number one, Marco.
Just stop thinkin'.
Now, class,
meaning you,
our next lesson is of
utmost importance
to the survival
of a warrior.
We're gonna learn how to
make some weapons.
The higher I go,
the closer I get
to reaching the stars.
Be resourceful with
finding material.
( girl screams )
See? Now I have
a sturdy chain
to chain stuff with.
Easy breezy taco peasy.
Go make your own
warrior weapon.
All right, Star,
you got this.
It's just like
arts and crafts,
but with weapons.
Which ones are yours?
( sighs )
Those two.
( screaming )
Oh, bless your soul.
Come on, Star,
anything can be a weapon.
Oh, my goodness.
Look at this string.
How lucky could I be?
And what is this?
A pine cone?
Everything's comin' up Star.
Let go of my bat,
you naughty lady.
Mina, did you finish
building your weapon yet?
I have created
the most deadly of maces.
Awesome!
You know, I'm actually
pretty proud of mine, too.
Uh, kazza kazza wha?
It is a pine cone
tied to a string,
and then, I put some flowers
on it and drew a face.
I call him Davey.
Fantastic!
Ho!
When they turn
18, they're the
government's problem.
Hot dogs here.
Get your hot dogs.
Hot dogs.
Lesson number  tres.
You gotta gather intel.
Sh, someone may be listening.
Learn from
your new surroundings.
Learn from new
surroundings.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't know
it was a wig.
Who is your ruler
on this planet?
Not from around here,
are we?
- She's a foreigner.
- Oh, how exotic.
This is the United States
of America.
We don't have any rulers here.
We're free.
But who makes the rules?
We make our own rules
through the radical
process of voting.
( screeching )
Just trying to wrap
my head around this.
You mean you vote if you
can do something or not?
That's right,
little lady.
- So I can do this?
- Sure.
- And this, too?
- You betcha.
Is this legal?
Actually,
that's arson.
Freedom!
ALL: Freedom!
MINA: No chains
or limitations.
I'm freedom!
We have learned there are
no rules on this planet.
It's an anything goes
fight to the death.
Star, wait.
You've gotta stop this.
Stop what?
What am I doing?
You guys ruined
the entire park today.
Marco, Mina was my idol
growing up.
Imagine if you randomly
met your idol one day,
- and didn't
follow them around.
- But your idol is bananas.
Look, thanks for trying
to look out for me.
But I'm gonna go train
with my hero.
- Fine. I'm just gonna
enjoy the park by myself.
- ( siren )
Sir, we're gonna have to
ask you a couple questions.
All right, step one.
Just stop thinking.
Step two,
make a weapon.
Step  tres,
gather intel.
( panting )
Mina, I made it!
Come, little mud face.
You must partake in
the warrior's ritual.
Step inside
the circle of animals.
- Now, repeat these words:
- Repeat these words.
- Not these words,
the ones coming.
- Right. Sorry.
O great battle lords.
- Please protect us.
Carry our foes off to
the depths of space and time
so they may forever live in
the ruins of our victory.
( muttering gibberish )...
victory.
Lead us to the battle,
and you shall bathe in
our conquests. Ha!
( making weird noises )
So, mud sister,
what are we battling?
Some demons? Gargoyles?
- Them people.
- Joggers?
No, ding-dong.
All the people
of this forsaken planet.
( laughs )
No. You don't mean that.
That's wacky talk.
What these little ants
lack is a ruler.
And guess who's
gonna give 'em one?
Bink.
- Now, kneel before
your new ruler.
- Okay.
We're gonna have
so much fun rulin'
these folks.
I've made a huge mistake.
So a gonzo donut collector
came out of a dumpster.
- Uh-huh.
- To teach your friend,
another gonzo donut collector
in a dumpster.
- Yep.
- And together,
they destroyed
a family park?
Yeah. If I was trying
to cover my butt,
I'd say the exact
same thing.
MINA: Kneel before
me, minions.
I am the greatest warrior
that this world
has ever known!
( siren wailing )
Let's ride.
Mina, I can't
take over the Earth.
Aw, of course you can.
You're a warrior now.
Now let's start by
rounding up the rest
of these folks,
and pushin' 'em off
this here ledge.
( nervous giggle )
Mina, I care about Earth.
I don't wanna conquer it.
I thought you cared about
being a warrior.
I guess I thought
being a warrior
was something different.
Uh, excuse me, miss.
- Don't we get
a vote in this?
- ALL: Yeah!
What are you,
a bunch of comedians?
We ain't votin' on this.
I'm your ruler now.
Mm, all those in favor
of the crazy lady
being our new ruler,
raise your hands.
One, two...
six. okay.
All those opposed.
One, two...
five, six.
Looks like we have
ourselves a draw.
Hey, did anybody
not vote?
Me.
I didn't vote.
Come on.
You got mud on your face.
We're a team.
We can rule
this land together.
Mud sister.
No. You're bananas, Mina.
Like the bad kind.
Hey, freedom wins again.
( cheering )
I thought you were
a warrior.
You're just a little girl
living on a stupid
freedom planet.
- You don't even
deserve this.
- Davey!
I wouldn't dare rule over
this looney bin.
- ( siren blaring )
- Attention, citizens.
- We are looking for--
- She's in there.
Uh, there's
nothing inside.
Magic does exist.
I repeat, magic...
does exist.
You were right, Marco.
Mina was a lady
with no marbles.
You wanna go check
behind the French bakery
for some day-old
baguettes?
Of course I do.
Boop.
Mud sister.
- Camping!
- ( screams )
What's up, nature?!
You're gonna get tamed!
( buzzing )
( gasps )
Nature's touching me.
Hey, little guy.
( gasps )
Cataclysmic total extinction
death blast!
Star, we're not on Mewni.
( buzzing )
Nature's nice here.
You'll see.
We'll do some fishing,
a little hiking,
and then... this!
( gasps )
A treasure map?
What? No.
It's Old Youthful.
One of the oldest
geysers on Earth.
- And guess when
it's erupting.
- Today?
Mmmm-hmmmm.
Well, we got
a big day ahead.
Let's get started.
Aren't your parents coming?
Nah. You know how
most parents show
slide shows of
their vacation?
Mine show paintings.
And done. Next.
So it's just
the two of us then?
Yeah. Is that okay?
( explosion )
Camping!!
Dad!
Dad, oh, it's always
great to see you.
But what are you
doing here?
( straining )
What, I can't go camping
with my own daughter?
I taught you how to camp.
Yeah, and now Marco's
showing me how to go
camping here on Earth.
Really? Is he showing you
how to stalk
a Narinthian tar beast
for eleven days
with no food,
no sleep,
and no clothes?!
No, Dad, nature's
really nice here.
Look at what it gave me.
Love bites.
Here, Marco. Show Dad
how to Earth fish.
Yeah, sure.
Whoa. So, how do I...
Amazing. Now what?
You're already doing it.
Yay, Dad!
Now we just sit
and wait.
You wait for the fish
to come to you?
Just relax
and take it all in.
( breathing deeply )
Ah!
Smell that? Okay.
Where'd he go?
Fishing!!
Take that and that.
Is that what fishing
on Mewni looks like?
It says Old Youthful
actually got its name
from early settlers
who believed
that it had
rejuvenating powers.
That sounds really--
Boring!
Why are we walking
so slow?
Well, I was trying
to take it easy,
'cause, you know,
what you did to your foot.
But I don't
even feel it.
Come on, let me
magic you up some boots.
I don't need any of that.
I don't even need feet.
Can you do this, huh?
Can you do this?
I don't think you can.
Want a piggyback
ride, honey?
Aw, Dad. No.
Since when are you
too cool for piggyback rides?
Well, I'm not too cool
for a piggyback--
That would be weird, Marco.
Race you to
the water thing.
( laughing )
- Is that the right way?
- No.
Is your dad okay?
I think so.
He just really loves
family camping trips.
Okay, where'd you go,
big guy?
Got him.
What's he doing
way up there?
Hey, Dad.
Everything all right?
Sh. Staring contest.
Whoa! That's
a bald eagle.
We are breakin'
a whole bunch of laws here.
He started it.
Marco's right, Dad.
Let's go see
Old Youthful.
Don't worry, darling.
Once I break
his spirit with my eyes,
he'll fly us there.
( speaking gibberish )
Llama pajama llama...
pa... ja... ma.
This guy's unbelievable.
You can't let him beat you
in front of your own daughter.
She looks up to you.
Does she though?
What is that
supposed to mean?
Did you notice,
she's pretty much over
your piggyback rides.
She used to love those.
And she went camping
without you.
That Marco kid's
probably her boyfriend.
What? No way.
My little girl
isn't dating yet.
Whatever. Keep lying
to yourself, old man.
- Old? Who are you calling old?
- ( siren blaring )
Something is definitely
goin' on with my dad.
Okay, everything's cool.
Turns out that feathered
thing was some kind of
a sacred animal.
Heads up would've been nice.
You folks better
get a move on
if you wanna see
that old geyser.
Who are you calling
an old geezer?!
Oh. Geyser.
Yes, Dad, the thing Marco's
been trying to see all day.
We can still
make it in time.
This trail should
take us straight...
to it.
Let me see that map.
Is he eating the map?
I was hungry.
Everything is food when you're
struggling to survive.
Except we're not on...
Mewni.
Right. Sorry.
I'm staying
positive about this.
One of those trails
is the right one.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Eeny, meeny, miney...
Nooooo!
You know what?
I think this may be
my fault.
You kids wait right here
while I score us a ride.
Oh, man, if he could
get us a ride,
that would be...
( groaning )
You'll never make it
to Old Youthful now.
He goes off in five minutes,
and it's a ten-mile hike.
I'm sorry, Marco.
Oh, come on,
what's the big deal?
- Dad, what is up with you?
- Is this about the bear?
No, Dad. You've been
acting really weird all day,
and now, Marco's plans
are basically ruined.
He really wanted to see
Old Youthful.
No, Star, I've seen it,
like, ten times.
I wanted you to see it.
You've shown me
all kind of
amazing stuff
I never knew
existed.
I just wanted
to pay you back.
Show you something
amazing here on Earth.
Marco!
Marco.
I guess we can come back
to see Old Youthful erupt
some other time.
Oh, you poor,
poor boy.
- Didn't nobody tell you?
- What?
This here eruption
is gonna be the last.
- What?!
- Those big-city scientists
gave that geyser a look-see,
and he's all dried up.
He's been fadin' away
for years.
Oh, he used to be
impressive.
King of the geysers.
But now, he's just
a sad shadow of
his former glory.
Aged out
and obsolete.
Ready to retire
and getting in
everybody's way.
Yes, sir, to use
clever wordplay,
Old Youthful
is plumb out of youth.
We should just go.
Yes, Marco.
We will go...
and see that geyser.
Didn't you hear
what that guy said?
It's impossible.
Is it?
Tick-tock.
( slowly )
Tick... tock.
What do you say, Star?
One last piggyback
ride from your old man?
We're almost there!
Just a glacier and two more
war re-enactments.
You hear that, Dad?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
No!
Dad!
I'm so sorry, pumpkin.
I let you down.
Are you out of your mind?
You ran ten miles
in five minutes.
That's, like,
150 miles an hour.
I used to be able
to do it in four minutes.
I'm not the dad
I used to be, Star.
You need someone younger
to take care of you now.
Someone like...
your boyfriend Marco here.
I'm not her boyfriend.
You fell up a waterfall, dude.
Who does that?
I'm older, too, Dad,
but I still need you.
No matter
how old I get,
you'll always be my hero,
because you'll always
be my dad.
Come here, you.
Well, it's gettin'
chilly out,
so what do you say
we go find you
some pants?
( loud rumbling )
Wow!!
You gotta stop lying
to the tourists
about that geyser, man.
Yeah, I know,
But it sure is fun.
Marco.
It's beautiful.
( loud crash )
Look, Star.
Dad. You're so young.
Yeah. Fresh-out-
the-womb young.
Brand-new dad!
And here's the king
with his arms up.
putting his arms down.
And here he is walking
out of the crater.
And climbing
This is so much better
than a slide show.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪