♪♪
(  I'm from Another Dimension
by Brad Breeck plays)
MAN:
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo! ♪
♪♪
♪ Yeah-hey! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, paaa! ♪
♪ Oh, it's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( song ends )
( Gloassaryk clears throat )
Who is it? What do you want?
It's me, Star.
Oh! Oh, yes. Yes, yes.
( sighs)
I always forget the chain.
Star Butterfly
future Queen of Mewni.
What do you want?
Look.
( Glossaryck gasps in horror)
Okay, don't panic.
I got the stain remover.
You go start the car!
They're not dead.
Oh...
( strangled gasp )
It's my spells.
They're all messed up.
See?
Narwhal blast!
( gags )
Oh, you must stop.
It's not your spells,
it's your wand.
You see,
it's contaminated.
( whispering )
Contamina... Whaa?
How did that happen?
The only way to find out
is to go into...
( splash )
( muffled )
your wand.
( surprised )
What? You can do that?
Of course. But we won't.
Why not?
Because...
by decree of
Moon the Undaunted,
Queen of Mewni,
you must be that tall
to go on this ride.
( grumbles )
Mother...
Well, I,
Star the Underestimated,
future Queen of Mewni,
hereby decree:
Put me in my wand.
Okay.
( high-pitched squeal )
Now, there are
some things, young lady,
you need to know
before we go inside.
( mumbles excitedly )
Kay!
The wand is
an extension of your your--
( tapping )
Star, what are you doing?
Are you- Are you going
to listen to me or not?
( gasps )
Oh, sorry.
As I was saying,
the wand...
is an extension
of your memories.
So you must find the thing
that does not belong.
Find the thing
that doesn't belong.
Good. Are you ready?
Maybe.
( claps )
All right. We're inside.
What?
But we're still in my room.
We're in the memory
of your room.
Inside of your wand.
( inhales loudly )
( softly )
Whoa...
Yes. From this point on,
it's very, very important
that you listen only
to the sound of my voice.
And nothing else.
( door opens )
Hey. Have you seen my hoodie?
Uh... I'm kinda in
the middle of something
with Glossaryck.
GLOSSARYCK: ( horrified )
No! No, Star.
That is not Marco.
Only listen to the sound
of my voice.
Otherwise,
we will be separated.
Hey. Have you seen my hoodie?
Marco, I told you.
I am in
the middle of something
with Glossary...
( gasps )
( softly )
What?
School?
( frustrated groan )
Okay, Glossaryck, no.
I'm not going to school...
in my memory...
my wand memory--
( grunts )
( softly )
What?
( sighs )
Right, right, right.
This is one
of those mind things.
Where everywhere you go,
there's school.
School. School. School!
School. School. School.
( grunts )
( door rattles )
School.
I guess I'm going to school.
( locker door creaks )
( softly ) Whaa...
That's Marco's.
( gasps )
Well, this definitely
doesn't belong!
Over, under,
around and through.
Grab the little Mewni rabbit,
pull him through.
( singsong )
Oh, Glossaryck!
I found the thing
that doesn't belong!
Beam me out!
Or...
Beam me up.
Uh... Glossaryck?
( goat bleats )
Hello?
( mechanical whir )
Oh, burger time.
Don't mind if I do.
( munching softly )
Mmm. Memory burger.
( bleats )
Oh, no!
( bleats loudly )
( grunts )
( bleats )
Your welcome!
( softly ) Who're you?
Lil Chauncey.
Lil Chauncey, Chauncey?
( bleats )
Like...
my mom's Lil Chauncey?
(playful)
I'm pretty sure you died
on the battlefield, mister!
Let's get you out of here.
Hey Glossaryck!
I think I found the thing
that doesn't belong!
My mom's pig-goat.
( bleats and snaps angrily )
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
That's my boot!
Hey! Hey...
( bleats happily )
Hey, you!
Gimme back my boot!
And get down!
Sitting like a person.
My father would be furious
if he caught you sitting
in his-- ( horrified gasp )
( gasps ) Oh, Papa!
( softly ) I love you so much!
( radio crackle )
Gloassaryck, I definitely
found the thing now.
( loudspeaker screeches )
Can you come and pick me up
from school please?
Aah! What is that?
That definitely
doesn't belong.
Let's go get it.
( squish )
( fishing rod whirs )
Move out, Lil Chauncey!
Hyaaah!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey!
Uh... Hey.
Where are you headed?
Well, I was just
going to the foo-fo...
Football field
and Mewni Castle...
Wait a minute.
Who are you?
I'm Star Butterfly!
Nuh-uh, you're not.
Did you find the thing
that doesn't belong?
N-n-not exactly...
I mean I found Marco's hoodie
and my dad's chair and--
( grunting )
Lil Chauncey here.
( bleats )
( grunts )
Wait a minute.
( sighs )
Why are there
two of us here?
Didn't Glossaryck tell you?
If you're inside
your wand too long,
all your new memories
become your old memories.
Until eventually
your current timeline
is overwritten
by the future
versions of yourself,
like me!
Star Butterfly!
Wait...
so, you're gonna
replace me?
( laughing ) Yeah!
But don't worry.
You'll never know
the difference.
I gotta go.
( squeals loudly )
( bleats )
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
( threatening )
Stay out of my timeline.
( sweetly )
Thanks!
Fine. I'll just get
my own timeline. Moody.
STAR:
I guess I'm going to school.
Hey!
( bleating loudly )
Hello!
Go away!
( Stars calling
one after another )
Hello! Hello! Hello!
( gasps )
Okay...
( door creeks open )
( door creaks shut )
Oh! Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Whoa...
This is the grandma room.
Oh, I haven't been in here
since I was a little baby.
( grunts and gasps )
Are you nuts?!
There's no eating
in the grandma room!
You'll get crumbs
everywhere!
( loud thud )
( clattering )
( Star gasps )
( slow grating )
( loud thud )
Oh, no, no, no.
We got burger juice
on the wall rug, Chauncey.
( inhales nervously )
( squelch )
( shouting in panic )
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
( grating )
Celena the Shy?
Ooh...great,
great grandma Shy!
What hides behind
the golden fan,
the hand does sweetly hold
a trove of cosmic secrets
that never will be told.
( whispering )
Don't be shy!
You can tell me.
Right, Chauncey?
Chauncey?
Noo! No, no, no!
Get a hold of yourself,
Chauncey!
( Chauncey grunts )
Solaria the Monster Carver.
( gasps in awe )
A castle stormed
is a hero born
with might as strong as steel.
Kneels the void before her
and the crushing force
she wields.
( bleating loudly )
Chauncey, come back!
( hisses softly )
( gasps ) Oh.
Eclipsa, Queen of Mewni
to a Mewmen King was wed.
( inhales sharply )
But took a monster
for her love
and away from Mewni fled.
( shudders )
Bad girl...
( grunting )
What is it, boy?
What'd you find?
( bleating loudly )
Aww, that's you, isn't it?
Before you died.
( gasps )
that means this
is Mom's tapestry!
Get off!
( bleats )
The immortal monster
will long be haunted
by the darkest spell
of Moon the Undaunted.
My mom fought Toffee?
( squeaking )
( clattering )
( effort grunting )
( gasps )
( heavy breathing )
Glossaryck! You're back!
Oh! Do you have any idea
how difficult that was?
Sorry. Moody.
No, no.
( exhales ) It's fine.
And-and did you find
the thing that doesn't belong?
Well, I found Marco's hoodie,
and my dad's chair.
And Lil' Chauncey over there.
( growls and squeals )
( loud ripping )
But all these things...
belong in my memories.
Listen to me.
Did you see yourself?
Uh-huh...
All right. That's not good.
That's not good.
We gotta get out of here.
Step into my eyeball.
I-- Yes.
That's what I said.
Come on. Hop in.
Wait! But I--
I didn't fix my wand!
( rip )
( gasps in astonishment )
That's the thing
that doesn't belong!
( Stars echoing )
That's the thing
that doesn't belong!
Star! We've gotta go now.
Get into my eye.
All right, that's it!
( Glossaryck shouts )
( pop )
( squish )
( squelch )
Oh! Boy, that hurt.
( pop )
Ugh...
Pupil juice.
( gasps )
Glossaryck.
What?
I think we did it.
Yeah. That's kinda gross.
Let's get rid of it.
Uh... That's not exactly
what I meant.
You know what? ( sighs )
I think my mom was right.
I'm not tall enough
to go on this ride.
to go on any ride.
But I've been on them all.
Your, uh...
Your eyeball...
is uh... ( softly )
falling out a little bit.
Oh, thanks. Thank you.
Let me just, uh...
( laughs )
You gonna test out that wand?
I think I've had
enough magic for one day.
Hey!
Have you seen my hoodie?
( screams and grunts )
( groans in pain )
It worked!
This is the best
makeover ever!
This princess looks fly-ayy
and she's ready to partay!
Ladies!
What's up with your lips?
Don't be hate'n 'cause
we look good and you don't!
What are you talking about?
I look all right.
Marco! Why don't you
tell Ponyhead what we got her?
Uhh... we got you
something special for
your first friendship--
( singsong )
Friendship Thursday!
Hook a girl up already!
It's a friendship snuggly!
Uh... great.
Thanks, guys...
But how are we
gonna dance in this?
We're not going dancing, silly!
Excuse me, what?
( phone rings )
Fifteen minutes
to show time!
I'm gonna go get the pizza.
( whining )
Pizza?
Yeah!
You can't watch
"Fiesta de la Noche"
without pizza!
Fist full of what the what?
It's this awesome telanovela
about three friends
that go out every night
and have all sorts of fun!
Uh... ( chuckles )
Okay, yeah.
We're just gonna
sit on the couch
and watch other people party
on that rectangle box thing.
( laughs )
Okay. Go on.
( giggles )
Oh, yeah, baby!
That's what
Friendship Thursday
( softly )
is all about.
( spits )
Uh... I have to go
to the bathroom.
Hey, hey!
Looking good, Marco!
Thanks, Mr. Vendrosian!
You're lookin' good yourself!
Hey, Marco!
My watch stopped.
Can you tell me
what day it is?
You know what day it is.
Friendship Thursday!
Um...
Uh, actually,
it's my birthday.
I thought you knew.
Poneyhead...
Please go back to the house.
( annoyed )
Huh...
Alright, I'm gonna
squeeze past you here.
Sorry.
( whispering ) Weirdo.
Ponyhead...
What are you doing?
Come on!
I want to see some
Earthian night life!
I'm just picking up the pizza
and getting it back
before the show starts.
Let's go.
No.
( whining loudly )
Please!
No!
( screaming )
Please!
( singsong whining )
( groans audibly )
Okay, fine!
You can come.
Yeah!
Woohoo!
Just none of that Poneyhead
stuff you always do.
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Just promise
we're gonna go get the pizza
and nothing else.
( Ponyhead sighs )
( groaning )
Fine!
I pinky promise.
( gagging loudly )
( coughs )
I'm not touching that.
So, what's this pizza thing
you guys keep talking about?
Whoa-a-a-a Nelliee!
Did you just call
Emilio's Pizza "a thing"?
Uh... I guess.
Emilio's Pizza
is not a thing.
His family has been
making pizza forever.
His recipes goes back
to a time before pizza
even existed.
Oh, my gogo!
Look at those skinny jeans!
Those are some
skinny-skinny jeans.
Like very skinny.
What are you doing?
Okay, come on!
Let me just go in
and get a pair.
It'll just take a second.
You promised.
No distrac--
( bell dings )
Really?
Check me out, Marco!
Excuse me!
Are those skinny jeans?
Why, yes, they are.
No way!
I'm wearing skinny jeans!
( electronic music playing )
( Skinny Jeans gang partying )
( all cheering and hooting )
MARCO: Poneyhead!
Hey, Ponyhead!
The pizza! Remember?
( sirens screech )
Everybody freeze!
I'm shutting this party down.
Till we get
Little Red Riding Hood there
into a pair of skinny jeans!
( pants squeaking )
( Marco grunting )
When you promised
we'd just get the pizza!
How does that fit into this?
Oh, shut up, baby girl.
You know you look good.
Check it out, Marco.
I got us a cab.
Oh. Great.
Uh, we're going
to Emilio's pizza.
( nervous exhale )
Just take the car.
Don't hurt me!
I don't think this is a taxi.
Oh, don't blame me!
It's not my fault that
people like to give me stuff!
What did you--
( tires screech )
( cars honking loudly )
Okay, Marco,
tell me how to get there!
Pony! You need
to stop this car right now!
Come on. Just tell me
and I'll drive us there!
Stop the car.
Tell me how to get there.
But tell me
how to get there.
Stop the car.
Tell me how to--
( Marco screams )
Gah!
( panicked breathing )
I-uh-- I --
( screams )
Uh... Okay.
What are you doing?
We just stole this thing!
I have to get rid
of the evidence.
( panicking )
We gotta get as far away
from this as possible.
And then report it
to the police.
( crash )
MARCO: ( crying )
No! No, no, no, no!
( shrieks )
( metal crunching )
( strangled scream )
Aww, it's so compact.
( sobbing )
I'm totally going to jail!
You're not
going to jail, Marco!
PONYHEAD:
Go home to daddy, baby!
( honking )
( engine rumbles )
Okay, let's go
get us another car!
How about you stop doing
all that Ponyhead business
we talked about...
and let me get us there?
Fine.
Hey, up there!
How much for a ride
to Emilio's Pizza?
Uh... $650?
( sighs )
Okay...
( engine rumbles )
Okay, okay...
( inhales )
Everything's still in order.
( breathing heavily )
We're here...
Keep it cool--
Oh, my gogo!
It smells like
tomatoes and cologne.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
You can't just saunter
in there with your... sass.
This is Emilio's.
( stressing )
Emilio's!
For once today just...
let me handle this.
Let me handle this.
( bell dings )
Just sit here...
or float here
in the corner.
Don't say a word.
( singing )
Hey, Marco!
Hey, Emilio!
( both singing )
Good to see you, kid.
Here you go, Bubba.
( excited exhale )
May I?
Go ahead.
After it's left my oven...
it's not my baby.
( excitedly mumbling )
Huh...
Everything okay?
Uh, yeah.
Everything's great.
Well... ( sighs )
Are you sure?
You made that--
You know th-that face
I've never seen you make.
No, no.
It's-it's nothing.
I'll just, uh...
live with it.
Oh. Okay.
( sighs heavily )
Actually...
The thing is...
it's the mushrooms.
There aren't
as many mushrooms
as they usually are.
Not as many mushrooms?
Let me see...
It's-it's totally-
it's not a big deal at all.
Okay.
One...
Two...
No.
Three...
No, don't.
Don't count.
Four... Five...
Please don't count.
Six... seven... eight...
Okay, stop. Stop counting.
Ninety-one,
ninety-two, ninety three...
Let's not play
the number game, you know?
Ninety-four,
ninety-five, ninety-six...
( sighs )
Ninety-seven!
Ninety-eight...
Huh, yeah.
You're right, Marco.
Usually I put...
Put a hundred mushrooms
on a pizza, but there's--
There's only ninety-nine here.
All this time I thought
I was making good pizza.
( squelch )
( trash can rattles )
Uhh, President
of the United States liked it!
The Nobel Peace Prize liked it.
None of that matters...
because it wasn't good enough
( menacingly )
for Marco Diaz.
Well, don't beat
yourself up about it.
N-n-nobody's perfect.
( phone rings )
Emilio's Pizza.
I-I-I-- Let me just
stop you right there.
I cannot take your order.
( muffled talking over phone )
Well! Because I cannot make
a perfect pizza!
( muffled talking over phone )
Oh, well, thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
I appreciate that.
( muffled talking over phone )
I think it's very good myself,
but perfection
is a very high bar.
So, as of right now, I quit!
( muffled talking over phone )
Goodbye, and have a nice life.
( over phone )
Why are you yelling at me?
I am not yelling, sir!
No, no. You are yelling.
Lower your voice!
Not a word.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
You know,
this is all your fault.
With all your Ponyhead stuff.
Ooh, excuse me?
I knew Friendship Thursday
wasn't your thing!
TV and pizza
sounds boring to you.
But it's what Star and I
like to do on Thursdays!
Okay! Well, why did you
even invite me then? ( scoffs )
I didn't invite you!
When you're around,
everything goes bad!
Why don't you just say it then?
Fine! There's no room
for the three of us
in this friend--
( bell dings )
Is Emilio here?
He's gone.
Indefinitely.
Oh, okay.
Do you know why I like pizza?
No one cares.
There's something else
going on.
It's divided
into equal portions
so everybody gets
the same amount.
And, it's got no sharp edges
to stab someone with.
Because it's round.
Like the circle of friendship.
And I like the cwust!
Truce?
Truce!
How do you feel
about making a pizza
with a hundred mushrooms?
Oh, yeah, Boy!
( people cheering )
Uh... guys?
( Both snoring )
( softly )
Emilio's...
( gags )
( spits )
Way too many mushrooms.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me ♪
♪ It's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna
stay a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪