♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puuuhh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Perfect Princess Moon ♪
♪ She's great in every way ♪
♪ Everything she says and does
is absolutely right ♪
♪ Her hair is silky soft ♪
♪ Her favorite color's pink ♪
♪ She flosses every day
and she never needs to sleep! ♪
♪ The perfect Princess Moon
She's nice in every way ♪
♪ Always in a sunny mood
Even on the cloudy days. ♪
♪ Her sugar-coated
heart of gold ♪
Will make everything fine ♪
♪ She plays with puppies
and kisses kitty-cats ♪
♪ Eats her veggies and
Smells like lavender ♪
♪ Perfect Princess Moon ♪
♪ She's a fan of smiles ♪
♪  Perfect Princess Moon
♪ Will be our
Que-ee-e-e-e-een! ♪
Ugghh! Mom!
Worst. Song. Ever.
Do I have to have
one of those written
about me?
Yes, Star. It's a tradition
as old as the kingdom itself.
And it's your official
introduction as Future Queen
to the people of Mewni.
That song didn't say anything
about the real you.
You could plug any name
into that song
and it wouldn't make
a lick of difference.
How about Buttercup!
Sparkle! Snowflake!
They all happen to love puppies
and smell like lavender? Wow.
I don't have time for this,
Star.
Preparations for
your Song Day celebration
are already underway,
and the new official
Songstrel of Mewni
is heading to Earth
to write your song
as we speak.
Hmmmmm.. fine.
And remember, Star,
the people of Mewni
like their Princess Songs
light and fluffy.
Can you handle that?
Yes, Mom.
Oh, I can handle it--
by avoiding this problem
until it goes away.
( laser puppies
"barking" )
Moon, please. If I can't
talk you out of going,
at least take a bunch
of our knights with you!
I told you, River,
this has to stay low-key,
under the radar.
Besides,
I've been there before.
It's perfectly safe.
The Forest of Certain Death
is not safe!
And likely nothing on Mewni
is as safe as it used to be.
I promise you,
I can handle myself.
( smooch )
Hold down the castle
until I return.
Can't you just take
one little night?
(echoing) At least call me
when you get there!
( whoosh )
( doorbell rings )
Haha. The Songstrel.
Greetings, Princess Star!
I am Ruberiot.
♪ And may I just say ♪
♪ Though we have much to do ♪
♪ How much of a pleasure
it is to meet you ♪
♪ How great-- ♪
Stop. I get it.
Come in.
So, this shouldn't
take too long.
I just want to get to know
the real Star.
Oh, how rude of me!
Ha ha ha!
I didn't even
offer you anything.
What can I get you?
Water? Juice? Tea?
Ha. Well,
if you have mint tea,
that might be--
As a matter of fact, we do!
Marco is a member
of the Tea of the Month Club,
and I think we just got
some super-special mint tea.
Right, Marco?
Don't move!
Tea of the Month Club?
( thwack )
( clatter )
Should be just a minute!
( clank )
( clatter continues )
♪♪
( playing blue licks )
( penguin tittering )
Ooh, this tea is real good!
( blender whining )
Hey, Star!
Cloudy! Let's get out of here.
Hey, Janna Banana,
want to go to the mall?
( ominous, droning sounds )
( whinnies )
Easy, girl. Almost there.
MALE VOICE:
What is it?
Hello, Lord Brudo.
Huh? Queen Moon. Hmph.
What do you want?
I need to speak with you.
It's very important.
(grumbles)
Step back.
( unlocking door )
Hmm.
Ahem. You--you coming here
to what?
Eh, you're--you're
blocking the door.
I'll move. Geez.
( clangs )
Not even gonna pick up
a guy's crown for him.
(grumbling) My dear,
we have company.
You may want to get dressed.
Oh, Queen Moon!
To what do we owe the,
uh, honor of this visit?
I'm sorry to intrude.
Please accept this
bag of corn.
BRUDO: Corn?!
We don't need corn!
We're doing great, thanks!
But perhaps we can find
someone else who could use it!
So, what brings you here,
Queen Moon?
I'm here because your son
took a very important book
from my family.
My son? Which one?
Crudo?
Uh, no.
Not Yudo!
Hunh-uh.
Menudo?
Uh, nope.
Ugh. Okay, I'm just gonna
go down the list.
Dudo, Kudo, Mudo, Tudo,
Fudo, Zudo, Udo...
I have no idea who that is.
Not Dennis!
No, no, it's...it's Ludo.
(gasps) Ludo?!
Well, we don't say that name
in this house anymore!
Not since he and his goons
took over our castle
and changed the locks
when we were on vacation!
Not that this place
isn't lovely...
Do you know
where he is now?
We don't.
You know, he is
a grave disappointment to us.
BRUDO:
Well, what do you expect?!
We had a lot of kids.
Ludo was the runt.
He didn't even fit
in our family portrait.
We were extra hard on him
to toughen him up.
And look what happened!
Was he grateful? No!
Instead, he destroyed
our ancestral home
and brought shame
on the family name.
There, there.
We can't always control
the path our children
choose to take.
Thank you,
Lord and Lady Avarius.
If you hear from Ludo,
please let me know.
SONGSTREL:
♪ Where is Princess Star? ♪
♪ Has she traveled far? ♪
♪ I am very musically skilled ♪
♪ But if I don't write this
I'll surely be ki-- ♪
( door opens )
Hey!
BOTH:
You're back!
You're still here!
Well, good-bye.
Please! Princess!
I have a job to do,
and I can't leave
until it's done.
And I won't stay
until you're gone.
But...what about your
Song Day celebration?
In just a day,
the people of Mewni
will be expecting us
to perform this traditional
Princess Song--
Ah-ah-ah!
I don't want to hear it,
Songstrel.
If you don't leave right now,
maybe I'll leave for good.
Hey, Star!
Before you leave us alone
again--
for a very long time
with no explanation--
could you help me make some
more popcorn in the kitchen?
Kit-chen!
Please. Just do what he says.
He's been singing at me
for eight hours,
asking where you are!
Well, I'm sorry,
but I don't want
anything to do with Ruberiot
and his stupid Princess Songs.
My mom's was so stupid
and so fake and so
old-fashioned--
it's just not me.
It's okay, Star.
Everyone knows you're
anything but ordinary.
Aww. Thanks, Marco.
Huuuugs.
He's, uh--
he's staring at us,
isn't he?
Yup.
Ugghh! Fine.
Ru-ber-i-ot,
if that even is
your real name--
You. Me. My room. Talk time.
( rustling )
I know you're there.
Come on out, if you know
what's good for you.
What do you want?
It's me. Dennis.
You were just at my house.
Why are you following me?
Are you looking for
my big brother because
you want to help him?
Help him what?
He's not well.
Do you know where he is?
I can take you to him.
Oh, uh-- What is this?
We must go by wing, M'lady.
Oh.
All right, then,
well, let me just--
hold on--
( gasping )
He's over there.
( angry squawking )
What is that?
( gasps )
What is it?
We have to go.
We have to go now.
It's an honor to be
your official songstrel,
Your Highness.
I have some really
exciting ideas
that I can't wait
to get your opinion on.
Ruby, just stop.
Please. I know
my mom sent you here,
but honestly, I am sorry,
I can't help you.
Princess Songs
are objectively awful.
They are these
trite little puff pieces
about perfect little princesses
with perfect little eyes,
and that's not me!
And songstrels like you
are part of the problem!
Your music just puts pressure
on future princesses
to be perfect!
So you might as well
take your stupid notebook
and your stupid lute
and go back to Mewni,
because I have no interest
in helping some stupid hack
write a stupid Princess Song!
Oh, really?
Yeah, really!
Fine. But for what it's worth,
I also think the songstrels
before me were hacks.
You didn't think
I had an opinion?
That maybe I had
some integrity?
I wanted to write a real song
about a real princess,
with all her gifts and flaws.
Don't Mewmans deserve to know
their future queen?
(choking up)
But you won't even
help me do my job!
(sniffling) I might as well
just take your mom's song
and just plug your name in
and be done with it!
You know, like
some kind of hack?
Wait! Ah, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Ruby!
( whinnies )
DENNIS:
So, can you help him?
I'll...I'll do what I can.
RUBERIOT:
♪ Perfect Princess Star ♪
♪ Is great in every way ♪
Hmm.
♪ Perfect Princess Star's is-- ♪
Argggh!
It's so awful!
( discordant note clusters )
♪ Stupid, stupid song ♪
♪ Why do I even try? ♪
Face it, Ruberiot.
You are a hack
like all the rest.
You'll never amount to anything!
Whoa. So you're, like,
a totally tortured artist.
Cool!
That is a lot of paper
just to plug a name
into a previously existing song.
What do you want?!
You, uh, you forgot
your stupid notebook.
Ruberiot, do you really hate
Princess Songs as much as I do?
I do, Princess.
I thought I could change them.
I-I know they can be better.
I can do better.
But the show is tomorrow,
and I have nothing.
If I go out there
with your mom's old song,
I'll be just as bad
as all the others.
Arrgh, this is bad.
Why did I drop out
of lawstrel school?
Good-bye, aspirations,
hello, flipping cornburgers.
Ruberiot, nothing is that bad
when you have a magic wand.
How about you and I
turn this silly tradition
into something real?
Oh, darling! You're back!
You're wearing that
to Star's Song Day?
(gasps) Song Day.
( music, conversation )
Get your corn slaw here!
We got corndogs, kettle corn,
bacon-wrapped corn...
Get your exclusive
Star Butterfly merch here!
( King panting )
(sighs) Whew.
Okay. We made it.
Oh, you lost one of
your curlybadoos, dear.
STAR: Hey, everyone!
Mom, hi!
Hey, Queen.
Oh, my gosh, I had the worst
wardrobe malfunction.
Do you know how hard it is
to find a decent shoulder tassel
in an Earth mall?
Oh. Hey. You got
a little thingy
in your hair.
A what?
A little thingy-thing.
Oh. Thank you, dear.
How'd that get there?
Star, I want to
tell you something.
I know it's not very
princess-like to show up late,
but did you see traffic
on the Royal Mile?
Please,
let me finish.
I just want to say how--
how proud I am of you.
What?
I know Princess Songs
aren't exactly your cup of tea,
and I know I can be...
hard on your sometimes,
so it means a lot to me that
you still went through with it.
Thanks, Mom, but, uh...
just so you know,
Ruby and me,
we kinda changed some stuff.
I mean, it's just not
gonna sound exactly like
your Princess Song did.
So, you know, don't freak out
or anything.
Thank you for telling me,
Star,
but I trust your judgment.
Oh, thank you!
But we really went off-script.
It's all good,
but there might be, like--
EMCEE: And now, Mewni's
newest court composer,
the songstrel Ruberiot...
...in honor of
the Royal Family...
I really hope you like it.
I think I know you will,
but I really hope you do.
...presents Star Butterfly's
Princess Song!
♪♪
♪ Who is the maid
with the buttercup hair? ♪
♪ Who sleeps on moonbeams
and dances on air ♪
♪ With tears made of honey
and a heart full of bunnies ♪
♪ Whose infinite virtues
are known near and far ♪
♪ It's Mewni's own sweetheart,
our dear Princess Star ♪
( lute continues )
♪ And under the shimmer
and rubies and pearls ♪
♪ Lies hidden a fierce
and adventurous girl ♪
♪ The forces of evil
that lurk in the night ♪
♪ Will cower in fear
when this shooting Star... ♪
♪ Ignites!!! ♪
( all gasp )
♪ ( propulsive rock beat ) ♪
♪ Weaving magic
like a born spell-caster ♪
♪ And wreaking havoc
like a natural disaster ♪
♪ She rocks her Narwal Blast ♪
♪ And Warnicorn stampede ♪
♪ She's gonna earn her crown ♪
♪ So hail to
the Que-e-e-e-e-en! ♪
( fireworks explode )
( all cheering )
♪ She's a rebel Princess,
she's the best ♪
♪ She's a bolt of lightning
in a hot pink dress ♪
♪ She's a thunderstorm
roaring through the night ♪
♪ She's a shooting star ♪
♪ And she's lighting up
the sky ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
Yeah! That's my girl!
What a delightful
little ditty!
Good job, Star!
Uh, right. It's not over yet.
( slow, heavy beat ♪
♪ Shooting Star
shining in the night so bright ♪
♪ She started to attract
a pair of envious eyes ♪
♪ The villain rose up
from behind the jester's cross ♪
♪ She drove him away, but didn't
know what she had lost ♪
♪ Glossaryck
and her book of spells ♪
♪ How could she know Ludo
would take 'em for himself? ♪
♪ She confessed to her parents,
all full of dread ♪
♪ The King and Queen
exchanged a look
♪ And this is what they said ♪
♪ This is what they said,
this is what they said ♪
♪ We will keep your silence
for you ♪
♪ From the citizens of Mewni
and the High Commission too ♪
♪ To keep the peace
we will play the game ♪
♪ Royal secret
from Royal shame ♪
♪ Royal secret... ♪
Star?
(Star makes choking noises)
Star.
Mom, what did you expect?
I told you
I couldn't do some puff piece.
I had to do
what felt right for me.
Look, it's over now,
so we just gotta move on--
Oooh. What?
♪ Royal secret --
one last to tell -- ♪
♪ A princess
under true love's spell ♪
( gasps )
Wait, is that me?!
Unhh. Ruberiot never told me
about this part!
♪ Who is the boy
in the Earthly attire? ♪
♪ The Prince of the Princess's
deepest desire ♪
♪ I don't need to show it,
I think we all know it ♪
♪ But just to be certain
I'll say it again ♪
♪ Star Butterfly is in love
with her best friend ♪
♪ And his name is Marco Diaz. ♪
Oh, no.
♪ Forever... ♪
♪ ...more! ♪
( panting )
( confused chatter )
What's wrong?
You're supposed
to be clapping!
Say what?!
The Queen lied to us!
Well, technically,
it was a lie by omission.
Omitters!
Boo!
( angry yelling )
( crowd booing )
(angry yelling)
Mom! I---
I didn't realize
this would happen!
I thought they wanted to know
the real Star Butterfly!
They don't, Star.
They just want to believe
that you're a perfect
little Princess.
And sometimes,
the truth is dangerous.
HEKAPOO:
With all due respect, Moon,
withholding information
about Glossaryck
and the spell book
has put us all in danger!
( bleating )
Uh, yeah!
Like the goat said!
I assure you,
I had every intention--
Every intention of what?!
I had everything under control!
How dare you hide
something like that?!
QUEEN: I wasn't trying
to hide anything!
( argument continues )
Uh...so--
Hold that thought,
Marco.
Hey, Star!
Hey, Cloudy.
Let's, uh, get out of here.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something,
cuz I been through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna
stay a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪