♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( blowing fanfare )
Ladies and gentlemen
of the Butterfly-Johansen
annual picnic,
lunch is served.
( cheering )
Food!
You know, Lord Wildrew
is still single.
Never too late
to start over, dearie.
Yes, Aunt Etheria,
I heard you the first
hundred times.
May I present
the first course?
Check out this big girl
sitting at the grown-up table!
I'm too old to be sitting
at this stupid kids' table.
It's not stupid.
We get all the Mewni
corn we want.
It's so good.
My man here knows
what I'm talking about.
Right, hungry buddy?
I mean, really,
sippy goblets.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's the big deal?
All the fun is happening
over there.
( slurping loudly )
Oh, it's starting to happen.
What's starting
to happen?
Grown-up stuff.
( all talking at once )
There's no need for
any of this, I just want--
You Johansens
spoiled my appetite
like you've spoiled
the Butterfly family tree.
Let's put a stop to this.
Tut-tut.
Your neck ruffles are choking
off the oxygen to your brain.
- River!
- You... oh!
Yes, of course, of course.
( clears throat )
Now, now.
There's no need for
all this back and forth
about who's better
than who.
We're all royalty,
as you know.
There is a way we can
settle this petty dispute
like the civilized
people we are.
With flags!!
Flag!
Oh, dear.
It's about time.
I've been thinking
about this all year.
Come on, Marco.
Let's play.
All we have to do
is be the first
to get this flag
up there.
Oh, like
king of the hill.
I rock at that game.
Not that hill.
- That hill.
- Oh.
And the winner gets to
look down on everyone else
for a whole year.
I am so ready for this.
- No way.
- Hey. That's my flag.
You can have it back
after the match.
but you won't be
playing Flags today.
Why not? You played Flags
when you were my age.
- I did a lot of things
you won't be doing.
- ( groans )
I know it's boring to be
the oldest at the kids' table,
but you're not ready
to be the youngest
at the adults' table.
Now go and help your little
cousins chew their corn.
I'll show her.
I can play this game,
and I will win.
Come on, Marco.
You're on Team Star.
But you heard your mom.
We're supposed to stay
at the kids' table.
Don't you worry.
We'll be sitting at
the kids' table.
The game will commence
when all participants
are at the ready.
So if both sides of
your family are playing
against each other,
whose side are we on?
Duh. Our side.
Here's to another
spirited game of Flags.
Let us not have a repeat
of last year's unfortunateness.
What happened
last year?
Just before he
reached the peak,
Uncle Lump
got his body cut off.
- What?!
- Relax. He's fine.
He's right over there.
Neigh, neigh.
I think he likes it
better this way.
Ready, set...
flags.
Here we go, Marco.
And both families
are at the course.
The Johansens take
an early lead,
but the Butterflies
are making up the slack.
That's my girl.
Star, little help.
Oh, here, my dear boy.
Allow me to assist you.
- Hey, thanks.
- Marco, no!
By my troth, you must surely
ate it on that one.
Smooch my royal
hindquarters.
- Toodles!
- Nice takedown,
Uncle Heartrude.
- Let go!
- You good?
Why did you congratulate him?
He pulled me down.
That's Flags.
That's how you play.
We gotta keep moving.
Prithee, may I accept
some assistance?
Dream on,
Uncle Jerkface.
Whoa sakes. I have
not the choice
but to
gnaw off my own fibula.
We're going into
the rain zone.
( thunder rumbling )
Oh, no.
I can do king of the hill,
I can not do wet socks.
Flags doesn't care
what you like.
We gotta keep moving.
Out of the way,
old lady.
- Wait a minute.
- Eyes on the prize, Marco.
( laughing )
Star, we gotta
go back.
We are never
going back.
I think your family's really
trying to hurt each other.
Yeah. Isn't it awesome?
Not again, not again,
not again.
And there's the repeat
of last year.
Adieu, Uncle Lump.
Who shall take the hill?
I am beside myself
with anticipation.
Star.
Look at my girl,
all grown up
and playing Flags.
You make me so proud.
Aw, Dad, you're so sweet.
Great job, honey.
You just threw your...
You got me.
( muttering indistinctly )
You just threw your dad
down a mountain.
Haven't you figured
it out yet?
You don't waste time
on anybody.
Keep up.
And the herd of participants
is being further culled.
There is now only a handful
vying for the top of the hill.
So dreadfully exciting.
Lady Etheria and Lord Grunt
lead the pack
with a late appearance from...
oh, my.
The Princess Star Butterfly.
What?
Star?
You've been a stone in
my poulaines for too long,
my incorrigible little niece!
You're about to
abdicate the throne!
What is she doing?
Marco, come on.
Star, this game
is changing you.
It's not about
who versus who
or rivalries
or whatever.
It's about winning
no matter what.
And that's just
not you.
Eat this.
Let's just go back
down the hill.
Star.
She's got our flags.
Get her!
Get our flags.
Give me flag.
Give it to me!
Mom?
- Are you all right?
- Oh, man, Mom,
those are
some sweet magic moves
with your big old wings
and stuff.
Star, you're never
going to believe,
but I just met
your twin sister.
She was made
out of corn.
I don't even remember
giving birth to her.
River, did I ever give birth
to a corn baby?
No. I'm afraid
we just have the one
child, my dear.
Thank you, River.
The name is Star.
Okay. Why don't you
just lay back down?
Thank you.
You see what Flags
does to your brain?
I'm sorry I tried to
trick you with my corn twin.
And maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm not
ready for Flags.
But maybe the real problem
is that Flags is dumb.
I found her.
Star Butterfly.
Our only child,
my dear.
Okay.
Hungry.
I was trying to bring
all these flags
to the top of the hill.
Not so that I could
win the hill for myself,
but to claim the hill
for all of us!
( cheering )
Who wants food?
That's the most adult
thing I've heard all day.
I misjudged you, Star.
You earned a rightful seat
at the grown-up table.
Hug!
Star, public displays
of affection
aren't a Butterfly virtue.
The Johansens,
on the other hand,
are amazing at it.
You are the perfect blend
of both sides of the family.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks, Mom.
Only an idiot would wanna
win this game.
Whoo hoo!
I'm the winner.
King of the hill.
In your face.
Uh-uh-uh.
Now, when you carry
the four,
let V be the finite
dimensional vector
space over K.
Where we're
solving for K...
( loud sigh )
( Skullnick continues )
'Sup?
For cosine localized
algebra, we write K.
Blaah!
( teacher continues
in monotone )
Okay.
Fly free, little Marisol!
- ( yells )
- Oh, no.
Be free!
Why did you do that?
Because she was bored!
We're all bored!
She's bored, he's bored,
he's bored, Marco's
definitely bored.
Don't drag me
into this.
Bored out of his mind.
That's it.
- Detention.
- For that?
Marco, go get my hamster.
Viva Marisol!
Oof!
( growls )
Sit in there and think
about what you did, hooligan.
'Sup, Star?
Welcome to D-ten.
Looks like you're
one of us now.
Math cage, hamster cage,
detention cage.
You guys can stay
in here if you want,
but I won't be caged.
I'm outta here.
Oh, yeah, that's cool.
I mean, you were elected
mayor of detention,
- but whatever.
It's no big deal.
- What?
Yeah. It says so right here
on this thing.
This paper...
piece of paper.
But I just got here.
No, no, I get it.
It's cool.
The mayor has
more important things to do.
Uh, hey, everybody,
can I have your attention?
Listen up.
I have some bad news.
The mayor is busy and won't
be able to help us today,
so I guess we'll just
go back to our previous
system of anarchy.
( glass shatters )
Let me see that.
Hey. This is fake.
Every election is fake.
What does the mayor
of detention even do?
Well, the townspeople have
a list of requests.
And the mayor, you,
fulfill them.
Let's get this over with.
Candy.
Tattoo.
And comb.
Well, looks like
my work here is done.
See you, guys.
Won't be needing this anymore.
( crying )
What's up with Waterworks
over there?
Oh, that's Toby.
Yeah, but why is he crying?
Oh, he's just bummed
'cause he didn't get
his request in on time.
- Not your problem.
- Ugh. Okay.
Fine. One last thing,
but then I'm gone.
Toby, what's your request?
Well, usually,
we all gather around
this little window like so,
and we watch wrestling
on the TV across the hall.
I can control it
with this stolen remote.
Except the batteries
are dead.
Worst timing ever.
The Junior Mustache
is fighting the Sterling
Stallion at 4:00 p.m.
So where we gonna get
fresh batteries, Miss Mayor?
Hmmm.
- ( music playing )
- ( gasps )
That's it. Oskar's
keytar uses batteries.
I like your style.
Come out, Marisol.
- Here, baby.
- ( squeaking )
Fine. I'm comin' in.
Aw, come on.
Huh?
Oh, hey, Jackie.
Do you need some help?
Just hangin' out.
I drew up a plan.
We'll cross the field
to the parking lot,
but we have to get back
by 1:00 p.m. sharp.
That's when Skullnick
checks in every day
for roll call.
The school ground's
a harsh, unforgiving landscape
not to be taken lightly.
( yelling )
First, we gotta get past
the fall hall.
Next, we must blend in
with band practice.
And lastly,
Miss Skullnick.
I got it.
Shimmering destructo cannon.
How about we call that
Plan B?
I was thinking we could
just scare her away
with this.
Potato chips!
I don't get it.
Not chips.
This.
Aw, he's so cute.
( chewing loudly )
Oh, when did I pack you?
Sour cream and ham flavored?
My favorite.
Oooh, I better not.
Oh, but what could
one chip hurt?
Who are you kidding,
Margaret?
You wouldn't just
stop at one.
But you have been doing
your water aerobics every day,
so you deserve this.
What's going on here?
( kids chattering,
cameras clicking )
They better not be having
fun on school grounds.
Don't worry. I have him
pretty much wrapped
around my finger.
Let me do the talking.
Hey there, Oskar.
We'd like to borrow your...
( Star shuddering )
Uh, Madame Mayor.
Batteries.
( stammering )
Mayor. Star!
Ugh, forget it.
Hey, Oskar, can we borrow
your keytar batteries
to watch wrestling?
There is no cause worthier
than the wrestling arts.
Great. I'll just take
those batteries then.
No, you can't have these.
I gotta keep jammin'.
But I have a spare set
of batteries in the trunk.
Somewhere in one of these.
Batteries!
Nailed it.
I hope you didn't hurt
my sweet Marisol.
No, I'm fine, thanks.
Where's the stuck kid?
- Ahem.
- It's probably him.
Don't worry, little fella.
We'll get you out in no time.
Wait. Wait, wait!
Is this safe?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
- All free.
- Finally!
Whoo, I don't have to look
like an idiot anymore...
Marisol!
My little Marisol.
( smooching )
It's almost time to
check on the degenerates.
You wanna check on
the degenerates, Marisol?
Yes, you do,
yes, you do.
OSKAR: Oh, yeah, this bad boy
is one of my favorites.
I got it near that library
that serves the best tacos.
That is such a great story.
( phone buzzing )
- Mayor Butterfly,
it's almost 1:00.
- Ah!
No, not this one.
- No.
- Zilch.
- Nope.
- Aha!
Thanks, Oskar.
No problem.
( making keytar sounds )
Get in.
Porcupine beast
transformation!
GIRL: Those girls are
so weird.
Oh, my little Marisol.
That cloud
looks like a tree.
And that one looks
like... aaah!
Oh, yeah, that one
does look like an aaaah!
( kids screaming )
( laughing )
Skullnick.
- Star.
- Radiant rainbow bridge!
STAR: Made it.
Oh, you must be
so hungry.
Aren't you? How about
something to eat, huh?
( anguished shriek )
Has anyone seen
my Marisol?
Oh, you mean this Marisol?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Does this mean
we can leave detention?
No!
ANNOUNCER:  This has been one
exciting Wrestle Rama,
ladies and gentlemen.
Looks like Junior Mustache
is getting ready
to pull off his
Boom Boom of Doom.
Oh! That looks like it hurt.
One, two, three...
ANNOUNCER: And he's out.
Well, duties fulfilled.
You are free to go.
Why, thank you.
You, too.
Get him, get him!
ANNOUNCER:  This has been
one exciting match, folks.
You know you don't have to
wear that badge anymore, right?
I know, but if I take it off,
we wouldn't be matching!
- Rip his head off!
- Tear him apart!
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪