♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Mom, don't tell me
what to do ♪
♪ I don't have to
listen to you ♪
♪ I don't have
to follow your rules ♪
♪ I'm gonna live in my car
at the school, hey hey ♪
♪ ( keyboard solo ) ♪
( school bell rings )
Star!
Time to go.
You got some paint or something.
Right here.
Marco, this is not paint.
Well, looks like
you got another heart.
Quiet, Marco.
This is serious!
I think I'm going through
mewberty.
Waaaahh....
Weeellll, okay.
Uh, mewberty. Heh heh.
That's nothing
to be ashamed of.
We have a similar thing
here on Earth.
Don't confuse this with
your Earth things, Marco!
I'm from Mewni!
(whispers) This is
gonna get really weird.
You gotta keep me
away from boys!
Wait a second--
Marco's a boy.
( nervous chuckle )
When you say things
are gonna get weird,
do you mean typical Star weird
or, like,
destroy-the-school weird?
Destroy-the-school.
That's what I was
worried about.
Let's get you home.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Okay, here comes a boy.
You got this. You got this.
Avert your eyes.
Marco, I don't think
this is such a good ideaaahhh...
Hmm. Huh?
My turn.
Whoa.
Okay, let's go.
BOTH:
Whooooaaahhhh!
I'm stuck.
Um, let me help.
No!
Your little boy hands
are part of the problem!
Isn't there some way
I can help?
Maybe there's something
in your book of spells
that can stop this.
STAR: Maybe.
I'll go home and get it.
It's not at home!
I gave it to Ferguson!
Why?
I lost a bet, okay?
Do you want to help me or not?
Okay, but we gotta talk about
that betting thing later.
( all speaking Spanish )
Ferg.
Ferg!
I need Star's
book of spells.
Lo siento, Señor Marco.
Solo puedo hablarte
en español.
Where is Star's book?
No no no.
Se pronuncia "libro." Libro.
Where is Star's  libro?
Muy bien.
Mi dio el libro
a Janna.
You gave it to Janna?!
Ohh!
De nada.
Ohh. That's better.
( school bell rings )
(gasps) Oh no.
( chatter )
No no no no no no no no no!
( bell rings )
Huh. That wasn't so bad.
MAN: All right, boys,
we're gonna do our warm-up
out here today.
Pool's been compromised.
Poop. It was poop.
Somebody pooped
in the pool.
Okay, let's get to it.
( joints crack )
(shudders) Ohh....
Hey, you guys want to see
a dead possum?
Um, no, thank you.
Um...
(laughs) I'm just
messin' with ya.
Seriously,
check this out.
Tada!
Awesome! What is it?
We can do all  kinds  of
witchy stuff with this thang.
Can we use it to get
my parents to stop fighting?
Totally.
Gimme that!
Let's get outta here!
I've been looking
all over for this!
Now that you found
your little book,
let's make some magic
with it.
I don't need your help, Jenna!
Thank you.
Whatever.
You'll need me soon enough,
Marco,
'cause I got
your house keys.
Arggh. Gotta stay focused.
Mewberty, mewberty, mewberty...
This doesn't
make any sense!
Isn't there a glossary
in this thing?
Did someone say Glossaryck?
Wha?
'Cause that's me.
Sir Glossaryck...
Of Terms.
At your service, milady.
Uh, I'm not a milady.
Coulda fooled me. Goodbye.
No!
This book is not
for the likes of you!
Magical princesses only!
This isn't for me! I'm trying
to find a spell for Star!
Ha ha ha!
Ah, Star Butterfly.
What's wrong with her?
She says she's got mewberty.
I usually don't
make exceptions,
but maybe we can
work something out.
Pudding.
What?!
I want pudding.
Pudding?
Corrrrrrect.
High schools have
excellent pudding.
Pudding.
Ehh...
( music blares on earbuds )
Boy...
( rattling )
( banging )
All right.
Here's your  pudding.
Ahhhh...
What are you doing?
You've got to feed me,
of course.
Pudding doesn't
eat itself.
Ahhh....
Its-- You got it
all stuck in your beard.
( chatter )
Whoa!
( crackling )
Boy...
So...you said Star
is going through...
( burps )....mewberty?
How do I make it stop?
Well, can't stop it.
That's not an option.
It'll be over soon.
Star should be back to normal
by, uh...
three-fifty-seven p.m...
or she won't.
She won't what?
Be back to normal.
That's it?
Th-There's nothing
I can do?
Ahhh...
It's empty.
You ate it all.
Scrape the sides!
Now talk.
Look, kid,
nature is like
a runaway dump truck--
hot, fast, and full of garbage.
What?
Nature cannot be stopped.
That is all.
There has to be more
you can tell me than that!
Ha ha ha ha!
Of course there is.
But then,
you're out of pudding.
BOY: No!!!
Thanks for  nothing.
Uhh.
Whaaaaat?
Hey. You gotta
get us out of here.
( boy whimpering )
Aaaah!
What the...?
Star?
Star, you gotta
get ahold of yourself.
You're scaring everyone.
( whimpering ) Aaah!
I said, stop!
Now she's mad.
( whimpers )
Ow!
( distant music )
♪♪
Oskar.
Oh no.
♪ Why don't you clean
your  room, Mom? ♪
♪ I don't like
your boyfriend, Mom ♪
( all scream )
Whoo.
Whoa!
Whaa!
( screaming )
You're making things worse!
♪♪
( sighs )
Goodbye, Star.
( beeping )
( beeping stops )
Whaaah!
What's up?
Star!
Ohhh...
You came back!
( flapping )
What was that?
Aaaahhh!
Look, Marco!
I got my mewberty wings!
Does that mean
you can fly?
Let's test it out.
Whaa!
Ahhh...
Whee-hee-hee!
Nope.
Another one.
Another one!
Awright, awright, awright.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
call anyone.
MIRROR:  Calling anyone.
( all giggling )
Uh, hello?
Greetings!
I am King Fergon
of Fergustan.
Would you care
for some treasure?
Uh, is this a joke?
Okay, here's my booty!
'Cause I don't really think
you're doing the joke right.
Ferguson, you're supposed
to moon him.
Oh, yeah, right.
I don't have time for this.
( all laughing )
Hilarious!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Making crank calls!
Join the party!
Awesome!
Mirror, mirror,
call someone else!
I'm sorry, but you have
exceeded your minutes.
Your mirror service has been
temporarily suspended.
Please visit our office in
Pixtopia to settle your bill.
Hee hee hee!
Ohh! No!
What if my mom
tries to call me?
She's gonna freak!
Ohh. Sorry, Star.
That's my bad.
The calls were
totally my idea.
Marco, you messed up!
Now you're just like me.
Yeeess.
What? No!
I-I made one mistake.
You sure "Starred"
this whole thing up.
How's it feel?
Not bad, right?
Oh, Marco, now
we can be mess-up twins!
What?! Man,
I ain't no twin!
I'm--I'm--I'm Marco Diaz,
only child.
Where are your scissors?
Let's go pay your bill.
( gasping )
BOTH:
You gotta take us with you!
This dimension is so boring!
Sure!
Yeah!
BOTH:
♪ Going into Portal-land,
teenage boys are holding hands ♪
♪ Messed-up twins
secret handshake ♪
( laughs )
PIXIES: Welcome!
Welcome to Pixtopia.
♪ In Pixtopia
we love everything ♪
♪ With our Pixie hearts
and our Pixie wings ♪
♪ We're friends with
every frog we meet ♪
♪ Even our bathrooms
smell so sweet ♪
Ahh! They're so small!
Here we are!
How you gonna
Star this one up,
Twindy?
I already told you, Star,
I ain't no twin!
Marco Diaz came
into this world alone!
Alone!
( clicks tongue )
Uhh! Uhh! Uhhhh!
PIXIE: Next?
Ow!
Go ahead, Marco.
Pay the nice Pixie.
You guys gonna
pitch in for this?
I have this flat penny
from the state fair?
I have this jawbreaker.
But I sorta had plans for it.
Marco, did you forget
to bring money,
like  I  did?
No, as a matter of fact,
I brought....
♪ Marco's
Emergency Cash Stash ♪
This is for
the Butterfly account.
I think that
should cover it.
And, uh, this is for you.
Go buy yourself some of those
thimble-sized shoes.
I'm sorry, sir.
We only accept gold and jewels.
You'll have to
work off the bill
in the shard mines.
ALL: Shard mines?
( buzzer )
( screaming)
Next?
( screaming )
( all grunt )
Aaaaaah!
Hey, guys.
Wow, Marco, I could not
have Starred that one
better up myself.
Like I was supposed to know
to bring jewels.
Welcome to the shard mines.
Now get to pickin'!
I, uh, I'm sure this was all
just a big misunder--
Wha--whoa!
Jeez!
Now what?
Don't worry, Twindy.
I got this.
Strawberry Annihilation!
( buzzer )
Strawberry--
Straw--
( buzzer )
Ha ha! Nice try, blondie.
These mines block magic.
Okay, you want some of this?
Let's go, little man!
Whoa, easy, Star.
Okay, sir, I'm sure
we can work this out.
See, this is
the Princess of Mewni,
Star Butterfly.
Her dad has connections.
And I'm King Fergon!
Yeah, yeah.
And I'm the Duchess
of Daisyland.
Ooh! Pleased to meet you,
Duchess of Daisyland.
No, the pleasure's all mine,
King Fergon!
Take him away!
Uh-oh. Ahh!  Hey, wait!
Oohhh!
Guys, help!
( Ferguson sobbing )
Empress, this prisoner
was disobedient.
He looks  delicious.
Eh?
Are you a king?
Uh...this is a plunger.
Tell me.
Are you betrothed?
Yes. What is betrothed?
( giggling )
Oh, such wit!
Whoa whoa whoa.
Are you, um...
Are you, like, into me?
Oh, big-time.
Wow. Wow!
All right!
So, ya think you can
let my friends--
( coughing )
Looks like your friend's getting
a bad case of Pixie lung.
This is crazy!
We have to find a way
out of here and save Ferguson!
Sorry, there's no way out,
not that I've seen.
What about that mine cart?
But that's the bathroom.
Like fried eggs.
Come on!
Guards! Seize them!
I've never met anyone
with such beautiful,
soft, excess skin.
( laughing ) Oh, yes!
I try not to move
around too much.
( screaming )
Hey! You should
watch where you're going!
You watch
where  you're  going!
ALL: Uhh!
( all gasp )
( chain saw buzzing )
Hey! I was just about
to come rescue you guys!
Ferguson!
I was so worried!
Yeah, turns out
they worship me here.
And  check out
my new girlfriend.
That's right, I did,
I said "girlfriend."
He calls me Sugar Wings.
( giggles )
I am so happy
you guys are here.
You're just in time
for my wedding!
( Wedding March plays )
Are you two ready
to swear your undying love
for each other?
MARCO: Don't!
This is crazy!
Ferguson, think about this!
You're not ready
for this kind of commitment!
You're only fourteen!
You still paint a face
on your stomach
and make it talk!
He has a point.
Empress, you're an amazing
flying Pixie lady
and you're really cool.
but I didn't really
think this through.
I'm sorry.
I can't marry you.
Hmm.
Guards, kill them all.
Aaaah!
Aayyahh!
Aaaaah!
Fly free, little Ferg!
And I am saving  you
for later.
Yaahh! Yaahh!
Winter Storm Hyperblow!
Let's go!
EMPRESS: No! I haven't
killed you yet!
Rainbow Fly Trap!
I still think you're cool!
Ohh. He was out of my league
anyway.
That's it. I'm switching
service providers.
Yeah, good call.
Star, I feel bad.
I think I may have ruined
Ferguson's one chance at love.
Maybe we  are  mess-up twins.
Oh, Marco. That Pixie
didn't love Ferguson.
She just wanted to eat him.
Really?
And let's be honest,
Ferguson does
look  delicious.
( both laugh )
Yeah, I guess
nobody's perfect.
Uh, why are you guys
talking about me
like I'm not here?
And where's Alfonzo?
You may now kiss the bride.
( spectators cheer )
Yay! I will make
a great Pixie king!
I'll be very tyrannical.
Hmm?
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something,
cuz I been through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna
stay a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪