♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh
puh-puh-puh-puuuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
( snoring )
"Don't touch!
I will find out!"
Sure you will, Marco.
Sure you will,
heh heh heh.
( clank )
( growls )
( straining )
Unh!
( click )
Uh...
Really?
( groans )
All right.
One...
and two.
Thanks for nothin'.
Chancellor Lekmet!
( bleats )
My liege.
I come bearing an offering
of great momentousness,
should it please thee.
( bleats )
Uh, well, it's kinda heavy.
I was hoping that thee could
come down here to see it.
( sighs )
( chair whirring )
( shorting )
Oh, dang!
Is that on the fritz, too?
Hang on, I've got you.
So, um, speaking of
the interdimensional fritz?
Baaaa?
I've been doing
some digging on my own,
and, uh, I think I've
found what's causing it.
( bleats )
Stay right there.
I present to you...
the source of the fritz.
Baaaa!
Evidence? I've got
your evidence right here.
My gut told me she's evil,
so I took her out.
Boom! No more fritz.
( weary bleating )
Yeah, I know,
she's Queen Butterfly's
daughter, but--
( bleats )
Okay, that kinda hurt.
I know it came
from a good place,
you know, but...
Okay, Chancellor,
for the record,
we had nothing
to do with this.
( grunts, pants )
Yeah, we told him
it was a horrible plan,
but Rockhead
here didn't wanna hear it.
He never listens to us!
But he would listen
to you, Lekmet!
Tell him, Chancellor!
Tell him!
( bleating )
Okay, everybody,
just calm down!
Why don't you sit?
I'll grab you
a glass of warm milk,
and then we can talk this out
like rational people.
( bleating )
Shoot! I forgot
I put him there.
Okay, so I actually
don't know who this is.
A servant maybe?
A very tall dwarf?
But he's
definitely evil.
Gut's honor.
( bleats )
( snorts )
You'll what?
Please don't call
the Magical High Commission.
( bleats )
You... You think we should make
other living arrangements?
( bleats ) Uh-huh.
But... who's
gonna take care of you?
( grumbling bleat )
Lekmet, no. Stop!
Please!
( sighs )
You'll ruin everything!
Stop! Stop!
( beeping )
Guuuuhh!
Dude! You just crystallized
the High Chancellor!
Do you have any idea
how much trouble we are in?!
Stop yelling at me!
Look, I just really need
a win right now.
I mean,
you guys are my hands!
You're supposed
to be on my side!
Can't you just...
( sighs )
Hey...
I bet a few reps
would clear your head.
Huh. You know,
that's not a bad idea.
Bench presses,
couple of biceps curls. Hmm?
What are you lookin' at?
Huh?
What? No! Uh! Hey!
( beeping )
Hyah!
Ohh!
( grunting )
Eee!
Yah!
( panting )
Oh, man...
Oh, geez!
( whimpering )
( gasps )
You! I know
you're the source!
I can feel it!
Huh?
Why did you
cause the fritz?!
Aaaaah!
No! No no no no!
( screaming stops )
I really just can't take
any more yelling today.
Aah!
Princess!
My name is Rhombulus.
I work with your mom,
and I need you
to answer one question.
Rhombulus?
Ohh, ohh!
You're the time-out guy.
What? Who calls me that?
I bet it's Glossaryck,
isn't it?
Omnitraxus
calls you that, too.
And my mom and dad.
Really all of the members
of the Magic High Commission
call you that.
Time-out guy.
Ohh, never mind!
Why are you causing
the fritz?
What's the fritz?
The leak.
The reason why nothing's
working up here?
( mumbles )
I don't know.
Oh! Something has been draining
the power of magic
from the universe.
See? Crystal orbs
are down.
And then there's
the Green Hole over there.
( droning )
Yeah, that part
definitely looks broken.
And look at the crystal
I trapped Lekmet in.
This stuff used
to be hard as diamonds.
Now it's like...
rock candy or something.
I'm sorry your powers are
all crazy, but it's not me.
You have to be the source!
You see all these guys?
My gut told me
they were evil,
so I crystalized them.
There's Zedlord, who blew up
an entire planet.
Astrobell and
the black hole she created.
Stopped
that one just in time.
Oh, and then there's
pizza delivery guy.
Delivered the pizza
to the wrong address.
Then, of course,
I am most proud of
the evil twins...
John and Jack.
They're pretty hard
to tell apart,
but one of them
was definitely evil.
This is what I do.
I find
the source of evil,
and I encase it
in crystal forever.
So... your snake hands,
they're evil, too?
What? No.
They're my hands.
What
about my friend, Marco?
What did he do, exactly?
Oh, him? Well...
And what about
that old goat man?
Is he evil?
( scoffs ) There's
nothing evil about Lekmet.
He's the most pure-hearted,
hard-working angel goat
demon there ever was.
Well, why did you
crystallize him then?
Hmm?
Look, time-out guy,
I think you need to think
stuff through a little more
before you rely on your gut.
It's making you crystallize
innocent people.
Maybe you're right.
I thought
I could trust you, gut!
( grunting )
( shouting angrily )
( crystals shattering )
I'm free!
( panting )
( grumbling )
I've been wrong
about everything lately.
The commission
thinks I'm a joke.
I thought if I could find
the source of the fritz,
my hands and I
could earn the appreciation
of the Magical
High Commission again.
Huh?
Aw, man.
I actually
crystallized Lekmet.
And I love Lekmet!
( sobbing )
Ooh, pretty!
I'm gonna be in time-out
for the next ten thousand years.
Glossaryck is gonna
have a field day with that.
Let me tell you.
Ah, I wouldn't
worry 'bout him.
He's not coming back.
What? Glossaryck's gone?
Oh! ( chuckles )
Uh, yeah...
Glossaryck's gone?
This is amazing!
I mean,
it's actually really bad.
( chuckling )
But it's good for me.
But, yeah, wow.
That's bad news
for the universe.
Why?
The thing about Glossaryck
is he may be a jerk,
but he's the most powerful
all-knowing magic jerk
in the universe.
That's why I can never win
an argument with him.
He's just so hard
to deal with, right?
Even when
I tried to rescue him,
he didn't
want to come back.
You know that fancy crystal
in his head?
I gave it to him!
But did he
ever thank me? No.
Every time we got donuts,
he just sat on them.
( sighs )
What a waste of donuts.
You know, I made some donuts
for a meeting yesterday,
and I think
there's some left over.
Uh... you want any?
Ooh.
You know, you shouldn't
feel so down on yourself,
Rhombulus.
Your crystals
are really pretty.
( clinks )
Ah!
Close your eyes for a minute.
Okay.
Now open!
Oh.
Here.
Ooh!
Is that
evil twin Jack?
It could be.
Either way,
I want you to have it.
Thank you, Rhombulus.
So, I guess you've got
to turn me in, right?
I mean, crystallizing
the princess is
kind of a big deal.
Uh, not necessarily.
Okay, look, if you
don't tell the Magic
High Commission
about Glossaryck
or the Magic Book
of Spells
and how I lost
both of them,
then I won't tell
them about this.
( clink clink )
Really?
Yeah.
Deal.
What about
the old goat man?
Well, don't
worry about him.
I'm the only one who can
understand what he says.
Also I need my socks back.
( straining )
( grunts )
Ooh, phew.
Hey.
Thank you, Princess.
W-w-w-wait!
You still
gotta unfreeze him.
Oh, yeah.
Ow!
Good morning, Marco!
Star? What happened?
You were
in this ice cube.
And there was
this big guy, and he
had a big square head!
( laughs ) What
a funny dream, Marco.
Mmm!
Blech!
Were these
on the floor?
( rats squeaking )
Hyah! Mush! Mush!
Hyah!
LUDO: Hello! Yes!
I have arrived.
Did you keep him up
all night?
You haven't fed him, have you?
Good! Then
he must be about to crack.
Time to turn up the heat.
( low humming )
What's that?
Hold on a minute.
I have to take this.
What? Yes.
Oh, of course.
That'll be our last resort,
heh heh.
( door creaks )
Well, well, well!
How do you
like my monster temple?
Pretty cool, huh?
My wand told me
where to find it.
( loud bang )
Aah!
Hellooo...
( mumbles )
What are you doing?
I was just out
for my morning stroll.
But then
who is in your bed?
Oh! Oh! Oh! Um...
Easy. ( chuckles )
Easy. Don't shoot.
It's, uh...
It's just my robe.
Girls! Bring me the book!
I want you to teach me this,
to make me awesome...
at this!
You will not resist!
Resistance is pointless!
Uh, you mind
hopping off?
Thank you.
Okay.
Let's get started.
But... you're
not going to resist,
even a little resistance?
Look, it's your book now.
I'm just here
to help you... or not.
Up to you.
Really?
You want to teach me?
Oh, yes. Sure.
What's your game?
You must want something.
Oh, I don't have wants.
I have a job.
And that job is to help you
reach your ultimate
potential with this.
Well, then...
Pudding!
Someone just earned
themselves some pudding.
You, little man,
you are going to make me
the most powerful being
in the universe! Ha ha ha!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now, slow, slow,
slow your roll.
Look, all I can promise
is to help you reach
your full potential.
Oh, goody!
Is it going to be hard?
Mm, could be.
Exhausting?
Mmm, quite possibly.
Almost unendurable?
Uh... Well,
do you want it to be?
Oh, yes!
I so want it to be.
( straining )
Stroke! Stroke!
( grunting )
( grunting, panting )
This... is so hard!
When are we going to
start doing spells?
Whenever you want.
What?!
Are you kidding me?!
What was all of this?!
Oh, this?
Well, I was only doing that
because you said you wanted it
to be really hard.
I don't know what I want!
I've never done this before!
You know what my dad
taught me about making
my way in the world?
Nothing!
Zip! I was one egg
out of fifty!
Everything I've learned,
I had to learn dirty!
But for once in my life,
I'd like some guidance.
Okay. We can do that.
Really?
So when am I going
to learn a Narwhal Blast?
Pshew pshew pshew!
Oh, oh. Oh, that.
Yes, well, mm-hmm...
You see,
Star made that up.
It's not in the book.
She just used
her imagination
for most things.
Ooh!
What's an imagination?
( sighs ) Okay.
Well, let's start
with the basics.
( snaps )
( mumbling )
Let's see... okay.
Oh, that's probably
a little too advanced.
Okay, okay...
( mumbling )
Oh! Here we go.
Uh, why don't you
take a look here?
Now note
the stance and posture.
Basically, you're
going to want to put your arm
out and your feet...
Ahem... less out.
You got that?
Okay.
Rrrrrrr!
Hmm...
( straining )
Would you just relax?
Oh.
We're going to start
with some simple
object transfer.
Let's have you try
Levitato.
Now, when you're ready,
I want you to bring me
that apple.
What apple?
That one.
Levitato.
Levitato! Aah!
O-kay.
Oh! You see that?!
How am I supposed
to work with this?!
I listen to my wand,
but it never listens to me.
Look, kid,
it's your first try.
Don't worry about it.
( snaps )
We'll just try again.
Relax.
( inhales )
Levitato!
Levit--
Okay, okay.
No, no. No, no, stop.
Look,
you're really being sloppy.
You need
to really feel it.
Say it with conviction.
Levitato!
Lev-i-tato.
It worked.
( gasps )
Levitato.
Hey!
Now you're getting it.
Nice job.
Am I better than Star?
Well, I...
Well, I guess you're better
at following the spell book.
Are you... proud of me?
Yeah, um...
Yeah, you're doing fine.
Could you say
"proud of me," though?
Uh, huh.
Uh... ( chuckles )
I'm proud of you.
( giggling )
Hmm.
( wand zapping )
Levitato. Levitato.
Levitato.
( whirring )
Yep.
GLOSSARYCK:
Um, you see,
it's a complex theory
behind the levitations...
Levitato.
you'll be performing...
Levitato!
as a magic user.
And they all lived
happily ever after.
The end.
Levitato.
You'd better
get some sleep.
You have a lot of work
to do tomorrow.
Levitato.
Might even learn
a second spell
or something.
This was a really great day,
Glossaryck.
I'm sure it was.
Will you tuck me in?
Um, well, I...
Uh, okay.
And my wand.
Uh...
( excited chuckle )
Ahem... there you go.
And pat my head?
Pat pat pat,
see you in the morning.
And say, "Good night,
my darling."
Are you kidding me?
Um, good night.
My darling.
Um, uh...
( stammering ) my darling.
( snoring )
( whispering )
Are you still awake?
I can't sleep, either!
I'm too excited
to sleep!
Today was wonderful!
( wand humming )
Why would you say that?
Glossaryck is proud of me.
He said
I was better than Star!
( humming )
What do you mean,
he showed her
something hidden?
Don't be silly!
We just started.
I'm sure we'll
get to it soon.
( humming )
He kept it
from me on purpose?
( humming )
No. No, no, no, no.
He'd never lie to me!
Levitato!
Glossaryck? Wake up!
Didn't we just do bedtime?
Glossaryck.
I know this is crazy,
but my wand told me...
( chuckling ) It's just
my wand told me
there's a chapter in this book
that you've shown Star
that you haven't shown me.
But that's crazy, right?
No, it's true.
What?!
Why didn't you show me?!
You know,
you didn't ask.
Well, I want to see it!
( sighs )
You want to see it.
You want to see--
Well, you know,
I don't know.
It's really advanced.
Um, you know,
dark stuff.
Did you show it to Star?
Um, technically,
I didn't show her,
but, uh, she has seen it.
Show me!
Okay, it's your book.
Secret chapter.
Unlock it!
Are you truly sure?
It could taint you.
Oh, I got plenty
of taint already.
Now unlock it!
( sighs ) As you wish.
Hmm!
I thought
there'd be more pict--
Aah!
Ohhh!
( Toffee's voice )
Hello, Glossaryck.
Hello, Toffee.
Time to give it up,
old man.
You'll never get him
on your side.
But I don't have a side.
You don't, do you?
( chuckles )
Excellent.
♪ I think Earth is
a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me
its just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I can call this place home! ♪