♪♪
(  I'm from Another Dimension
by Brad Breeck plays)
MAN:
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo! ♪
♪♪
♪ Yeah-hey! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, paaa! ♪
♪ Oh, it's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( song ends )
STAR:
Whooo!
( gasps )
Awesome!
Again. Again. Again
Again. Again
( whoosh )
( die crashes )
MARCO: Two.
One. Two.
Punch! Punch! Chiii-Oop!
That's boring, Marco.
Stairs are boring.
( die crashes loudly )
( whispers )
Yeah.
Hmm. Six.
One. Two. Three.
Fourrrr.
( gasps excitedly )
Fuh-fuh-fuh.
Fiiivvveee!
( excited gasp )
( exhales slowly and giggles )
MARCO:
Uuh... Siiixxx...
I don't want to go six.
I want to go five.
You rolled six. You go six.
Those are the rules.
If the rules get in the way
of the fun what's the point?
STAR:
Sing it, Sister.
TINY MARCO:
The point is to use
the steps to get to the end.
( chuckles )
I'm sorry Star.
I'm gonna
have to agree with this
super handsome little guy.
( Tiny Marco chuckles )
Oh, stop it.
No, you stop it.
( portal zaps )
BOTH:
Buffrog?
Buffbabies!
TINY MARCO:
No, please don't close it!
( Tiny Star screams )
( Russian accent )
Star Butterfly...
I am needing your help.
( whines )
My babies!
Please be baby-sitting them.
( coos excitedly )
Babies.
I don't know
anyone else to ask.
Oh, I got this.
I'm like, basically,
the Crowned Princess
of Babysittonia...
Right, Marco?
( phone rings )
Excuse me.
Da?
( whispers ) You've never
baby-sat before, have you?
( slowly and playfully )
Nooooo.
But I was a baby once.
Yes, yes, I bring weapons.
What am I? Tadpole?
It's not that easy, Star.
Will bring
torture bag as well.
See you soon.
Here is Binder.
All of babies schedules
and informations inside.
( sighs sadly )
Katrina...
My most delicate
little glassy pearl.
Please be
extra careful with her.
It'll be just fine.
Star and I got this handled.
Just like a suitcase.
Totally handled.
Take good care of them...
Or else...
( gulps nervously )
Okay.
Daddy will come get you
after work.
Six o'clock sharp.
Be good and listen
to baby-sitters.
Ooooh
So young,
so full of dreams.
What bright new adventures
will we take you on?
A nap.
What!?
We follow the instructions
Buffrog left us and they nap.
Then this will be a nap
they will never forget!
Just read me
what the book says.
Fine.
Boris, Alexi, and Anastasia
sleep on their sides.
Dimitry, Ana, and Igor
prefer their stomachs.
Mikhail, Leo, and Irina
sleep on their right sides.
Nadia and Sergei
on their left.
Katrina is delicate
and must be held to sleep.
Awwww.
I got you lil' babe.
Okay, what now?
They sleep,
then we feed them.
( excited and softly )
And theeeen?
( softly )
They sleep agaaaain.
( excited and softly )
And theeeen?
That's it.
They just sleep.
Oh, come on.
Where's the fun in that?
It's not just about
having fun, Star.
But babies  need  fun.
( Russian accent )
No. Babies have
routine and schedule.
Ugh.
Now you keep an eye on them
and I'll make their lunch.
( softly )
Hey, no fair!
You wanna make 12 lunches?
I'll watch the lil' bits!
( coos and exclaims )
Awww! So cuuute!
( struggling )
Just. One. Boop.
MARCO:
Star. No booping.
Just watch.
Okay, let's see here.
Feeding...
feeding... feeding...
( grossed out )
Uuugh!
Awww! Precious
little babieesss!
Especially little
Katrina-kins.
( tiny yawn )
You just wanna be
boopity-booped.
Okayyy...
Just one boop.
Then, I-- No!
But she's so cuuute!
I just gotta...
( coos )
( shudders loudly )
Ribbit!
( gasp )
( Babies croak loudly )
Star, everything okay
in there?
( babies croaking loudly )
( Star shudders in panic )
Star!
I booped, Marco.
I booped so bad.
Its okay!
I got Buffrog's binder!
( clears throat )
To stop croaking,
feed babies lunch.
Ah, that's easy.
I got lunch all ready
in the kitchen.
Oh, mah babies gotta eat!
( flies buzzing )
No way. My babies
ain't eating that slop!
( croaking continues )
Star, hurry up in there.
( singsong )
Aaall ready!
Wait. What did you
put in there?
Cake.
You can't feed babies cake!
What? Fun, Marco.
Remember?
You guys like fun,
don't you?
Don't you wittle guys?
( loud burp )
No! No, no!
( shudders )
Oh, wait. Don't do that.
We gotta call Buffrog.
Whoa there, Diaz.
I told Buffrog
I was the Crowned Princess
of Babysittonia.
We're doing this
by the book then.
( Babies croak
and barf loudly )
( grunts )
It says they need a bath.
Okay. You corral the babies.
I got the bath.
Squeaky Clean Bath Beam!
( crash )
( duck quacks )
I got one!
Oh!
( burps loudly and barfs )
Aw! Really?!
( inhales deeply )
( shudders )
( exhales heavily )
This isn't working.
( phone ringing )
( star screams in panic )
What do I do?
Answer it!
I don't want to answer it.
STAR: Aww,
they're dancing
to the music.
Quick. Get 'em into the tub.
( phone continues to ring )
That is so cute.
( gasps )
Oh, my gosh!
We gotta send
Buffrog a photo.
Say "Co-o-orn!"
"We miss you Daddy.
We are counting on you."
Aand send!
You know, Marco,
you're pretty good at this!
Thanks. I just used
the old trusty binder.
( croaks loudly )
( gasps )
Leeegss!
Legs, legs,
legs, le-hegs!!
There's not a chapter
in the binder
about growing legs!
( Babies croak loudly )
They're  all
growing legs!
( screams )
( gaps )
Quick! Catch 'em!
Aww, except little Katrina.
She feels left out.
Never mind Katrina.
Do something!
Fine. ( sighs )
Stay put, little buttercup.
Gotcha! Whoa!
Whoaaa! Ow!
Don't play too rough now.
Have fun.
( gasps audibly )
Fun? This isn't fu--
( shouts )
Hey! Let me in!
( Babies croak happily )
( beeping )
( muffled )
What the?
Oh, no! No! Hey!
He-e-ey! No!
Stop! Sto-o-op!
( breathing heavily )
( shouts )
( Babies croak happily )
( Star squeals joyfully )
( Star squeals )
( Babies croak happily )
Star! Quit messing around!
Buffrog will be back in...
( ticking slowly )
( gasps )
Four minutes?!
We have four minutes
to get these babies
under control!
Relaaax, Marco.
We got this.
You take care of
the ones with the legs,
and I'll take care of--
( gasps )
Katrina?
We gotta find her!
No. No!
No.
Nope.
MARCO: She's.
STAR: Not.
MARCO: In.
STAR: Here!
There's only one room
left in the house.
( door crashes and thuds )
We need an army
to search your room!
Great idea!
Hey, Babies!
I hope them legs came with
buuunnnss!!
( Lady singing )
♪ Space Unicorn! ♪
♪ Soaring through the stars! ♪
♪ Delivering the rainbows ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ Space Unicorn,
Shining in the night ♪
It's working! Now what?
Give them
their marching orders.
♪ Smiles and hugs forever
All around the world ♪
( music continues )
All right, Babies.
Line up--
Marco, make it fun.
Hey, Babies,
wanna learn a new dance?
First, shimmy
your leg like this.
( Marco hums along to music )
Ah! Ah!
All right.
No-o-ow!! Pose!
Great. Great.
Now, back it up.
Back it up and spin!
Then look for your sister
under the nearest object!
( clock bell gongs )
♪ Space unicorn!
Soaring through the stars ♪
They're doing it!
♪ Delivering the rainbows ♪
I think they found something!
♪ All around the world! ♪
Katrina.
Star!
Why do you have
so many bear traps?
You're afraid to tell Jackie
you have a crush on her,
but you're not afraid of bears?
I don't get you, Marco.
How are we gonna get to her?
We use the binder.
What?!
( Star grunts )
( slow-motion scream)
Nooooo!
( traps snap and clang loudly )
Babies!
( Babies croak )
( gasps )
( Babies croak loudly )
Awww. ( sobs )
Hey, are you okay?
( sobbing )
I miss baby tadpole grow legs!
Most important
developmental stage
of child development.
Well, little Katrina
hasn't grown her legs yet.
( gasps happily )
My little late bloomer.
Come to Papa!
( Buffrog giggles )
( Katrina croaks loudly )
Booooop!
Bye little Katrina-kins.
Don't forget the binder.
Look, we added a chapter.
( bear traps clang )
Aww...
Thank you, Star girl.
And Karate Boy.
I will remember this,
like something I will
never forget.
( portal zaps close )
I like that guy.
Yeah. Me too.
TINY MARCO:
Wohooo!
You know,
sometimes you do
have to forget the rules
and focus on
just having fun.
You can't forget them
completely though.
They make the fun
that much sweeter.
You think
they'll  ever get that?
( Marco and Star snore softly )
TINY STAR:
Give them time.
They're still young.
( crickets chirp in distance )
( jovial music starts )
( music comes to
a jarring end slowly )
( Babies croaking softly )
( croaking continues )
Call BooFly.
( beeping )
( nasally voice )
Hey, Buffrog!
Long time no see, man!
I heard you have kids now.
Yes, 12 beautiful babies.
Very hungry.
I hear you're hiring
for a job.
Are you sure you're up for it?
You've been
out of the game for a while.
Oh,
don't worry about me.
I am just as evil as ever.
Hmm. Hehehe.
( evil laughter )
( toy squeaks )
It'll be just fine.
Star and I got this handled.
Just like a suitcase.
Totally handled.
Okay. Daddy will come
get you after work.
Six o'clock sharp.
Be good and
listen to babysitters.
( portal zaps close )
( bawls loudly )
( sniffs )
Come on.
Pull yourself together, man.
Who's more evil than you?
( gruffly )
Nobody!
( grunts and shouts )
Hiya!
Hya! Hya! Hya!
( shouting fades )
( grunting )
Buffrog?
Bufforg.
Buffrog, Buffrog?
Buffrog, Buffrog.
The  Buffrog?
Actually...
it's Yovginei Buffgoiapov.
What?
Guys, welcome
the newest member
of our team.
This guy?
Look a little... soft.
To me.
Soft?!
( grunts and snarls )
Oooh.
He's just like me.
Ah, whatever.
Last time he got
his hands dirty
he was changing diapers.
Heh-heh.
You want me
to change  your  diaper?
( gasps )
( growls angrily )
Guys! Guys, guys, guys.
We're all on
the same team here.
We have work to do.
( country music plays )
( tap tap )
Cooorrn!
Coorrrrrrnn!
Wait. Only Mewmans
have corn.
How rats have corn
when monsters are starving?
That's what we're here
to find out.
In that case,
let's get show on road.
BOTH:
Thumpie-bumpies!
Okay, here is plan.
A) We capture rat.
B) Make him tell us
where he got corn.
Well, great.
I'll just go grab him!
No, no.
Give your abs a break.
We must do this quietly.
Let me teach you about
the element of surprise.
( grunts and shouts )
BOOFLY:
Aw, yeah! Buffrog's back!
( rat squeaks )
( softly )
Surprise!
( cackles triumphantly )
Okay, little guy.
You and me
will have little talk.
( shouts in surprise )
Wait!
DOGBULL:
What was that?
Baby oil on your fingers?
( laughs )
BOOFLY:
Umm, Buffrog?
Did that just happen?
Uhhh...
Look what was in
the Lost and Found.
He-he.
Yeah, 'cause he lost it.
And we found it! Right?
( laughs )
Uuuhh...
Hey Buff Frog!
Why don't you show
the team your patented
interrogation technique.
This guy's the best!
( chuckles nervously )
We will do this the easy way
and  the hard way.
Easy for me,
and hard for you.
This is amazing!
He-heh.
Told you he was good.
Where did you get the corn?
Uuhhh!
( groans )
This rat is tougher
than I thought.
You're not going
to want to see this.
Uuh, yeah I do!
No, no, no.
Lets, uh, leave the master
to his work.
You know how artists are.
( chuckles )
( whimpers )
( thud )
Ooh! What is happening to me?
( squeaks )
I can't do this to you.
Wait. What am I doing?
I know what you're thinking.
You think I'm soft because
I have children, don't you?
( growls )
I'll show you!
( Rat squeals loudly )
( Rat screeching )
Oh, and can you believe
Nadia here?
Seriously. There ought
to be a law against
something that cute.
Oooh! We should do
live chat with them.
I call Star right now.
( beeping )
( Rat screeching )
It's ringing!
BOOFLY:
I'm telling you,
He probably found
all the corn by now.
What did you just do?!
You let him go?!
Umm, yes.
But it's uhh--
It's all according
to the plan.
I've seen him do this
a hundred times.
It's a classic.
Buffrog interrogates
the prisoner,
then lets him go,
'cause he's so freaked out that
he'll lead us right to where
the corn came from...
technique.
Am I right, B?
Oh, yes.
Yes, never fails.
( sniffs )
Well, I guess I can track
his scent from here.
( continues sniffing )
Hey, Bruh, are you good?
'Cause, um...
that didn't look good.
I know. I know!
This should be easy...
but nothing is feeling right.
You blow this again,
I'm not gonna be able
to cover for you!
No, no.
I got this.
( footsteps
in marching cadence )
Jackpot.
Yes, but this
is not the source.
Is only supply route.
Hey, Buff-Daddy.
You with us, or what?
Yes. One hundred percent.
Okay, guys...
( softly )
quiet...
( soft metallic whooshing )
( loud baby music plays )
( Buffrog gaps and fumbles )
( rats squeak )
Uuh... Umm...
Shh!
( grunting )
( hoarsely )
Stop it!
( music slows down )
( Buffrog grunts )
( Rats squeak and squeal )
( baby music
fades into distance )
That was...
Katrina's favorite--
( growls menacingly )
Guys, guys, guys!
Keep your cool.
Now, we're gonna
do this my way.
We follow the supply route
back to the source...
and we'll be swimming
in delicious corrrnn!!!
BOTH:
Cooorrrrrnn!
Cooorrr--
No, no.
Not you.
( whimpers softly )
All right!
Everyone else, move out!
Oh, wait! Boo Fly! Please.
I need one more chance.
Just go home, man.
Thumbie-bumpie?
No, man.
No thumpie-bumpie.
( phone rings )
( explosion )
( gasps )
( sobs )
ALL: Corn!
( shouting in joy )
( grunt and groan )
( force field hums )
Noo!
Stupid Mewmans!
( thump )
( force field hums )
( buzzing )
DOGBULL:
Huh? Green hole?
( growls and grumbles )
( grunts and growls )
You can't fit in there.
You need to try
something small--
Hey!
( grunts and struggles )
Corn, corn, corn.
Ha ha! Corn! Corn! Corn!
( grunting in distance )
Huh?
My corn!
Come on, man,
suck in your gut!
You there, monsters!
Get away...
from my corrnn!!
( fire roars )
Woopsie!
( Monsters gasp )
Noo! Later!
We're toast!
( fire roars loudly )
( groans )
( Buffrog roars )
I thought you went home!
We are  all  going home.
( groans )
My ab! My Ab!!
I'm missing an ab!
( ab creaks )
Oh, thank corn.
Thanks, Buffrog!
Thank you for saving us.
Sorry we were mean!
Just doing my job.
I'm never making
fun of dads again!
Aww, c'mere,
my little perogis!
( Monsters chuckles shyly )
I don't want to ruin
a moment but, um...
we didn't get any corn.
True. We did not get corn.
But mission
not a failure.
We found hole
in Mewman force field
that they did not know
was there.
We just need a way
to get in through that hole.
If anyone can do it...
you can!
Now, I must get babies.
( gasps happily )
Daddy missed you so much,
my little kreplachs!
( portal zaps close )
Know what?
I'm gonna call my dad.
( Rats squeaking )
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty gre-e-eat place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me ♪
♪ It's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna
stay a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪