♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( car alarm chirps )
( car alarm blares )
HEINOUS:
Gemini, the door is jammed.
GEMINI: Are you sure
it's not locked?
I know what it looks like
when it's locked.
Get me out of this car.
Gemini!
Oh. Oh, coming.
How is my hair?
Like you just came
from the salon.
Filthy lies,
but I'll allow it.
Come now, Rasticore.
There's my baby
bounty hunter.
You're growing back
so fast, yes, you are.
Yes, you are.
Now we are prepared
to wreak recrimination
on our foes.
Yes. Recrim-mim-mim-ination!
Hello?
Now are you convinced that
parking meters aren't
filled with candy?
It's all just
a big tease.
How was I supposed
to know... oh.
Okay, that was not
like that before.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'll cover the back door,
and on my mark,
- you bum rush
the front door.
- Got it.
One...
Two...
- Three.
- ( yells )
( karate yell )
- Marco?
- You!
You!
- Get her.
- Narwhal blast.
Yeah! Get him, get him!
What did you do
to my parents?
Unhand me, you little--
Stop! Marco, let go
of that poor old woman.
Wait. You're mad at us?
We're trying
to save you guys.
We let her in.
You are both
being very rude.
Star, put away
your magical whale.
It's a Narwhal.
You, too, Marco.
Let Miss Heinous go.
But she's evil.
- Now!
- Aahh!
This is the princess
who ruined my life.
That's right,
Princess Marco.
I recognize you.
Even with your super-cute
new haircut.
What is going on here?
This lady tied me
to a chair,
and tried to
brainwash me.
That's a gross
exaggeration.
Your child has
terribly wronged me,
and I'm not going
anywhere until justice
is served.
But if she
doesn't leave...
Then how are we gonna
have dinner with...
BOTH: The Morrisons?
- Who?
- The Morrisons are so cool.
We've been on the wait list
to have them over for months.
This dinner
needs to be perfect.
We can't mess it up.
Wow. That sounds
really tough, guys.
You're gonna resolve
whatever issue you have
with Miss Heinous right now!
( evil chuckling )
Here you go.
Thank you,
Your Highness.
What exactly is
your issue with Marco?
Gemini.
Once, I was
the headmistress of St. Olga's,
the most esteemed princess
school in the multiverse.
It was a wonderful place
where delinquent princesses
were taught manners
and respect.
Until one day,
an insolent princess showed up,
and inspired all the students
to rebel against their elders,
who knew better.
Princess Marco left,
but the school
was never the same.
They made her
the face of a revolution,
even inspiring merchandise,
influencing the next generation
of young princesses
with her devious ways.
Wait a minute.
You have merchandise?
Yeah. I get a $650
royalty check every month.
As I was saying,
my students lost
all respect for authority.
Soon, they were cutting classes
just to party,
even inviting the boys
from a neighboring
prince reform school.
They threw me out.
And now,
I live in a car.
- BOTH: Oh!
- Oh!
Don't touch me.
And it's all thanks to
Princess Marco,
and her little sidekick,
Princess Butterfly.
Marco, is this
all true?
Well, yeah, but that place
was a prison.
Those princesses were
being oppressed.
They're way happier now.
And they blew up
my bodyguard.
Yeah, we were wondering
what that was.
He's my dear, sweet Rasticore.
This is just his arm,
but he's part lizard,
so his whole body
will grow back soon.
And then he'll be
a big boy, won't you, sweetie?
( groans )
So how shall we proceed,
Miss Heinous?
With a punishment
commensurate with the crime.
How about we annihilate her
and display her skeleton
as a warning against
any further insurrection?
Agreed? Good.
Now, Rasticore, bring me
Princess Marco's bones.
- Gemini.
- Yes. Yes, milady.
( angry growls )
Okay, enough of this.
( karate yell )
Gemini, Rasticore, attack!
Get ready to feel
the painous, Miss Heinous.
No, Star.
Excuse me.
Is this 4815 Avocado Terrace?
The police!
Yes, it is.
You're here just in time.
That lady is trying
to destroy me.
And that trollish-looking
guy-man-thing is totally
helping her.
Uh, just ignore the girl
waving a magic wand.
And it's probably
a lesser charge,
but this severed lizard arm
is complicit, too.
Well, that's something,
all right.
Now if you'll all
stay calm,
I'm sure we can
clear this up right now.
Okay, I got a call about
a car double parked,
but, uh, since the wheels
of the top car
ain't on the ground,
that's not my jurisdiction.
What? That's it?
You're gonna ignore
all the evil going on?
Evil. Evil. Evil!
Ho-ho, that doesn't
look dangerous.
It's one of those
animations, right?
You mean animatronics.
Listen, kid,
once there's a real crime,
give me a call.
( growling )
All right,
let the bargaining begin.
I leave if you let me rip out
Princess Marco's spine
and wear it as
a fancy scarf.
Okay, that seems
a little extreme.
Honey, we really don't
have time for this.
The Morrisons are gonna
be here soon,
and we haven't ' even
picked out the placemats.
Um... what if we ground Marco
for a week?
Or you let me
grind her bones into a pulp.
- ( stammering )
- We won't let Marco
play video games.
Do you even know
how bargaining works?
No meat on Fridays.
Or even let me
disembowel her.
He can do the dishes.
What if I just apologize?
An apology.
Yes.
An apology will suffice...
under certain conditions.
( relieved sigh )
Marco, you can't
give up that easy.
I'll do anything to get
Heinous out of here.
Whatever you want,
Miss Heinous.
Just name it.
Why did I day
whatever you want?
( evil cackling )
It's finally happening.
Let's see what those princesses
think of their idol now.
I can't believe our son
led a revolution
and we didn't even know.
I'm not sure if
I should be mad or proud.
Hang on, hang on.
A princess can't go on camera
without blush.
Dude, don't do this.
All those princesses,
like, really look up to you.
I know. If I know a thing
or two about princesses,
it's gonna take a lot more
than some dumb video
to break their spirits.
Marco.
So how do I look?
Super pretty.
Enough dilly-dallying.
Let's get on with it.
Just be careful.
Gemini, are you
ready yet?
Yes, milady.
And we're rolling.
Uh, hey, princesses
of the multiverse.
It's your girl Marco.
- What up?
- MOTHER: Psst.
Morrisons.
Anyway, last time I was at
St. Olga's school,
I said and did some stuff
that I shouldn't have.
And that was... bad.
And, um, I just wanted
to say, um...
I just wanted to say
that I'm, like,
super sorry
that I told you guys
to resist your oppressors
and stuff.
As princesses, we should
never think for ourselves,
and just, you know,
give up on our dreams
and our own individuality.
Oh, I mean all this
from the bottom of my heart.
And I'm definitely not just
saying that because
Miss Heinous is threatening me
and my family.
Okay, was that good?
Milady, I have notes.
( laughing )
It's perfect. Perfect!
Miss Heinous, we just
want to apologize again
for Marco's behavior.
Yes. We hope this can be
a fresh start for all of us.
Hm. We shall see.
Maybe this will inspire you
to take a more active role
in your child's life.
FATHER:
Good-bye, Miss Heinous.
Safe travels.
Well, this was
a real eye-opener.
What else have you
been hiding from us?
Now is the time to
own up to any other
inter-dimensional chicanery.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No chicanery here.
All good.
Nothing to report.
I think we have
some responsibility
to accept, too.
Maybe we haven't
been around enough
for the two of them.
We can start
fresh tonight.
I say we cancel
dinner with the Morrisons,
and instead,
have a family game night.
( all cheering )
Who needs to hang out
with the Morrisons anyway?
The Diazes are so cool.
There you are, milady.
Pillow's fluffed
just the way you like it.
Sweet dreams, milady.
And sweet dreams to you,
too, Princess Marco.
The fairest in the land.
Soon, the multiverse
will shiver in fear
once I destroy
Princess Marco
and Princess Butterfly.
With you at my side,
Rasticore...
Why, Rasticore.
You've grown an elbow.
You'll be a big boy
again soon.
So very soon.
Karate brings the essence
of ka, ra, and te
together in a circular balance
of the elements.
It is time for you
to demonstrate
all that you have learned
about the "DUH's" of karate.
Discipline.
Ed-U-cation.
And most importantly,
Honor.
I, Grandmaster of
the How To Karate video series,
am coming to your dojo
in your town of...
to watch your top student
perform.
If Grandmaster
deems them worthy,
your dojo will be
How To...
This is a great honor
for our dojo.
With Grandmaster's
certification,
we won't just be
a mini-mall dojo anymore.
We'll be a certified
mini-mall dojo.
The student I will choose
to represent the school
will be someone who has
constantly impressed me
with their dedication
and commitment.
Someone who has contributed
so much to the dojo,
who really puts the "ra"
in karate.
I will let you know my decision
by the end of the week.
Uh, sensei, it's Friday.
Oh. Then it's Jeremy.
What?!
( nervous stammering )
Anyway, great class today.
You're all dismissed.
( evil laughter )
How does it feel, Marco?
He actually chose
an eight-year-old over you.
L-o-s-e-r.
Marco lost to who?
J-e-r-e-m-y.
That spells winner.
That's me.
Jeremy.
Yay! This is going to be
the best trip yet!
Ready to board?
You bet, Sir Acha.
Let's sail away
on our friend ship.
Hey, little buddy.
What are you doing
in my room?
( New Age music plays )
Hajime.
Whoa. That was amazing.
So is Jeremy still
your choice to
represent the dojo?
Yeah, for sure, Jeremy.
What?! I broke, like,
three boards.
Marco, I didn't pick Jeremy
because he's better at karate.
I picked him because of...
you know, who he is
as a person.
Who Jeremy is as a person
is a jerk.
( muttering ) As a person?
Who do you think is a person?
Marco, listen.
No, you listen.
I'm ten times the person
Jeremy is.
You're making
a huge mistake.
Let's sail away on
our friend ship.
( gasps )
You still have a lot
to learn about honor.
Fine.
Mom, next time you cut
the crusts off,
leave 'em in the bag.
Just 'cause I don't
want 'em on my sandwich
doesn't mean I don't
eat 'em later.
MOTHER: I'm sorry,
my little cherub.
Is that...
That's a hundred-dollar bill.
Really?
Yeah.
That's a Benjamin.
That's my favorite one.
But it's got
all that stuff on it.
Yeah, it's
a lot of stuff.
You know how many vinyls
I could buy with that?
Three.
I'm going in.
Ew. Why does it smell
like that?
Pretty rank, huh?
Well, maybe if I...
I'd start with
the corner.
Man. Somebody glued this
to the ground.
Glue?
What kind of a sick joke
is this?
Try the other corner.
My glasses.
And it's my birthday!
Uh, butler, refill.
- Shameful.
- Hey, Marco,
whatcha doing?
Do you mind?
I'm collecting
evidence here.
( gasps )
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Keep it up, Jeremy.
You're giving me
everything I need.
( rustling )
- Star? What are you doing?
I'm just helping you out
at the scene of the crime,
collecting evidence.
Uh, it's not really
a crime scene.
I'm hiding in the bushes
and recording all of Jeremy's
bad behavior.
Oh, so you're like a...
like a...
like a creep.
What? No.
I'm not a creep.
I've got lots
of proof here, Star.
It's okay, Marco.
Wave that creep flag.
This isn't creepy.
This is justice.
I'm gonna show
all this bad stuff to sensei,
and then he'll have
to change his mind
about letting Jeremy
represent the dojo.
Huh?
( karate yells )
Hey, sensei.
Mr. Diaz.
There's something
I need to show you.
If it's those pictures of
the dog playing the harmonica,
I've seen them,
and they're excellent.
No, no,
this is not that.
It's about Jeremy.
Okay. What is it?
I wanna show you...
how...
Well?
How...
sorry I am.
I shouldn't have
overreacted the other day.
You have every right
to choose who you want
to represent the dojo.
And if you really think
Jeremy is the best choice,
then I can accept that.
I appreciate
your apology.
It shows your
noble spirit.
You're like a lion,
or a really cool bird-lion.
- ( watch beeping )
- Oh, man!
Grandmaster's gonna
be here any minute.
Or is Grandmaster
already here?
( all gasping )
Grandmaster.
Thank you for coming.
Do not thank Grandmaster.
It is by the will
of karate
that Grandmaster is here.
That's the coolest sentence
I've ever heard.
Who have you chosen
to represent your dojo?
Me! Jeremy!
Yay. We love you, son.
I would like to express
what a huge honor it is
for all of you
to watch me perform.
♪ Jeremy is awesome ♪
♪ He's the best at
everything he does ♪
Ahem.
Applause.
♪ He's the greatest
that ever was ♪
Yah, yah!
- Mom, picture.
- Yes, sweetie.
What a jerk!
I cannot stand
that boy.
Why'd you bring me here
for our anniversary
No, I'm not done.
Okay, that's it.
I'm sorry, sensei.
I just can't
accept this.
Why did you pick Jeremy?
Because he brings so much
to the dojo.
So much what?
Money, dude.
His family's
filthy rich.
They give the dojo
tons of cash.
That's how I keep
this place afloat.
I really shouldn't be
running a business.
So, wait.
You don't think
he's a better person than me?
No. Of course not.
He's a toilet.
Jeremy, Jeremy...
Why didn't you tell me
this in the first place?
Because you and I
are friends,
and that's what friends do.
They do hurtful things
to each other,
without explaining why,
because they know
their friend will understand.
That's not how... wait.
We're friends?
Duh. You're my dojo bro.
Why else would I keep
texting you to grab tacos?
You don't text me.
Whose number is this then?
For the record, friends are
up front with each other.
Really? I gotta stop
learning life lessons
from children's shows.
I'm so ignorant in
the ways of friendship.
Perhaps you could be
my friendship sensei.
I'd be honored.
( loud snoring )
Yes. Uh... yes.
Yes, indeed,
yes, indeed.
Wonderful performance.
Just wow. Wow all across the...
But I wasn't even done.
Yes, Grandmaster
gets the gist.
Punch, punch,
kick, kick.
Very good, William.
It's Jeremy.
This dojo
has proven itself
worthy of
Grandmaster's certification.
The wind of karate
beckons once again.
Grandmaster must go.
How did he do that?
Huh. Grandmaster
is like the wind.
He is not bound
by physical constraints.
You can't leave
the Grandmaster!
Looks good.
Sure does.
( phone buzzes )
"Let's go grab some tacos."
Someone invited me
to get tacos.
Wanna come, too?
Sure.
You wanna go get
some ice cream?
No? You wanna go glue
some hundred-dollar bills
to the ground?
Yeah? Okay.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪