♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another,
whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪♪
( gasps )
Goblin Dogs!
Goblin Dog family? Whee!
Star! Star!
Will you please eat me?
Don't mind if I do!
( Goblin Dog laughing )
Eat me now, Star.
-Eat me!
-Eat all of us!
( laughter )
( grumbling )
Oh, blech!
What a satisfying
and filling dream.
( knocking on door )
MARCO: Star, are you up?
It's time for breakfast!
I found Captain Blanche's
Sugar Seeds here on Mewni.
They have an importer.
( yawning ) I'm all good.
I just had
the most ♪ amazing ♪ dream
where I was flying,
and then there were
all these Goblin Dogs
that were also flying,
and then I ate them.
( burps )
Ew. Smells like Goblin Dogs.
Uh, Star,
what are all those?
What the--?
Goblin Dog wrappers?!
You've been sneaking out
to the Goblin Dog truck
without me?
No, no, no! I swear,
I am not-- ( burps )
Ew, a receipt!
I did go to that dimension!
-In my sleep?
-How is that possible?
I have no idea.
Okay, Marco,
you know the plan.
You stay up all night and see
if whatever happened last night
happens again tonight.
But then what?
Shouldn't we tell
somebody about this?
-I mean, what if--
-Marco!
Shall I remind you
you are my squire?
So I order you to sit there
and watch me sleep.
-Okay.
-Good.
Oh, and don't tell Tom
about this, either.
Oh, heck no.
Good! Good night.
Aah, Glossaryck!
Mm, Glabgor.
All right, but just
for a little while.
You're so... warm...
and cozy.
-Wha! Whoa!
-Star?
( gasps )
( truck plays music )
( startles )
( music whirs down )
( zooming noise )
-Star, wake up!
-( giggles ) Hey, buddy.
There's definitely
something weird going on.
( panting )
Marco, what happened?
I might've dozed off
for a minute,
but when I opened
my eyes,
you had opened a portal
and gone through it.
Without dimensional scissors?
You came out of the portal
as that big scary thing
you turned into
when you defeated Toffee.
Well, that shouldn't
be happening.
So, Mom! You know that big
butterfly thing
you can transform
into when you get all mad
and feel
like scaring people?
It's not
for scaring people, Star.
Right.
Right, right, right.
So, does that ever happen...
unintentionally?
Well, it starts
with muberty,
but after that,
it requires years
of training.
Oh, good.
Good, good, good.
But what if it just
sort of happened...
randomly?
Star, it doesn't
happen randomly,
okay, it happens...
in times of need,
like when you
defeated Toffee.
But what if it...
did happen randomly?
Catastrophe!
( hearty laugh ) Yes!
-We'd have to put you
in the dungeon!
-River--
No! Then the magical
high commission would come
and take you away!
There'd be weeks
of examinations.
You'd be locked
away forever!
( chortles )
River, please.
I mean, if this happened,
eventually we'd just have
to adopt a new princess.
River, enough!
Star, is everything
all right?
Oh! Yes. Everything is
totally normal, obviously.
I was just asking
so that I can be prepared
to handle it
if I ever do learn
to transform like you
on purpose.
Queen Moon--
-( thunk )
-Ouch!
I... have nothing to say.
( crickets chirping )
Food truck bed transform!
( whirrs )
All right, Marco,
let's try this again.
So... this'll keep you
from morphing
into Butterfly Star?
Yep! Don't worry,
Marco, I got this.
But even your mom
seemed concerned--
My parents cannot
know about this!
You heard what Dad said!
"Locked away forever!"
I think he was
exaggerating a little.
Marco, my squire,
you are the only person
I can trust with this.
Promise me
you won't doze off again.
Don't worry,
not gonna happen.
And even if it does,
this chain will alert me
any time you move,
and I'll wake up, too.
Thanks, Marco.
( sighs ) Good night.
Aah! Glossaryck!
Oh, no, you don't.
You're not making me
fall asleep this time!
Out you go.
Globgor?
( crickets chirping )
( snoring )
( mystical music )
Ohh!
Huh?
-( Marco gasps )
-( Star grunts )
Star!
Oh, no. Aah!
Whoa! Uhh! Uhh!
Huh? Aah!
What the--?
Aah! Whoa!
Wha--!
( grunting )
Star! Wake up!
Marco?
I need you to fly us
back to that portal!
Portal? Oh...
( determined grunt )
Huh?
You're easily...
( both wailing )
Oh, no, no, no.
What?
( both screaming )
( impact grunts )
Are you two all right?
Eclypsa! I am so glad
you're here.
Wait a minute.
Why are you here?
I'm returning this little guy
after he wandered into my tower.
Eclypsa! ( gasps )
Isn't she
that ancient evil queen
everyone's talking about?
We don't trust you
one bit!
Oh, are you afraid I'll get
my evil cooties on you?
Stay back, woman!
What's this?
Some sort of sword
hand dance?
This looks fun.
Don't come any closer!
Marco, she's really
not dangerous.
-Aren't you adorable!
-Who are you calling adorable?
STAR: Stop!
I have had ten times
my daily dose of weirdness
in the last hour,
so let's just call it
a night, okay?
What? You can't just--
-Nope. No, no, no, nope, nope.
-But--!
( groans )
Eclypsa! Wait.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I need to ask
you something.
( sighs ) So,
that's about it.
Every night I still go all
"Rah! Butterfly monster!"
Oh, I just wish
I could stop it.
Do you need to stop it?
You saw what happened tonight.
It was horrible!
What about the other times?
Were they so horrible?
Well, no, not exactly.
In fact,
they were really fun.
They were actually
the most amazing dreams
I've ever had.
I wouldn't run
from these dreams.
I would embrace them,
see where they take me.
Really? You think I should
just let them happen?
It's the only way to learn
what you're truly capable of.
All knowledge
is good knowledge,
I always say!
Well, I should get back
to my tower
before the guards
realize I'm missing.
Oh, yeah, how did you
break out of there, anyway?
I thought you were
under tower arrest.
So long as we're
spilling secrets--
Oh, Captain!
Permission to come aboard?
( bell clangs )
What?!
I never knew
that was there!
Yes, I used these secret tunnels
constantly when I was your age.
All knowledge
is good knowledge, my dear.
( crickets chirping )
Okay, so the chains
were a bust, but how about--?
Actually, Marco, I don't need
you to watch me tonight.
Oh! Did you figure out
how to stop transforming?
No, but I thought
maybe I should see
what I'm capable of,
or whatever.
Star, you don't know
anything about this.
Yeah, and I'll never know
anything about it
if I keep trying
to stop it.
I know it's weird,
but I really need
to see this through, okay?
Okay, I guess, but could
you at least take
my dimensional scissors
with you
in case you get trapped?
Sorry, Marco,
but if I'm gonna do this,
I can't do it halfway.
Okay, fine!
I tried to help!
No one can say
I didn't try!
Because I tried.
So if you die out there,
don't go blaming me,
all right?
- All right!
Well...
good luck out there.
Globgor.
Yeah, Gloss, I'm not sure she
can do this alone, either.
MAN: Deep in the sand,
a wicked ember glows,
though all around,
a chilling wind doth blow.
With heat and spark
and smoke uncurled,
bring forth the fires
of the underworld!
-( laughter )
-( playfully ) Get back here!
I'm gonna claw you in the head!
I love how ♪ spooky ♪
underworld beaches are.
Isn't that kind of...
the underworld's thing?
Yeah, it's pretty metal.
Hey, Star, finished
your marshmallow.
Aw, I finished
yours, too! Twins.
( blowing )
Wait a second--
is that one of my hoodies?
Yeah, I gave him
a spare one for the beach.
I gave it
a little custom job.
-You want me to do yours?
-No! Oh, man!
( sighs ) Kelly, can I have
one of yours?
Um, I actually licked
all of these.
Yeah, okay, never mind.
Aw, it's okay, Marco,
you can have our last one.
Here you go, dude.
Oh, man, the Soulrise
is gonna be
♪ so great ♪ this year!
Hoo-yeah, and we got such
a good spot to watch it.
What are you jerks
doing in our spot?!
Your spot?
We were here first!
Yeah, I don't see
your name on it.
Well, maybe you
need more eyes.
Hey, back
off my girlfriend, man.
Sounds like this guy's
looking for a fight.
There's only one way
to settle this.
-( grunts )
-( gasps )
BOTH: Yeah!
MARCO: How are
we settling this?
How are we settling this?
Let's go! Ugh!
( players grunting )
MARCO: I got it!
I got it!
Point, Team Ulric.
-Ha ha!
-Yah!
( grunting )
Kelly, it's yours!
-BOTH: What?
-That's cheating!
Hey, your friend
looked upset.
Maybe you should
check on her.
Kelly! Guys,
where did Kelly go?
It's okay. We can
still take these chumps.
Star and I haven't even
unleashed our secret weapon.
( both whooping )
Fine. Marco will fix it.
( impact grunt )
Kelly?
Did you say Skelly?
No, I said Kelly.
What's up with Skelly?
'Cause that's me.
Oh, hey. Hey, there.
I'm Skelly, too.
Have you guys
seen my friend?
I don't know, man,
but I'll fight ya.
I just wanna
find my friend.
She's, like, this tall
and has a lot of body hair.
No?
Sounds like
I could take her.
Two on two sound fair?
Okay, well, uh,
thanks anyway.
He seemed nice.
Are... you okay?
No...
Tad and I broke up.
Oh... sorry.
I-- I mean, you guys
will probably work it out.
You always do, you know.
No. This is
very much the end.
Oh. Well, I know
how you feel.
Jackie and I
split up, too.
Hey, if you need
to talk-- Aah!
( grunts,
yells in retaliation )
Jorby, what
are you doing?
Oh, I don't know, Kelly,
what are you doing?
Is this
your new sparring partner?
You know what?
I had to fight Greg.
Greg! And I killed him
in, like, three seconds!
You didn't kill Greg.
Yeah, well,
I killed his pride.
Leave her alone, man!
She's going through some stuff.
We all are! Everyone's
in a constant state
of falling apart.
Existential war cry!
Does everyone
on this stupid beach
wanna fight?
( grunting )
Stop! I cannot--
( sighs )
I cannot deal with
this much static right now.
Sorry, man, I didn't know.
I'd help you talk to her,
but I got my own lady
I gotta deal with.
( gibberish )
I'm coming!
Oh, kill me.
Kelly, wait up!
I just wanted to say
if you need to talk--
( sputters ) I don't know
who I am anymore.
All I know is I'm tired
of being Tad's girlfriend,
and I can't seem to move on.
That stuff takes time.
I know, but--
( sighs )
Tad's still in here.
He'll always be in here,
but it gets eas--
No, Marco, he hasn't
moved out yet.
He's still in here.
Wait, what?
He just isn't getting it,
and I've already hurt
him too much.
I could try talking to him.
Really? Hmm, well.
Maybe he'll
listen to you.
You are
his best friend.
( laughs nervously )
I am?
Come on in.
-In there?
-Yeah.
-In your hair?
-Yeah!
Get in here! Get it?
"Get in hair."
Um, hey, Tad.
Oh, hey, bestie.
( sighs )
Kelly dumped me again.
Yeah, that's why I'm here.
She asked me
to come talk to you.
Are we getting
back together?
No. She needs you
to move out, bud.
She keeps saying that,
but I've been looking.
Oh! That's great. Where?
Mm, like, on the back
of these pizza boxes?
Uh, inside these chip bags?
At the bottom
of these soda pops?
Look, dude, I felt
the same way
when Jackie and I split.
That's your B., man.
Kelly and I break up
and make up constantly.
We'll get back together
in no time,
so why even bother
getting out of this chair?
Tad, it's for real this time.
You're harshing
my groove, Marco.
Dude, Kelly wants to move on.
You should give her that chance.
-Come on, man!
-No!
You're just making yourself
miserable hanging around her.
( sighs ) You're right.
You're the expert.
Well, yeah, I'm an expert
in many things-- Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
How you're making
yourself miserable
hanging around Star.
What?! Psst.
What does Star
have to do with it?
If anything,
I'm miserable because--
because Jackie dumped me.
Marco, you didn't come here
for the Soulrise.
Yes, I did.
Oh, Marco, Marco,
Marco, Marco, Marco...
-( yowls )
-Shh.
I've been watching you
all night.
You have feelings
for your best friend, dude.
What?! No! No. No...
Dude, you have
dimensional scissors!
You could be
knocking back soda pops
and crushing pizzas
in any dimension!
And you're choosing
to live with
your unavailable crush.
When it comes to making
yourself miserable,
you are the master, bro.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Marco, are you okay?
-No...
-Buddy?
No... no.
KELLY: Hey, did you
talk to him? Marco!
♪ All my plans
are falling apart... ♪
It's okay. Ice cream melts,
but our love is forever.
( groaning )
I'd fight anyone
for you, babe.
Who would
you fight, me?
To the death!
Aww!
( groans )
I'm glad
I found you, Skelly.
Me too, Skelly.
Being in love
with your best friend is great!
♪ And I don't want to see ♪
♪ The things
that I've been shown ♪
♪ But I can't shut my eyes ♪
♪ So I'll walk away alone ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
( zipping noises )
Oh, there you are.
Whatever you said
to Tad worked.
He moved out.
I feel lighter already.
Also, I think
the zipper works,
so, yeah,
you don't need to--
I'm glad that that
worked out for you.
I know that face.
Come on,
Kelly's driving.
( grunting )
I'll walk!
You know, Tad and I?
We used to come
to every Soulrise.
So why come here now?
I love the Soulrise.
I don't want it to be
a place that makes me sad.
The only thing I could
think to do was face it,
rewrite it,
so it was mine again.
Where... are we?
Should we even be here?
It's the best view
of the Soulrise!
Ladder!
Wow. You can
see everything.
KELLY: Told ya!
MARCO: I guess
we should
go find Star
and Tom, huh?
They don't need this.
They haven't earned it.
( zapping )
Uh, what are you doing?
Oh, I was just trying
to warmthen you...
you know,
you looked cold.
( sighs )
Thanks.
I... I was cold.
( screeching )
Is-- is that thing--?
Wah! Oh! Ha ha! Sorry.
Is it past midnight?
Yeah.
Then it's my birthday.
Happy birthday,
Marco Diaz.
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ There goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪