♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another,
whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[whistling]
[inhales deeply]
I'm back.
Uh, what?
I said, "I'm back!"
What y'all doing?!
[all cheering]
Yes, yes, I'm very excited
to see me, too.
I know how it feels.
Ponyhead,
I missed you so much!
Girl, boundaries.
Now look, I been cooped up
with my batty sisters
for way too long.
So, I need to brunch,
and then I need to party,
pronto!
-Who wants to watch?
-[all] I do, I do!
[scratching]
[giggling, cheering]
[laughing]
[all laughing]
[laughs]
[awkward laughter]
[all laughing]
That's what it is!
Okay, that's great,
but who wants to
get brunched in the face?
Hold on, there.
Come with me
to my office.
You have a office?
You do realize those robots
are killing machines, right?
We reprogrammed them.
A lot of things
have changed here,
and if you wanna brunch,
you gonna have to
pass a new final.
I know how to brunch, Patty!
All right, then.
What are the four
pillars of brunch?
[scoffs] Waffles.
Mm-hmm.
Eh, eggs, obviously.
Uh-huh.
Buh-- B-B-B-Bacon?
-Yeah.
-Ugh, and, uh...
Hold on, it's on the tip
of my tongue.
Now you're making me nervous.
Uh, uh, uh...
Uh...
And more bacon.
You're gonna have
to take the exam.
What?
I gotta take a waffle test?!
That's crazy!
I'm not doing that, okay?
I invented brunch!
Did y'all hear that?
Old Underarm wants me to
take a test just to eat.
[laughs] Yeah, Ponyhead.
It's so cool that you
can get through brunch
without passing a final,
but some of us
aren't as cool as you.
Well, sorry.
No need to get
all emotional about it.
I guess, huh?
What I'm saying is...
Maybe if you don't like
the way things are here now,
you should just go.
Come on, girls.
What?
[Star]
Hey, girl! Or boy.
Sorry I missed your call.
Leave a message after the--
[beeps]
Girl, you would not believe
how whack St. O's is now.
They're trying to make your girl
take a brunch test.
-[Coachman] Aah!
-[gasps]
Ponyhead!
[evil laughter]
Oh, no!
[growls]
Princess Arms! Oh...
What do you want?
It's Ms. Heinous!
She's trying to take back
the school!
-[gasps]
-[alarm blaring]
[gasps] It's Ms. Heinous.
-Full house, girls!
-[all yelling]
[all screaming]
Do not let them
enter the school!
[grunts]
[Gemini]
Oh, M'lady!
[cackles]
What-- What are you doing?
-[beeping]
-[gasps]
[all crying out]
-[sobbing]
-Come on!
Don't just stare
at it. [grunts]
Oh, no.
Everyone back inside!
[grunts]
[Ms. Heinous grunting]
Lower the pizza boxes!
[sobbing]
We're gonna die!
-No, we're not.
-Yeah, this is like
a year's worth of pizza.
There's no way she's
getting through this.
Shh!
Listen.
I think they stopped.
Did you miss me?
Wah!
[Princesses screaming]
[grunts]
Whoa!
[Gemini chuckles]
All right, girls, Plan B!
[Princess Arms]
Hold it right there!
If you wanna get
to the brunch room,
you're gonna have to
go through us.
[shudders]
[Princesses screaming]
[distant screaming]
-Oh!
-[loud eating]
Ponyhead,
you're alive?!
[loud gulp]
What are you doing?
I'm brunching
on your four pillars
before Heinous finds me.
[gasps]
She's after you?
Isn't everybody?
[loud crashing, sizzling]
If I don't make it out of this,
I want you to know...
I hate you.
What?
[door creaks]
[mechanical whirring]
Young lady, did you unplug me?
Good morning, St. Olga.
Oh, no.
You changed your look.
It's called a tail,
and I think
I look great with it.
I think you looked better
without it.
Well, I think
she looks great
with or without--
[groans]
I need you to show me
my master file.
Of course.
A trip down memory lane.
I found you when you were
just a street baby.
I raised you as my own
out of the goodness
of my heart,
and I managed to find
the perfect work-life balance.
Show me the real master file!
I do not know
what you are talking about.
There we go.
You know, my mind's
been wandering so much lately,
I thought I could use
a little refresher--
get me back on track.
Time for a nice,
relaxing brain massage.
[Heinous]
No, not that memory!
Rewind more.
Go back.
Mother, why do I have to
hide my tail?
You know that
old rhyme, dear.
Boys do not make passes
at girls
with devil tails.
No, rewind.
Oh, Mommy,
Mommy, look!
My cheeks are glowing.
Isn't it pretty?
Do you know what
would make you
even prettier?
What, Mommy?
Suppressing your flaws.
[Young Heinous]
Mommy, wait!
I can fix it.
Please, not this memory.
Go back further.
King Shastacan,
the Lady St. Olga
is here to see you.
Oh, St. Olga,
thank you for coming.
This.
This is it.
This baby is unfit
to inherit the kingdom.
She's absolutely heinous.
[sneezes]
Heinous,
what a pretty name.
Mewni should've been mine.
I did my best
raising you.
All the other robot moms
laughed behind my back.
It was not easy.
You should thank me.
Yeah, thank you!
Hey! This school has
become so dear to me
since I got here
ten minutes ago!
And I did not come here
to watch you destroy it.
-[growling]
-Ooh, you know what?
You are clearly
going through some things,
that actually, I'm just gonna
circle back later. Wow.
-[growls]
-[Ponyhead] Aah!
I'm just gonna
sneak by you.
Oh, Rasticore.
Hmm.
Looks like it's just
you and me now.
Yeah, about that.
I really appreciate you
nursing me back to health
and all, but uh...
Look, you're great.
Uh, you know that.
Why am I telling you, huh?
Ugh! I'm so bad
at these things.
I don't deserve
a gal like you.
-What?
-Uh...
I'm so busy
with this job.
I'm addicted to work.
Sometimes I say to myself,
"You know, Rasticore,
wouldn't it be cool
if you could meet Heinous
like four years from now?"
It's Meteora.
Yeah, yeah. See?
I don't even
know your name.
Such a jerk. Ugh, yeah.
I gotta go.
But promise me this one thing:
Twenty years from now
if we meet up,
and we're both still single,
you'll be my soulmate.
What am I talking about?
That's not gonna happen.
You're gonna find
some awesome guy
that's gonna steal you
away from me.
Looks like it's just
-you and me.
-Ugh!
Uh, if you wanted my heart,
[powering down]
all you had to do was ask.
Oh, Rasticore.
Time to take back
the throne of Mewni.
I take you, FoolDuke.
I take you, Ruberiot.
[both]
In sickness and in health.
Till death do we part.
Through pirate attacks,
monster raids, and corn famine.
I do.
[all cheering]
Aww, mazel tov!
[lively music]
Isn't this
just beautiful?
It's too bad
Ponyhead never showed up.
Yeah, the photo booth is--
[gasps]
Photo booth.
Okay. Well, I'm just gonna
go get some pie, then.
No way! [gasps]
Wait, Marco, Marco, Marco!
You can't leave yet.
We gotta take pictures!
But I gotta take Nachos home
and feed her.
-Kelly can do it.
Let's go!
-No, wait!
Do not take her for a ride!
You got that, Kelly?!
Kelly! Aah!
Yeah, for sure.
Totes.
[Star]
Wow...
The memories
in this place.
Star, can I go?
Oh, my gosh! [gasps]
[grunting, panting]
Look! Old photos from our
days at the bounce lounge.
Can we just take photos
some other time?
Sure, as soon as
we take some photos.
[groans]
-What?
-Money.
Excuse me?
What? Money--
give me, give me.
Now, come on!
Where is it?
Star, I'm not
made of money.
Yes, you are.
Oh! Found it.
Ohh!
Six hundred fifty dollars!
See, Marco?
You're a boy made of money.
Yeah, yeah,
that should be enough.
[Star hums tune]
First let's do
a silly one.
Wah! [chuckles]
Ooh! Okay, now
a fighting stance.
Hi-yah!
Ooh! Okay,
now let's do one
where we're stuck
inside a monster's belly,
and we're slowly drowning
in its toxic stomach acid.
[inhales sharply] Blech!
Okay, I go now.
Wait! [grunts]
One more!
Best friend pose.
Oh, boy, oh, boy,
oh, boy, here we go!
What the--
Marco, what is this?
They look like photos.
These aren't photos.
They're travesties.
Gee, Star.
I asked for
best friend photos,
but these are business
acquaintance photos.
So...
Okay, let me look
at the old photos.
What do we got here?
Happy-go-lucky, fish face,
"Oops, I did it again,"
too cool for school.
Okay, let's do it.
Ooh! [sighs]
Perfect! Well, see ya!
You know you have
my ankle, right?
Something's... [sighs]
Something's not right.
What?
These are
exactly the same.
I don't know what you want.
I want your face to
look like this face.
I was just making that face!
Yours was a fake face.
This is a best friend face.
I know the difference.
Nope, that's not it.
Something's off.
These are all travesties!
Enough shenanigans.
It's time to get real.
Too big to fail.
Come on, Marco!
Star, I'm trying.
I know you are, Marco.
But it's not
good enough!
[alarm blaring]
[both]
Hmm?
[straining]
-Oh, we're stuck!
-[engine revving]
[gasps]
Oh, no!
-[engine revving]
-[laughing]
Oh, yeah!
Help! Let us out!
It's an emergency!
[bell dings]
It's here.
-[both startle]
-Star?
What the heck is that?
[mumbles]
Did somebody say "emergency"?
Who are you?
I'm Ben Fotino.
Booth repair
extraordinaire.
[laughs]
Does Ponyhead know
you live in her photobooth?
Does a hot dog have bones in it?
Dude, I don't know.
Can you let us out
of here, please?
Well, I'd like to,
but I can't.
It's broken.
Gonna have to take you back
to my shop for repairs.
[cackles]
Wait, what's happening?
-[cackling]
-[Marco] Where are you
taking us? No!
No! No, no, no, no, no, no!
-[evil laughter]
-Let us out of here!
We gotta get
out of here!
[grunts]
[screeching]
[screams]
[panting]
[sighs]
Hey-- Hey, Ben?
Could you get us
out of here, please?!
Gotta get my mind juices
warmed up.
[gulping loudly]
Ahh.
Hmm.
[straining]
Aah! Whoa, whoa!
Hmm.
Hmm...
Well, I think
I found your problem.
-Really?
-Now, this here photobooth
ain't just any photobooth.
Is it... Is it magic?
-It's magic!
-Oh, no.
This booth can look
deep into your soul
seeing all truths that lie
beneath them pictures.
Wow.
Well, what does
it want from us?
Heck if I know.
I ain't no magic photobooth.
Ugh! I hate magic.
-Marco!
-Sorry.
I told you something was up
with those photos, bub.
I knew it, the booth knew it,
-your face knew it.
-What does my face know?
That we're not taking
best friends photos.
Give the people
what they want.
Well, this is gonna
take a while.
Good luck getting out
of that death trap.
[snoring]
All right,
what's going on here?
You used to love the photobooth.
You're my little
camera hog.
I'm-- I'm just worried
about Nachos.
And call me crazy,
but I didn't want to end up
on a magical adventure today.
But nope, magical adventure.
[Ben snoring]
Well, I like
our adventures,
and I thought you
liked them, too.
And we only got
one money left.
What? Where'd it go?
Photobooths are expensive.
Plus, I gave a tip to Ben.
Much obliged.
This is all
we got left.
[sighs]
You wanna know what's
different in this photo?
This was before.
Before what?
Before you told me...
you had a crush on me.
[gasps, sighs]
I just blacked out.
Mm, go on.
Well, I was caught
off-guard by it,
and then like a Marco,
I never brought it up again,
and that stunk.
I stunk.
Well, a lot was going on,
but yeah, that stunk.
It's getting harder
to end up on
these adventures
pretending things
aren't different.
Are they?
They are for me.
Oh.
Oh. Oh!
Like different,
different?
[sighs]
[groans]
Well, no wonder
we're stuck here
hearing truth bombs like that.
[imitates explosion]
Weird question, but what
do your guts feel like?
My guts?
Yeah, my guts
were all like,
[gibbers]
You know?
Uh, my guts
are more like,
[long groan]
[chuckles]
Well, they do feel better
after you talk about it.
Yeah, I guess.
Last photo.
Anything you need
to tell me?
No, but there's
one last thing
I need to do.
What's that?
Take the photo the booth
is waiting for.
Go get 'em, tiger!
[exhales sharply]
Uh...
[rowdy music]
Congratulations!
Three cheers
for the happy new couple!
Hip, hip...
Huzzah!
[Star groaning]
Star? I'm sorry.
It's just the booth.
It's magic!
-[giggles]
-What?
That photobooth ain't magic.
It's just a booth!
[laughing]
Did-- Did you trap us in there?
Look, I seen a lot of pictures
in my day,
and your photo showed two
young'uns who needed a smooch.
You trapped us in there.
I trapped you in there.
Okay, back in the booth.
We kissed.
I thought the booth was magic.
You're my squire.
Which is a job
I take very seriously.
I have a boyfriend.
His name is Tom.
I was just trying to
get us out of here!
Hey...
I'm glad you were
honest with me.
Just maybe not
that honest.
I'm sorry.
At least it can't
get more awkward.
Whoo!
-Okay.
-That's enough photobooth.
Now if you kids
need any more help,
you know where
to find me.
-Creep.
-[loud chomping]
Nachos! [sighs]
Oh, I was so worried
you took her out
on a joyride.
Eh, ye of little faith.
[engine revving]
See ya--
I'll see ya later, Star.
Hey, boo, sorry.
I've been off
falling in love
with this pie!
[laughs]
Man, it's getting
pretty serious.
Am I the only one
who loves this pie?
[phone ringing]
Hey, there's your phone.
Hello?
Something's wrong with Pony.
[startles]
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry
when it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪