♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Oh. Hello, children.
Uh... hey.
You should be at home
with the door locked.
We're here for your...
to see your haunted house.
But this is
the most dangerous place to be.
( sniffs )
Well, then,
step inside...
at your peril.
Is this a joke?
Just remember our deal.
Perhaps you are
more brave than smart.
Or perhaps you are
just like me.
Perhaps you, too,
have sympathy for the monster.
Oh, boy.
But beware.
( gasps )
Do not do
what I have done.
You must never
let the monster inside.
( mechanical grunting )
I can't do this.
Can you turn on
the lights, please?
Look, man, you seem like
a nice guy,
and I wanna
be scared,
I really do.
But the truth is,
I'm eight.
That's like 90 years old
in Halloween years.
Next year, we might not even
be afraid of monsters.
I don't wanna
waste my time.
I'm sorry.
You're just not scary.
I'm not scary?
Come on, guys.
Let's go to a real
haunted house.
We had a deal, remember?
( grunting )
Okay. Halloween is over.
Janna and Star
need to go home now.
Dad, Star lives here.
( laughs )
Yes, Marco.
It doesn't always
have to be an argument.
Sometimes we just
do what Daddy says.
( straining )
Now if anybody needs me,
I'll be in the shed.
( struggling )
He does this every year,
and it makes him miserable.
Okay, so what do we do?
Oh, I got it.
Let's go to that other house
down the street
and just ditch this one.
What? No.
You're missing
the point.
How do we make my dad's
haunted house scary?
We can always summon
Hungry Larry.
Uh... who?
Oh, Hungry Larry.
You know, you summon him,
he comes and haunts your house.
I hear he's a real creep.
We're not summoning...
anyone.
We're not summoning... ugh!
I can't believe I even have to
have this conversation with you.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go bribe
some five-year-olds.
Maybe they'll think
my dad's scary.
No summoning.
Okay, it says here,
"If Hungry Larry is
the haunt you need,
do these actions
and you'll succeed.
A lick of mustard
you must bear,
off an old takeout menu
if you dare."
All right.
Done.
"Then three times
his name is said.
Arrive he does
with scares and dread."
BOTH: Hungry Larry.
Hungry Larry.
( knocking )
Uh, Star Butterfly?
You summoned me.
Can I come in or what?
Star, invite him in.
Please, come on in.
Honey, I know you're
probably totally humiliated
that you wrestled
that blow-up doll
in front of your son
and his friends,
but everyone inside
loves you.
( sighs )
There's a bowl of candy corn
for you out here on the porch.
Don't step on it.
Rafael, I can see you
in the window!
So, basically,
we just need the house
to be, like,
super scary.
Mr. Diaz hasn't scared
a single kid all night.
Actually, I don't know
if he's ever scared
a single kid ever.
But Janna and I
are pretty handy,
so how can we help?
- ( practicing scary noises )
- Larry?
( continues practicing )
Larry,
whatcha doing?
Oh, you guys
are still here?
We're not guys.
Cool.
Can you leave?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, fine.
You're working.
I get it.
You guys
are still here?
That guy isn't scary.
He's creepy.
( sighs ) Bummer.
I really just wanted Mr. D.
to have his haunted house.
Even if you did give him
a haunted house,
that wouldn't make
Mr. Diaz scary.
Yeah, maybe not.
But at least
it'd be something.
Should we just
call it off?
You mean fire
Hungry Larry?
I guess.
Oh, can I fire him?
- Go for it.
- Yes!
Poor Mr. Diaz.
( Janna shrieks )
( shrieking continues )
Star, what was that?
- Uh, I think
it was Janna.
- ( doorbell rings )
( clamoring )
Hey, did that scream come from
inside of this haunted house?
Uh...
Yes. Welcome, kids,
to the Diaz
House of Horror!
( cheering )
Star, seriously.
What is going on?
Okay, Marco, I know
you said no summoning,
but we summoned,
we summoned Hungry Larry.
You what?!
Oh, Chill, Marco.
Everyone's having
a great time.
Can't you hear
all those bloodcurdling screams?
( silence )
I don't hear
anything, Star.
Candy.
Uh, no duh.
It's Halloween.
This is saliva.
Hungry Larry?
( screams )
Where's Hungry Larry?
He's... still... hungry.
( kids screaming )
KIDS: I'm still hungry.
What the...
Hungry for what?
Marco!
( splashing )
KIDS ( whispering ):
I'm still hungry.
( voices echoing )
GIRL: I'm still...
KIDS: ...hungry.
( shrieking )
( loud metal music plays )
Oh, no, no, no.
( blow-up doll groaning )
Honey, I'm... I'm sorry.
I thought this year
was going to be different.
Honey?
Kids?
Marco, Marco, Marc... oh!
Wet ceiling.
Oh!
Kids.
( eerie voices )
They're in here.
Who are you?
( many voices )
I'm Hungry...
( clears throat )
( one voice )
I'm Hungry Larry.
I've been summoned here
to haunt your home,
because you're
not scary.
But where is my family?
I told you.
They're in...
( many voices )
...here.
- Help!
- Get us out of here!
Kids!
Oh, your wife
is in here, too.
Um, uh, somewhere.
She's pretty.
Oh. Thank you.
I would eat you, too,
but I'm stuffed.
So, uh,
count your blessings.
I guess.
But my family
is my blessings.
Oh.
What I meant to say was,
get out!!
Give me back
my family!
( girl shrieking )
( all screaming )
Aww!
Mr. Diaz!
You were terrifying
in there.
Best Halloween ever!
Yeah, Dad,
that was amazing.
It's like I always say.
Nothing more terrifying
than a man
who has lost everything.
Leave this place.
LARRY: How rude. Whatever.
Oh, man!
( coughing and groaning )
We got chewed up
and spit out.
Why the sour
word play, guys?
How about some
Cold Ones
for my number ones?
Yeah, you're all
my number ones. Ha ha!
You're number one,
Spider.
I don't know why you guys
are acting all sore,
because the battle I saw
was like,
"Oh, I'm Mr. Bad Guy.
I'm gonna eat up
the childrens."
And then the warnicorns
came in and were all, like,
( roaring )
and the bad guy was, like,
"I didn't mean any harm."
He is totally right.
No, no!
( laughing )
And, the piece de resistance,
that Narwhal Blast!
( yelling )
( laughing and cheering )
STAR: Toothpaste
tidal blast!
You're up, bud.
Looks like Star's
getting ready for bed.
See you guys
in the morning.
Night, dude.
Night.
( gibberish )
Hey, Spider, we all
really appreciate you.
Everything we do is the most
important life or death
situation all the time,
and it's nice to be greeted
with something frivolous,
something light.
See you in the morning, bud.
Hey, Narwhal.
For real, how do you do
that Narwhal Blast?
It's easy.
You hear the call,
and your warrior spell
instincts kick in.
It's like...
Narwhal Blast!
But hey, I like
the way you do it.
Good night.
Spider with a top hat
blast!
I will break you.
Spider with a top hat
blast!
Blast!
Top hat blast!
( alarm clock buzzing )
( groaning )
( buzzing continues )
Rise and shine.
Whoo! Whoo hoo!
Yeah!
Morning!
Whee!
Oh, everyone's happy.
( all exclaiming )
Morning spells.
Ooh.
( all gasping )
Oh. Ow!
Ow.
( cracking )
Ow. Ow.
Are you okay?
What happened
to your leg?
I'm fine.
I just slept funny.
Oh, Spider, everything
you do is funny.
( giggling )
Let's curl it!
( straining )
Hey, Rock, can I work out
a few sets with you?
It's Spider!
So you wanna work out
with the big dogs?
Start with a one-ounce
and a two-ounce.
Actually, I want
a big weight like
you guys.
Oh, yeah, well,
you should probably
leave the big weights
to us, Spider dog.
But I can do it.
Uh, well, he does have
the headband. Okay.
Let 'er rip, boys.
( struggling )
I'm doin' it, guys!
Guys, look.
I'm doin' it.
Uh, we haven't let go
of it yet.
( straining )
Oh, well, come on,
let it go then.
Spider? You good?
Uh... how do you do it?
Take that kind of punishment
every day
and go back for more?
I don't know.
Push through the pain, I guess.
Yeah, I kinda
like the pain.
Pain!
BOTH: Pain!
Spider with a top hat blast!
Get up, Spider.
Push through the pain.
Is that the face
of a quitter?
No!!
( mirror shatters )
Warrior spirit!
Spider with
a top hat blast!
Spider with a... top hat.
Huh?
( gasps )
Spider.
Narwhal, I got
something to show you.
All right, what is it?
Spider with
a top hat blast!
Dude, that's hilarious.
( raucous laughter )
No. I'm being serious.
Oh, I thought
you were kidding.
Look, singing and dancing
is great,
but fighting,
you could get hurt.
Or worse.
You could get
Star killed.
Good night.
( crying )
Hey, Spider.
Come on.
Honey, is everything
all right?
- I hope so.
- ( baby cries )
( groaning )
( coughs )
11:30?
We overslept.
I gotta get
to work, honey.
- Everybody up.
- This isn't good, guys.
- Where's Spider, dog?
- What happened to Spider?
He didn't
wake us up.
Uh, Spider,
you okay?
You're acting funny.
Not like funny-funny.
Like something's wrong-funny.
Everyone's really
worried about you,
especially me.
Yeah, we missed
your morning dance number
with the bubbles.
Yeah, and the lights.
What? Did I fail
to entertain you?
Um, yes, you did.
Well, I'm sorry if I don't
feel like being
your little
dancing clown today.
Fine. We'll make
our own coffee.
STAR: Cupcake blast!
Come on, Spider.
What's up?
All of my life,
I've had this crazy dream,
and now, the dream is dead.
STAR: Emerald snake strike!
Honeybee tornado swarm!
Flying pig blast!
Wow, that's a lot
of spells at once.
Mega Narwhal blast!
Whoa, whoa!
MAKEUP BLAST: Sweetheart?
He'll be fine.
It's not a big deal until
she calls out the--
Warnicorn stampede!
Bean bag monster
metamorphosis!
Toothpaste tidal blast!
Wait, those aren't
even warrior spells.
This has never
happened before.
What do we do?
Makeup Blast!
Is anyone left?
Hello?
Rock!
( groaning )
Star's calling you next.
But I'm just
an entertainment spell.
I can't fight.
You have fire
in you, Spider.
I hear you in there,
throwing yourself
at that wall every night.
( coughing ) You've got
the hat of a warrior.
Hat?
Wait. No, I mean heart.
You've got
the heart of a warrior, bro.
You just gotta
dig deep to find it.
( coughing )
No!!
I can't do this alone.
Spider with
a top hat blast!
( crying )
Where's Rainbow Fist?
I can't see.
I can't see!
Spider, you have to help--
Bean bag!
A spider with a top hat?
How is that gonna help?
Marco!
( ferocious roar )
( Star screams )
( coughing )
Bro, remember
what I told you.
You have the hat
of a warrior.
Uh, I'm Spider with a top hat.
And a laser cannon.
War cry!!
( groaning )
Star?
Spider with a top hat did it!
My little top hat,
strongest spell I've got.
You did great
out there, Spider.
( all cheering )
Any time you wanna get
pumped up with us,
it's okay with me.
( cheering )
STAR: Spider with
a top hat blast!
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪