♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puuuhh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
CHOIR:
♪ Born to the wilds,
a gift from above ♪
♪ A story of triumph,
a story of love ♪
♪ An army of rodents
with he at the helm ♪
♪ He toppled the old king,
brought peace to the realm ♪
♪ Handsome and fearless
and brilliant and tall ♪
♪ Beloved by Mewmans,
he tends to us all  ♪
♪ Our dearest King Ludo,
he tends to us all ♪
Ah, yes, this is wonderful.
Let's hear it for Ms. Bucket
and the Mewnese Youth Choir!
Yeah?
( tepid applause, cheers )
( rats squeaking )
( enthusiastic applause )
That was good. Huh?
Oh, you're right.
You're right, they were
a touch off key.
Levitato!
Aaah!
Singin' with the angels.
Play me out, boys!
♪♪
Throne room, sir?
Full steam, Manfred!
Yes'm.
Hmm. Remind me
to levitato Manfred.
( band audible in distance )
( humming along )
That is--is catchy.
Huh?
Aaah!
Manfred! Manfred,
my most trusted ally!
I need you!
Aaah!
( crash )
Where's my dad?
Ah, Butterfly?
Where's my dad!
Are you out of your mind?
( grunts )
( roars )
( both grunt )
Hmm?
Hmm? But it's not a good time.
You're talking
to your hand, dude.
Hold on!
I have to take this.
Ah, look, this is
not a good time
to have this conversation.
Okay, so, my hand said
I can't destroy you,
so I have put you
in the dungeon.
For the last time,
where is dad?
Didn't you hear the song?
Ohh. I defeated him.
( giggles ) I levitato'd him!
And now I'm king.
You what-a-ta-tay-to'd him?
Levitato. Ta-tato. Tato!
Levitato!
You're Princess of Mewni
and you don't even
know levitato?
You don't know, do you?
You're being controlled,
Ludo.
You're right. You're right,
I am being controlled.
Controlled by my lust for power!
No, Ludo, you're being
controlled by Toffee.
What? No, Toffee's dead!
I did this. Me. See that?
Me! Me!
And now I'm doing this, too.
Take her to the dungeon!
It's your waaaaand!
Ohh! You think
you're so tough!
Get back here,
you jerks!
( grunting )
( banging on door )
( hinges creak )
Marco?
Star!
Hai-yah!
Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
Okay, that was dumb.
Probably shoulda used the keys.
I can't believe you're here.
I was thinkin' we'd maybe
never see each other--
Star?
Your horns...
are poking me.
Take 'em off.
( rustling sound )
Your stomach
just made a weird noise.
Yeah, that was supposed
to be a surprise.
I brought you this...
box of Captain Blanche's
Sugar Seeds.
Sorry there's none left.
Me and your dad ate 'em all
when were locked up
in the dungeon.
Aw, man, you guys
got to eat cereal together
in the dungeon?
Jealous.
Star, your dad, he--
Yeah, I know.
Ludo tev-a-tay-tato'd
ta-potato'd him.
If Ludo mastered it,
it can't be dangerous.
I think it's kinda bad, Star.
Marco, honestly,
he's been through worse.
Way worse.
I think we have
bigger problems right now.
Well, you're in luck, Star.
( whistles bird call )
Come on, guys,
we practiced this.
( bird call )
Mourning dove?
FOOLDUKE:
That's not what doves
sound like on Mewni.
Argh! Just get down here.
Star, allow me
to introduce...
la resistance!
MARCO: The easiest way
to depose a ruler
is to destroy
his credibility.
So this virtual pet
will represent Ludo.
And this $650 is us.
And this feather
is Bird and Spider.
Normally, they're always
with him or nearby,
except...Bird and Spider
break to feed
every five hours.
When he's alone,
we take this air duct
to the throne room.
And that's when Foolduke
hits him with...
Rubber chicken!
No.
( squeaks )
How about whoopee cushion?
No, we talked
about this before.
Ruberiot?
I have a ripping parody song
I've been working on.
He is great at ruining
people's lives with songs.
Marco, it seems like you guys
are just kinda playing pranks.
Yeah, we're still workin' on
that payoff part.
Okay, look,
what you're doing here is,
like, totally super-admirable,
and Marco, you've never
looked cuter in that beret,
but Ludo
is not the problem here.
Toffee is controlling him.
And I don't think a song
is gonna fix things--
Star, I was thinking ab--
Guards!
( rats squealing )
You'll never silence
the resistance!
You! You're coming with me!
Levitato.
Aaaah!
What the heck?
( gasping )
( panting, coughing )
STAR: Oh, of course.
All right, Ludo.
What are you gonna do now?
Levitato me again?
Oh, I'm so scared.
That was the worst.
Actually, you said
something earlier about my, um--
about my--
( clears throat )
--about my W-O-N-D.
Oh, so now you want my help?
Of course I want help!
I've been talking
to my own hand!
It keeps me up all night!
I can't sleep,
I can't think,
I can't focus on my new job
as Mewni's beloved monarch!
Wha--?
Oh, hello.
Yes, of course.
I-- No-- What?
Of course I'm beloved!
Didn't you hear the song?
Ludo! Why do you think
I came here without a wand?
Because...
you were surrendering?
It's corrupted! By Toffee!
He's in the wands, Ludo!
In the wa--
In the wands?!
Get him out!
I don't want to be corrupted!
How did he even get in there?
I don't know
how he got in there.
The last time I saw him, he--
Ooooooh.
( Ludo groans )
Yuck!
Ludo, please.
I think I know
how to get Toffee out.
And then I can go back
to being a beloved monarch?
Uh...yeah. ( laughs )
( whispering )
ALL (CHANTING):
We are the resistance!
We remain insistent!
We're the resistance!
You can't silence
the resistance!
And gimme back my beret.
( chanting continues )
( squeaking )
Wait, why are you--
Actually,
the resistance
can be quieter.
Be brave, Marco.
( chanting )
You may fall,
but the resistance lives on!
What?!
Why just me?
( blows landing )
Karate boy.
( squeaking )
Buffrog!
And...
Marco!
Queen Moon?
Where's Star?
Ludo took her.
We have to find him
before he does something awful.
What about
arts and crafts
friends?
The resistance
will live on without me.
ALL: What?
( grunting )
Star!
Hey, Mommy.
Hi, Marco.
I, uh...
I'm sorry, you guys.
( whinnies )
The-- The Whispering Spell.
No! Star! You get--
You get away!
You run away from there!
It's too late, Mom.
So does this mean
that everything's
back to normal?
It's not over yet.
What do you mean
it's not--
No!
MARCO: Star!
Oh, no.
Buffrog, we have to go now!
( grunts )
( shouts )
Ludo! Where's Star?
( gasping )
Where am I?
Where is my daughter?
Mom! Mom, Mom!
STAR'S VOICE:
I'm in here!
Star? Is that you?
Yes, it's me!
Oh, thank goodness! Oh!
Mom, stop it.
( kissing )
Oh, Star!
Where are you?
Well, I'm totally fine,
bu-but, ah,
I don't exactly
know where I am.
That's okay, sweetie.
The important thing is,
you're safe.
Just stay right there.
And no matter wh--we'll
find you--( voice breaking up )
Mom? Mom, can you repeat that?
( indistinct )
Star?
Are you still there?
Mommy?
Oh, what is happening?!
Mom!
( gasps )
Ohh, crazy eye, crazy eye,
crazy eye!
( whimpering )
Hello, Princess.
Toffee?! Aha!
I knew it! I knew it was you
all along!
Wha-- Wait.
Is all this goop you?
Ew ew ew ew ew ew ew.
You don't even recognize
your own magic
when you're swimming in it.
This stuff is the magic?
TOFFEE: It was.
Until I got here.
Oh, boy, that's not good.
Mom! We've got a problem!
TOFFEE: Only I can
speak to her now.
TOFFEE'S VOICE:
Hello, Moon.
Toffee.
( Marco gasps )
Give us back Star.
Oh, of course.
But I'd like
something from you first.
Something that belongs to me.
Take it.
No, Mom, stop!
I can take him!
Just hold on! Please!
( panting )
( cries out )
( whimpering )
TOFFEE:
Poor little Butterfly.
You've lost your wings.
Now, Your Majesty...
do we have a deal?
Good-bye.
No--No!
Yeech.
Where's my daughter?
Where's Star?
She's gone.
( gasping )
( crackling sound )
( Moon panting )
( Moon roars )
Oh.
( straining, grunting )
I call the darkness onto me
from deepest depths
of earth and sea.
From ancient evils unawoken
break the one
who can't be broken;
From blackest night
I pledge my soul
and crush my heart
to burning coal.
To summon forth
the deadly power
to see my hated foe devoured!
( crying )
Are you finished?
( groans )
Please...just tell me.
Did I have
any part to play in this?
No.
( gasps )
( gasping )
Oh!
Hmm. Come on. Come on.
What are you doing?
( Star panting )
( deep breath )
( muffled scream )
BUFFROG: Karate boy. Wake up.
I think the Queen, uh,
needs...help.
MOON: Come on, come on.
Why won't you fit?
Come on.
Queen?
But maybe if I-I put the wand
back together, it'll--
it'll--it'll bring her back.
But this piece won't fit.
MARCO: Here.
Try this one.
GLOSSARYCK: Hey, Star!
Does this need, uh, salt?
Hey, hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey--
Oh, knock it off!
More salt? More salt?
Bleeech!
More salt.
What is wrong with him?!
What's going on here?
Where am I?
I have no idea.
No one's ever been here before.
Oh, no. I'm dead. I'm dead.
I died!
( sighs )
Well, if you're dead,
then I'm dead.
And if you're calling me dead,
I find it--
well, I find it
a little insulting, frankly.
Oh, no.
I am totally dead.
And I'm stuck here.
With you.
Uh-huh? Again.
A little insulting.
You betrayed me!
I'm sorry it seemed that way.
Can we get beyond this?
And just enjoy
our time here together
in...wherever we are.
Ha! You think
I'm gonna stay here with you,
eat your dumb magic soup
while Toffee is out there
doing who knows what!
Star-
Marco and my mom
probably think I'm dead.
Star.
Maybe I am dead.
Star! Look at me.
This is where we are now.
And this soup
is not magic anymore,
it's just...soup.
So stop being foolish
and eat the soup.
( sniffles )
No.
I get what you're doing.
Mm-hmm. What am I doing?
This is just another one
of your games.
You're going out of your way
to make me get to this
on my own.
Oh, you didn't think
I'd catch on, Glossaryck,
because you think I'm a skimmer.
But am I dipper.
Star, what are you doing?
I'm getting us out of here.
Star! No! It's boiling!
Dip...dooown...
Ow!!!
Uh-oh.
( rumbling )
♪♪
Star!
Hi, Mom!
Hi, sweetie.
Don't you look lovely.
( distorted voice )
Where's Toffee?
( roaring )
( gasps )
ALL: Star!
Oh, my baby.
Hi.
ALL: Hi.
( squishy sound )
Huh?
( chuckling )
You think you've won?
Ha! You don't
make the plans--
I do! Me!
Only I know how
this all turns out!
It turns out you're dead.
That's what you get!
Hey! Look!
Look what I did!
All by myself!
Oh, no! I can't see a thing.
Ha ha!
Do you think
he's really gone?
Looks pretty gone
to me.
Can't get more gone than that!
Ohh!
MARCO: Star, I've never seen you
do a spell like that before.
STAR: Yeah, I'm not sure
what that was.
Eclipsa.
Okay, Princess,
I think we can both agree
that I've got
some stuff to work on.
You want me to
cut off the beard?
No!
Throw me back
in the void.
I need to...find myself.
I'm ready.
Do you, uh,
need a minute with them?
What, them?
I'm sorry.
I have intimacy issues.
Try to move on.
Okay.
Well, here goes.
Aaah!
Good luck.
CHOIR:
♪ An arm of eagles
with he at the helm ♪
♪ Rescued the children
and brought us all home ♪
♪ Handsome and fearless,
valiant and strong ♪
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
♪ Our dearest King River,
we praise him in song ♪
( eagle calls )
Papa!
That was amazing!
Ever since Ludo
levitato'd me,
I've been living
among the eagles.
They made me their king, too!
Where is Moon Pie?
I don't know.
She was just here.
( Moon panting )
( laughs )
Oh.
♪ She's a princess,
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry
when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will
keep the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪