♪♪
[upbeat music plays]
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird,
gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here,
I'm from another-- woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows,
I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puh-p-u-u-uh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
- [gavel bangs]
- All rise!
The court of
the Magical High Commission
is now in session.
Her Majesty, Queen Moon
of Mewni, presiding.
Thank you.
We are gathered here today
for the trial of Eclipsa--
I'm sorry!
I-I'm sorry I'm late!
[panting] We haven't
had a trial in so long,
I didn't know where
to find the typey thingy.
Usually Rhombulus just
crystallizes everybody. Ha ha!
With his laser eye.
But a real trial!
This is exciting!
That depends
on where you're sitting.
- As I was saying...
- [keys clacking]
we're gather here today
for the trail
- of Eclipsa--
- [clacking stops]
[growls]
[soft clacking]
We shall determine once
and for all whether Eclipsa
has committed the evil deeds
recorded in our histories.
If she is found guilty,
the punishment will be--
Death! Death!
Rhombulus,
we talked about this.
Well, we crystallized her
last time.
Look how that turned out!
Death!
Hey! Sit down.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, that's all in order.
But what is she doing here?
This is supposed to be
a private hearing!
Star was the one
who convinced me
to hold this trial
in the first place.
If Eclipsa is found guilty,
I want her to be here to see it.
Or if she's innocent,
which she is,
I wanna see all y'all's faces
when you realize
how wrong you were.
If you think you can just
waltz in here--
I can waltz wherever I want!
- [growls]
- No!
[all chattering angrily]
Excuse me!
Hey, sorry, but could you talk
a bit slower, please?
[whispers angrily] No.
Queen Moon, what evidence
have you brought us?
I'm afraid
this is the evidence.
It's less impressive
than it looks.
These are all
secondhand accounts,
oral histories, folk stories,
none of them verified.
There's no way around it.
Come on, everybody
grab a stack.
You guys aren't gonna
seriously sit here
- and read all of that?
- Yes, I don't mean to fuss,
but exactly how long
is this trial meant to last?
[sighs]
As long as it takes.
Now to begin,
we must organize each
and every one of these documents
by date and author.
[groans] Sounds like math!
Once we've constructed
a rough timeline, we can--
That won't be necessary.
I request a trial by Box.
- Awesome!
- Well, it looks like I won't
be needing these anymore.
Sean,
cancel my lunch order.
We're gonna be done here
pretty quick.
Lunch?
Eclipsa, are you sure
about this?
The Box is a ruthless seeker
of truth.
If you attempt to conceal
anything from it,
crystallization may be
the least of your worries.
I'm tired of sitting around
waiting for you
to decide my fate.
I'll give you the truth,
all of it,
and if that means
crystallization, so be it.
Sean, we wish to invoke
trial by Box.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The Box of Truth
has arrived!
Wait, is that Truth
or Punishment?
What? No, no, no, no.
This is the Box of Truth.
That, my friend,
is Truth or Punishment.
We played it
at my sleepover.
You played it?
The Box is not a game!
[intense male voice]
Who do you have a crush on?
[stammers] Queen Moon!
[sighs] It must be
on the wrong setting.
We need to talk.
All right, ladies,
are you--
Prepare for judgment!
The rules are simple.
Each member of
the Magical High Commission
shall ask one question,
and the accused must answer.
[whirring]
To all who seek the path
of knowledge,
listen well to this decree.
Surrender to the eye
of justice.
Swear an oath of Truth
to me.
Ooh. Different poem.
Different poem.
- I swear.
I swear.
I, uh... swear?
- [hisses]
- I swear.
And now, it's time
for trial by Box.
Eclipsa, did you write
the evil chapter
in the book of spells?
Exhibit A!
Yes, I did,
but, for the record,
I never called it
the Evil Chapter.
That was your people's
name for it.
I wrote plenty
of eviler spells
that never even made it
into the final draft.
Writing is rewriting,
you know.
Truth!
[scoffs] Whatever.
Have you guys even
read her chapter?
Hekapoo, the second question
goes to you.
Box, pull up
the royal archives
for me, would ya?
Exhibit B.
Did you abandon your husband,
King Shastakan,
and your kingdom
to elope with a monster?
Oh, hello, sweetie.
Yes, I did run off
with a monster.
But could you
really blame me?
How could I resist
a smile like that?
Truth again!
Aww! Huh?
- Uh-huh.
- Come on, Eclipsa.
- Rhombulus, the third--
- Did you eat those babies?!
What?
Ugh! Bobipsa was
the baby-eater,
not Eclipsa!
Oh, right.
I wanna take
my question back.
There are no take-backs
in trial by Box!
[babies crying]
Well, I hate
to disappoint you,
but I'm afraid
I have not eaten
even a single baby.
Now, I did hurt
the occasional teenager,
but only psychologically,
and they always deserved it.
We're on a roll here,
people!
What is wrong--
didn't you hear her?
She didn't eat those babies!
Star, sit down.
We must respect
the rules of the Box.
Fine!
Eclipsa...
Are you sorry
for what you've done?
No, I'm not.
- What?!
- The nerve! Outrageous!
That settles it.
Rhombulus, if you would.
- Right.
- One moment.
I haven't asked my question.
Wait. What?
- [laughs]
- She can't ask us a question.
Um...
[singsong] I think she can!
Right, mom? My mom said!
She said in the rules!
Technically since Eclipsa
was once a queen of Mewni,
she is still a member
of the Magical High Commission,
and every member
gets to ask one question.
[clears throat]
What did you do
with my daughter?
[all gasp]
Uh, I have no idea
what she's talking about.
We didn't do anything
with your daughter!
And honestly?
I-I'm kind of offended.
Too bad for you.
[bellowing]
Everyone lied!!
- [gasps]
- [yelps]
What's happening?
We told the truth!
[Box]
Are you sure about that?
[all gasp]
Uh, c'mon, guys,
spit it out!
We didn't do anything wrong!
The Box seems to differ!
We aren't the ones on trial!
If you'd rather get
to the truth more quickly,
I can work with that.
- [rumbling]
- [all gasp]
That's not good.
Guys!
[grunts]
My magic's no good in here!
[grunting]
Moon, please shut it off!
I can't do that.
We all took the oath!
Oh, no. Okay, I'm done!
I want out!
We're gonna be crushed!
You know, this is so unfair!
You enforce the laws of magic
on everyone around you.
And yet for some reason,
you can lie to us?
How does that make you
any different
than the villain you say
Eclipsa is?
We got rid of
your daughter, sorry!
Truth!
[groans]
What the heck,
Rhombulus?!
I'm sorry, I'm tired
of keeping it a secret.
Tell 'em Omni.
[sighs] Fine.
Eclipsa, your ex-husband,
King Shastakan,
he wanted nothing to do
with your half-monster daughter.
So we swapped her out
with a peasant girl.
We gave her
the Royal Magic Wand,
and she became
the next Queen of Mewni.
Eclipsa has been found guilty
of crimes against Mewmanity.
However,
the Magical High Commission
has also been found guilty
of tampering
with Mewni's history
and omitting the truth
from the Butterfly family
for generations.
This concludes the trial.
Although if we're
all being honest here,
it seems like y'all still have
some issues to deal with.
So it was just
as we suspected.
[both] What?!
Uh, Moon?
We knew there was
something missing
from our family's history.
Eclipsa's daughter
should be recorded here
in the royal archives,
but she's gone.
[gasps] Wait a minute.
This whole trial was a set-up?!
[panicked whimpering]
You were planning this
all along!
Actually,
we all planned this.
[panicked whimpering]
We thought you might be
hiding something.
And it turns out
we were right.
You lied to our family
for generations.
[carriage-return bell dinging]
We had to.
Can you imagine
if the power of Magic
fell into the hands
of a monster?
You let us live a lie.
We shouldn't even have
the throne.
Eclipsa isn't even-- wait.
You aren't actually
my great-great-great-
great-something-grandma.
No, sweetie, I'm not.
Then... that means...
we're no more royal
than anybody else.
You're still a princess,
Star.
No, Mom. We're nobody.
Star! Star, wait!
[panting]
Okay, Trot-Fudge Sundae!
You got this! [wails]
[both panting]
Here you go.
[grumbles, grunts]
[grumbles]
Junk... junk... junk...
Mm, what's in here?
Ugh! The worst junk.
When will they stop
sending us that garbage?
Huh, Ludo shirt, Ludo mask,
Ludo mask, Ludo mask, Ludo mask.
[groans]
[gasps]
Dimensional scissors?
All right, Ludo,
where are you?
Oh! Blue!
Let's see, what's blue?
Please don't be
the cat-face dimension.
Wait, green?
Okay, green.
No, pink.
Okay, that's--
Blue again?
What's going on?
Uh-oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
[coughing]
Dennis!
What's going on up here?
- Nothing.
- Well, that nothing
interrupted me
and my stickers!
[inhales] Mmm.
Good old scratch n' sniff.
What's this?
[groaning]
Honey!
He's doing it again!
Dennis, do you know
what a deadbeat is?
It's you!
That's what
you're gonna be
if you keep acting
like your brother,
collecting all this garbage,
destroying property,
acting like
you're too good for us!
Oh! Are we berating Dennis?
It's not even dinnertime!
He's hoarding
Ludo stuff again.
Dennis, how could you?
Ludo betrayed us.
He and his goons
took over the castle.
He was the worst.
You're the worst.
You got something to say?
No.
No what?
No, sir.
That's what I thought.
Now clean up this mess
and come help me
and your mother
with our stickers.
And mind your nails.
We need those fresh
young fingers.
[sighs] No, you guys, you need
to get back in the closet.
My dad catches you out here,
here's gonna freak.
Spider, these things are useless
unless I know where he is.
What? Y-you just
want me to...
Okay.
Be my guest.
[squawks softly]
I-I told you they don't work
if you don't know where he is.
[sighs] Okay.
[squeals]
[groans] Come on!
Stay awake!
What is it?
[gasps] You found him!
Let's get my brother.
[yelps]
Our... house?
made of garbage.
[whistling tune,
water running]
Ludo?
Wha-a-a-t?! Spider!
[laughs] That's you!
Oh, my friend!
Brother, it's me, Dennis.
Dennis?
How long has it been?
Last time I saw you,
you were this tall,
and now you're exactly
as tall as I am!
What are you doing here?
I came to bring you home.
Dennis, this is my home.
Come inside.
I just cleaned up.
I can't have you come
into the house.
You'll make a mess.
Look, papa
hasn't forgotten about you.
Ooh, been saving up a stash
for my best girl!
[laughs] Bon appétit!
Come sit.
Let me take care
of this for you.
But that's your helmet
from when you ruled
the Monster Army.
And now it's ruling
the garbage.
That was a piece
of your legacy.
I'm done with that part
of my life.
Now how about a drink, you?
Nothing too fizzy, of course.
Make yourself comfortable.
Could you ask mother and father
if they'd like a beverage?
Uh, mother and father?
Dennis, do you want
crushed ice or regular?
[humming happily]
Oh, thank you, Mother,
I do make the best sodas,
don't I?
Thanks, yeah, look, Ludo?
You gotta come home.
Mom and Dad
are driving me nuts.
But you can't say that
in front of them, Dennis.
Okay, fine, Ludo,
let's just go talk
in the kitchen, then.
Look, I really,
really need you
to come home.
- I am home.
- No, Ludo, I'm at my wits' end.
The yelling, the berating,
the stupid
scratch n' sniff stickers.
All they do is push me around
and talk trash about you!
What are you talking about,
Dennis?
Mother and Father love us!
They're so happy you're here!
We're even going to play
cha-rahds after dinner!
They always let me win!
[giggles]
- What are you talking about--
- Just kidding!
I'm just really good
at cha-rahds.
Now stop worrying.
That's not the Dennis
I barely remember.
Make that frowny
turn upside-downy!
Okay.
But after dinner--
And cha-rahds.
And after... cha-rahds...
we're leaving, okay?
Yes, Dennis,
whatever you say.
There we go, all tucked in!
What's that?
Oh, yes, how could I forget?
Good night, my darling.
They're finally asleep.
What angels!
Awesome, cool.
Now let's go.
Go? Dennis,
I can't just go.
- Ludo--
- Shh!
We don't need to whisper!
There's no one who can hear us!
Now come on!
This is ridiculous.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
Ooh! What the--
Mother! [laughs] Father!
What are you doing up?
What are you doing?
Cha-rahds?
At this hour?
Mmm, well, you twisted my arm!
I'll do it! [giggles]
This whole thing is a cha-rahd!
[grunts] Charade!
Just one more round, Dennis!
Let's humor them.
Come on, what do you say?
Okay, let's get out of--
Where did--
I don't know.
[groans]
You know what? Never mind.
The sooner we leave, the better.
But mother and father
want us to stay.
[groans] No, forget it!
Wow they really wanna play
cha-rahds.
Once they get going!
[laughs]
Stop! This isn't funny!
These aren't our parents.
This is actual garbage.
Oh, no! Mother!
We can fix this.
It's fine, we can fix this.
- We can fix this.
- You're losing it.
[deep] Calling his own
mother and father garbage?!
How about I teach you
to apologize?!
[high-pitched]
Watch his fingers, dear.
You watch your fingers.
[deep] What did you say?
I said you watch
your fingers!
Sir!
- Dennis!
- [growls]
[deep]
This is what we get!
[high-pitched] For raising brats
like your and your brother.
[roars]
[deep] Oh,
but you're a big man now
Who thinks he and his brother
are too good for this family!
Yes, I do!
[grunting]
Look at you, you're just
like your awful brother.
Good.
Because he's... my... hero!
[roars in slow motion]
Dennis!
You stood up for me!
No one has ever
stood up for me.
Of course.
I love you, big brother.
Oh, I lo--
lub--
oh, how to--
l-o-o--
ove?
Lo-o-ve...
yo-- u-u?
Tu...
[slurred] I love you, too.
Let's get out of here.
We can face the real mom
and dad now.
I can't.
Something very important
happened today.
But I have lots more
I need to work through
before I can leave.
Well, I'm here to help.
You're not alone anymore,
big brother.
I know that now.
But I have to do
this part on my own.
But... you're my hero.
No one else in the family
was brave enough to leave.
I can't stand up
to them on my own.
Dennis, you just did.
Did you see that dunk?
You can jump higher
than they could ever reach.
You need to go
find your own adventures.
You're going to be
just fine, kiddo.
Take good care of Spider.
She's quiet,
but she's a smart lady.
And I'll take care
of Bird, too.
I don't know who that is.
Goodbye.
Hello, Star and Marco.
How about a game
of cha-rahds?
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Ohh,
there goes a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining sta-a-r ♪