♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh pup-pup-pup
pup-pup ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[rhythmically]
Stabbing all the trash
with the stabby stick.
Stabbing the trash
and I put it in the sack.
Gonna stab the trash--
Hey, I was eating that!
Come on, you know
this stuff is garbage.
-What are you doing here?
-Same thing as you.
Getting the trash.
Hey!
Uh, I can see that,
but I meant what did you
get in trouble for?
-Huh?
-Did you waste somebody?
What? No, I volunteered.
Uh, for detention?
Are you okay?
[laughs] Totally!
No. I'm actually
pretty messed up.
Ah, me too.
You know, I think
I'm the first princess
to lose everything,
which is kind
of impressive.
I'd log it
in my spell book,
but I don't have
my spell book,
and I would tell
Glossaryck,
but I don't have
Glossaryck, either!
How am I supposed
to know where to go
or who I am
if I don't
have a history?
And if I keep myself busy,
I won't be able to mess up
anything else!
So that's
what I'm in for, Janna.
Mm-hmm. Uh...
Because I'm out.
Yo, what did you do?
What did I do?
You just put Otis
in the dumpster. Right on.
-Otis?
-Otis!
You know, he's, like,
the school mascot or whatever.
Okay, probably that shouldn't
be in the garbage.
Phew, it's okay.
That made a crazy sound
when I threw it in.
It was all, like,
[imitates springing noise]
[tinkles]
So, you're gonna be
in detention... forever.
[screams]
[shuddering sigh]
Oh, Principal Skeeves,
I am so sorry!
Without Otis,
I would be dead.
I remember
the moment well.
It was very cold
that day.
Winters here are
quite harsh, you know.
I was being chased
through the halls
of this very school
by a herd of bullies,
and hid beneath
Otis's underside.
I hid for days,
survived by eating
the frozen gum
stuck to Otis's
great big belly!
He saved my life.
Principal...
Life!
I'm gonna take off, yeah?
So, just, uh, you know,
find a brother in the hallways
when you're ready
to give her detention.
Hah...
You want that door
open or closed?
Hit the lights.
Okay, that was not normal,
even for Skeeves.
[tearfully]
Excuse me!
Hey, guys,
what's going on?
[sobs] We're waiting
for Mr. Candle's
grief counseling.
Grief counseling?
Sorry, everyone,
no counseling today.
I'm too torn up
about Otis.
No point in pulling you
onto a sinking lifeboat.
Uh, Mr. Candle, how can
you be torn about Otis?
You're not even
from this dimension!
But look at them, Star,
look at their little
droopy, baby-fat faces!
Contact grief is
a real thing, okay?
Dang! Oh, dang.
Hey, come on, guys.
I'm really sorry about Otis.
Please, is there anything
I can do to help?
Let me fix you.
It's not your fault.
It's our fault.
Good morning, everybody!
I've invited you
all out here
to say I'm so sorry
for yesterday.
I made a pretty big mess,
but I think I made
some magic today.
I give you Otis!
-Otis is really here?
-It's a miracle!
Otis? Otis, is that you?
My dear boy, I thought
I lost you forever.
But you're really here!
Ohh-ho-ho-aah!
Wait a second. I used to put
my used gum there!
Where is it?
Yeah, and where's
all the scratches?
It's too shiny!
And where is
the kissing hole?
Kissing hole?
You know, the hole where you
practice your kissing?
-What?
-Where's my kissing hole?!
This is Otis,
right, Star?
Duh! But the old statue
was all beat up,
so I made
a shiny new one.
Isn't that great?!
[imitates voice]
It sure is, Star.
That's not Otis.
That's a fake!
No, it's Otis,
just better!
Otis was perfect
the way he was!
[sobbing]
Wait, wait! Come back!
Come back! Otis is back!
What's wrong?
That's just a horrible reminder
of everything we've lost.
What? I need to find out
what I did wrong.
-Marco!
-Ow!
-Oh, I'm sorry!
-It doesn't matter.
Excuse me!
-Aah!
-Oh, never mind.
Zeke, I think we
should break up.
But, Becky, I love you.
I love you, too, Zeke,
but nothing matters anymore
now that Otis is gone.
Hey, everybody!
It's me, Otis. I'm back.
-Otis!
-I love you!
Otis, we love you!
What did I do
to this school?
School's done for, Miss.
Everything's crumbling.
Hooray!
Who am I? Who am I?
-Who am I? Who am I?
-Marco!
Where are you?
[echoing] Star,
I'm right here.
Oh, no, Marco's a locker?
This day just keeps
getting worse!
I'm just trying to avoid
all the craziness
in this school.
Hey, the lockers
are talking!
The end is near!
Hooray!
Marco, I am so confused
by this statue stuff.
I know what I did was wrong,
but I also have no idea
what I did wrong.
[sighs] Star...
Let me take you back
170 years ago
to the top
of the Mt. Angelus Mountains.
[folksy accent] In the dead
of winter of 1846,
the Bonner party
had set out
for the shores
of the western coastline.
Packed with nothing more
than a week's ration of food
and a dream
for a better life,
the Bonner party
stood no chance of survival.
They gave up quick
and decided to settle
in the tame suburban valley
of Echo Creek.
But one last challenge
lay between them
and their American dream:
possums.
To stake their claim
to the land,
the Bonner party
went to war.
Man and possum fought,
biting one another
with force and vigor.
A letter
from Timothy Bonner:
[settler reading]
After 26 days
of miserable war,
Otis, the very last possum,
was sent scurrying
into the forest.
The Bonners' land
was now possum-free.
They built a statue of Otis
to commemorate
the first victory
of their small town.
But it was the last time
Echo Creek won anything.
Football players
kiss it before games.
Teachers make
offerings to it.
Others just stare
and wonder, "What's a possum?"
Otis has come to represent
Echo Creek's history,
and without it...
[coughs, in normal voice]
We don't know who we are.
Oh, I know that feeling.
Remember when I lost
the book of spells?
-Yep.
-I went a bit crazy.
You kept calling me
Glossaryck.
You tried to shove me
in a book!
Because that's
where you live.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's terrible losing
something you care about.
Something with history,
something with...
Star, it's okay.
Oh, I got it!
Mr. Skeeves, I'm making
an announcement!
Don't try and stop me!
Check. One, one, two.
One. Can you hear me,
Echo Creek?
Can you hear
my loud voice?
-Teachers...
-What?
...students,
janitors, friends,
I have destroyed something
you had history with,
and I understand
that no magic
-can fix that.
-Yeah.
But you were more than just
a statue of a possum!
You're from Echo Creek!
You're better than possums!
-Johnny Raisinberry!
-Who said that?
You have been held back
seven times at this school!
My wife keeps telling me
to give up.
But you have
perfect attendance
every one of those years,
and you should be
super proud of that.
You are better
than a possum.
Thanks!
-Brittany!
-What?
You are really
judgmental and mean,
but maybe that's
because you want us
to keep being
better than possums.
[offended] Yeah!
Mr. Skeeves,
you dropped the ball
today on looking
after your school.
But, hey, at least
you got a school!
I like those Possums!
Star Fan 13, you're
the second-best me
there is, baby.
Oh, my gosh!
Ferguson! Alfonso!
I haven't talked
to you guys all year,
but you're always there
in the background
doing your thing.
You don't need a big possum
statue to make you proud.
That's just letting
the possums win.
We're from Echo Creek
and we're better than possums,
so, like the Bonner party
before us,
on that fateful day
in 1846,
let's get rid
of that possum!
[folksy accent] Like
their ancestors before them,
the students of Echo Creek
got rid of Otis
with pride
and school spirit.
They destroyed that possum
statue as one mob of unity,
and Old Janitor suggested
they burn down the school.
Star Butterfly
stepped in and said no.
That day, our town
was victorious,
and a girl
named Star Butterfly
shined brighter
than the Northern Star.
Hey, Star, you, uh,
gonna help me clean this up?
[folksy accent]
I suppose I should.
Why are you
talking like that?
Because today, Janna,
was a great day in history.
Seriously, stop it.
Not today, Janna.
Not tomorrow.
Not ever.
[synthpop playing]
[lip-synching]
♪ It was no secret ♪
♪ The way that we feel ♪
♪ A love that's so pure ♪
♪ A love that's so real ♪
♪ You showed me your world,
and it felt like a sign ♪
♪ But you acted
too slow ♪
♪ And you ran
out of ti-ii-ime ♪
Oh, man,
the only thing cooler
than these Love Sentence
singing toothbrushes
is the fact you got us tickets
to see them tomorrow!
Duh. That's what
friends are for!
Plus, Love Sentence
is like our thang.
You would know.
You're my best friend.
Good night, Marco.
Sleep tight!
[snoring]
[phone buzzes]
Hello?
Marco! Are you awake?
I forgot to tell you,
there's more.
-[phone buzzes]
-Aw, wait.
I'm getting
a call from Jackie.
Yeah, you are!
Hey, Jackie, uh, is
everything all right?
Dude,
Love Sentence tickets?
You're smoother than you
let on, Marco Diaz.
[chuckles] What?
Ooh, gotta go.
Gotta crush this ramp.
See you tomorrow!
Star! Did you get tickets
for Jackie, too?
Star! I know
you're there.
Hello? Did you get
Jackie tickets?
You did. Aren't
you excited, Marco?
You guys
are a thing now!
The three of us are gonna
be hanging out a lot.
I don't want Jackie
feeling left out
'cause I'm a supercool girl
who's also
your supercool best friend.
Yeah, you are, I'm just--
I'm just worried
that with you around,
Jackie will realize
I'm not as supercool.
I've dated before.
Trust me, you'll be fine.
[sighs] Ah, fine.
Just let me sleep.
♪ Yay! ♪
This is gonna be ♪ awesome! ♪
Now, get them
beauty sleeps.
Time to get
dressed, Marco!
Come on! Come on!
Jackie's gonna be here
any minute.
I know. That's what
I'm worried about.
Aw, poor thing.
I told you,
there's nothing to
worry about, right?
We just want to make
Jackie feel included
in our fun times
together!
Yeah, I guess.
[grunts]
Come on, it'll
be fine, I promise.
Now get dressed!
♪ La la la... ♪
Uh, I am dressed.
Red hoodie. Jeans.
That's pretty much
dressed for me.
Ha, no, you're not,
'cause I made concert tees!
Oh, man, Love Sentence
concert tees!
Handcrafted.
♪♪
Perfect.
I know, right?
Put it on!
[chuckles]
Little tight.
-[doorbell rings]
-Jackie's here!
[grunting]
Hey, girlfriend!
No way! You made
concert tees?
Oh, yeah.
Check it out.
That's so funny, 'cause I made
concert skateboards, whoa!
No way.
I can't believe we
had the same idea!
Great minds, am I right?
♪ Trade! ♪
So, where's Marco?
Oh, he's getting
dressed.
[straining, panting]
Hey, Jackie.
Hey, Marco.
[strains, pants]
Nice shirt.
Shows off your pecs.
Skateboards, really?
I thought we were
taking the bus.
Yeah! Skateboards.
It'll be fun!
Summoning Cloudy Charm!
Love Sentence,
here we come!
Whoo!
[sighs]
Ooh, I got one.
How many times did
Love Sentence break up
before their
fourth reunion tour?
Uh, six, if you count
the time they broke up
on the morning
of their second reunion tour
and got back together
after lunch.
Yes! Except it was
before lunch, not after.
No, it was
totally after.
Let's ask Marco.
Yeah, where is Marco?
[wheezing]
Right behind you!
Wow. Maybe we should've
taken the bus.
No! Can we just get
to the concert?
[honking]
Aah!
[protesting honk]
-Aah!
-[thud]
[chirping]
Whoa.
The ducks will be fine.
Marco should be fine, too,
provided he takes some
skateboard lessons.
The skateboard
didn't make it.
Your bill.
$650? Aw!
Come on!
Oh, they are so cute!
Little
disease-ridden angels.
I want to help!
Let me help!
-Oh, quack quack!
-[alarmed chirping]
Marco, you're
scaring them.
It's okay,
little babies, he's gone.
Aw...
Calm down.
You're at your new home.
Aw, come on, little dudes,
don't be nervous.
Yeah, this place is great!
I used to live here.
Me too. Wait, what?
Yeah, for, like, a day.
But you guys will make
friends so quick!
There's the lady
who steals hair,
who lives over there.
[laughs] Really?
Yeah, she smells
like shampoo all the time.
-It's crazy.
-No way that's true.
Seriously, it is!
And around there
is where I met the dragon.
I think... Oh, oh, oh.
And there's a really good
taco place around here.
Star, dude.
Oh. Time to say bye!
Marco, come say bye!
Huh?
Marco, dude.
Are you okay?
You and Star should just
go on without me.
You'll have more fun.
I'll just be here
ruining things,
breaking skateboards,
ripping shirts,
and traumatizing
families of ducks.
[angry honking]
Dude.
Don't worry
about the skateboard.
My uncle works
for the company, and...
I'm having fun
with you, but...
these guys
deserve an apology.
-I'm s--
-I'm kidding, Marco,
but that was
really sweet.
We should be apologizing!
Me and Jackie
were having so much fun,
you probably felt left out,
but you shouldn't.
Yeah, we wouldn't
have met those cute ducks
if it weren't for you.
STAR: And that was magical!
Heh. They were cute.
The idea was
we go together.
Yeah, Marco, come on.
Let's go have fun.
[klaxon]
Remain calm
and shelter in place.
This is not a drill.
[thud]
[audience cheering]
Hello, Echo Creek!
Oh, my gosh!
Such pageantry!
I love it. I love it!
Straight out
of the Echo Creek Penitentiary,
I'm Justin Towers,
and this one
goes out to everyone
who's "just friends."
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
Our second-favorite song!
Playing
my favorite song!
Whoo! Dance
with me, Diaz!
[chuckles] Okay.
♪ It was no secret ♪
♪ The way that we feel ♪
♪ A love that's so pure ♪
♪ A love that's so real ♪
♪ You showed me your world
and it felt like a sign ♪
♪ But you acted too slow ♪
♪ And you ran
out of ti-ii-me ♪
♪ And now we'll be ♪
♪ Just friends ♪
♪ We will be ♪
♪ And now we'll be ♪
♪ Just friends ♪
♪ Be just ♪
♪ Friends ♪
♪ I didn't mean
to hurt you ♪
♪ You didn't
have a clue ♪
♪ So you went out
and got busy ♪
♪ And found
somebody new ♪
-♪ New ♪
♪ And now we'll be ♪
♪ Just friends ♪
♪ Oh, we will be ♪
♪ And now we'll be ♪
♪ Just friends ♪
♪ Be just ♪
♪ Friends ♪
♪ And now we'll be ♪
[guitar solo]
♪ I didn't mean
to hurt you ♪
♪ You didn't
have a clue ♪
♪ So you went out
and got busy ♪
-Wow.
-♪ And found somebody new ♪
-♪ New ♪
-♪ And now we'll be ♪
-Star?
-Where are you going?
-♪ Just friends ♪
♪ Just friends ♪
Are you all right?
I'm sorry about the--
the, uh...
It just kind
of happened.
Oh, don't be silly.
I just wanted to be
down here by the stage
so I could feel their sweat
spraying on my face.
[chuckles] It's wet.
Are you sure?
Duh! What are
friends for?
Now, go up there
and be with
your girlfriend!
You're the best friend
a guy could have.
[weakly] Yeah...
Now, go.
She's waiting!
[new song]
♪ We spiraled high
on a gust of love ♪
♪ And I knew
right from the start ♪
♪ Nothing could
tear us apart ♪
♪ Till the day
you broke my heart ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪