♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Uh-huh. Okay.
( crashing )
You know what, Jackie?
Can I call you back?
Look, Star, this is
a stressful situation,
I get that.
But would it kill you
to slow down for a second?
You're going
kinda overboard.
I mean, do you really need
to pack this vintage laptop
and this purple-y,
bubbly tea thingy?
( typewriter bell dings )
Why don't you try
some breathing exercises?
I don't have time
to breathe.
( straining )
I can't waste a... second.
( frustrated yell )
Need some help there?
No. I am a strong,
independent warrior princess.
At the very least,
you should give your mom a call.
Someone has to fill her in.
No, you cannot
call my mother.
She'd kill me if she
found out about this.
Ludo stole my book.
He took Glossaryck.
I made this mess.
And I'm gonna be
the one who cleans it up.
"And so, Brave Sir Croakian
banished the wicked Mewmans
from the land.
From that day on,
the monsters had all
the corn they could eat."
Told you your backpack
was too heavy.
Buff Frog, I need to know
where Ludo's hiding.
I think he's planning
something big.
Yes, I know.
Did you not get my letters?
Letters?
You mean these?
I thought the babies
were sending us fan art.
Seriously. Who writes
warning notes in crayon?
Oh, so I not go to school
for learn fancy handwriting.
Sorry.
I make this map
when I infiltrate Ludo's lair.
I mark secret entrance here.
Thank you, Buff Frog.
This is exactly
what we need.
( sheepish chuckle )
Uh, double thank you.
You do not need
big pack.
- Hey!
- Only need wand.
Hmm.
Huh.
Huh?
Heh.
Cupcake Blast!
Tiara Tornado!
Stardust Daisy Devastation!
( all groaning )
- Where's Ludo?
- Ludo?
Don't you play
dumb with me.
I know he's here.
Hey, guys, I know it's late,
but we gotta make
a chore chart or something.
This shower is grody.
Oh, no.
Violence.
What is going on here?
We're not
fighting monsters.
We're alternative
monsters.
Then what's up
with all the weapons?
We found them here
when we moved in.
They're perfect for tearing
fashionable holes in clothes.
You're one of us
now, dude.
This place really
is abandoned.
( groans ) This was
all a waste of time.
Poor Glossaryck.
Who knows what horrible things
Ludo's doing to him?
Well, you tried.
And now we can
both agree it's
time to call your mom--
For the last time, Marco,
we're not calling my mom.
Whoa, hey,
calm down.
You're not seeing
the situation clearly.
Seeing clearly?
That's it.
I'll use
the spying spell.
Since when do you know
a spying spell?
Uh... since
I learned it.
A while ago.
You weren't there.
And I need to
do it alone.
No distractions.
Nice jeans, dude.
Can I dye them for you?
Hard pass.
I summon the all-seeing eye
to tear a hole
to let me spy.
Or was it
"in the sky"?
Ow. That wasn't it.
Ahem.
I summon the all-seeing eye.
( yells )
Eww.
I summon the all-seeing eye
to tear a hole
into the sky.
Reveal to me
that which is hidden.
Unveil to me
what is forbidden.
What? Oh, not you.
Ew! No, no, no, no, no.
( gasps )
Janna. You scoundrel.
No!
Ugh. Definitely no.
- Marco!
- Sorry.
Concentrate.
Concentrate on Glossaryck.
( moaning )
Glossaryck!
Don't worry.
I'm coming to rescue you.
( moaning continues )
Is that pudding?
A whole tub of pudding.
- Where are you?
- In flavor heaven.
No, physically,
where are you?
On the ground.
But where are you
in the universe?
Oh. Right.
I'm in a cave
on the ground.
Glossaryck, come on.
The spying spell
doesn't work that way.
I have never
seen that before.
Grab my hand.
No can do.
Sorry.
I belong to the book,
and the book belongs
to Ludo now.
Ludo stole you.
Well, that's out of my hands.
Come on, Glossaryck.
I can almost reach you.
Come on.
Yes, you are
surprisingly close.
Glossaryck, don't you
wanna come with me?
I thought
we were friends.
Friends?
Well, that's
such a simple concept.
Glossaryck, come on.
My mom is gonna ground me
for, like, a thousand years.
Yes, probably,
but you'll be fine.
Or not. Anyway,
your spell is collapsing.
But I need you.
Maybe this is what you need.
Glossaryck.
Star!
Are you okay?
Yeah, my hand's fine.
That's not what I meant.
Well, Glossaryck
is no longer on the team.
I never really
saw Glossaryck as
a "team player" anyway.
Oh, my gosh.
It is her.
We just realized
you're Star Butterfly.
We're your
biggest fans.
Um, I think
you're confused.
Monsters hate me.
Sure, it's not popular
to like you,
but we're not about that.
Yeah! You're
the rebel princess.
Rebel princess?
Yeah. You do things
your own way.
Like us.
Please, shoot us
with a spell.
Rip some awesome holes
in our jeans, something.
Um, I guess I could
cast something.
How about Super Strawberry
Shake Quake?
( laughing )
Wow!
That is awesome!
Look at this sweet rip.
Let's go show the guys.
Dude, I can't believe
we met Star Butterfly!
So, what now?
Now, I call Mom.
So...that's pretty much it.
Oh, no, this is
really bad, huh?
I messed up.
I really messed this one up.
I am so sorry,
Mommy and Daddy.
Sweetie, it's...
it's okay.
But the book of spells,
our family history,
is all gone.
Don't worry.
It's just a book,
and a little magic man.
What matters is
you're safe.
But isn't there
anything I can do?
Don't do anything.
We'll handle this.
You just sit tight.
Good night, sweetie.
Whoa. That went way better
than I expected.
Uh, yeah.
I guess so.
You know, you should just
take your parents' advice
and sit tight.
Right.
Good night.
( door closes )
Rebel princess
doesn't sit tight.
Rebel princess does things
her own way.
Mega Narwhal Blast!
Oh. Mega...
Narwhal Blast.
Chapter one:
Mega Narwhal Blast.
Hurry up, Star. I don't
want us to miss the cake.
I wonder what flavor it is.
I hope it's ogg-berry.
That's not a thing
on Earth.
Seriously? Oh, man, you guys
are really missing out.
I think I'll hold on
to my gift until I see Sensei.
Don't worry, Marco.
There's some room left
right... there.
( glass shatters )
STAR: Whoo! Sensei can really
throw a par-tee!
( people chattering )
Come on, I wanna give him
his birthday punches.
Be careful.
He knows Tan Soo Do...
sort of.
Hot meat. Hyah!
I... I caught it.
Me next.
Got it!
This is a henna
tattoo, right?
Yeah, Henna, Jenna.
I can do whatever
name you want.
Oh, hey, Sensei.
Sick move,
birthday master.
Yeah, you're Sensei-tional.
( both chuckling )
Thanks, guys, but you
ain't seen nothin' yet.
The great Preston Change-o
is performing.
You didn't tell me there
were magic users in
this dimension.
That's something you
wanna let a sister know.
Oh, Preston's not
a magic user.
He's an entertainer.
He does magic tricks.
Trouble at my party?
No burn chicken.
Party on!
( cheering )
Waaahh...
The meat speaks.
What?
He has arrived.
Preston Change-o.
Yeah!
Whoa ho!
Okay.
Why don't you stick
your head in my armpit there?
Preston Change-o.
( cheering )
Neat. Let's get closer.
Hold your mole, Marco.
That little guy
is using magic.
All right, everybody,
watch the rings.
( blowing raspberry )
That's not magic.
There's a gap in
one of those rings.
I saw it on TV.
You do magic,
do you?
You don't wash
behind your ears.
( giggles )
Preston Change-o.
Ear money.
- Tell your mom
I said hi.
- Hi, Mom.
What do we have here?
More dirty ears.
Just kidding.
It's a pencil.
Oh, to write with.
- Preston Change-o.
- ( exclaims )
What just happened?
Did your hat get bigger?
You are magic.
Yes, my dear, that's
the nature of being a magician.
And a good day
to you.
Marco, that's
a real magician.
He said so himself.
It's a part of
his act.
This wasn't an act.
Look at his hat.
Don't you see?
It's taller.
Look, Star, I get it.
The first time I saw
a party magician,
I was pretty emotional, too.
Now if you don't mind,
I'm gonna go enjoy
some birthday magic.
Mr. Preston, would you do
a magic trick for me?
Of course I can,
Jennifer.
First I'll need
an ordinary five-dollar bill.
Sure. Hey, uh...
Where's my wallet?
Are you looking for this?
It's your wallet.
Whoa. No way.
Preston Change-o.
- That was...
- Hey, hey, hey.
What was that?
Why is Marco sad?
- Marco, why are you sad?
- I'm not sad.
I merely performed a bit of
sleight-of-hand, my dear.
No way.
You're a real magic user.
Takes one to know one.
I already told you,
I'm a magician.
- What's happening?
- He... ( sputters )
He did a trick,
and these lights came out,
and hat... hat...
his big hat.
Ugh. My mom hired Preston
to entertain us.
He's just doing his job.
I'm beginning to sense
that my magic act
isn't welcome here.
No, no, no, no, no.
We love it.
Let's just bring
your act over here.
Star, it's not real.
The point of Earth magic
is to allow yourself
to be entertained by
pretending that it's real,
just like love.
Who wants cake?
Where's the birthday boy?
I'll go look for him.
Sensei!
Hey, Jeremy, have you
seen Sensei?
Sensei? Who cares?
Nothing matters anymore.
Preston Change-o.
Hey, wakey-wake,
it's time for cake.
Wait. No more magic?
Not until after the cake.
Then there'll be magic
for everyone.
Yay!
Stop right there,
Preston.
This is the end
of the line, mister.
Fess up. You're doing
something to these folks.
Now tell me
what it is.
All right,
you got me.
Look, I'm not
human, all right.
I'm a joy sucker.
- A what?!
- A joy sucker.
Sadly, I can't create
my own joy.
So I suck a bit of
the joy from others
when I perform my tricks.
Think of it, you know,
as taking their empties.
You took a lot more than
a little from Sensei just now.
Yeah, but that dude
really loves magic.
He had a lot to spare.
You gotta go.
But I have a party
to entertain.
You want the wand?
Sensei's been on
my wait list since
he was a little boy.
At least let him have
the satisfaction of
seeing my grand finale.
I mean, his mom paid for
me to be here, and I
kinda owe it to him.
You're just gonna suck
all their joy.
Come on, my hat's full.
I don't even have room
for any more of their joy.
You don't wanna ruin
a guy's birthday, do ya?
All right, fine.
Do your finale.
But I'm watching you,
little man.
You start to suck joy,
and you get the wand.
Deal.
Promise. No joy sucking.
- Say it.
- I promise.
Be cool, Star.
Do it for Sensei.
Just keep cool.
Hey, isn't this fun?
Yeah, that's
one word for it.
Aw, h ere comes
the cake stick.
Everyone!
I just wanna thank you all
for showing up
to my 38th birthday bash,
especially the very great
Preston Change-o.
Because without him,
this party would be
totally lame.
Preston Change-o, everybody!
( upbeat music plays )
- Whoo hoo hoo!
- Sh!
Sensei exclaiming )
No! Mama, he brought
the box.
How about a little girl
from the audience, please?
( yells )
Take me, take me!
My body's your body.
I've got
my eye on you.
Get lost.
This thing is sharp.
Yeah!
( laughs )
Whatever.
Preston Change-o.
( all murmuring )
What are you doing?
Sorry, Sensei,
I tried to be nice.
Tell 'em, Preston.
- Tell 'em the truth
about your magic.
- All right, okay, fine.
It's true.
I don't do real magic.
All my tricks are just that.
Tricks.
I did keep my cards
up my sleeve.
( all groaning )
The rabbit I pull
out of my hat... paper.
Oh, man, spoiler alert.
These blades
aren't even sharp.
What?! I knew I didn't
feel dismembered.
Not that.
The joy-sucking thing.
Oh, yeah, right.
I suck a little bit
of joy from your heads
every time I do my tricks.
It's harmless really.
No. No, it's not.
- I think you broke Jeremy.
- ( sobbing )
Come on, that kid had
no joy in him to begin with.
You still shouldn't
take their joy.
It's theirs.
You're right.
I am sorry.
It's what I do.
I can't help myself.
Oh, who cares?
That girl just
ruined our magic show.
What? Me? No, but he was
the one stealing your joy
and making you sad.
You just stole
my joy forever
by making him explain
how his tricks are done.
I'll never see
a magic show again.
( feedback whines )
Happy now?
I'm a happy guy.
He can have my joy.
But I helped.
Wait. Wait, guys, guys, guys.
Is all you want
a magic show?
( mimicking )
Yeah, that's
what we wanted.
( crying )
I'm not sure it was worth
ruining Sensei's birthday
just to be right.
No, you weren't
right, Star.
Preston's birthday magic
was fake.
Yeah, but I was right
that Preston was magically
sucking people's joy.
Oh, stop arguing,
both of you.
You did ruin my birthday
magic show, okay?
But you're right.
That little guy was a creep.
I don't want nobody
stealing my joy.
By my next birthday,
I'll forget any of this
ever happened.
Magic will be real again.
But for now, I'm just
gonna be bummed out,
and it's okay.
I'm glad I didn't get
all my joy sucked, you know.
Where is Preston anyway?
Oh, yeah, I put him
in the trunk.
- What?
- Weirdo.
- STAR: No way.
- SENSEI: Disappeared.
- I was right all along.
- ( groans )
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪