♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh
puh-puh-puh-puuuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
( school bell ringing )
Math, is a symphony...
of numbers-uh.
( snoring )
It's the poetry of logic.
The magic behind nature.
The beauty of sea shells.
( snoring continues )
( thud )
Hey, Star.
Uh-huh.
Why did the chicken
cross the road?
I don't know.
To get to the other side.
( laughing )
What's so funny?
Miss Skullnick, get this.
She said
"to get to the other side."
Ha ha ha!
Get it?
Ah, you expect
the punch line
to be one thing,
but what you
end up with
is just logic.
Classic anti-humor.
Hey, stop messing around.
I need to know this
for tomorrow's test.
OK, Miss Butterfly,
if you are so enamored
with logic,
why don't you get up here
and solve for "c"?
Ooh!
Oh, relax, people. Mmm.
( humming a tune )
Thank you.
OK...ahem!
And "c" equals...
cat face!
( gasp ) Cat face!
I walk back to desk.
What? No, Star,
"c" equals
the circumference.
You just drew a cat!
Yeah, but I don't
just draw cats.
I draw rainbows,
lightning bolts,
hamburgers.
I don't know where
this stuff comes from.
Star.
Might draw a chicken later.
Star!
Depends on how bored I get.
Get up here
and solve for "c."
I got nothin'!
( growl )
I'm so bad at math.
No one is going anywhere,
until you come up here
and solve this math problem.
( mocking )
Solve this math problem.
( groans ) Fine.
( humming a tune )
Ta-da!
( sighs )
Uh...
( clock ticking )
Star, what's going on?
Ah!
Huh?
Uh...
( exasperated sigh )
OK, let's just
get this over with.
Hey, Star.
Why did the chicken
cross the road?
What?
To ask out the rooster.
Uh, didn't we
just go through this?
What?
Uh, that joke.
You just told me
it a minute ago.
But it was a little different.
What are you talking about?
And where
did you get that hat?
Is there something
you want to tell us?
Yes, there is.
What the heck is going on here?
Hey, stop messing around.
I need to know this
for tomorrow's exam.
I'll tell you what the heck
is going on, Star.
You're going to get up here
and solve for "c."
Ooh!
Miss Skullnick,
I already told you.
I don't know how to do it.
( angrily )
Get up here and try!
Are you feeling OK?
( coughing )
But, Skullzy,
I don't know the answer.
( rumbling )
Because that's where
she parked the car.
Hey, are you guys all
messing with me or something?
What are you talking about?
Hey, stop messing around.
I need to know this
for my homework tonight.
I thought you said
it was for tomorrow's exam.
Huh?
Get up here now
and solve for "c."
Ooh!
Knock it off
with the "oohs."
Miss Skullnick,
I already told you,
I have no idea
what the answer is.
( rumbling )
Because she flew the coop.
( laughs )
What is happening?
And why do you keep
wearing these terrible hats?!
Hey!
How dare you
interrupt my class!
Stop messing around.
I need to know this for--
Oh, just can it, Marco.
Get up here now
and solve for "c."
This is no time for math.
I need to find a way out
of this nightmare.
( rumbling )
Oh, come on!
Because it wanted
to lead by egg-zample.
Solve for "c."
Never!
( thud )
( rumbling )
Just 'beak-cause'.
You know, beaks.
Solve for "c."
No!
( rumbling )
Because she
didn't chicken out.
Solve for "c."
No!
( rumbling )
Because she was chicken
out the other side.
Solve for "c"!
No!
( rumbling )
Because she needed
the exercise.
Solve for "c."
( rumbling )
( speaking
foreign language )
Solve for "c."
No!
( rumbling )
( speaking indistinctly )
Solve for "c."
No!
( rumbling )
( clucking )
Solve for "c."
No way!
To get away from the farmer.
( screaming )
Stop it with the chicken jokes.
They're not funny.
Star!
What in the world
is going on back there?
Stop messing around.
I need to know this for--
The test tomorrow! I know!
Oh, no. There's a test?
Get up here...
( together )
...and solve for "c."
Oh, Miss Skullnick.
( laughs nervously )
OK, gotta go.
I gotta figure this thing out.
Hey, Father Time!
Father Time?
Father?
Father... Ooh!
( humming a tune )
STAR: Hey!
Father Time!
You're stuck in my wheel.
Can you help me?
I ran over you.
I'm stuck in some kind
of weird time loop,
and I can't figure
a way out of it!
OK!
Ya-haw!
Wait, I can't figure out
what's happening!
I need your--
( screaming )
( grunts )
Help!
( groans )
I gotta find way
to end this!
MAN:
What do you need?
Who said that?
MAN:  I said it.
What do you need?
I need Father Time.
I'm stuck in a time loop.
OK, now, you don't need him.
He's time-time.
I'm space-time.
Who are you?
I'm Omnitraxus Prime.
I'm the space-time guy.
The time loop,
that's my territory.
It's a space-time problem.
Father Time problem is
like,
"I burnt this toast that
I really wanted to eat."
Look.
"Oh, dang" it.
I burnt this toast.
I wish I could go back
in time before it was burnt.
I need--
That kinda thing.
I need some answers.
I am stuck
in a nightmare math class
that's repeating itself,
but now
it's changing, too.
Like, super weird changing.
OK. What's it keep
returning to?
The same stupid math problem.
Oh, well...
why don't you
just do the math?
Omnitraxus Prime has spoken.
W-w-w-w-w-w-wait.
I did do the math.
Hmm?
Miss Skullnick wants me
to do the work.
OK, so do the work.
Omnitraxus Prime has spoken.
I can't.
( groans ) I have a ton
of things to do today.
I can't do the work.
I never paid attention
in class.
I tried to use my wand
to solve it,
but I ended up
right back where I started.
Oof. Look...
I can see
what's happening here.
I can show you
how to sort this out.
But there's gonna be
some tummy-time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a second.
Get up in my guts.
Nice.
Whoa, it's neat in here.
Mm-hmm. So...
all time and space are
considered as one.
And within it, infinite
parallel universes exist--
Bored!
I'm bored.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Let me explain this
another way. Hmm.
In the crystal fields
of interwoven continuum.
( gasps )
So pretty.
Ah, you see?
Here is infinite
versions of you
in infinite parallel timelines
in infinite parallel
math classes.
Ohh! I'm adorable.
OMNITRAXUS: And all
those versions of you
managed to work
through that problem.
You're the only version
of you that didn't do it.
( rumbling )
That sound!
That's the same sound
from the classroom!
That's your parallel timelines
colliding with each other.
If you don't figure out
that math problem soon,
they're all gonna shatter
and forever be lost within
the fabric of time-space.
Uh, space-time.
Oh, I know.
I bet you're great at math.
You can solve it for me!
Did-- Are you even
listening to me?
There's no short cuts
to this.
Answer the math problem,
or your world's
gonna fall apart.
Just do the work, Star.
Do the work?
Why did the chicken
cross the road?
Who cares?
There are infinite chickens
crossing infinite roads, OK?
So why don't
you just ask them?
( groans )
( gasps ) Hold on. That's it.
If all the infinite versions
of me know how to solve
that math problem,
then I must know
how to solve it, too, right?
Uh, it's just a joke
about a chicken.
Miss Skullnick,
I would like to solve for "c."
Star, are you feeling well?
Perfectly fine,
( baby voice) Miss Skullnick.
( old woman's voice )
I have a math problem...
( normal voice )
to solve.
Come on, Star.
You can do this.
( growls )
( rumbling and crashing )
OK, infinite me's in
infinite parallel dimensions,
let's do this.
I already know how to do this
in the other dimensions,
so I just need
to channel those me's.
OK, lets see.
Solve for "c."
Well, first,
16 minus 7.0.
( shouting )
( speaking indistinctly )
..which means that "c"...
( continues speaking
indistinctly )
( speaking indistinctly )
Meow meow meow meow meow.
...to the fourth power...
divided by root of "c"
over 12,
and therefore "c" equals...
Seven. Seven?
Yeah, seven.
Yes, I did it!
Hmm, wow!
Yep,
you did it all right.
I know!
I solved the problem!
Well, no, I mean,
it's totally wrong.
But you tried,
so it's a start.
Nice job, Star.
Now take your seat,
please.
MARCO:
Star, don't feel too bad.
It's pretty complicated stuff.
Oh, Marco,
You have no idea.
Mr. Diaz, get up here.
It's your turn.
( wailing )
Uh, Pony Head?
What's wrong?
Oh, no!
Pony, use your words.
Hyah-cha!
I heard screaming.
Oh, it's Pony Head.
What, did she run out of
rainbow toothpaste again?
Yeah, probably.
Whatever it is,
we'll go through it together.
( sobbing )
OK, I'll tell you.
I am ready to reveal.
The Bounce Lounge is closing.
( wailing )
( wailing continues )
( glasses break )
( Star coughing )
( sobbing )
The Bounce Lounge
is cl-cl-closing?!
No! No!
Hey, let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
It's probably
not even closing. I mean...
since when has Pony Head
been right about anything?
( gasp ) Oh, yeah.
MARCO: It's closing.
I just...
I can't believe it.
WOMAN:
Believe it.
( dance music )
PONY HEAD: ( gasps )
Oh, my goodness!
It's Millie Sparkles.
My liege.
Marco, it is the owner
of the Bounce Lounge.
The Bounce Lounge
is indeed closing.
The party is over.
But why, Millie?
Because business has been slow.
( cawing )
No one comes to
party here anymore.
Fare thee well, loyal partiers.
And may the Bounce Lounge
be with you...
always.
Wow, you girls used
to party here a lot.
( gasps ) Hey, Pony, look!
It's us!
STAR: Oh, besties!
Mmm, and there's
our junior prom night.
Uh, yeah.
I'm actually trying
to forget that.
O.M.G. That is a classic!
'Cause that is
the old Bounce Crew, girl!
We used
to rule this place.
Nobody partied harder
than we did.
Man, where did the time go?
Actually, time doesn't
go anywhere.
Sometimes things just end,
and there's nothing
we can do but accept it.
Please be quiet.
Because Star and I are
trying to have a life moment.
We haven't been here
for so long.
I can't help but feel
like this is our fault.
And now a part of our life
has gone forever.
( muffled sob )
Unless...
we get the old Bounce Crew
back together.
Oh, girl!
STAR: Hey, Kelly.
Uh... where's Ted?
Ted and I broke up.
There's a bald spot on my head
where my heart used to be.
Oof, that's,
like, real sad!
And worse news,
they are closing
the Bounce Lounge!
And we're getting the crew
back together to save it.
Puh!
Why not? I can be
despondent anywhere.
All right,
let's go, Kelly!
Who's next?
Johnny Blowhole,
the party dare extraordinaire.
JOHNNY: I don't know, guys.
( claps )
I have a lot of partying
that I have to do here.
OK, you do not look like
you're the one partying.
No, I'm pretty sure
this is partying.
When you're done,
grab your mop.
The commode could use
some heavy duty partying.
( both gasp )
He's forgotten
what partying is.
They're using you,
Johnny.
Yeah, ditch these nerds
and you need to come with us.
Sorry, ladies.
Johnny stays with me.
( nervously )
Uh... uh... uh... Hey!
( crunching )
( screaming )
This is my life now.
I'm not good
at partying anymore anyways.
I guess, you're right, Johnny.
You have lost
your partying powers.
You probably never even
had them in the first place.
Oh, you lost them,
Johnny Blowhole! That's weak!
You guys are wrong, OK?
I have my moments.
Prove it. I dare you to
save the Bounce Lounge.
I dare you to stop me!
( laughing )
Whoo! Johnny's back!
PONY: Headphone Jones?
Lady Scarfs-a-lot?
Yo, wake up!
What do you want?
And make it quick.
You're harshing the cool.
They're closing
the Bounce Lounge.
Good.
Yeah, that place hasn't
been cool in months.
We were getting
the crew back
together to save it.
This is a way cooler
place to party.
This is partying?
HEADPHONE: Yeah,
look how cool we look.
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
Uh-huh.
( siren )
What?! I thought that was
what you were thinking!
Ah, Millie!
Millie, Millie, Millie!
The Bounce Crew
is back together.
Wassup, Mills?
I'm afraid that's not enough.
You see, the only thing
that will save the lounge
is paying off the mortgage.
And I can't do that with only
one, two, three, four, five,
six customers.
Well,
how much do you owe?
Like, a bajillion dollars.
That's a lot of bacon.
Is that
even a real number?
Let it go, darlings.
Sometimes things just end.
And there's nothing
we can do but accept it.
That is so deep,
so new, so unique.
Nobody ever said that before.
Seriously?
That's the exact
same thing I said.
No, no, sorry.
I don't remember
you saying that.
So, goodbye and thank you
for your patronage.
( sighs )
It's no wonder
the place lost money.
What a dump!
It always
looked like this.
Our partying gave
the Bounce Lounge its life.
And our partying
is gonna save it.
Save it? What?
No, no, no,
she's right.
The Bounce Lounge can't go down
with the Bounce Crew around.
Hit it, Pony.
( electronic party music )
Let's get this party started!
Come on, Bounce Crew,
what are you waiting for?
Hey, I heard some dance music.
Is there a party in here?
Yes, admission is $25.
Oh, no, I just need to
use your bathroom.
How many is that?
None!
Looks like we need
to dance harder.
WOMAN:
Let's get our groove on!
Oh! It's working!
Whoo! Move to the groove!
Yes!
How many is that now?
Almost a bajillion
less than a bajillion.
Harder!
JOHNNY:
You heard Star, dance harder!
PONY: That's what
I'm talking about!
Whoo!
Now?
We're gonna need
a lot more partiers.
You are so right.
Get in there, Marco!
Just move your body!
Be yourself.
Myself?
Hi-yah!
( karate sounds )
This goes out to all you
desert dimensioners out there!
Whoo! Yeah!
How about, MC Money?
Let's hear it!
Make some noise!
We still need more!
Johnny,
use your blow hole!
We were passing by outside
and got sprayed.
The Bounce Lounge is back!
Now?
We need one more partier.
One more?
Think that's everyone.
Ted?
Oh, hey, guys.
Where's my girl?
Ted.
What are you doing here?
Don't you remember, baby?
This is the first place
we ever broke up.
Wanna get back together?
Yeah!
BOTH: Whoa!
Did we make enough?
One, three, fifteen,
eleventy, thirty,
Mmm, nope.
We're short 6.50.
But I thought we had--
( giggling ) Wait! Oh...
I've never had more fun
in my entire life!
( cheering )
Yes, we did it!
The Bounce Lounge lives forever!
Now let's party!
MILLIE: Star, wait.
Thank you, all of you,
for what you've done.
But I've been partying
for over 5,000 years.
( gasps and shocked cries )
It was never about the mortgage.
I'm closing the lounge
because I just really
need to stop partying.
Like, right now.
Aww!
If this is the last night
of the Bounce Lounge,
let's make it
the best night ever!
( excited whoops )
No!
The party is over.
( screaming )
But we saved the lounge.
Nothing lasts
forever, princess.
But thank you for the party.
( sighs )
The Bounce Lounge is gone.
( dolphin chatter )
Uh, at least I have you,
piece of gum
I scraped off a table
to remember it by.
( kiss )
Yeah. I got a chip
of the dance floor.
Or someone's tooth.
PONY: Aw, you guys are lucky.
All I got is this photo booth!
STAR:
Photo booth! Photo booth!
♪ I think Earth is
a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me
its just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I can call this place home! ♪