♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( horse neighing )
( door creaking )
Hey, that's a handicap spot.
( playing keyboard )
Ah, who's that?
Look it.
He's hot.
( gasps )
Aah!
Hey, Star.
I'm here to take you...
to the Blood Moon Ball.
Nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope.
You need to leave
right now.
Take your carriage and fire
and dead horse,
and go back
to the underworld.
Wait, I'm dead?
Oh, come on, Starship.
It's the Blood Moon Ball!
It only happens once
every 667 years.
We broke  up!
Period!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Star, hang on.
I'm a changed man, okay?
I've got a life coach,
Brian.
Hey.
He's awesome.
A happy bunny.
And, and, I have been
anger-free
for 53 days.
53?
Don't you wanna
pet my bunny?
Well, he is adorable.
Hi-yah!
Oh!
Back off, demon!
Marco!
( growling )
Oh, no.
Walk it out
and talk it out.
Walk it out...
Uh, you better run.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Ha ha.
No, no. Oh...
Oh, that's why I got
my support system.
I'm good.
Got the angries out!
Everything is-- hoo--
under control.
Marco, don't karate him.
This is... Tom.
Demon ex-boyfriend Tom?
Nice to, uh, meet you,
Marco.
What is he doing here?
He wants to take me
to the Blood Moon Ball.
Star, never go
with a predator
to a second location.
Look, I can see you're mad.
You think I'm a total jerk.
I get it.
But I have changed.
Remember, I'm not
the only one with horns.
Why didn't you tell me
I'm dead?
( making karate-like groans )
No pressure. If you decide
you want to go,
just toll this bell.
( flames whooshing )
Oops, almost forgot
the little hammer.
I hope I see you there.
You're making
a big mistake, Star.
Maybe, but it could
be fun.
Why don't you just
stay here,
where it's always fun?
Like, guaranteed.
Well, this is
a different kind of fun.
Don't look.
I'm gonna change.
I just don't trust Tom.
Maybe I should go with you.
Marco, you weren't
invited.
Besides, you gotta trust me
to do the right thing for my--
Self-aaah...
Are you okay?
Yeah, totally,
totally, totally.
I just gotta stop
using magic on--
on-- on my face.
All I'm saying
is guys like Tom
never change.
Well, there's only one way
for me to find out.
What do you think?
You look amazing.
Thanks, Marco.
( strained whisper )
Don't go.
( whispering )
I'm totally going.
( deep, resonant gong )
Mmm.
Smells like burnt toast.
Let's get this show
on the road!
Which floor, mortal?
Uh, I guess the bottom.
Let me just
ride down with you.
Good-bye, Marco.
See you after
the  Blood Moon Ball.
Oooooh...
( groaning )
( flames wooshing )
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, guys.
I don't know what
you're about to do,
but I want to keep things
low-key for Star.
You want to turn
the Blood Moon Ball
into a greeting card
holiday, go ahead.
Wait, which one of you
said that?
Me.
No, okay, whoever
was just talking,
raise your hand.
Master Tom, Princess Butterfly
has arrived.
Wow.
Star Butterfly.
Don't you clean up nice!
Uh, thank you...
I guess.
I got you this.
What is it?
It's a hair thing.
It goes in your hair.
It'll help you
fit in down here.
How sweet, Tom.
but, yeah.
I kinda got
my on thing going on here.
I'm pretty happy with it.
Let's go have fun now.
( angry groan )
You can be positive
that your anger is negative.
( music playing on radio )
I'll have my own
Blood Moon Ball
in Star's bedroom,
where it's always fun.
MAN'S VOICE:
Blood moon tonight.
VOICE:
The moon of lovers.
( eerily )
Smile.
( both groaning )
Beautiful.
I'm so excited to be
covered in blood with you.
But don't worry, it's not real.
It's from a unicorn.
My best friend
is a unicorn.
Well, they're not related.
I'm not gonna bathe
in unicorn blood, Tom.
( stifled angry groan )
What's that hand doing
back there?
Nothing.
Whoa, wait a second.
Are you getting angry?
No.
Look, you do you, Boo,
I'm gonna go get a drink.
STAR:
Here he comes again.
Hello, Henry.
His name is Henry.
You must be
Tom's date.
I guess I am.
Well, I hope you're happy.
He made this whole
entire ball
completely boring,
all for you.
I wouldn't say
it's boring.
Oh, really?
Aloof attractive people.
Boring!
Bubbling cauldrons that
don't even melt your flesh off.
What is it,
nap time or something?
'Cause I'm bored.
Piece of garbage that
doesn't destroy the universe.
Stupid cockroach
that lives inside.
I'm over it already.
( screaming, sobbing )
You wanna dance?
Her dance card's full.
Oh, I get it.
I bet you think that, like,
your soul, and, like,
her soul
are totally gonna...
mmmmmm!
What is "mmmmmm"?
( speaker feedback,
clears throat )
Good evening,
ladiesngennlebremen.
It is my pleasure
that I request you now
to turn your heads skyward
when the light of the
blood moon drupples down,
and selects
two lucky souls,
binding them together
for eternity
in its hypnotic,
ruby brodum.
Whoa.
( eerie organ music playing )
Oh! That's the wrong
piece of music!
This is gonna
drive me crazy.
All right, don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Ooh.
( hushed tone )
Star.
( whispering )
Star. Star!
( all gasp)
Oh!
( music playing )
( gasps )
( angry groan )
Star...
How did you know my name?
It's me, Marco.
( gasps )
Marco?
What are you doing here?
Let's get outta here.
This place is the worst.
( angry growl )
That dance was meant
for me!
Walk it out...
No, Brian!
( demonic roar )
Let's go, Marco.
( flames whooshing )
( bell dings)
Thanks for the lift.
Ugh! So infuriating.
I hate to say it,
but I warned you about Tom.
No, you!
You're infuriating.
Me? I was just
trying to help.
You don't trust me
to do things by myself.
I'm 14.
I can handle a demon.
I know you're trying
to look out for me,
but you have to let me
figure things out on my own.
I don't nee a hero.
I need a friend.
( sighs )
You're right.
I should have
trusted you.
I'm sorry
I ruined your night.
Well, it wasn't
a total disaster.
Now I know
you can dance.
( both chuckle )
Hat hair. Whoa!
We both said--
The same thing.
Okay, stop that.
( both gasp )
( stifled laugh )
( both laughing )
Well, that was new.
Yeah, weird.
Now go make me
some nachos!
MARCO:
Okay.
( pained cries )
How are you losing?
You guys have, like,
200 pounds on her!
( crying )
At least hit her
with a rock or something!
( growling )
( frustrated groan )
Whoo-hoo!
Off the cactus,
over the tree.
Nothing but net!
Unh!
Told you I could do it.
( all growling )
Double or nothing.
One kick,
seven monsters.
Hyah!
Noooo!
After a victory
like this,
there's only
one thing to do.
Get Chinese food!
Ooh, Chinese food!
I have no idea
what that is.
( groaning )
( angry cries )
( screaming )
You guys are useless!
( groaning )
( squeaking indistinctly )
You're always screwing up
my brilliant plans.
I need someone who can wrangle
you imbeciles.
Oh, go get change!
( bubbling )
Delicious.
And it's so fun eating
with these tiny wands.
( "pew pew" shooting noises )
Oh, and there's cookies, too.
I don't like the filling.
These are fortune cookies.
They can
magically predict the future.
What? No way.
"A friend will greet you
with a smile."
Aww, how sweet.
( gasping )
See, the cookies know all.
No, it can't be.
"Think positive and good luck
will come your way."
( excited shouting )
More cookies!
They're stale.
Gimme!
You're a weird girl.
Wow, Star. Good luck
did come your way.
It did, it did.
These are incredible.
Star?
APPLICANT:
Eh, previous job experience?
Nope. No one's ever been
dumb enough to hire me.
Weaknesses? I don't have any.
( blergh )
How am I under pressure?
Awesome!
LUDO:
Hmm, is that so?
Ah, yeah, um, why?
Did you hear otherwise?
I can't take it anymore!
( screaming )
APPLICANT:
Where do I see myself
in ten years?
Oh, we're best friends,
and we hang out all the time
sharing feelings
and holding hands.
( incomprehensible garbling )
You make absolutely no sense.
Go away.
Soft. So soft.
LUDO:
Next!
These idiots are even dumber
than you idiots.
West Mewnin swamp water.
Or, do you drink
from the bottle?
On days like this...
Tell me about it.
Oh, I'll tell you... ( garbled )
I've been trying to steal
a wand from a teenager.
It's harder than it ought to be.
Wait a second.
Where did you come from?
I let myself in.
When?
After you hired me.
I hired you?
I accept.
Excellent.
MAN:
We'll start tomorrow.
Get some rest.
LUDO:
Uhh...
Did anybody catch his name?
Toffee?
I guess his name is Toffee.
( birds chirping )
Oh, wise and powerful cookies,
bestow your sugary prophecies
upon me.
Ehh...
Gotcha, Star.
Those fortunes aren't magic.
They're put there
by people in a factory.
Next you'll tell me
that's how they get
the snow in snow globes.
It's clear they're the work
of dark wizards.
I'm serious. They're not real.
They're just vague so you can
read things into them.
"An unexpected visitor
will soon arrive."
See?
No one's here.
Now, who wants nachos?
Did someone say nachos?
Well, hello,
my unexpected visitor.
Ferguson, Star thinks
fortune cookies are magical.
Will you please tell
her they're not?
Now, whoa, man. Whoa.
Cookies are magical.
Once, I ate one
from the floor of a cab,
and I met my spirit animal
that night.
It was a wolf.
Why are you suddenly
a non-believer?
"Reach for the stars
and achieve your dream."
( groaning )
( screaming )
( alarmed yelling )
Huh?
Pegasus feathers.
I have always dreamed
of having a skylight in here.
( groaning )
Blindly following
these fortune cookies
is the best decision
I've ever made.
Can you give me a hand?
Yes.
Okay, Toffee,
I'm going to show you
what we're working with here.
♪ This is my house,
this is my house ♪
♪ This is my...
my house ♪
♪ This is my house,
this is my... ♪
this is my house ♪
♪ This is my... ♪
( yelling )
( groaning, screaming )
Guess I'm doomed, huh?
Be honest. I can handle it.
Ludo, Master.
The girl thinks the messages
in her cookies are fortunes.
She does whatever they say.
Interrupting!
Well, Toffee.
Give it to me straight.
Are my monsters the worst ever,
or what?
Uh...
( groaning, cracking )
Oh, man. It's stuck.
Maybe we can do something
with those fortune cookies.
What? What is... what, what?
You sure you trust him, boss?
Of course.
Oh, last cookie.
I can't wait to get more.
Star, I'm telling you,
they'll back me up
at the restaurant.
Food can't predict the future.
Sure it can.
On Mewni, there's a place
where you can get calzones
that'll tell you
how you're going to die.
You will die from choking
on a calzone.
Just kidding.
Heh heh.
A giant's going to sit
on your face.
♪♪
♪ My house, my house ♪
What are they doing?
Shh.
I think one of them's
about to get served.
♪ This is my house,
this is my... ♪
Well done.
( growling )
Fooled you, ha ha ha!
Hi-ya--
Hold on.
"Love is always the answer."
Hmm.
What?! Not in this case.
Fighting is.
Sorry, Marco.
It's not the will of the cookie.
Really? Now? Whoa!
Hugs.
There's the wand.
I can totally grab it.
Patience.
( sad moan )
Hi-ya!
( clucks )
Star, forgot
that stupid fortune.
Help me!
Sparkle, don't fight.
Then they'll stop fighting you.
STAR:
Trust the cookie.
( laughing )
MARCO:
Hey, let me out!
Hey, hey!
You guys really need some hugs.
It's actually working.
Love is always the answer.
( excited yelping )
There it is!
Out of my way!
( excited squealing )
Mine! Mine!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Back off, dude.
I've been waiting for this
since middle school.
What?
You idiots
are screwing up the plan.
Plan?
Huh?
( sighs )
Okay, look, Star.
This is really hard to say,
but, if this is going to go
any further,
I want our relationship
to have a foundation of honesty.
Me, too.
So confused.
Fortune cookies aren't real.
It was all a trap so Ludo
could steal your wand.
( panicked squeals )
Anyway, I hope--
We hope...
We hope
this isn't a deal breaker.
You know what this means,
don't you, Star?
Oh, yeah.
Love is never the answer.
Oh, man. I wanted to say it.
Mega mushroom destruction blast.
( whimpering )
( screaming )
Welcome to my life.
( groaning )
Sorry, I should have
listened to you.
Obviously you know better
than a dessert.
No, it's my fault.
I shouldn't
have messed with you
and said those fortunes
were magical in the first place.
( door opening )
Oh, weird perky girl.
You want some more
stale cookies?
Who could say no to that?
( chuckles )
What? They're not real fortunes,
but they're still real cookies.
"A great evil
has been unleashed."
BOTH:
Ooooohh.
Cheers.
That was the closest
we've ever come,
but that girl
always gets the best of me.
Yes, well,
you're not the first monster
to fall victim to their magic.
LUDO:
Things will be different
when I get the wand.
( laughs, makes "pew pew"
shooting sounds )
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something
'cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪