♪♪
[upbeat music plays]
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird,
gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here,
I'm from another-- woo-hoo ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows,
I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puh-p-u-u-uh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Okay, okay, me next,
me next, me next!
Who am I?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
I don't know.
Me, neither!
[both laughing]
Got your unicorn!
Not for long!
-[laughing]
-[splashing]
[laughing]
[panting]
Hmm?
[laughing]
Where's my unicorn?
I don't know, watch.
Watch, watch.
Oh, that looks
super-duper fun.
Well, it ain't half bad.
-You should try it.
-Cannonball!
[unicorn whinnies]
Oh, what are you doing here?
You're coming with me.
[chanting]
Where'd the hairy lady go?
I don't know,
I don't know.
-[phone buzzes]
-Ohh!
[Star on recording]
You are Star Butter--
-Hey!
-[gasps]
Guess what I found?
-Butter?
-A unicorn!
[unicorn] Hi.
Cool!
Where'd you find that?
Oh, just in the other world
at the top of the waterfall.
Another world?!
[pleasant music playing]
I'll always
take care of you.
Uh-- Uh, hey,
where are you going?
To see if there's
more worlds.
Come on!
Okay!
[squeaking with each squeeze]
Turdina!
I'm getting bored!
Well, I guess
I'll just be on my way.
All right, we gotta
come up with a new plan.
Oh, I got one.
Let's run for it!
We could just
hang at the tavern,
wait for this thing
to blow over.
I second that.
Uh, that does sound
pretty good.
Oh, come on, guys!
We're on a mission
from the acting queen!
Wait!
She's not even queen?!
Marco,
the plan didn't work, man.
Well, of course
it didn't work!
I thought we all knew that
when he named it "The Doom Nut."
Aw, come on!
Look, we're not
following Marco's plans
because they're good.
We're following them
because he's Marco.
He is gonna come up
with another terrible plan,
and when that one
doesn't work out,
he'll come up with another,
and then another.
That's why he's our leader,
'cause he's just dumb enough
to never give up.
Um, yeah, that's true.
Yeah!
Hey, uh, inspirational
speech and all,
but I ain't gettin'
my dang soul
sucked out of me!
-We'll take a group photo.
-I'm in.
Well, what are we
gonna do about those eyes?
Um, we could put
some shades on her.
That'll keep her cool.
-Ugh, Talon!
-Geez, man!
Come on!
Oh! Only Turdina
can come up with ideas!
Guys, I got a  plan.
-Ohh!
[Moon] I've never seen
anything like it.
Who's the guy
with the hot dog head?
Oh, he's creepy.
But I like it.
-Oof!
-Oof! Hey!
Let's see what's up there.
[straining]
This is dumb.
This world is dumb.
-Let's go.
-Okay!
[deep breaths]
Where you wanna go next?
[unicorn] Hey!
What's that?
I don't know,
but it has way too many legs.
-What should we do?
-Run!
We have less legs than you,
but we can still run!
[grunting]
How does this thing work, man?
Just unhook the clasp
in the back.
Oop! Oh, there it is.
Now get in position!
Got it, ma'am!
Aah!
[Marco] Over here!
Hey!
[mariachi music playing]
Welcome to Britta's Tacos.
Can I get your order?
Your friends are doing
all the fighting for you?
Are you afraid, Turdina?
Turdina...
fears... no one!
-Oh! Ohh!
-Kelly!
Floor it!
[engine revving]
[Kelly]
Let go! We're good!
Tom!
[demonic chant]
Talon! Cinch the rope!
Yeah!
That's how you do it!
You're only making things
worse for yourself!
Whoo!
Oh! Ah!
[bell chimes]
Hey, nice work, guys.
[Hekapoo]
I'm impressed.
I was pretty sure Talon
would mess it up.
-Hey! I'm a professional!
-[revving engine]
-[tires screech]
-Whoa!
Whoa!
-Huh?
-Ohh! Ohh!
Oh, no.
[groaning]
Whoa-ho!
[Tom] I got this!
[demonic chant]
[Meteora shouts]
And that takes care
of that.
-[rumbling]
-Huh?
She's gone.
Is it gone?
Hmm. Wait.
What am I looking for?
[gasping]
Aah!
Who are you?
Uh, who are you?!
I'm... um...
[gasping]
Where'd she go?
She wasn't
supposed to be here.
Aw.
Well, now I'm all alone.
You're not supposed
to be here, either.
[wind whistling]
[Kelly]
Are they gonna be okay?
I... I don't know.
[fighting tears]
I guess it's time
for that group photo.
[sniffles]
Get over here, guys.
[rumbling]
[laughing]
Dang it.
Run!
Not today, you turd!
Ohh! [groans]
Oh! I'm okay!
I'm... okay.
[weak voice] Kelly!
Wait. What?
Tad?
Kellyyyyy!
Unh!
What are you doing here?
You were supposed
to move out.
I was just collecting
the last of my...
[cough cough] ...things.
That's...
really mature of y--
And, uh, writing
the greatest love poem
of all time.
Can I recite it for you?
You don't have to.
Rose are red,
your hair is blue.
I was a bad boyfriend,
-I don't deserve... you.
-[zapping noises]
Just... let me go.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna die now, baby.
Okay, no,
you're not gonna die.
What?
-You're not gonna die.
-[zap]
How do you know?
Are you some kind
of doctor or something?
[coughing breath]
Because you never
go away.
That's the thing
with you, Tad.
-You never go away!
-[zapping]
Every time
I think you're gone,
you're back,
living inside my hair.
But where am I 'upposed to go?
-Live in the woods, Tad!
-[loud groan in background]
Live in the woods!
[zapping]
[weakly]
Kelllyyyyy!
Uhh.
Delicious!
[Meteora, sing-song]
Turdina!
Marco, it's over.
We're the only ones left.
I don't think
the Marc-nificent Two
is enough to stop her.
You're right, Tom,
but someone needs
to go warn Star.
I'll stay and buy
you both some time.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
I'm not leaving you!
You're...
You're my best friend.
I kissed Star.
What?
Yeah, so you don't
owe me anything.
Now go...
[footsteps
running away]
Wow, no hesitation.
Hey!
Oh, hello, Turdina.
I've been looking for you.
[clangs]
Well, I'm right here!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
You're a smart girl.
Figure it out.
But aren't you
gonna savor this?
I'm Princess Turdina!
Yes, I know.
But I'm looking
for a queen.
[zapping]
Rah!
-Tom!
-Huh.
What are you doing?
[gasps]
Calling your bluff!
No! I really did kiss Star!
Oh. Well, it's too late now.
Let's try that again.
-[groans]
-Tom!
-[gasps]
-You're-- You're back?
I have thousands
of spirits in here!
Wha-- [gasps]
This might...
[gasps] ...take...
[gasps] ...a while.
Huh? She's--
She's getting bigger!
I may not have-- Aah!
[gasps]
...thought this through.
Aah!
Tom!
Hi-yah!
Aah!
[Tom groaning]
Oh, what happened?
Marco? Marco!
[Meteora] Marco?!
Run.
Turdina!
What are you doing in bed?
You're supposed to be
looking for your mother.
Oh, Papa, I had
the most wonderful dream.
There were unicorns
with too many legs
and marshmallows and Mom.
Mom? [gasps] Mom!
You found your mother!
Where is she?
I don't see her.
[sighs] No.
I mean-- I mean, I did.
I did.
But she was there.
She was standing
right next to me,
and I let her get away.
It's okay, dear.
We'll just keep looking
until we find her.
Meteora!
Then it has come to this!
Ryah! Ha ha!
Ha ha!
Dad!
Ha ha! To battle!
My queen, Sir Marco's
expedition has returned.
[panting] Marco!
Tom?
I tried, Star.
What happened?
Where's Marco?
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
Aaah!
Scatter!
Star, she's right behind us.
What do we do?
Wait a minute.
Uh... Meteora?
I'm so dumb.
What?
I'm an idiot!
Uh... Oh, no,
don't say that.
How could I forget
the Magic Sanctuary?
What?
But Meteora-- Aah!
[Tom] Star,
where are we going?
[Star] This is
where me and my mom
brought
the Magic High Commission
when they were
all balloonified.
Obviously, I can't bring
the whole kingdom here,
but at least we can
start with Marco.
[bubbling]
[gasps]
There he is.
Hold my balloon.
Bwah!
-She's lost her marbles.
-Bwah!
Bwah.
Yah.
What?! No!
No, no, no, this is
not how this works!
Go get the Sanctuary!
Wh-- What did you think
was gonna happen here?
I'm doing the thing
my mom showed me!
You talk to the Guardian,
he swims in, he goes down,
the Sanctuary comes up
out of the water.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
[pop]
Star, I'm sorry.
It-- It would have worked
if my mom was here.
But I'm not her.
It's all over.
Where are you going?
[demonic chant]
Star, I promised Marco
I'd keep you safe.
We need to go.
Meteora won't find us
in the Underworld.
We'll be safe
and very, very warm.
[wind whistling]
[thunk]
What the...?
[somber music playing]
[Star] Eagles!
She got Dad?
What am I doing?!
I can't leave!
Star?
I am the queen,
and these are my people.
I have to stay and fight.
But Meteora
will destroy you!
Stay here
and take care of Marco.
Wha...? Did-- Did--
Did you know
she could do that?
[gasps]
[door creaking]
-Globgor!
-Aah!
Glossaryck! Ohh!
You almost gave me
a heart attack!
Now where is Meteora?
Globgor.
Star?!
[gasps]
-[Meteora growling]
-Oh, shoot.
[gasps]
[squeaking]
Oh, great!
Eclipsa got out!
That's awesome.
Another thing
I gotta deal with.
-[Tom screams]
-[gasps]
Aah! Ooh!
Tom!
That was so much easier
than sucking all those souls.
Just one punch. Bam!
Tom, you gotta wake up.
Don't tell me
you've forgotten
all about
your other boyfriend.
Marco!
Isn't it ironic?
All that time I was chasing
after Princess Turdina,
I barely even noticed you.
As it turns out,
I was chasing after
the wrong princess!
Mega Narwhal Bla--
Whoa!
Oh, man, this form
really packs a punch.
Winterstorm Hyperblow!
Ohh!
Cupcake Blast!
Strawberry Annihilation!
Supersonic Leech Bomb!
[beeping, popping]
[groans]
Aah!
Raspberry Ribbon Lasso!
Unh!
Ohh!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! [straining]
[groaning]
Jellybean Hallucination Mist!
Ohh!
[shouting]
Thermonuclear Butterfly Bla--
Whoa-ho!
End of the line, Butterfly.
[straining]
Okay, I get it.
You're angry.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd be angry, too.
But you don't have to do this.
We can fix everything.
You can't fix
what your family's done!
[groaning]
You're right!
I can't!
You want my power? Take it!
[straining]
[shouting]
[grunts]
[groaning]
You little brat.
Where are you?
Where are--
[whimpering]
[growls]
Nah-- Narwhal...
[groans] Narwhal...
Huh?
Eclipsa!
[gasps]
Found you!
Midnight Shriek.
Mama?
Whaaaat?
You blasted me!
You can't do this,
Meteora!
But this--
this should all be ours!
They stole it from us!
So, what, you're just
going to destroy it all?
Something like that.
Stop!
[groaning]
You're on their side?
Black Velvet Inferno.
[gasping]
Mommy?
-No! No!
-[pounding]
[Meteora screams]
[gasping]
I'm sorry.
What did you do?
What I had to.
[balloon squeaking]
I'm-- I'm alive!
[laughing]
[squeaking]
-[balloons squeaking]
-They're--
They're turning back!
[gasps] Marco!
Aah! I gotcha!
I gotcha!
Aah! Oof!
Marco!
Marco? Marco?
Huh? Star!
What happened?
I got you, Marco Diaz!
Aww! I'm--
I'm just gonna
make this weird.
Tom!
Okay, Marco,
this is great,
but your butt's making
my legs fall asleep.
[laughs] Sorry.
Eclipsa, you...
You saved us.
Star? Well, thank you
for letting me borrow this.
No, keep it.
This wand was yours.
It belongs to you.
Things haven't been right
since my family
took the kingdom.
The best thing
I can do as queen
is return what my family
stole from you.
[baby crying]
Uh...
[cooing]
Hello there little one.
What?
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Totally, totally, totally.
Uh, Eclipsa?
What did you just do?
Where is she going?
Globgor! Globgor!
Globgor! Globgooor!
Yes, Glossaryck, Globgor.
We know.
No, no, no! Eclipsa's
monster love, Globgor.
She's going off
to be with him.
I've been trying
to tell you for months.
Anyway, see ya around.
Is his voice different?
Hello, my love.
We're home.
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Ohh,
there goes a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining sta-a-r ♪