♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Uh, next.
Where are you going?
I thought you wanted
a goblin dog, right?
Do you see
the goblin dog truck?
This is the place.
I am positive.
You've been saying that
for the last 12 dimensions,
and I'm hungry.
I'm gonna go home
and make a sandwich.
I think I found it!
There it is.
The goblin dog truck.
That line is, like,
a million miles long.
It's all good.
My friend Kelly's
holding us a spot. Yo, Kelly!
Oh, hey, Kelly.
Yo, Star, come
stand by me, girl.
Oh, my goodness.
We got so much
catching up to do.
Let's start doing it.
Not you, Marco.
You can stand over here
and talk to Kelly.
Hey, Kelly.
Uh, have you been
waiting long?
That's so cute.
You guys are basically
like the same person.
Yeah, but, uh,
are you sure
you wanna wait
in this crazy line
for just a hot dog?
It's not
just a hot dog.
It's a goblin dog.
Some would kill
for a goblin dog.
Just like how I almost
killed you with that ax.
Just to be clear, I'm
the one who threw that ax.
I pulled myself out of
the ground for a goblin dog.
I'm a bit tender.
Oh, please, I had
a goblin dog
- just last week,
and it was the bomb.
- ( all exclaiming )
♪ You might think
this line is long ♪
♪ But listen to
my goblin song ♪
♪ It's been hours
since you ate ♪
♪ But goblin dogs
are worth the wait ♪
What is happening?
With Ms. Heinous gone,
St. O's is like a total
party school now.
Did you guys see
that little man
playing the music?
Marco, you're
ignoring Kelly.
- Rude.
- Oh, sorry.
Did you see that
little man playing music?
Okay.
I gotta have
a tall man, you know,
'cause I like to float
like, five feet
off the ground,
so it's like,
I'm 4'6",
but with six-inch heels,
you know what I'm saying?
I mean, sometimes it feels
like they're the kids
and I'm the parent,
you know?
Whoa! You got another
one of those? I'm starving.
You gotta be
kidding me.
- What the...
- All right, kiddies.
You're just moments away
from maximum mouth-ertainment.
So stay cool in a hot
goblin dog T-shirt.
Me, me!
In my mouth.
I want it in my mouth.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
- You work here?
- Yes.
We've been waiting forever.
- How do we get
a goblin dog?
- You wait in line.
And can you tell me
how to get in that
short line over there?
Oh, that's the VIP line.
It's my boss' idea.
How do we get
to the VIP line?
Well, it's pretty
exclusive,
but I could s-n-e-a-k
you guys in.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna go with
no, thank you.
What? He just offered
to sneak us in.
Oh, what? I thought
he spelled something out.
That's my bad.
Welcome to
the VIP line!
Okay. Who's ready to buy
some goblin dog products?
That's okay. We just
want the hot dog.
You're in the VIP line.
That stands for...
Buy the products,
stay in the line,
- get the dogs.
- I don't have any money.
Oh, I think
I got some.
Check in my back
pocket, girl.
Oh, uh-uh. No, I think
that's my keys.
Oh, I found it.
Uh, 27 cents
and two pistachio shells.
I got some cash.
Marco, how much money is that?
- Like 650 bucks.
- Yep, that'll do it.
This will get you
the executive package.
Man, this goblin dog stuff
is ridiculous.
Yeah, you dropped a ton
of cash on all this swag.
No, I got us into
the right line.
Oh, my gosh. Look.
We're next!
Four goblin dogs, please.
Oh, you have to wait
in that line now.
How many lines
are there?
Oh, it's all one line.
There's just a lot of them,
so after that line,
you'll go to that line.
Then that line,
then that line,
then it hooks back
like a dog's leg,
then you gotta
take a number.
from a little number
ticket pulley thingy.
Okay, I'd like to speak
to the manager, please.
Certainly, sir.
Yes?
What's the deal, man?
We waited six hours
and bought all your stuff.
I'm sorry, sir.
- Did you say you've been
waiting for six hours?
- Yes.
Well, some of these folks
have been waiting years.
ALL: Years?!
Years!!
So what did
my manager say?
ALL: You're the manager!
You know what?
Forget this, okay?
- I'm not waiting years
just to try a goblin dog.
- What?
Ponyhead, I thought you said
you had a goblin dog before.
Well, as it were, uh...
Have you had a goblin dog
or not, Ponyhead?
Uh, I don't know.
Who can tell?
Like... maybe not.
- I'm done.
- Marco, come on.
Ponyhead didn't mean bad.
She's just a liar.
( angry muttering )
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait? That's all
we've been doing.
I'm sweaty,
I'm hungry,
and on top of everything,
you lied about goblin dogs.
Look, Marco,
I mean,
all of these people
have lied.
She's right.
I lied, too.
I'm not the one who
threw this ax at you.
Hi. My name's Stan.
ALL: Hi, Stan.
I'm also a liar.
I told my wife
this was a mink coat.
It's just my body.
My glasses are fake.
Ooh, it feels good
to let that out.
These aren't my teeth.
Look, we've all lied,
and lying is not cool.
But there's only
one person here
who has lied to
all of us.
Yeah. Ponyhead.
ALL: Yeah!
No. No, no, no.
That guy.
Oh, yeah.
He did lie to all of us.
- Get him!
- ( all yelling )
You're gonna lose
your place in line.
Look out, Marco.
Oh, no!
All right, Ponyhead.
He's getting away.
We lost him.
Oh, no, we certainly
did not.
Grab on, turd.
I'm not sure
I like you calling...
Summoning cloudy charm.
Magnificence marshmallow mush!
( groans )
Okay, Roy, now get out
the goblin dogs.
Okay, you got me,
severed horse head.
- Goblin dogs aren't real.
- What?
It's a ruse.
I took you for everything.
Come on, you guys.
Let's just go.
Look, kids, you can
have your money back.
You know what?
- Keep it.
- Uh, Marco,
that was 650 bucks.
Yeah. Well, now,
every time he sees my $650,
he'll remember the three kids
whose dreams he wrecked.
No, I'll just spend the money.
He's right, Marco.
We'll take the money,
okay, thanks.
No, Star, we're going home.
( giggling )
( maniacal laughter )
What the...
- Star.
- ( laughter continues )
You've done it.
Ready when you are, Star.
No. You earned
the goblin dog.
What are you
talking about?
Goblin dogs are real.
I had one before.
- Kelly?
- Oh, we thought you died.
MARCO: What?
No, we didn't.
Oh, okay, well,
I'm sorry.
I thought she did die,
so excuse me.
Wait. You've had
a goblin dog?
Got it from Roy.
So goblin dogs
are real?
They are.
Yes.
This was all
some kind of trick.
Not a trick.
A goblin dog must
choose its master
through trial,
and today,
the goblin dog
chooses you.
ALL: Wow!
Behold!
Oh, my gosh!
( all exclaiming )
Those aren't goblin dogs.
These are goblin dogs.
Oh, yeah!
Here, Pony.
Bon apetit.
This tastes like
a normal hot dog.
It's basic
but it's good.
Hm. Yeah.
I guess I was expecting...
( gasps )
Goblin dogs!
That was amazing!
I gotta give it
to you, Ponyhead.
Those hot dogs
were pretty good.
Oh, well, you know,
the best for my besties,
and whatever,
all that kind of stuff.
But, you guys,
on the real,
I am so done
with this place.
I'm ready to hoof it.
Oh, no, you can't
say that. No.
Roy makes me go through
this every time.
Why are those goblin dogs
so good?
Hey, Kelly, it's been
really great talking to you.
Yeah, man, it was really
cool hangin' out with you, too.
- What?!
- Oh, hey, I'm Tad.
I'm Kelly's
boyfriend.
You've been there
this whole time?
Yeah, I don't really
eat hot dogs.
I'm a vegan and stuff.
But, you know, I like
to hang out.
( loud rumbling )
( groaning )
I don't even
understand, girls.
This thing is impossible
to control... ( screaming )
Why won't you work?
Hm?
You can talk?
Tell me your secrets.
Star Butterfly?
But I don't want
to see Star Butterfly.
She doesn't have
a wand anymore.
Oh, you're right.
She doesn't need a wand
for me to steal her wisdom.
Girls, pack your things.
It's time to catch
a butterfly!
( groaning )
I'm not good at
these new spells.
Why can't I just stick with
a normal blast?
Because there are
other spells in your book.
Yeah, but...
Oh, Star. Look.
This one's got pictures.
Can we do it?
That's got
a lot of steps.
Star, can you just
do the spell, please?
This book is so heavy.
Ugh! All right.
( groaning )
What do I gotta do?
Start with the first one.
Mmm, close enough.
I guess.
Now how about this one?
Okay, see, to me,
it looks like you're
gonna wanna get both arms up,
like way up
together.
More.
Up and out, Star.
Look at me.
Huh?
All the way up.
Pointing at 11:00.
Earth 11:00
or Mewni 11:00?
They're the same, Star.
Ugh, this is impossible.
Look, I know how
to cast a spell, okay?
Twirl, twirl, twirl,
helicopter arms,
helicopter arms.
Warnicorn stampede!
See, I did it.
But, Star,
that's a single warnicorn.
A stampede is
many warnicorns.
( laughs )
I think somebody
needs to get back to
studying her spell book.
Help.
You know what, Glossaryck?
I'm done with
the book for today.
Come on, Marco.
Let's go have fun
with our friends.
Oh.
I thought we were friends.
What? Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
We're friends.
I just don't have
fun with you.
But that is so fine,
'cause it's not like
you like having
fun, right?
Obviously. It's like
you're alone all the time.
Lonely people can be cool,
like you.
You're like a wise old hermit.
Or like a wise old monk.
Or... or a...
like, I don't really know
what you are...
Wow.
Say no more.
I know when I'm not wanted.
No, no, no.
I won't be bothering you
ever again.
Oh, my gosh.
I am so sorry, Glossaryck.
Of course you're
our friend.
Uh, is he though?
All this guy has
ever done for us
is hand out weird riddles
and eat pudding.
Don't you talk like that
about our friend, Marco.
We have to
make it up to him.
All right. Look,
my Uncle Enrique
hid in a box for
three days once.
I know how
to handle this.
We can never be together,
Isobel.
We're from two
different worlds.
( screeching )
Society will never
accept us!
See? Isn't this fun?
Just three good friends
watching a movie together.
'Cause that's what
good friends do.
Marco, please tell Star
we are not talking.
Star, Glossaryck said
he's still not talking.
Glossaryck, can you be nice
and pass this popcorn-candy
mix to Star?
Hm, let me think.
- No, but I will
have these.
- Hey!
Oh, Boom Nuggets.
I know where
you're going.
( grumbles )
Hey, no big deal.
- I'll just make us
some more snacks.
- No, wait!
Cotton candy cloud!
That worked out better...
You know, it might not kill you
to study a bit more.
Don't you start, too, Marco.
Glossaryck, you'll miss
the whole movie
if you stay in there.
I thought you liked
romantic comedies.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I've seen this one before.
And the squid lady
dies in the end.
( all groaning )
( screeching )
I can't hold her back
much longer.
Glossaryck, help me.
Marco, could you do me
a favor and tell Star
she should ask one of
her Earth friends to help out?
( burps )
You can stop, Marco.
He called our bluff.
( screeches )
- Stop, Marco.
- Oh, sorry.
This is the most disgusting
dumpster in town.
The smell will get him
out of the box.
All right. We're
getting Glossaryck back.
Glossaryck!
What the...
Ludo?!
You're back?
Ludo's back!
Yes, I am.
I tossed you
into the abyss.
She tossed you
Yes, you did.
- What?
- Huh?
- BOTH: You have a wand?
- You both have wands.
Okay, seriously, Marco,
that's getting annoying.
Actually, he's right.
Star Butterfly,
you're coming with me!
Rainbow fist punch!
What?
Ha ha!
That's your rainbow punch?
Heart attack!
This is the worst
wand fight I've ever seen.
Oh, no, I don't
have time for this.
Hey, we aren't done.
Come back here.
Seriously?
( car alarm blares )
Nice.
Star, the lid.
It isn't holding.
Glossaryck!
Oh, no!
No!
Now, Princess,
I give you a choice.
Come with me or die.
Warnicorn stampede!
Fine. Have it your way.
It's going to be
pretty hard to miss from here.
Star!
Om!
- Glossaryck?
- ( whistles )
What? A book.
Now, read.
Warnicorn stampede!
What is that?
- Oh.
- You did it!
That was so cool.
Yeah, it was.
And all I had to do
was read from the book.
Well, my work here
is done.
Glossaryck.
I'm sorry
we hurt your feelings.
Oh, you didn't
hurt my feelings.
I have no feelings.
It was all part
of the plan.
What do you mean,
part of the plan?
Yeah, why'd you lock yourself
in the donut box then?
I went into that box
on purpose,
because I needed
to get to that candy.
Oh! Wait, why?
Well, how would you rocket
yourself from a trash compactor?
What?
I don't know.
Marco, Marco, I had to be
in that donut box,
so I could land
at Ludo's feet
to trip him up
and save the day.
Wait, wait.
So you're saying
you did all that on--
Boom Nuggets.
( laughs )
( sighs )
Fine.
( maniacal laughter )
Guess what.
There's a book.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪