♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Kingdoms of Mewni,
each year,
we hold this dance
to celebrate
the peace between us.
Welcome to
the Silver Bell Ball.
( cheering )
Whoo hoo!
Yeah!
The rules of the ball
are the same as always.
Each royal heir
will dance with all the others,
representing the bonds
between our kingdoms.
Their kingdom got
taken over by rats.
How could they
let that happen?
Hey, hey,
they were big rats.
Oh, girl,
okay, okay.
What do you think
of the line-up?
Be honest.
It's just the same
bunch of borings
as every year, Pony.
Okay, that's fine,
but, like, check out
Prince Larry Kelpbottom.
Mm-hmm, okay.
Somebody came up
and hit him with
a hottie stick.
Guess it is kinda cool
to see everyone dance.
- Hey, Princess Jaggs.
- Hey.
Hi, Princess
Spider Bite.
Hello.
Oh, look, there's
your annoying cousin.
Yeah. Guess
I should say hi.
Hi, Rock.
Your cousin.
Over here.
Rock Johansen.
Okay, he hasn't changed.
Oh, looks like Rich Pigeon
got himself some new legs.
Ooh, somebody's
missing, Star.
Yep.
He's always late.
This is where
you two met, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Drama.
Drama!
Drama, drama, drama,
drama, drama, drama...
Pony, no drama this year.
I told my parents
I was gonna focus on
the princess biz.
Oh, come on,
you're the bomb
at shakin' up
these dusty
old traditions, girl.
- Not this year.
- Oh, come on.
- No.
- Come on.
No, Pony.
Seriously.
Did you not hear me
when I said come on?
- Come on, come on.
- I'm serious.
Sh!
I've caused a lot
of trouble this summer.
It's time to be
a better princess.
Sunglasses at night.
Classy.
MANFRED: Announcing
the arrival of
Prince Thomas Lucitor.
Hey, everybody.
And his parents,
Lord and Lady Lucitor,
of the underworld.
Hello, Wrathmeelior.
- Hi, Dave.
- Hey.
Will the dancers
please stand
for the commencement bow?
( gasps )
Did you just see that?
Ho ho ho, yes!
Ooh, I think
the whole room saw that.
Girl, you're
getting club-snubbed.
Oh, no...
What is that?
Oh, I don't know,
it's just the best way
to get someone
all up in your business.
Watch.
Hey, Kelpbottom.
Kelpbottom!
No, no, not you. Not you.
The handsome one.
You hear that, honey?
I'm the handsome one.
( snorts )
Pony, what the...
I thought you liked him.
Oh, I do, I do.
But listen, the more
you ignore somebody,
the more they fall
deeply in love with you.
That's, like, science.
It's scientific or
something like that.
( sniffs )
Ugh, okay. Can you please
give me some space,
'cause I really
need that from you, okay?
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
- It works every time.
- Weird.
Let the first dance begin.
Ahem.
Anyone?
Oh, my.
It seems Prince Thomas
has taken
the initiative,
and he appears to be
walking towards Princess Star.
Star and Thomas
have always been
the best dancers at
every Silver Bell Ball,
and we all know they had
a very tumultuous relationship
before breaking up
last year.
( groans )
Manfred.
May I have this dance...
Well, all right.
Let's do this.
Princess Jaggs?
( all gasping )
Uh, yeah, okay.
You look lovely today.
What? No, you do.
Well, this is
a surprising
turn of events.
No mistake.
At the previous
Silver Bell Balls,
Tom always chose
Princess Star first to dance.
Pony, I think I am
getting club-snubbed.
Ooh, this is some
next-level club-snubbing.
He wants you bad, girl.
Ugh. Tom always does this.
When is he gonna realize
I'm not interested?
Okay, calm yourself,
Butterfly.
You're a princess,
for goodness sake.
Oh, it's on.
Hm, let's see,
let's see.
- I choose you.
- ( cooing )
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, Princess Star
has chosen Prince Rich Pigeon
as her first dance partner.
Could there be
a new romance waiting
in the wings?
Oh, Richard.
I had no idea you were
such a good dancer.
( coos )
Good job, girl.
Mm-hmm, that
oughta show him.
( laughing )
( growls )
At last, the dancers
have completed the ceremony,
and are seated
with their parents.
All except Star
and Thomas.
They're saving
the best for last.
( laughing )
Hmm.
Come on, Star.
Dance with him.
May I have this dance...
Manfred?
( all gasping )
Oh, dear.
Oh, snap!
( laughs )
No one has ever
asked me to dance.
( giggles )
Ladies and gentlemen,
Star has asked me,
Manfred,
to the dance floor.
I feel like
I'm in a dream.
Your daughter just
club-snubbed my son.
Your son's been
club-snubbing
my daughter all night!
My son
is a gentleman.
My daughter is
a delicate flower.
Delicate flower? Let's see
how delicate a flower you are!
- ( arguing )
- Unbelievable!
No, no, no, no,
you do not get to make
sad eyes at me.
This is your fault.
Look, I still don't
wanna date you.
I have been through
a lot lately,
and what I really
need is a friend.
But all you wanna do
is play your little
childish games.
Games?
Oh, don't act
all innocent,
you club-snubber.
What? Star, I was there
on Song Day.
I know you're
with Marco now.
Oh, Ruberiot.
That song is gonna haunt me
for the rest of my life.
No, no. It was
a huge wake-up call.
I finally realized
you're not into me.
So during the dance,
I wanted to do the right thing,
and give you space.
If you'd asked
to dance,
I totally would've, but...
I wanted it
to be your choice.
Okay, first of all,
me and Marco, not a thing.
- Really?
- Hey, not the point.
Second of all,
giving me space
doesn't mean pretending
I don't exist.
That's just rude.
I was just trying
to do the right thing.
It would've been nice if you
didn't ignore me all night.
I don't know
how to be nice!
At least give me
credit for trying.
This wasn't easy.
( yells )
You're being
really dramatic.
Whatever, Star.
I was just trying
to give you what you want.
This isn't what I want.
KING: Look what you did!
You're paying for that chair!
I'll pay for the chair
when you pay for
all the damage
Toffee caused.
I'm starting to rethink
being allies with your kingdom.
Oh, why don't you just
crawl back into
that little hole
you came out of?
Please, everyone,
settle down.
( cooing )
How could they let
that happen?
Tom, may I have
this dance?
I'd be delighted.
Aw, look at 'em go.
Um, Star?
We should probably
stop dancing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And this concludes
the Silver Bell Ball.
( loud thumping )
Awwww.
I forgot what
a good dancer you are.
Yeah, thanks.
So, um, would you
maybe wanna get
a corn shake or something?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I could do that.
Beep beep.
Excuse us.
Look at me, Star.
Ooh, it's a new
club-snub record.
( laughing )
Ready, Glossaryck?
- Here comes the airplane.
- ( makes airplane noises )
Globgore, globgore.
Come on, Glossaryck.
Be a good boy.
Glossaryck,
what have I told you?
We express ourselves
with our words,
not our pudding.
- Globgore!
- ( gasps )
Oh, Glossaryck.
Here, boy.
- Do you wanna...
- Globgore?
...go for a walk?
Globgore!
Glossaryck, slow down!
Globgore, globgore.
( Star yelling )
Glossaryck,
what the heck?
Stop that,
bad Glossaryck.
Are we gonna have to go
back into the diaper,
'cause I will do it.
( chittering )
Globgore!
Ah, Glossaryck!
No!
Oh, Glossaryck!
Oh, my goodness.
I am so sorry
about your roses.
He... oh!
Don't worry.
They're just flowers.
It's not like they're
something really cool,
like a squirrelicorn.
- Isn't that right?
- Globgore!
Globgore, globgore.
Oh!
How did you do that,
and teach it to me now.
( laughs )
He just looked like
he needed a little
head scratch.
( quietly )
Globgore.
You know,
once in a while,
you've got to slow down
and appreciate the feeling
of a nice head scratch,
or the smell of
a freshly bloomed rose,
or the taste of
a delicious candy bar.
( chewing loudly )
I might have
some self-control issues.
( both laughing )
Yeah, me, too.
You seem so familiar.
We met before, right?
Maybe. I used to visit
this garden a lot.
Oh, have you been to
the Rose Tower?
The view of the garden
is absolutely divine.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
That's been condemned
for forever.
Well, don't let
that stop you.
( giggles )
Hey, if you're
around tonight,
you should come to
the royal dinner.
Oh, that sounds
delightful.
But I may have
other plans.
Aw. You got
a hot date?
Something like that.
- Star!
- Mom!
Omnitraxis!
Star, are you okay?
Did she hurt you?
What? No.
No one hurt me.
I was just talking
to that nice lady.
Nice lady?
Star, that's Eclypsa.
Long time,
no speak, Moon.
How did that spell
work for you?
Not another word
out of you, Eclypsa.
That's Eclypsa?
We need to
decontaminate you.
- Look into
the light, please.
- What?
- Uh, to check for
spots of evil.
- Spots of evil?
Well, there's no telling
what Eclypsa might have
done to you.
Stop it. I am telling you,
Eclypsa didn't do
anything to me.
I am fine.
What are you... hey!
Cover your left eye
with the paddle,
and read the lines
as best you can.
I-A-M-E-V-I...
No, you don't.
That just spells
"I am evil."
That was, like,
totally an admission.
What? No, this is rigged.
I was reading the thing.
Skin check.
Oh, dear.
You always had this mole?
Yes, but it doesn't
make me evil.
Just a little
self-conscious sometimes.
And why is there
a monkey?
- To check for evil fleas.
- Evil fleas?
- ( screeching )
- He found something.
- Never mind. He says
they're just regular fleas.
- I knew that.
Stand here,
arms down.
- One moment.
- Hey!
Do you even know
what you're doing?
No, but we still
gotta do a test.
Are you evil?
No!
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Are you evil, are you
evil, are you evil?
- Is she all right?
- I am fine.
I talked to Eclypsa for,
like, two seconds,
and she was
really nice.
No big deal.
It could be
a very big deal.
Okay, fine, but why?
Star, she betrayed
her kingdom.
She abandoned her people
so she could run off
with a monster.
Mm-hmm, yes, right.
I knew that.
Kinda selfish.
Okay, then what?
She blew everything up?
No. They crystallized her
before she had the chance.
Wait, you crystallized her
for being in love?
To a monster.
And that's not all.
She didn't respect
the natural order.
She meddled in the dark arts,
and created her own chapter
of dangerous evil magic.
Have you ever even read it?
Of course not.
Well, I have, and it really
wasn't that big of a deal.
Ugh. Chime in
any time, guys.
You knew her, too.
Uh, I mean, I saw her
double-dipping in the ranch
at the royal ball once.
She told me she thought
Rhombulus was annoying.
- Can you believe it?
- Yes.
Oh, yeah? She totally
used to eat babies.
Nope, nope,
that wasn't Eclypsa.
That was Bobipsa,
the barbarian baby eater.
Are you calling
me a liar?
I'm pretty sure Eclypsa
was a pescaterian.
Okay, guys,
as fascinating
and fact-filled
as this conversation is,
I'm feeling kinda done.
The tests say I'm fine.
Star, please, these tests
are for your own good.
Ugh! I am good.
It sounds like Eclypsa didn't
deserve to be crystallized.
I mean, what's next,
you gonna crystallize me
if I do something
you don't approve of?
Give us the room.
When I first
met Eclypsa,
I trusted her, too.
I didn't know
any better.
Truthfully, Star,
you're very capable
for your age, but--
Then why won't
anyone listen to me?
It's complicated.
Eclypsa can
be very...
convincing.
For your safety,
let me handle this.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm afraid the only
option is immediate
re-crystallization.
What? No. No, no, no, no.
That's so harsh.
- You can't just go--
- This isn't a debate, Star.
I gave my orders to
the Magic High Commission,
and they're on their way
to her cell as we speak.
She's to be re-crystallized
immediately.
Oh, we'll see about that.
Oh, Globgore!
My wand!
Locked! Glossaryck.
- Glossaryck!
- Globgore?
Glossaryck, the wand.
Globgore?
Wand.
Globgore!
Oh, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes!
Globgore.
No, Glossaryck.
We have to save Eclypsa.
Globgore.
Gotcha.
Super sparkle cloudy.
Wheeeee!
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Rhombulus, no, wait!
Turn it off!
Great. Now I got crystals
growing outta my...
Oh, Star, you caused
quite the ruckus.
Will you all just
listen to me for one second?
Crystallizing people
is a serious punishment,
and so far, no one
has been able to convince me
that Eclypsa deserves it.
Star, I know Eclypsa
seems nice,
but she can get into your head
and make you do things
you don't want to do.
Oh, my goodness,
you're right.
Giving you that spell
to destroy Toffee
was her idea.
Oh, no, wait.
You were the one
who went to her
for help.
Yes, but...
And you made
a deal with her.
If Toffee was destroyed,
she'd be set free.
Well, hey,
Toffee's gone,
and you wanna go back
on your word?
But Star, look what
her spell did to me.
When I performed
that spell,
I could feel the darkness.
Eclypsa is
evil, Star.
I know you don't
believe it now,
but if you wait
to find out the truth
for yourself,
it'll be too late.
Okay, fine. If she is
as bad as you say she is,
then put her in a crystal.
But she at least deserves
to have a fair trial.
Oh, for goodness sake, fine.
We'll have a trial.
Yes!
Due process, due process.
but I'm only allowing this
because I want there to be
no doubt amongst anyone
in Mewni--
I'm looking at you, Star--
that Eclypsa is evil
and deserves her fate.
See, Eclypsa?
Around here, we believe in
a little thing called
the justice system.
Hey, where are you going?
It's going to take
a little time
to get the trial
all set up.
You can't just leave her
chained up
in this dark
and smelly dungeon.
You know, I always did
enjoy gazing at the roses.
Oh, hello,
Princess Butterfly.
Stand aside.
- Eclypsa.
- Star. I was hoping--
- Don't move.
I want some answers.
Did you or did you not
mess with dark magic?
Well... I did
what I had to do for me.
If the Magic High Commission
and your mother
think that's evil,
call me a villainess.
Wait. Are you in my mind?
They said you could be
in my mind, and I
wouldn't even know.
Definitely not.
But if I were,
I wouldn't tell you.
That's a joke.
Oh, it wasn't
very funny.
- But that's okay, 'cause...
- Globgore.
Globgore!
- Glossaryck!
Good to see you.
- Globgore!
He's, uh, he's been
kind of a handful lately.
Could you maybe do that
crystal-y tickly thing again?
- Sure.
- Globgore, globgore.
I might corrupt him.
What?!
( nervous laughter )
That was another joke.
Right?
Globgore?
Globgore.
Aw, they're so sweet
when they're sleeping.
Okay, listen, just because
I didn't want you
crystallized again
doesn't mean I trust you.
I just want you to be
treated fairly.
Although, this place
doesn't exactly seem fair.
What in the rodent is that?!
Well, I love it here.
Actually, this was
my room, you know,
back in the, well,
you know, before.
A lot has changed.
But the most important
thing's still the same.
Wow!
This view
is incredible.
Isn't it?
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪