♪♪
[upbeat music plays]
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird,
gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here,
I'm from another-- woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows,
I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puh-p-u-u-uh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[Star] Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay, and how exactly big
was this portal?
[stammering]
It was huge.
I mean, massive.
"Ginormous portal..."
And you say
it was rainbow colored?
Yes, all kinds
of swirling colors.
She went to it
like a moth to a flame.
Ah, right,
I know that one.
I'm so sorry.
Moon would have stooped her
if I hadn't interfered.
Now Meteora's heading this way.
[pen clicks]
Okay, well,
that about covers it.
Guards!
[Lady Whosits and guard]
Hup hup hup hup hup!
Hmm! Not me.
Her.
Hup hup hup hup hup!
[clank]
Star, what
are you going to do?
[Eclipsa] What are you
going to do to my daughter?
Come on, Marco.
Hup hup hup hup...
-Hup hup. Uh...
-[lock clicks]
Kyle?
[Kyle] Uh, I'm...
I'm in here.
Hey, you doing okay
with this queen thing?
Ugh!
I'm not queen.
I'm acting queen.
My mom's still out there!
Right! Right,
right, right, right, right.
Acting queen!
Well, are you doing okay,
acting queen?
Marco!
I'm freakin' out, man!
I know.
I'm freakin' out, too!
Being a queen's squire,
it's like a...
a big deal.
Mmm.
Sorry, acting queen.
Everybody's looking at me
for decisions,
but all I can think about
is my mom.
Ohh, what would Mama do?
What--
What are you doing?
Waiting... for an answer.
-[trumpet blares]
-Aah!
Queen Star.
Acting queen.
We have a situation
that demands
your attention.
May I present
Mr. Bugbert Swampington
and his family.
Aah!
What happened to 'em?!
Big monster ramp-ragin'
through the countryside,
gave 'em the eye
and made 'em all floaty.
Meteora.
Sir, I assure you
the Butterflys are
on this job,
and we will fix this.
You have my word.
Yeah? All right.
[blaring]
Manfred!
Stop with the horn.
Sorry, my queen.
The scouting raven
has returned
with news of the monster.
The monster,
it approaches...
the castle!
Must...
fly away!
What do we do,
my queen?
We're gonna
figure it out.
Bless you, Queen!
Bless you.
[Rhombulous]
What do we do?!
Okay, everybody, hi.
Thanks for coming.
Look, my mom is gone.
Uh, she's coming back.
Workin' on that.
In the meantime,
we need to come up with...
Hey! What are you
doing here?
Uh, counseling you?
No! No!
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm sorry,
no liars allowed.
Leave now!
Out, out, out, out!
Go! Out!
[Rhombulous] Big mistake.
[Hekapoo]
You're gonna need us.
[Omnitraxus]
Omnitraxus Prime has spoken!
Uhh! Okay,
here's where we're at.
Meteora is on her way
here right now
to destroy us all,
and so far nobody
has been able to stop her.
Pretty serious.
So I am opening up the floor
for any ideas you've got.
[laughs]
C'mon, gang,
there's no dumb suggestions!
Sir Scarsguard!
You've led the Mewni army
against legions
of marauding monsters
for three generations.
You even taught me
how to wield a sword.
In this time of crisis,
your expertise--
What'd she say?
She said that
there's a monster
that they want you--
-What?
-You to go and fight,
to be
fighting the monster.
-I can't hear a word.
-[louder] There's a monster...
-Not a single word!
-...that they would like you--
I must be out of batteries.
You're not even trying.
You see?
He acts like
that thing doesn't work.
Okay, uh, thank you,
Lord and Lady Scarsguard.
Welcome to my life.
[whimpers]
-Okay...
-[taps table]
Sir Muscleton!
What's up, baby girl.
What did you...
-[chair legs squeak]
-What did you call me?
I think I called
you... baby girl.
Aah!
Yeah, so
Sir Dashing of Muscleton
isn't gonna be able
to help us.
Marco, what do ya got?
What about Mina Loveberry?
Oh, right, Mina!
[laughs] Perfect!
That nut mix
is a one-woman army!
Way ahead of you!
We already sent Mina
out to do just that.
Aha-ha, great!
And she lost.
[balloon-like squeak]
-Queen Star?
-Acting queen!
We just need to know
what the Royal Kitchen
should make for dinner.
Just choose anything!
Queen Moon always decided
on the menu, not us.
Okay. Well, today's
the day you start!
Surprise me.
Of course.
What would you like us
to surprise you with?
Star! Wait!
What is it, Dad?
I want to help you plan.
Oh, Yes!
Oh, thank you, Papa.
How do we stop
Meteora?
No, I meant the dinner menu.
I've got some ideas.
Ugh, not helping, Dad.
I'm sorry, Star,
but you're queen now.
I've seen how strong
you've grown.
You'll figure it out.
And whatever you decide,
I'll back you!
Think about a corn medley.
Cornbread, cornmeal.
That's an entire meal
of corn.
[sighs] Thanks, Dad.
I do love corn.
-Globgor!
-[Star groans]
Mommm!
Your job is really hard!
I need your help.
I can't do this alone.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
Glossaryck,
what do I do?
-Globgor!
-Arghh!
-[Star growls]
Uh, buddy, the chefs
are working on dinner,
but they wanted me
to ask you about dessert.
Argh! How am I supposed
to delegate anything
to these cornheads?
Can't anybody here actually
think for themselves
without my mom around?
Good day,
acting Queen Butterfly!
Finally,
somebody gets it right.
I have your laundry,
freshly pressed!
Thank you, just leave it
on the thing.
I've sorted it all
from your favorite
to least favorite color
and removed
a couple stains I found.
I also re-dyed a few items
to better compliment
your skin tone.
Oh... thank you.
That's actually really helpful.
I also ironed your socks
-and re-hemmed your
favorite dinosaur skirt.
-Wow, that's amazing.
It seemed better to head off
the problem before it got worse.
Why didn't I see it before?!
Lavabo, its you!
-Me?
-Him?!
You!
Steadfast Lavabo,
dependable Lavabo!
Sir Lavabo,
I have a job for you.
-What?!
-My queen,
it would be
an honor to serve you
in any way--
No, no. No, no, no.
Nuh-uh, no way.
Can you, um-- Can you
please excuse us for just a--
What are you thinking?
You can't send him!
Do you have
a better plan, squire?
Because I have been waiting
to hear one all day!
Me. Send me.
You? Marco, no offense,
but it's gonna take
more than a red belt
to defeat Meteora.
You forget I have 16 years
of experience fighting
thousands of Hekapoos.
Go ahead, hit me
with your best spell!
Marco, I'm
not gonna fight you.
Weeaakkk!
Ugh! Come on, Marco,
I really don't have time
for this nonsense--
Strawberry Shake Quake!
Hyah! Yah!
Come on, Star, I said
your best spell!
Narwhal Blast!
Yah! Hi-yah!
Rude!
My turn!
Uh! Not cool!
[blowing raspberries]
Warnicorn Stampede!
[whinnying and neighing]
-Yah!
-[both whinnying]
Hi-yah!
Hi-yah! Hah! Hah!
Sparkle Kitten
Firework Shower!
[loud meowing]
[Star]
Honeybee Tornado Swarm!
-[bees buzzing]
-[Marco] Hah!
[panting] Ha!
Is that all you got?
[growling]
Spider with a Top Hat Blast!
War cryyy!
-Aaah!
-Whoa-ho!
-Aaaah!
Glooobgor!
[grunting]
[squeaks]
[both panting]
Okay, not bad, Diaz.
[laughs] Told you!
No, Star,
my abs are not back.
Just checking.
Look, just because
you can take on my spells
doesn't mean
you can take on Meteora.
I don't
know if anyone can.
Your mom can.
You heard what Eclipsa said.
If she hadn't interfered,
your mom would
have beaten Meteora.
I don't have to stop her.
I just have to
buy you time to find
your mom and bring her back.
Okay, we gotta
divide and conquer.
You keep Meteora
from reaching the castle
while I go find my mom.
How are you gonna do that?
My mom is stuck
in the magic dimension.
I gotta go there
to find her.
But that's where
you lost your memory.
That's really dangerous.
I know,
but I don't have a choice.
Okay, as acting queen,
I order you,
my squire Marco Diaz,
to do whatever it takes
to stop Meteora
from reaching
Butterfly Castle.
I accept my orders.
Okay, well, then
you get started on
that order right away.
Hey, Star. Y'know,
you don't have to pretend
to be strong around me.
I'm your best friend.
Mmm. Uhh! I need a hug!
I'm really scared.
Yeah... me, too.
Hello, Queen Butterfly!
Dinner is served!
-Great talking.
-Yes. Thank you, friend.
Just a talk, bro.
Uh... anyway,
we did what you said.
We got creative!
[jiggling]
Good first try.
Can I go now?
Oh, hey! It's you!
You wanna paddle
around with me?
No! Nu-nu-nu-nu-no way,
buster!
If I have fun with you,
I'll forget who I am
and be stuck here forever.
Yeah!
Doesn't that sound great?!
Nice try, but this time
I came prepared!
[buzzing]
[Star, on recording]
You are Star Butterfly.
You must find your mom
and bring her home.
I am Star Butterfly.
I must find my mom
and bring her home.
Okay, have fun!
I'll see ya soon!
I've called you all here
because you're
the most cunning,
the most agile,
the most experienced,
hardest hitting wahoos
I know.
Each of you
were hand-picked for
your specific set of skills.
Hekapoo's basically
a one-woman army,
and she's also on fire.
-[rock guitar riff]
-Talon is... is really big,
and I think Hekapoo
has a crush on him,
but it's probably
just because of his body.
Wait. What?
[Marco]
And then Jorby and Kelly...
Ahhh!
...they're, um, well...
Kelly's got a lot of swords!
Anyway, I feel proud to call
you my "Marc-nificent Seven."
[Jorby speaking
gibberish]
Oh, yeah, good point.
You're right, Jorby.
Yeah, Jorby says, uh,
your math is off.
Yeah, there's only, uh...
There's only four of us
here plus you.
That's five.
Two short of a seven.
He forgot about me!
-Uh...
-Who's that?
No, I-- I didn't
forget about you.
I-- You're late.
And what is that thing
on your head?
Oh, that's just
my battle axe.
I'm basically
like a cyborg now.
I could change
into anything I want.
Mascara brush,
-little tiny Ponyhead.
-[tiny whinny]
-Chainsaw!
-[buzzing]
Okay, I get it, Ponyhead.
Talon!
What are you doing?
What am I doin'?
I'm handing out shades
for our group victory photo.
We're not doing
a group photo.
Dude, every group
I've ever run with
-takes a cool
sunglasses group shot.
-[rock guitar riff]
Are... Are those
Little League teams?
Little?! There's nothin'
little about them!
You don't know
what it's like to
be alone on the field,
your friends covered
in boo-boos and ouchies.
[Tom] Hey!
-[flames hissing]
-[organ music playing]
Listen to your commander.
Ha! See? I told you
there were seven of us.
Boom.
Eat that Kelly.
Earthturd!
Are you gonna tell us
the plan or what?!
Oh, yes.
The plan is simple.
We're gonna build...
The Doom Nut.
[blade rings]
Jorby and Kelly,
you're gonna make
a huge dugout circle.
Talon and Pony will
fill it with wood.
When Meteora steps inside,
Tom's gonna set
the wood on fire,
trapping her
in a flaming prison.
Ohh, "Doom Nut,"
because it looks
like a doughnut!
Earthturd,
that is very clever.
I am into this plan.
I'll open up the floor
to questions
if there's anything
you'd like to ask me
about the plan
of this thing in my hand
that I'm holding.
Oh. Well, I'll just
take the bait here.
Where did you get
that sword, Marco?
Oh! This old thing?
Funny you should ask.
This is El Choppo.
I got this sword from the mists
of the Never Zone
when I was
in my early 30s,
and it's still even
got some dried blood on it.
Any other questions?
Yes, Kelly?
Wait, how are
we going to convince her
to step into what
is an obvious trap?
Ya know, I'm no longer
into this plan.
Simple, Kelly,
we use the best bait.
-Me.
-Aah!
-Dude.
-Sorry.
-[splashing]
-Find Mom. Find Mom.
Find Mom. Find Mom.
Find Mom.
[jellyfish moaning]
Whoa!
-[phone buzzing]
-Aah!
[Star, on recording]
You are Star Butterfly.
You must find your mom
and bring her home.
Right! Find... Mom!
[jellyfish moaning]
[Kelly, imitating
back-up warning]
Beep! Beep! Beep!
Beep! Beep!
Click! Click!
[grunting]
[rock guitar riff]
Whoo! I'm beat!
[chuckles]
[gulping]
Dude!
Save some for me.
[mouth full]
Oh, my bad.
Well, here you go.
Ehh...
Marco, you know, I--
I kind of treated you
bad sometimes.
like that Ping-Pong game,
or the...
the Blood Moon Ball,
those Mackie Hand tickets,
Naysaya...
I-- I get it, Tom.
The monster arm.
-That wasn't you.
-It wasn't?
Anyway.
Look, the point is,
I actually think
you're a great dude.
Whatever happens today,
we'll make it through.
Thanks, Tom.
I'm really glad you're here.
[calling out]
Mom?!
Find Mom, find Mom, find Mom.
-Find... mmm... mmm... mmm...
-[popping sounds]
Marshmallow?
[popping sounds]
Find marshmallow!
[unicorn whickers]
-What ya drinkin'?
-[startled whinny]
It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt ya.
[whispering]
Please don't go.
Huh?
[gasps] Find Mom!
Find Mom, find Mom, find Mom.
Find Mom, find Mom,
find Mom, find...
[inspiring music playing]
[rock guitar riff]
Whoo!
Whoo-whoo!
[tires squeal]
Um, I cannot see!
Can everyone else see,
'cause I cannot!
All right,
Marc-nificent Seven,
it's go-time.
[tires squealing]
Who... Who was that?
That was--
That was Marco.
He's gonna look great
in that photo.
Find Mom, find Mom,
find Mom, find Mom, find Mom,
find Mom.
Find Mo--
Mom!
-Hello there.
-Mmm!
Mommy!
Mom, you might not
remember who you are
or who I am,
but I'm here
to take you home.
What's "home"?
[uneasy laugh]
-Okay, you are Moon--
-[phone buzzes]
[recording]
You are Star Butterfly.
I am Star Butterfly.
Aah! No, no, no, no!
Shut up, me!
You are Moon Butterfly.
Look. This is you.
And this is your husband.
I am your daughter.
We are your family.
Do you remember?
[buzzing]
You are Star Butterfly.
I am Star Butterfly.
-Ugh!
-[splash]
You are comin' with me!
Where are we going?
We are going to...
I have no idea.
Woe is me!
A rebel princess
in distress named Turdina!
Nachos, my precious steed,
what will I do?
-[loud footsteps]
-[crows cawing]
All right, Nachos,
stick to the plan.
[footsteps echoing]
Are you okay?
Uh, sorry.
Looking for a different monster.
I just thought
you needed help.
Yeah. Actually, hey,
we could really use your help!
Huh. Well, now it just
kind of feels weird.
I don't know.
Good luck finding your monst--
[loud zapping]
[sing-song]
I'm right here!
Huh? [gasps]
-[Nachos sputtering]
-Really?!
[roars]
Whoa-ho!
[screaming]
[Marco] Whoa!
Jorby!
Go! Go go go go go!
-[roars]
-Now, Tom!
Huh?
Ohh!
Hey, Metenormous!
Looks like you're trapped!
I think... I think we did it!
Whaa!
Hey,
what's the plan now?
Run.
[jellyfish moaning]
[splashing]
Whatcha doin' over there?
I don't know,
feels good though.
I want to feel good, too.
Let me try.
What the...
What are these symbols?
[phones buzzing]
[overlapping recordings]
You are Star Butterfly.
You must find your mom
and bring her home.
You are Star Butterfly.
You must find your mom
and bring here home.
I'm Star Butterfly!
Oh, no!
It's happening again!
Mom! Mom, Mom, get up!
Huh?
We have to go right now.
[Queen Moon]
Ooh! What is that?
It's amazing!
Whoa... it is amazing!
Turdina?!
I know we've had
our issues,
but it's nothing
we can't talk about!
[panting]
Come on, Star! Hurry up!
Whaa!
[Hekapoo, straining] Marco!
Dude, get up.
[all groaning]
[grunts]
I don't know
how much more
we can take of this.
[Meteora/Heinous] Hey!
You might've put out
someone's eye!
[swords clanging]
[growls]
Talon, launch me!
You got it.
Haaaa! Aah!
I don't hear nothin'.
She's dead, right?
I won?
Where's Star?
[Queen Moon laughing]
[Star]
Oooh! ♪ La la la ♪
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Ohh,
there goes a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining sta-a-r ♪