♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
There. What do you think?
I love it!
Me next, me next, me next!
And make me look
exactly like Star.
And I mean exactly.
Fun sleepover,
huh, guys?
Best sleepover ever!!
And it's about to get
a lot better.
( ticking, alarm rings )
I never made
brownies before.
I used real
magic sprinkles.
ALL: Mmm!
So good, right?
Yes!
Oh, so good.
( jazzy piano music playing )
Oh, hey, girls.
I was just
practicing piano.
It's jazz.
Hi, Marco.
Oh, I didn't know
you played, Marco. Yeah!
Oh, hey, Jackie.
Didn't see you there.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Why don't you come and try
one of my brownies?
Brownies? These days,
I'm sticking with
the protein shakes.
It's what keeps
these bad boys happy.
Oh, oh, uh-huh.
You got it bad.
Bad? No.
( nervous laughter )
( stammering )
It's game time, Marco.
And since you're so good
at playing the field,
I got a game that
would be perfect for you.
ALL: Wow!
It's a box.
It's called
Truth Or Punishment.
It's all about
telling your friends
your deepest,
darkest secrets.
And I'm out.
Give me one second.
Marco!
Marco, Marco, Marco, Marco.
Why don't you wanna play?
I just think maybe
some things are better
kept secrets.
What are you
talking about?
Oh, Marco,
come play with us.
Yeah, Marco.
Come share a secret.
- He's coming.
- I hate you.
Okay, you're supposed
to ask three questions,
each one harder
than the last,
and all we do
is answer them. So...
Deceit and fables,
lies and fiction,
even with
complete conviction.
If truth is absent
from these events,
all will face
the punishments.
- What does that mean?
- It means if you lie to him,
something bad'll
happen.
Pledge an oath of truth.
- Pinky swear to me.
- Okay.
I promise to tell
the truth.
- The truth.
The truth.
It's time for
Truth Or Punishment.
Pony, this is
already awesome.
The first question:
Uh, Pony?
Oh, girl, maybe the first one
is very easy.
The next one's probably
something interesting,
like have you ever
killed a man.
Mm, actually,
that's still easy.
Pony Head,
favorite color?
- Pony Head color. Done.
- What?
It's a very popular
color on Mewni.
Uh, Star, what's
your favorite color?
Uh, I have to go
with yellow.
( gasps )
Me, too.
No way!
( both giggling )
- Jackie?
- Neon green.
How about you?
Well, I like red.
Blood red?
Uh... no. Just like,
putty red.
Well, I like black.
I can see that.
Oh, black is
my second favorite.
Black is pretty cool.
Someone is lying.
( all laughing )
One of us, speak up.
Okay.
I love pink.
It's my favorite.
- Truth.
- ALL: Pink?!
I just hate contributing
to gender stereotypes.
Janna likes pink
and fights the patriarchy.
That was awesome!
Yeah. It's, like,
we're inside the game.
Second question.
Easy. Everybody
loved my brownies.
Okay, yeah, they were
very watchamacallit,
- very good, right, guys?
- Yeah, they were great.
Yep. Good brownies, Star.
Actually, I didn't have
a brownie,
so I guess
I missed out.
Oh, that's too bad, Marco,
because they were really good.
Jackie?
Yeah. Delicious.
- What?!
- What's happening to us?
( whinnies )
Someone is lying.
And this is what lies
look like on the inside.
( all screaming )
Wait. Who didn't
like my brownies?
I just... ha ha... uh...
I told you, I didn't even
have a brownie.
Somebody tell the truth.
Quick.
Okay. Fine.
Sorry, Star, I lied.
Those were, like,
the worst brownies ever.
- Huh?
- Poor Star.
Okay, I lied, too.
Those brownies
tasted like dirt.
Okay, if I had a stomach,
I would be very sick
inside of the stomach, okay?
Well, I loved
her brownies.
Okay, okay, I lied.
The brownies
were horrible.
Okay, I don't wanna
play this game anymore.
Yeah. I'm sorry I brought
this stupid game now.
Come on, let's go
to the Bounce Lounge.
- Good idea.
- Let's get outta here.
Nobody leaves
until you answer
the final question.
Okay, let's do
something else.
Okay, guys, we can do this.
Let's just answer
and end this.
Go ahead, game.
We're ready.
Who do you have
a crush on?
Okay, this really cute guy
from skate camp last summer.
He's really nice.
ALL: Aww!
See? That was easy.
Okay, now you go, Marco.
No, thanks.
I, uh, I'm good.
It's Star's turn,
I'm sure.
I say who goes next,
and I say
Star goes next.
Oscar Greeson.
Everybody knows that.
Good choice.
Star Fan 13,
your crush?
Star Butterfly,
of course.
Pony Head?
If we're really
being honest here,
and we're gonna be vulnerable,
I guess I just have to
admit it and say,
it's me.
I love myself.
Go, Pony.
Well, I think we all know
who I have a crush on.
- Don't we, Marco?
- Uh...
Eighteenth-century
poet John Keats.
Ha ha.
Okay, Marco Diaz.
Your crush.
Oh, Marco, you don't
have to...
No. It's... it's fine.
Ugh. Okay.
My crush...
my crush is on Jackie.
- Jackie Lynn Thomas.
- What?
Somebody lied
big time!
Who lied?!
Janna, was it you again?
No. It is John Keats.
Mine is the cute guy
from skate camp.
Ha ha. I love Star.
And I love Oscar Greeson.
Marco!
I told you, I have
a crush on Jackie.
At least,
I think I do.
What does that really mean?
I put her on
this sort of pedestal.
So do I like the image
of her
or who she really is?
I mean, I like her enough
to know that she deserves
someone who wants to get to know
her, which is definitely me.
Wow!
I always
get to the truth,
but that...
kudos, really.
But you weren't the one
who lied!!
( evil laughter )
Don't worry, guys.
I got this.
Star!
Marco!
Jump!
( evil laughter )
Stop it! What did we do
to deserve this?
Lies are a plague.
- A virus.
- A weed.
- And to stop a weed...
- You must kill the root.
But it's not
really lying.
Huh?
Sometimes, you don't know
what you think.
Your head
and your heart disagree.
You think you know
how you feel about something,
but then it changes.
Pony, ask me
my favorite color.
You already said it.
It's yellow.
- Ask me again.
- What's your favorite color?
Right now? Blue.
Wait! Stop it!
- You can't change...
- Your mind.
Jackie, who do you
have a crush on?
Uh... I don't...
I don't know anymore.
No!
( shrieking )
You think that everything
is black and white,
and you can't.
Stop!
It's a bunch of
different colors
A rainbow of feelings
that's always changing.
STAR: Thanks for coming
to my sleepover.
Thanks, Star.
- Crazy night, huh?
- Yeah. Crazy.
See ya at school,
Marco.
Bye, ladies.
Uh, hey.
What say we get
our Sunday morning
breakfast burritos?
Nah. Not today, Star.
I'm gonna go catch up
on some Z's.
My room's that way.
( giggles )
Marco?
Marco Diaz!
Truth. Star Butterfly
has a crush on...
Thanks for meeting us
here today, Rasticore.
We have a problem with
some rogue princesses,
which I hope
you can help us with.
( growling )
Destroy the blonde one,
but bring the dark-haired
one to me.
( stammering )
Gimme a break.
- Do you--
- Working on it.
Oh, Miss Heinous,
I cannot wait to recapture
our former glory.
It has been a long time
since I last ate.
- ( stomach rumbling )
- Indeed.
Here. Take this.
The last of our savings.
Oh, you're so generous,
Miss Heinous.
Finally, some little food
for my mouth.
It's not for food,
you fool.
It's for my hair.
Miss Fairol's number 112.
Golden brown.
And bring back a receipt!
( laughing )
"Billie's Ballet Shoe
Emporium.
Our discounts are
on pointe"?
Marco, why do you
even have this?
For your information,
they are incredibly
comfortable to wear
around the house.
What are you guys doing
looking through my wallet
anyway?
Can't a guy get
any privacy?
- Nope.
- Hey, what's with
this weird card?
It's all shaky.
Let me see that.
Hey, this is the Quest Buy
gift card I got for you, Marco.
I can't believe
you haven't used it yet.
I got this for our six-month
friendship-aversary
so you could get yourself
something special.
If you don't use it,
it'll expire.
Look, Star, it's not that
I don't appreciate it, okay?
It's just that the last time
I went to Quest Buy,
I almost got killed.
But, Marco,
it expires tonight.
Come on!
( whimpers )
( sighs )
Fine. Let's go.
Yay. Perfect!
- Back in a bit, Janna.
- Laters.
All right, let's get you
the perfect gift!
Oh, no.
See anything you like?
Look. There's
a Skullaroid camera.
Takes pictures
specifically of ghosts.
Uh, I don't think so.
Oh, how about some spooky
haunted garden gnomes?
Look at all this stuff.
This is exactly why
I do not like shopping.
I can never
make up my mind.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy there,
Mr. Picky Pants.
Luckily, we got
until midnight.
Tell me where Princess Star
and Princess Marco are located.
Uh, loud.
They went to Quest Buy.
The one near
the galactic vortex,
or the one with
the big parking lot?
( growling )
Never mind.
I found them.
Come on.
Why did you even ask
if you already knew?
Ooh, that is getting
a little too close for comfort.
Marco, I don't mean
to rush you,
but it's been hours.
If you don't find
something soon,
the card will expire
and go to waste.
You know it's hard for me
to shop in public.
Plus I'm just not that into
Quest Buy gear.
Ugh, Marco!
They have literally
everything in the universe here.
There has to be something
you want.
Please!!
Hurry up!!
If you're going
to rush me,
then I'll just buy
some piece of junk now,
and come back to exchange
it later, okay?
What the heck?!
( laughing )
Oh, yeah. That.
I may have forgotten
to mention that this is
a "friends to the end"
gift card.
You have to truly, deeply
want the item you spend it on,
or else it won't work.
Star, why would you give me
a card like that?
Because I wanted to get you
something you really liked.
Okay. Fine.
Just, uh, nothing
in this section.
Good, 'cause I don't
like you either.
I see why
you're on sale.
All right, all right.
- Ugh!
- How about this?
No, no. Too gaudy.
How about one of these?
Another keychain?
I'll pass.
How about one of these?
Uh, maybe. Nah.
How about this?
Star, you know the neck
is gonna stretch out on that.
Ow! All right, all right!
I'm sorry, but I really
can't decide under
this kind of pressure.
Maybe we can get
an extension on the card.
Well, we can try.
Excuse me.
I have a question.
- Not my department.
- But you're customer service.
Oh, yeah.
We really need
to ditch that sign.
Fine. How can I help you?
Is there any way we can
extend the expiration date
on this card?
- Shouldn't be a problem.
- ( beeps )
Uh, you know what?
No. This is a "friends
to the end" gift card.
It's not only impervious
to change,
- but when it expires,
so do you.
- What?!
Like, we die?
Geez. Everyone's gotta die
some time.
This just guarantees
that you'll die sooner.
It's all here in
the contract your friend signed.
If you don't use it
by midnight, zap, ha ha.
Both of you get blasted
into oblivion.
Zap?!
Tell me again, Star.
Why did you get me
a card like this?
I didn't know.
I never read the fine print.
Always read
the fine print, Star.
I mean, look at
this contract.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
Nope. Sorry, dude.
Um, dudes.
Seeing as there's
only a few hours left,
you better go find
something you really like.
( both screaming )
Uh, yes, before you ask,
this is not my...
- Oh, no. Ten minutes
to midnight.
- We're toast.
Activating expiration mode.
Shooting star explosion!
Enough nonsense.
Choose your gift.
Your life
depends on it.
Commencing countdown
to your expiration date.
You have ten minutes.
- See anything
you like, Marco?
- No.
Nine minutes
until expiration.
- What about
gourmet hair gel?
- No
8.5 minutes until
expiration.
Who designed this card?!
Why do you have
to be so picky?
I'm not picky.
I'm just...
highly selective.
Wait, Star.
Hold on.
The ultimate in privacy.
It's even my favorite color.
And a thumbprint
privacy setting.
( laughs )
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's yours, Marco.
Get it, get it,
get it out.
( straining )
It's stuck.
- Sorry, sir.
That's a display model.
- ( screaming )
We gotta get
the Quest Buy
sloth employee to help us.
( laughing )
Stand back.
My friend Marco needs
one of your privacy wallets.
Uh, well, I am on my break,
but, sure, let me check.
Can you see if
they have it in plum?
Uh, sorry. Looks like
we're out of stock.
No. It can't be.
One minute
to expiration.
This is all my fault.
I should've let you know
there was an expiration date.
And I wasn't being lazy
when I bought that thing,
I promise.
I genuinely thought you would
love to pick out
what you wanted.
Sorry. Did you mean
jeans pig unwanted?
I know a lot of this
wouldn't have happened
if I was easier
to shop for.
Okay, I will search for
cheesier mop store.
Let's hug,
so when they find
our charred skeletons,
they'll know
we were friends.
Sorry. There was zero results
for snow made worm pants.
Wait! I know what I want!
Hey, there's only one thing
in this whole stinkin' store
that I could ever want.
Star's my best friend,
and friendship is the greatest
gift I could ever receive.
You need to pick something
you can purchase from the store.
Well, it was
worth a shot.
- It was sweet, Marco.
- Preparing to honor
expiration.
Good-bye, Marco.
Good-bye, Star.
( angry muttering )
Where are the stairs
in this place?
Princesses, my name is
Rasticore Chaosus Disastorvayne.
Miss Heinous sent me.
Invalid entry.
Expiration imminent.
Hold it. We do have
one more privacy wallet
in stock.
- ( both exclaim )
- Only, sorry.
We don't have it in plum.
Just, we have it in, um,
Prussian blue.
( sobbing )
Oh, it's perfect.
Prussian blue
is my favorite color.
Even more than plum.
Sheesh. So dramatic.
Good doing business
with you, sir.
Contract obligation
fulfilled.
( beeps )
( explosion )
Well, that completes
your transaction.
Have a good day, sir.
We got you
the perfect friendship gift!
What is with this thing?
How the heck are you
even supposed to open this?
Let me see that.
Nice try, ladies.
Its thumbprint lock
will allow no man or
magical creature to ever--
Got it.
Janna, get out of town!
- How did you do that, Janna?
- I've got Marco's thumbprint.
In fact, I've got all of your
sensitive information, Marco.
Get outta town!!
Delivery from
Quest Buy, milady.
But I wouldn't open it.
You're not going to like it.
Oh, well, then there are
two things in this room
I don't like.
Rasticore!
I'll get you,
Princess Marco.
I'm sorry. What's the other
thing you don't like?
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪