♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( sighs )
Whoa!
Oh, hey, guys.
We're gonna
miss you, dude.
Come on, Marco,
can't you stay
a little longer?
Love to,
but Earth's calling.
All right then,
see ya on
the flip, Marco.
Whoa!!
Uh, well, I guess
this is good-bye.
And what a pleasure
it's been.
This place won't be
the same without you, my lad.
But before you go,
there's something
I want to give you
for all you've done
for our kingdom.
Squire!
Ahem.
Ta-da!
Whoa! Cool.
Ha ha, you're like
a real live knight now.
Look at you, my boy.
In fact, if you ever
want to be a knight one day,
give me a call.
Wow, thanks,
River.
Take care of yourself
back on Earth.
Thanks.
I guess this is it.
Well, bye.
Wait, Marco.
I need a longer
good-bye than that.
Me, too.
Well, bye.
Again.
Bye.
What... oh, you're
going to the portal.
That's this way.
- Uh...
- Oh...
( nervous chuckling )
Well, bye.
Bye.
- Okay, Marco.
- Right.
Oh, and can you let me know
if you see my hoodie anywhere?
I told you
I haven't seen it,
but if I find it,
I will send it to you.
Okay, cool.
Thanks. Okay.
Bye.
I'm... going
to my room.
But sweetie pie,
your room's this way.
Uh, yeah, it's wherever
I want it to be, Dad.
Sparkle glitter
bomb expand.
( sighs )
( sniffs deeply )
( coughs )
Gross, Marco.
Smells like that time
we went on that dimensional
school field trip!
( sniffs )
Ugh. Gonna vomit.
And that smells like the one
time we got Chinese food
after the double feature
karate movie!
( coughs, gags )
And that smells like the time
we tried to save
the bounce lounge.
- Hey, girl!
- Pony Head!
I heard what went down
in your kingdom,
and so I rushed
right over as soon
as my hair was done.
You know I need
to do that. Wait.
Are you hiding
something from me?
No. This is me.
Totes normal.
You better not be
keeping secrets from me.
Okay, fine.
It's Marco's hoodie, okay?
Are you happy now?
Oooh!!
Darn it, that thing
smells like feet.
I know, but it smells
like Marco.
I know I should return it,
but I really miss him,
and it's the only thing...
What the...
hey, what are you doing?
I'm washing
this stinky thing.
No!
Hey, girl, you need
to get a grip.
No.
Where are you going?
To get that hoodie.
Yes? Ah,
Princess Butterfly.
Hi, Lavabo.
I must apologize
for your blue dress.
It will not be ready
till Tuesday.
I don't care.
I'm looking for
a red hoodie.
A hoodie?
Date and time
you dropped it off.
Just now,
but it was a total accident.
It's perfectly clean.
I just need it back
before it gets washed.
A clean hoodie?
Not to worry.
You need
the pick-up window.
Welcome to
How may I be
of assistance?
Red hoodie.
- Size?
- Medium maybe.
Chain mail
or metal plate?
Cotton.
It's a hoodie.
- Thread count?
- I don't know.
I don't count.
There it is,
right behind you.
Double stitch
or single?
It's right behind you.
That should be
enough information.
I'll file this and get
back to you within 48 hours.
What?!
( frustrated groan )
This is all your fault.
You're gonna thank
me later,
once you come
to your senses.
I am to my senses.
Good news. I have
located your hoodie.
Unfortunately, it's filthy,
and must be washed immediately.
What? No, no, no, no.
I told you, it doesn't
need to be washed.
Don't bother yourself.
I'm sorry, princess,
but I must bother myself.
It is my duty.
I will never forget
the moment, as a young boy,
and I saw my papi
meticulously making sure
the royals' linen stayed
pure, noble, clean,
- and fresh!
- Uh...
And I swore at that very day
that I would never let
a garment go unwashed,
and I have kept that promise
for over 40 years.
Therefore, I will make it
my utmost priority
that this extremely soiled
hoodie be washed!
Okay, well, that
is unfortunate,
but now, let me
tell you about
this club I went to.
Glitter whale
battering ram!
Girl, what are
you doing?
Trying to get
my hoodie back
before Lavabo washes it.
Are you for real
right now?
Piled river panda explosion!
Through muddled scent
and stained shirt piles,
the dirt of yesterday shall not
be the enemy of tomorrow.
By the order of the Wash,
this is my promise
to my true kingdom.
Seriously?
You know,
I'm surprised to say it,
- but personally,
I really do admire this.
- Seriously?
Star, just let this old dad
do his job.
Yes, I must
follow my duty.
Order and rules are
always to be followed,
without fail.
Okay, calm down though.
Everyone must always
follow the rules
all the time,
always, forever.
What? Okay, did you just
tell my friend what to
do forever?
We are getting back
your weird red stink hoodie.
- We're getting it.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Two seconds ago,
you were like--
- I'm aware of my actions,
and I'm so sorry for
not always having your back,
and I hope we can move on
and grow as the beautiful
princesses we are.
I must uphold my oath.
No, no, no.
He can't wash the hoodie!
Get back here, Lavabo.
- Oh!
- Can't see anything!
I know.
Let's split up.
MARCO:  Good-bye
forever, Star.
No, no, no, no.
No! Don't go!
I won't let you go.
Ay!
Lavabo!
No. Give me
that hoodie!
Your Highness, I can't
stress enough how badly
I am not
going to do that.
Huppa!
Kitten Pegasus
battle barrel!
Stop! You're not
washing that hoodie!
Just give up.
As long as this body of mine
is capable of moving,
I shall always move
towards my duty.
Shimmer soap tentacle wave!
You're not moving towards
anything anymore.
This is
your last chance.
My entire life I have
dedicated to my knight's oath.
This is something that
cannot be bent or broken.
My brothers and sisters
taught me that.
I cherish the moments
we had together,
and hold onto them
every day.
It has made me who I am,
and soon, I shall
see them again.
Wait, what?
You thought I was
gonna kill you over a hoodie?
Is that not what is
going on here?
No. I was gonna maybe
turn you into a duck,
or, like, boop you
on the nose real hard.
But your eyes,
they had the blood lust.
That's just 'cause...
Pony Head was right.
I really am messed up
about Marco.
I mean, I spent all day
chasing down a knight
who was just doing
his weird job.
All because I thought that
if I didn't have Marco's hoodie,
I wouldn't have
any piece of him left,
which just isn't true.
I'll always have Marco.
We'll always be friends.
- ( water splashes )
- Whoa, what are you doing?
- ( sighs )
- Do not worry.
I put it on
a gentle cycle.
( sniffs deeply )
Miladies, the garment
is clean,
and up to the standards
of the Knights of the Wash.
( sniffs ) Oh, wow.
Now that is delightful.
Star, you should...
Awww...
Aw, don't be pouty.
Eh.
Come over here.
Milady, please.
( sniffs )
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It still stinks
like Marco!
What?!
No, it does not.
I just sniffed it.
Tell her it doesn't.
The hoodie is,
in fact, clean.
What you are experiencing
is the memory of a scent.
You don't need to hold on to
stinky hoodies any more,
you know why?
'Cause, like,
what we have learned
is that
Earth Turd's scent
is like in your heart
or whatever.
Thanks, Pony Head.
( laughs )
You got it, girl.
( sighs loudly )
( doorbell rings )
Hello?
( meows )
( gasps )
All right!
My hoodie!
( sniffs )
Hey, kinda smells
like Star.
( River laughing )
And then,
Lekmet said,
( guttural bleating )
( laughter )
Hors d'oeuvres,
Your Highness?
Uh, why not?
It's not exactly
princess food,
but it was Lekmet's
favorite meal.
That's how humble
that guy was.
To Lekmet!
Our selfless comrade,
who always gave to others
before ever taking
for himself.
( bleating )
( all bleating )
I told him that would
get him killed one day.
Give the can to
your father, love.
He's got teeth
like a tiger fish.
Glossaryck! Glossaryck,
wait. Glossaryck!
Oh, uh...
Hey, Star's upside down
in the punch bowl.
Oh, not again.
( bubbling )
Star!
Glossaryck!
Mom, did you see him?
He was in the bowl,
in that bowl.
You all saw him,
right?
Star, I know this is
an emotional day,
but this is Lekmet's
funeral, not Glossaryck's.
Mom, I saw
Glossaryck.
Star, we all
see Glossaryck...
here, and here.
And in
that punch bowl.
All bug-eyed
and big-mouthed.
Classic Glossaryck.
I bet he came
for the memorial.
Look, I get it, Star.
Funerals are unsettling.
Strange food,
Lekmet's friends.
Music.
It's all different,
and maybe a little scary.
But don't turn this
into a ghost story.
What? Who said anything
about a ghost?
I saw Glossaryck, Mom.
You didn't see Glossaryck,
and you didn't
see his ghost.
Okay, stop saying ghost.
It's weird.
Glossaryck is
gone now.
You just have
to let him go.
( sighs )
You know, when I was
a little girl,
and there was something
I couldn't let go,
my mother taught me
to say,
"Balloobalee
balloobalo,
I let you go,
I let you go!"
And I always
felt better afterwards.
Give it a try, dear.
What?
( screams )
( stammering )
Glossaryck!
Balloobalee, balloobalo,
I let you go, I let you go!
I let you go!!
Why didn't that work?
( ringing )
- ( chewing loudly )
- Janna!
( Star speaking
indistinctly )
You're seeing dead people?
That's the coolest thing
I've heard all summer.
No, Janna,
weren't you listening?
Not people.
Glossaryck.
I am being haunted
by Glossaryck's ghost.
I did my mom's balloobalee
balloobalo, but it didn't work!
- Baba what?
- Janna, I need your weird,
dark-sided expertise,
or I'm telling you,
there are gonna be
two ghosts up in here!
Okay, well...
- you're definitely
being haunted.
-  No!
Yeah.
If you're the only one
who sees him,
it might mean he has some
unfinished business with you.
Okay, can you stop eating
for one second?
Also, what
unfinished business?
- ( Janna chewing )
- Janna!
Sorry, it was getting cold.
Maybe there's an anchor
near you.
Something he left
in this world,
keeping his ghost
bound to it.
Are any of his
belongings around?
No. Glossaryck didn't
own anything.
The only thing that sort of
belonged to him was...
( gasps )
JANA:  Yo, Star,
are you dead?
It's the book.
I kept the remains
of the spell book
they found in
the monster temple.
Why would you keep that?
Jana, you're gonna get on
my case for keeping weird stuff?
Touché. It says here you gotta
let that stuff go,
and by letting go,
I mean bury it.
Bury bury?
Yeah, and deep.
Real deep.
Okay, okay, calm down.
I'm doing it.
And buried buried.
Good-bye, Glossaryck.
Whew!
No Glossaryck.
Oh, no Glossaryck.
( thudding noise )
What?!
Oh, Janna, you did not say
this would happen.
Oh, gross.
( yells )
( shuddering )
What?
Glossaryck!
Why does he have to have
so many fingers?
Leave me alone!
Janna, Janna, Janna, Janna.
- Yo, Star.
- Janna!
( Star babbling
indistinctly )
You buried it
in a pet cemetery?
Well, he's small.
Did you want him
to haunt you more?
It was better than
flushing him down the toilet.
That's not how
it works, Star.
Yeah, I can see that now, Janna.
He's still here.
Now he's, like,
here here.
Wait, you're seeing him
in the physical world?
Oh, that's not good.
You need to go bury
the pieces in a sacred place.
Somewhere that would have
significance to him.
Then you'll stop
seeing him.
And it looks like
you gotta do it right now,
or else, he'll
haunt you for eternity.
I think I have
the perfect place.
Okay, thanks so much, Janna.
Bye-ee!
- Ugh, loud.
- MARCO: Who was that?
No one. Shut up.
Why do we even
hang out with Janna?
Why, Glossaryck, why
are you still here?
I gave you
what you wanted.
What else do you want
from me?
( frustrated groan )
You are always
so frustrating,
and confusing,
and Glossaryck!
Okay, look, I know I was
a jerk to you sometimes,
okay, but you're being
an even bigger jerk now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Is that what you want?
I thought you were gone,
but no.
No, no, no.
Now you're just
spooky, bug-eyed reflections.
And a cloud?
Who is a cloud?
Under weird things
in my room.
I just don't get it.
I thought you didn't even
want to be around me.
You know, Glossaryck,
I have so much to do
to fix this kingdom,
and it would be
a lot more helpful
if you were really here
instead of just haunting me,
like some kind of
weird reflection creep!
( sighs )
You know, Glossaryck,
you never made it easy
learning from you.
Maybe that was the point.
You did always trust me to
figure things out on my own.
And you were still always
there for me,
and no one else was really
always there for me.
Teacher...friend...
weird book guy.
Whatever you were, you were
super important to me.
Thank you, Glossaryck.
Thank you
for everything.
I hope you find
your big bowl of pudding.
Balloobalee, balloobalo.
I let you go,
I let you go.
( loud rumbling )
Oh, no.
( gasping )
Do you
hear something?
Mom, Dad!
Star, I'm not going
to tell you again.
Stop kicking doors.
Mom, oh, my goodness.
You won't believe it.
I was in the sanctuary,
and I was saying good-bye,
and I really said good-bye,
and then, all this magic
shot out of the well--
Slow down, slow down.
What in the world
are you talking about?
I did what you said.
I did it,
I let him go.
I did your balloobalee,
but...he came back.
Glob gor!
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪