♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Stumps here. Get
your fresh stumps here.
Daddy, can we go sing
some Stump carols?
Not until we get you
some cocoa first.
[laughter]
Good evening, everyone.
Please gather round.
Aaah!
Today we pay thanks
to the roots of our kingdom!
To the Stump!
[all] To the Stump!
Yes! To the Stump!
Whoo hoo!
Tell us the story
of Stump Day, Uncle River.
Ha ha ha ha!
You don't tell me
what to do.
Now, let me tell you
the story
of the first Stump Day.
Centuries ago,
a small band of explorers
crashed their ships
on Mewni.
After weeks of traveling,
they began to get on
each other's nerves.
Aah! Oh, no.
They planned to go
their separate ways,
but suddenly,
a blizzard struck.
Blizzard!
And the crew was forced
to survive by huddling together
around a giant tree stump
to keep warm and share supplies.
They forged
a lasting bond that day,
and decided not to
split up after all.
To commemorate the occasion,
they carved their initials
on the back of the stump,
and the kingdom of Mewni
was born!
That is why, each year,
we come together
and honor the Stump
through our friendships
for a full 24 hours.
Or else.
- Or else?
- Sh!
Thank you, everyone,
for making this
- a Stump Day to remember!
- [people cheering]
Do you think the Stump
will visit me tonight?
Come on. Only babies
believe in the Stump.
Oh, don't listen to her.
I know the Stump is real,
and if you've been good,
the Stump will
never visit.
Happy Stump Day,
Mom and Dad.
Happy Stump Day, Marco.
Happy Stump Day,
everyone.
You're really
into this, huh?
Oh, you have no idea.
This is my favorite holiday.
It is so special.
[laughs] More special
than you think.
♪ All hail the Stump,
for it is great and kind ♪
♪ Don't anger the Stump,
or it will be unkind ♪
♪ The Stump is our savior,
we praise it on this day ♪
♪ Keep the Stump in your heart,
and let it lead the way ♪
Ah! The perfect
Stump Day.
[knocking on door]
[wind howling,
bells jingling]
The Stump!
[Marco] Star?
Are you decent?
Marco! Oh! Quit creeping
around, you creep.
It's Stump Day.
Sorry, sorry.
Can you come downstairs
for a second?
One of the windows
is stuck,
and I need your magic
to fix it.
Sure. I can...
I can do that.
It is Stump Day,
after all.
Stump-tacular.
A good try, Marco.
It's right over here.
Uh, Marco,
I can't see anything.
[all] Surprise!
[laughs]
Your birthday always falls
on Stump Day,
so we decided...
surprise  quinceañera!
Hit it!
♪ Cumpleaños feliz ♪
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no!
[cheering]
Oh, no, oh, no!
[screams]
Star, what's wrong?
We never celebrate my birthday
on my actual birthday, Marco,
because it's Stump Day.
¿Lo que es
un día de tocón?
Es un día
muy importante.
But it's your birthday, too.
Isn't that pretty important?
Not as important
as the Stump.
Today is the Stump's day.
Come on, Star.
Don't tell me you
still believe in the Stump.
Yeah, that's
a baby story.
Like, for babies.
Oh, I think
it's cute.
Get off me,
non-believer.
O, great Stump,
I beg your forgiveness,
for they do not know
the ways of the Stump,
and they are
but foolish teenagers.
Wait, so the Stump
is real?
[all] No!
It's just
a manipulative
fairy tale...
Parents tell their kids...
So that they're
less annoying during
the holidays.
Okay, everyone,
thank you so much
for this magnificent party.
I am overwhelmed with joy.
Really. But unfortunately,
I cannot celebrate
my birthday today.
As the song goes,
♪ We honor the Stump
each year ♪
♪ To this we have sworn ♪
♪ If we anger the Stump ♪
♪ We'll wish
we were never born ♪
[Star yells]
That's my girl.
[straining]
Come on, guys,
help me honor the Stump.
Um, Star.
What gives?
It took me a long time
to set up these decorations
and bake your favorite
flavor of cake.
Rainbow.
I even imported
a mariachi band
all the way from Earth
just so you could have
a birthday.
♪ Cumpleaños feliz ♪
- Guys, not now.
- [music stops]
Look, Star, I think
I know what this is
really about.
You're afraid of
getting older.
It's cool.
We've all been there.
What? No, this isn't
like that at all.
Yeah, Marco,
you know what?
Maybe this is
really about you,
and how you have to control
every situation like a maniac.
Okay? I mean, you
didn't even ask Star
if she wanted
a birthday party. That's rude.
Because that would've
ruined the surprise. Duh!
I told you this was
a bad idea, dude,
but you didn't
wanna listen.
Well, at least I wanted
to throw Star a party.
You didn't plan anything,
and you're supposed
to be her boyfriend.
[both] Oh!
Ohhhh!
What?
Marco, take it back.
You heard me, Lucitor.
Uh, I didn't plan anything,
because unlike you,
I actually thought about
what Star would want.
Did you?
Because this morning,
it kinda seemed like
you forgot.
[evil laugh]
That's it.
I'm gonna pound you
into next Stump Day.
Es el diablo!
Boys, stop it.
- Say I'm
a good boyfriend.
- Never.
Wow. Happy birthday, Star.
It's the ultimate gift.
- Two boys are
fighting over you.
- Ugh!
All right,
dinner and a show.
How can you say that?
Marco almost got
burnt to a crisp.
Geez, Kelly,
chill out.
Are you just mad because
Marco's fighting Tom
over Star instead of you?
What? Why would
you say that?
Yeah, Kelly,
why would you say that?
Tad! Ugh!
You need to move out.
Guys, stop it.
Tom, I really don't care
if you forgot
it was my birthday.
- I didn't forget.
- Yes, he did.
You better
stop fighting!
I'm mad because
Star is mad.
Nobody's paying
attention to me.
Also, this party
has no hotties.
No!
[all arguing]
Oh, see what I mean?
We've angered the Stump,
and now it's
tearing us apart.
Girl, what is
wrong with you?
Have you gone insane?
It's freezing out there.
That's right, Pony.
Nice and freezing.
Just like the settlers
felt on their first winter.
Let the cold settle
deep into your bones.
We believe!
- No, we don't.
- Yes, we do.
Tell the Stump
you believe, Marco.
- Tell it!
- I believe...
we're all gonna
get hypothermia.
Look, isn't someone
gonna do something here?
[Janna] I'm on it.
Janna, no!
Ah, that's nice.
Get away from
my stump.
Oh, no!
[thunder crashing]
It's here.
Marco, if you wanna
give me a back rub, just ask.
[screaming]
- It's real.
- [all] We believe.
We believe!
Too late for that.
Kids, what is
all this racket?
[screaming]
- Oh, no.
- The Stump is real.
Wait. You didn't
believe in the Stump?
It's a stump!
I should've
believed you, Star.
I should've respected
the Stump.
I'm sorry for being
a bad boyfriend.
And I'm truly sorry
that I was so hard
on Earth Turd,
except not really,
'cause he's improved
as a person
with my thoughtful
criticism.
At least we all
get to die together.
That's kinda cool.
I'm sorry for
blaming you, Star.
I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
I love you, Dad.
I love all of you.
We're...
okay.
We did it.
The Stump spared us
'cause we all came together.
No, Marco, it left
'cause it's midnight,
and Stump Day is over.
- It was definitely
gonna kill us.
- Oh.
Thank you, great Stump,
wherever you are.
Um, why are you
thanking it?
You just said
it wanted to kill us.
Oh, I know.
But it also reminded us
just how much
we mean to each other,
even in the face
of certain death.
In a way, this has been
the best Stump Day of all,
though it will be
very expensive
to repair the damage
to the castle.
And we'll have to have an extra
big celebration next year,
just to make sure things are
cool between us and the Stump.
- [laughter]
- Oh...
Hey, Marco.
I just wanted to say
thank you for planning
this party for me.
It was really sweet,
even if the timing
wasn't that great.
No problem.
You know, with
all the infinite
dimensions that exist,
it's still your birthday
somewhere, right?
Hey, guys, it's safe
to come out now.
- You cool with this?
- Mm-hmm.
All right, guys,
a-uno, dos, tres.
♪ ♪
[music continues]
Perfect!
Oh, hot, hot! Hot!
[straining]
Steady. Ooh, steady.
All right.
Looks like everything is going
to be A-O... oh, oh, no!
The chocolate fountain!
[yelling]
Up high!
You mean down low?
[laughs]
Because I'm short.
Oh, let me
get that for you.
Hey, you're
the new guy.
Uh, Seeing Eye
spell, right?
You settling
in okay?
Fantastic.
Well, I'll see you
at the party later.
[laughs]
I joke.
[bleating]
Well, if it isn't
the goats with the moats.
Uh, most.
These are beautiful.
Keep up the good work.
Bye.
[bleating]
Hey, Raccoon.
Thanks for washing
those... cookies.
But maybe you could
wash the fine china instead.
Thanks, buddy.
Bye.
Hey, Narwhal,
looks pretty good.
Thanks, Spider.
But there's something I need
to talk to you about.
- Okay. What?
- Well, I...
Narwhal, please.
Oh, dismount.
Next time, you're
the foundation.
So what's up?
Let's go somewhere
a little quieter to talk.
What? Is
something wrong?
It's Seeing Eye.
He's really creepy.
What? What are
you talking about?
He's fine. Plus,
spying is kind of his job.
Can we fire him?
He's seriously
harshing our mellow.
What do you
want me to do?
Uninvite him from
the Stump Day party?
[all] Yes!
I can't do that.
Stump Day is about
inclusiveness and love,
and not angering
the Stump.
But Stump Day is
the one day of the year
I get to cut loose
and guzzle beans.
How can I do that with
Spy Eye buzzin' around?
Yeah, let him
eat the beans.
Spy Eye is not even
one of Star's spells.
Yeah, he's from
Eclipsa.
But Star used him,
and he's one of us now.
Spy Eye is definitely
not one of my bros.
Hey, come on, guys.
We all have
our quirks, right?
Narwhal, you're always breaking
pillars around the house
with your blast
ever since I can remember.
And Snail, ugh, you leave
your gross snail trails
everywhere.
It's a side effect
from my medication.
And me, me, I've got
a laser cannon in my hat.
Look, Seeing Eye's just
part of our family now,
and you guys
need to give him
the same consideration
that you give each other.
Now, let's have
a wonderful Stump Day.
Yeah!
What do you say, guys?
Maybe Spider
has a point.
[all agreeing]
Hey, hey,
ya old Stump.
Glad you could make it.
Hail to Stump Day.
Whoo! Stump Day!
Merry Stump Day
to you.
Whoa, you really
outdid yourself.
Merry Stump
Day, Snail.
Cloudy, I'm likin'
the upgrade.
Hey, guys, can I interest
anyone in some fresh-baked
Stump cakes?
- Ooh!
- My favorite.
Hey, Spider,
hit me up.
That's what
a Stump should taste like.
There you go,
fresh from the Stump.
Did I get it?
Did I pin
the twig on the stump?
Oh, you sure did.
Way to stick it to him.
Great party, Spider.
Everyone's havin'
a great time.
[happy chattering]
That's not right.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Hey, Seeing Eye,
good to see ya, buddy.
You havin' fun
over here
in the corner,
by yourself?
You know what?
Why don't I
introduce you
to some of
the other spells, huh?
Sounds fun.
Come on.
So then I said,
forget about flying.
You ever seen
a pig do this?
I'm dancin'.
[laughter]
Good one.
Hey, speaking of
cool, funny things,
have you guys met
Seeing Eye?
He's a new spell that
Star's been using a lot lately,
and is an all-around
great guy.
[nervous giggle]
Anyhoo, Seeing Eye,
I could tell you
some stories
about these crazy guys.
Tell me about it.
[sneezes]
[blows nose]
Nah. Nah. Nah.
Cool. Free stuff.
Oh, there you go.
That's disgusting.
Whatever. You're the one
licking the cupcakes.
You put your head
in the punch.
- Not cool.
- [all arguing]
[nervous chuckle]
I guess he already
knows all of you.
Hey, do you lift?
'Cause, you know,
it's a pretty big
deal around here,
as you can tell
by my body.
[gasping]
[gulp]
You totally
lied to us, bro.
You broke a sacred
sweaty bond.
Hold on a second, guys,
don't be mad.
I'm not mad, I just
need some time to process.
Yeah, me, too, bro.
We have to go.
Wait, bros, no!
Ah!
You know what? No.
This is your fault.
Instead of taking
responsibility for
my actions,
I am gonna blame you
for recording them,
and then I am
gonna pummel you.
The Stump cakes you were
looking for,
they're over there.
Ha ha.
Fine. I'll be back
momentarily to
whoop your...
eye, I guess.
Seeing Eye,
what are you doing?
It's always best
to tell the truth.
Yes. Be that as it may,
we are at an office
Stump Day party.
Oh!
Look, just try
havin' some fun, okay?
No.
How's it goin'?
This is a nightmare.
You know what?
I'd like to tell
every spell
at this stupid,
stinkin' Stump Day party
that they stink.
- Ruining Stump Day
after all the hard work...
- Spider.
What?! I'm trying
to wallow.
That.
Maybe he didn't
hear us.
Let's just start dinner,
and get this whole thing
over with.
[chattering]
Attention, please.
Friends, we made it
another year,
and now we have
this beautiful feast...
- Licked by raccoon.
- Blecchh!
...to enjoy together
as a...
As a family.
Without any punch,
because a certain pig
drank it all.
You know what?
- Pig did drink
all the punch.
- Hey.
And Makeup Blast
licked our food,
and Raccoon,
he washed our cookies.
[disgusted snorts]
While Seeing Eye
is creepin' everybody out.
But it's his first
Stump Day, guys,
and you know what?
Where I come from, that counts
for something, right?
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah, let's hear it
for Spider, man!
He's the glue that
holds us together.
[all] To Spider!
To Spider!
You know what?
I'd like to tell every spell
at this stupid,
stinkin' Stump Day party
that they stink!
[all gasp]
Is that...
how you feel?
[all talking at once]
Well, yeah, but, no,
my exact meaning
of what I was saying...
Oh.
[groans]
What the heck, man?
It's always best
to tell the truth.
Whatever, man.
I hope you're happy.
We were a family, and you
could have been a part of it.
But now, no.
It's over!
And if I never
see you again,
well, it would be
fine with me.
[Pig]  Oh, Stump cakes.
Oh, excuse me.
Your hand
is really soft.
What?
Tell me about it.
- What? Oh.
- [both laugh]
[all laughing]
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah, I did
do that, didn't I?
[giggles]
You did do that,
didn't you?
Let me get
your jacket.
Why, thank you, Spider.
[laughing]
Dude is
such a gentleman.
I didn't realize
how hard he worked.
It's always best
to tell the truth.
Wow. Thank you,
Seeing Eye.
Aw, dude, that was
beautiful, man.
Come on,
bring it in.
You're all right, bro.
It's a Stump Day miracle.
[laughs]
Sure is.
Come on, guys, we got
a Stump Day to celebrate.
Really?
Ha ha,
you know it, buddy.
Come on,
Seeing Eye.
Let's get
this party started!
♪ Gather friends
around the Stump ♪
♪ We'll have such fun
♪ Drink some punch,
feast a bunch ♪
♪ Play some games
and laugh too much ♪
♪ Around the Stump! ♪
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪