♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[panting]
All right, Marco,
what do you think?
- Is it too much?
- It's not too much.
- Is it not enough?
- I think it's perfect.
But does it read as
Mewmans and Monsters together?
Yeah, basically.
Don't worry, Star.
Oh, Rich, it is really
cool of you
to pay for this party.
I cannot believe
you found this place.
No... problem...
Star.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm glad your
leg is better.
Legs heal, Marco,
but grudges
last forever.
Yeah, well,
I'm sorry.
Kidding, kidding.
[laughs]
Water under
the bridge.
Besides, I love
throwing parties.
What's the point of money
if you aren't lording
it over everyone?
Hi. Time to get
this thing started now.
Okay, I'm sorry that
I'm late, but guess why.
It's 'cause I brought
you a gift.
Hey.
Oh, Pony,
you're the best.
Oh, did you hear that?
The best. Me.
Ooh, but, girl,
this looks more like
a stand-off than a party.
There's tension.
[Star] Ugh. Maybe I pushed
too hard and they aren't
ready for this.
That's it!
Oh, no. No!
Ooh, okay, now
it's getting started.
If no one else
is gonna say anything,
I will.
How dare you?!
Uh, me?
Pre-distressed
ripped-knee jeans.
I should've thought
to wear mine.
What's it like
being the coolest dude here?
Oh, you're...
you're happy at me?
Yes, I'm happy at you.
Oh, well, thanks.
Where'd you get those horns?
I really like 'em.
Oh, ha ha.
These old things?
Yeah, boating accident.
I should've died.
Yeah, you should've.
[both laughing]
Yeah, it was
pretty painful.
Oh, thank corn.
See? You had
nothing to worry about.
Monsters and Mewmans
partying together.
Who'd have thunk?
[beeping]
Here he comes.
Aah! Geez!
Careful, Roy.
Milady, your cheek marks
are glowing.
Put in
the mix tape.
As you wish.
[thrash rock playing]
♪ Introductions! ♪
Hey, so, like,
wanna dance?
Mm, sure.
[techno dance music plays]
Beats, on point.
Punch.
Not cold enough.
- On it.
- Marco!
I have magic.
Hmm.
[muffled]
Cold. Oh, cold.
[groaning]
Oh, my dear sweet angel lady,
I thought I lost you.
Tom, when did
you get here?
Um, I helped you set up.
Remember, Rich Pigeon
made me carry in
that statue of him.
How did I not notice
that till now?
I don't know.
I looked great
moving it...
all by myself.
It's your loss really.
May I have this dance?
Aww, you're being
very sweet,
but I have to focus
on this party right now.
It's a new age, Tom.
Monsters and Mewmans
living in harmony,
and I want everyone
to remember this night
forever.
Well, do you remember this?
What are you doing?
Uh, being romantic
and kissing you.
[nervous laugh]
You might have to
help me remember then.
Okay.
[inhales, blows]
[coughing]
Star!
[kissing sounds]
I miss this.
I miss you.
I haven't seen you
at all recently.
Come on, just
one little dance.
Oh, Tom,
I miss you, too.
but I really gotta go.
We'll dance later.
Mwah!
I'll see you then.
Ice!
Oh, Star fixed it.
Dude, I don't get it.
She'll be queen
soon anyway.
Why not enjoy being young
just for a little longer?
She's been working on
this for months, man.
This is important to her.
She's trying to fix
centuries of bigotry,
and social biases
that plague Mewni...
Sorry, sorry.
Just gonna stop
you there, Marco.
I'm not into politics.
Dude, you're a prince.
Everything you do
is political.
Look, guys, I got him
to do it.
I got him to do
the sword hand dance.
Everyone,
sword hand dance!
[upbeat music plays]
No, it's...
It's not a dance.
This indicates
I'm poised for combat.
Hey, Marco,
wanna dance?
Okay.
- Ahem. Would you
like to...
- [splat]
Eww, no. Does that
actually work on girls?
Come on!
Well, yeah, it works
on everybody.
Girls' bites, boys' bites.
It even works on
grandmas' bites.
- Wait, what?
- My slime.
It's just like aloe vera.
You actually wanna cure
my spider bite?
Yeah. Well, only if
you want to.
Dude, I am so sick
of this spider bite.
Give me some of that.
Whoa! That's amazing.
You're amazing.
Oh, it's nothing.
Really.
[yells]
Oh, my gosh.
Slime, are you okay?
I'm okay.
You'd be surprised
how many times
that's happened.
There's some pretty
spooky statues down here.
Yeah. That one looks
like it's seen better days.
That one looks like
my old math teacher.
Yeah, and that one
looks like...
it's breathing?
[both scream]
This party is on point.
Good job, girl!
Aww, thanks, Pony.
You know, I think
I really did do a good job.
To Star Butterfly,
for putting on
this magnificent party.
And inviting
everybody to come.
Aww, you guys.
Stop.
[all] Speech, speech!
Okay, I'm blushing.
I'm literally
blushing, guys.
Well, we kids
are the future,
and starting tonight,
we are going to create
a new Mewni.
A Mewni where
everyone is welcome anywhere.
I'm so excited,
I could scream.
[Spider Bite screaming]
Help!
Oh, my gosh.
What happened?
It was a monster.
What's going on
over here?
Obviously, she was attacked
by that slimy monster.
What? Slime wouldn't
attack anybody.
Is he still
down in that chamber?
I... I...
We saw you
take him down there.
Yeah, like, what
did you do to him?
Has anyone seen
Slime Monster?
No, but Eric's
missing, too.
He was over by
that door earlier.
So was Tanya.
Weren't you dancing
with Tanya earlier?
There were a lot of girls.
I don't know all their names.
What did you do
with Tanya?
Nothing. Monsters do
whatever they want.
What is that
supposed to mean?
It means Mewmans
aren't the ones
attacking people,
and dragging them through
creepy hidden doorways.
You know monsters.
It's, like, their instinct.
[Squirrel Monster]
Oh, here it comes.
Just 'cause he's a monster.
- Hey, girl.
- Pony, thank goodness.
I don't know what you did,
but this party just got
way more interesting.
You're jumping
to conclusions.
Just common knowledge.
- Stop!
- [silence]
Please, everybody,
just let me take care of this.
Go back
and enjoy the party.
There's fresh punch;
it's very cold.
The Goblin Dog food truck
is out front,
and we even have
some... jokes!
Pony, keep everybody
entertained while
I investigate.
Ooh, I'm the jokes!
[Marco reading menu]
Roy, who...who
gets strawberry?
Can... Can I have one?
- Marco, I need you.
- Whoa!
Your hat
looks fine.
I was doing something.
Tom, I need your help.
Monster kids have
started disappearing,
and nobody knows
where Slime Monster is.
Star, relax.
It's a party.
They're probably just
off cuddling somewhere...
which is what
you and I should
be doing.
- Don't you think?
- Ewww.
I do not have
time for this, Tom.
Don't you understand?
If something bad
happens to those monsters,
everything I've worked for
will be ruined.
So you can either help me
or you can get out of my way.
Come on, Marco.
Princesses.
Pat, pat.
Hey, Slime.
Slimy dude.
You in here?
What do you think
this place was anyway?
I don't know.
These stairs
are not easy
in this dress.
Whoa, check it out.
It's like
a little campsite.
These earmarks are fresh.
[both gasp]
Slime?
If that was you,
now would be
a nice time to tell us.
[Marco] Matches,
matches, matches!
Okay, here.
I've got the candle.
- Here, here.
- I can't see where.
Wait, I'll just
use my wand.
What the...
Mina Loveberry?
Mud Sister?
What the heck are
you doing here?
I am throwing
a very important
Mewman and Monster
friendship party.
Wait, wait,
monsters?
I've been throwing monsters
into this closet
- all night.
- Get us outta here!
What? Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
You need to let them go
right now.
I need to keep
this place safe
from evil monster
treachery.
They're not evil,
they're my friends.
Come on.
This place is abandoned.
Nothing sinister
is going on.
Young warrior, everything
about these monsters
and whoz-its is sinister.
You don't understand.
I am trying to--
Interrupting!
You don't understand
the complexities
of this situation.
I am duty-bound
to protect this temple.
Doctor's orders.
This one's
all you, Mud Sister.
Maybe it's time
to get a second opinion.
You doubt the words
of a professional?
No, but, just... ow!
Okay, stop it!
Okay, Mina, look,
let's just calm down
and not escalate things.
I'm not the one
escalating things, escalator.
I've been waiting
hundreds of years... aaah!
Princess Marco.
Heinous?!
Oh, no!
I am done
running from you.
This ends now...
Okay.
Now to set the mood.
Play the music.
Again, milady?
Play it!!
Yes, ma'am.
[whispering]
Heard it 15 times.
[thrash rock playing]
Start the machine.
[muttering]
Milady, the lever is stuck.
What? Hmm?
When I push it,
it doesn't go down.
You imbecile!
Utterly incompetent.
But no matter.
This is between me
and Princess Marco now.
Milady.
[gasps]
It can't be.
So are we still
fighting or... ?
Leave the room, Marco.
What have you
got there, milady?
Dolls.
Oh, I...
I can see that.
These were my dolls.
I love my dolls.
That's...
that's very...
nice.
I can't believe it.
It's all
coming back to me.
That was my bookshelf,
and my toy chest.
This place,
this was my nursery.
[gasps]
And this...
this was my baby bed.
But how is
this possible?
Oh, it's possible,
all right.
I knew you'd
be back here one day...
Meteora.
I beg your pardon!
This is Miss Heinous,
the honorable
headmistress
of St. Olga's School
for Wayward Princesses.
No. Meteora.
That is my name.
At least, it was my name
a long, long time ago.
Milady, your arm.
No, no, no, no, no!
Shall I fetch your makeup?
Well, ain't this
a pretty picture?
First, Eclipsa wakes up,
and now, look who
comes a-cryin'. Typical.
Whoa, wait. Eclipsa?
What does she have to do
with this?
Yeah, can someone
fill us in?
Don't you ding-dongs
know anything?
She's her mama.
Eclipsa is
Heinous' mother?!
But how? Eclipsa's
hundreds of years old.
Besides, that would mean
Heinous is a...
a princess.
It means
she's a Butterfly.
she's a monster.
Now, uh, see here...
[shrieks]
Whoa, whoa, Mina.
Wait just one second.
I got a lot
of questions here.
Doctor's orders!
Double rainbow fist!
- Quick, go get
the monster kids.
- Right.
Stardust daisy devastation!
Whoa! Get out!
Oh, you let them go?!
You traitor!
Miss Heinous.
We must leave quickly.
Star? Star, are you
down here?
[Star screams]
- Tom!
- Star!
Look, I know
I did something wrong,
and I'm still
not sure what,
but I want to apologize.
That's great, great.
Kind of got
a thing here.
Spider with a top hat blast!
War!
[growling]
[magical chanting]
[pounding]
Ooh. Ah!
Where is she?
Where is Meteora now?
[screeching]
[laughing]
Okay, all right,
here's another one, okay?
- Knock, knock.
- [all] Who's there?
Where is Meteora?
Where's the monster?
Raspberry ribbon rainbow!
You're ruining everything
I'm trying to accomplish.
Well, you just helped
the most dangerous monster
in the history
of Mewni escape.
What's happening?!
- Everybody freeze!
- Oh, no.
The donut patrol?
I gotta make tracks.
So... you guys
came here to party?
[siren blaring]
You are in a world
of trouble, young lady.
Look, it was just
a party, okay?
We weren't doing
anything wrong.
Oh, really?
Then what was
that huge surge of magic
we detected in
the dungeon earlier?
Oh, yeah. That.
Do you have any idea
what this place is?
Uh, a fun place
to throw parties?
It's not just
a fun place to throw parties.
It's, well, I'm not even
authorized to tell you
what it is.
That's how bad it is.
[blows raspberry]
You don't know
what it is, do you?
What? No, I totally
know what it is.
- It's...
- [gibbering]
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I don't have
time for this.
You stay here.
I got a crime scene
to deal with.
Hey.
I made this for you.
I mean, no,
that's a lie.
They're just handing
'em out over there.
I was, um... here.
Aw, thanks, Tom.
So, sorry for being
a total nag back there.
I get it now.
You were dealing with
some serious stuff.
It's okay. Doesn't even
matter now anyway.
The party was
a disaster.
What? No!
It was a great party.
I mean, sure, some
monsters got trapped
in a closet,
and Mina probably
traumatized some people,
and we got busted
by the cops,
and I am not
helping at all right now.
This is all my fault.
I really thought I could
just change everything
overnight.
Ugh, I was so wrong.
Hey, don't be
so hard on yourself.
There's no way
you could've known
all this weirdness
would happen.
Yeah, that's
the problem, Tom.
I don't know anything.
I don't know how to fix
what's wrong with Mewni,
I don't even know
who my own family
is anymore.
All that stuff with
Heinous and Eclipsa.
I just...
Hey, hey, hey!
What do you think
you're doing?
Let those monsters go.
We found these hooligans
loitering outside the temple.
I need to take them in
for processing.
Oh, really?
Then why don't you process
those  hooligans?
- More hot chocolate,
Your Highness?
- Yes.
Well, uh...
- Let 'em go!
- Yes, Your Highness.
I am so sorry
this happened to
you guys.
It's okay, Star.
Trust me, this happens
to us all the time.
I can make it up to you.
Stay for the after-party.
Snacks on me.
Uh, thanks, but I've
had enough parties for a while.
Yeah, I almost
died for real.
Catch you later, okay?
[sirens wailing]
There's too much
heat out there.
We should get
going, Miss Heinous.
That's not my name.
I'm... sorry.
My name is Meteora.
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪