♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Mewmins and monster have just
misunderstood each other
for too long.
Mewni should be
a place of peace
and unity
for everyone.
Right, yes.
Like they don't,
like, get peace
or whatever.
But for that
to happen,
we need to stop
following the old ways.
We need to be the change
we want to see.
That's why I'm hoping
they'll sign
this super awesome petition
of friendship between
monsters and Mewmins.
Your signature is
the last one we need.
So... what do you say?
Will you sign?
[flapping]
Um... [giggles]
[cooing]
[cooing continues]
Is this the same
Rich Pigeon that, like,
killed it at
the Silver Bell Ball?
Uh, I think so.
Does he even understand
a word we're saying?
I don't know.
We've never
actually talked.
But just to make it
easier for you...
Pen.
Petition.
Sign.
Come on, Star,
he's just a dumb bird.
You can't expect him
to envision a utopian future.
Marco.
Ignore him.
How about one blink
for yes, and two for no?
Look, just, like,
grab his little foot
or whatever,
and sign the petition
for him so we can
get outta here.
This place is
giving me the creeps.
Yeah, Marco's right.
Whoa, did I just
say that out loud?
You just hold the petition,
and I'll grab his foot.
Yeah, I don't
know, Marco.
Doesn't really sound
like the right way to go.
Relax. I've seen
all the bird videos online.
I've got this.
Okay, okay.
Just be gentle.
See, now.
There we go.
[chuckles]
Birds feel weird.
[gasps]
Marco!
What did you do?
That was not gentle.
Fix it, fix it,
fix it now!
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
[angry squawking]
Run!!
Marco, I told you
to be gentle.
I was gentle.
Crystal narwhal...
My wand!
- A little help, please.
- I got you, Marco.
[relieved sighs]
I told you, birds don't
see what doesn't move.
Quick, in here.
[panting]
Okay, I think
we lost them.
Oh, great, now we're
stuck in a room
with paintings?!
I hate paintings.
Wait, these are all
paintings of Rich Pigeon.
Ah, bold, confident
brush work,
with a subtle nod
to neoclassicism.
Nice.
[pounding on door]
[groaning]
Wait. Barricade
the door.
Pony Head,
where you going?
I am sorry, but I cannot
deal with this anymore
right now, okay?
I need to do me.
Ah! Much better.
Pony Head,
what are you doing?
Get back here
and help us.
Guys, come quick.
I think I found
something.
[Star]
Oh, thank Mewni.
Look at me!
I can dance now.
[laughs]
Look at this!
Rich Pigeon's legs.
Pony Head, I don't see
how some extra legs
and jewels are gonna
get us outta here.
Well, first of all,
you are so wrong
on so many levels,
the second level being
that this is not
what I found
that I'm talking about.
[bell rings]
[loud footsteps]
Look at them calves.
Boom.
Whoa, those are
some big legs.
[birds screeching]
Everyone, pick a leg.
- Hurry up!
- Sorry.
We can't all just
float wherever we want.
Definitely not
with that attitude.
[all screaming]
[Marco] Look at
all these levers.
Push them all!
How does
this thing work?!
Stop yelling.
No, it feels
good right now.
No, I mean it.
Stop yelling for one second.
Do you hear that?
I don't hear
anything.
Exactly.
They stopped.
[silence]
Phew!
Oh, thank karate.
Now let's get--
Are they still
following us though?
- [loud screeching]
- Yep.
They're blocking
the exit.
Don't, stop. Marco,
you'll hurt the pigeons.
Oh!
Oh, hey, girl,
can I just ask you
something so quickly?
What the heck-y was that?!
We were almost
out of this trash castle.
If we hurt the pigeons,
we're never gonna get
Rich to sign the petition.
You really think that's
still a possibility, Star?
[cooing]
[nervous laughter]
Hey, birds.
Buddies.
About all this...
we are so sorry.
This is very normal
for me; it happens.
I know how
to deal with it.
Pony Head!
I know what I am.
Okay, we're so sorry
things got
so out of hand...
or claw...
or whatever you...
Okay, listen, how about
we all just please start over.
We didn't mean any harm
to Prince Rich Pigeon.
We just wanted to...
Pony Head!!
I thought that we might
need him for leverage.
Cool. Can't wait to die.
[loud squawking]
[angry squawking]
How is this a fair trial?
We don't even know
what they're saying.
Um, excuse me.
King Pigeon, sir.
I just want to
apologize again
for what happened
here today.
We did not mean
to break your son's leg.
Yeah, like, in
a thousand pieces.
I was gentle.
Okay, let's just...
We didn't come here today
to hurt anyone.
We just came here
to ask your son for help.
[angry cooing]
[gong rings]
[loud footsteps]
[all screaming]
Oh, my goodness!
This is not happening.
No. No, no, no, no!
[yelling]
Awww. Hey, there.
Ow. That kinda hurt.
Ow, ow, ow.
Okay, okay.
Ow. That's annoying. Ow!
Oh, I heard about
this before.
It's death by
a thousand pecks.
Ow. Well... ow...
this is gonna... ow...
take forever. Ow.
[door opens]
Set them free!
- [voice echoing]
- [angry squawking]
He can talk?!
I knew it!
And it's such a strong,
handsome man voice, too.
Oh, my goodness.
Hello.
Yes, Father, I disobeyed
pigeon law,
and learned
the Mewni tongue.
But I did it
for our kingdom's future.
Why must we proud pigeons
continue to pretend
to be mindless animals?
Princess Butterfly
champions a noble cause--
peace and friendship
between the powerful
and the downtrodden.
We must not let our prejudices
against the Mewmins
prevent us from joining
her fight for justice.
We are a small
but mighty empire.
I love this kingdom,
and it is my duty
as its prince to protect it,
but it is also my duty
to bring it forth
into the future.
Star Butterfly,
you have inspired me.
Seeing you work so hard,
it makes me want to be
a greater prince
for the pigeons.
Nay, nay, nay, nay.
For all of Mewni.
[triumphant squawking]
We did it.
We got all the signatures!
Yeah, thank you so much!
And, uh, sorry about
busting up your castle.
No, no, the damage
you did today
was far less damage
than we did
- when we conquered it
for ourselves.
- Conquered? From who?
Oh, you didn't notice
the skeleton rotting
in the hall?
Uh...
[nervous laughter]
[chuckling]
Enough business.
Now we must feast
to celebrate
our new beginning.
Finally!
I am starving!
I could really go for
some pizza or, like,
a bunch of soda
chips...
So you know what?
You keep living
your best life,
all right, and
I'm just gonna
head out and not
stay here anymore.
Bye-bye!
Is this the doorbell or...
[loud buzzer
and whinnying]
Oh, what did I do?
[Pony Head]
What are you doing?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I just rang the doorbell.
That's not a doorbell.
I'll come down and get you.
Oh, my gosh, Star!
Pony Head!
Good to see you, girl.
Check out
what I brought.
Oh, my goodness!
That is the finest
casserole I have
ever seen, girl.
Maybe this night might not
be a total disaster after all.
Right? Wait, what?
I've been trying to spare
you from my sisters,
I really have,
but at this point,
I need back-up.
What? They've always
been so nice to me.
You do not know them
like I do, Star.
They're like
peanut butter and jealous.
They have been trying
to take me down for years,
all because I'm
next in line for the throne.
Not to mention that
I'm so beautiful
and talented and humble.
Oh, Pony Head.
- I'm sure
they're not that bad.
- Star, look at me.
They are long-faced,
two-faced monsters.
All right,
listen up, people.
Okay, my friend Star
is here for our meal,
and we are going
to act like normal,
like a normal family
that spends time together.
Like normal.
Hey, Azniss. No.
Okay, that is
not normal.
This is what I'm
talking about, people.
Oh, no, it's fine.
You guys don't have to do
anything special for me.
Just act like
I'm not even here.
Pony Head, I forgot
everyone's names.
Oh, hey, Star forgot
y'all's names.
- Roll call!
- [stammering]
- Baby Pranciss.
- Hornanne.
- Jen-Jen.
- Pamanda.
- Khrystalle.
- Angel.
- Azniss.
No! Get back to
the table right now!
You don't introduce yourselves
with a musical number.
You say your name.
Just say your name.
Where are the twins?
Shonda and Shinda.
- [both] Yes?
- Get your creepy
selves over here.
You guys
are so weird.
Ugh! Are we ready
to eat?
Food?
Yes, Daddy,
it's time to eat.
- Get down here.
- [goofy laughter]
Fooooood!!
Well, dig in.
[Star chuckles nervously]
Hey, Pony Head,
is it okay if
I skip the trough,
and eat this cupcake
that's on a plate here?
That's Teta's plate.
She ran off.
We always make
a plate for her,
in the hopes that
she'll come back one day.
I hope she's not prettier
than me, though.
She probably ran off
because she can't stand
your sorry butts, okay?
She ran off because
you're always throwing
her shade, Pony Head.
She's always throwing
me shade
by doing her homework
and then being, like,
"I'm gonna donate
to charity."
You know what I mean?
Like, that's very rude.
[music playing]
Shonda and Shinda.
[music continues]
What are you doing?
[both] We wanted to play
some of our original
music for Star.
Nobody wants to hear
your creepy singing
except for dead people.
Are we at
a haunted house?
See what I mean?
I don't know,
I think it's kinda sweet.
I miss Teta!
How do you even know
who Teta is?
You were a zygote
when she disappeared.
- Not cool.
- Really mean.
[angry chattering]
Now, now, girls,
settle down.
[slurping]
I'm sorry you all
can't handle
how on point
I am right now.
Can't trust anyone
in this house.
Not even
my best friend.
I'm just gonna
go check on her.
Knock, knock.
Can I come in?
[loud belch]
So...
I'm really sorry
you felt ganged-up
on down there,
but you gotta admit,
you were being
a little intense,
right?
[beat boxing]
Hey, Pony Head.
Guess what's in
the casserole...
that I made.
Just take a wild guess.
All right,
I'll just tell you.
It is gingerbread
and ice cream.
Why don't you go eat it
with my sisters
since you think
they're so great?
- Oh, fine.
- [door slams]
This casserole
is delicious, Star.
Yeah, I know.
Was Pony Head
mean to you, too?
I don't get it.
It's seems like she just
flipped out of nowhere.
[sighs] Don't beat
yourself up about it.
She's like that
all the time.
You haven't picked up
on that yet?
I guess she can sometimes
be a little bit--
Of a party pooper.
We know.
She's pooped on
our parties more times
than I can even count.
And then, she
makes fun of me
'cause I don't know
all of my numbers yet.
[whimpering]
You poor thing.
Guess who's developed
a complex?
- Uh...
- All of us.
We all did.
She messed us up
real good.
It's true.
Because of
Pony Head's attitude,
I became terribly insecure,
and now, I have
to compensate by putting
all of my self-worth
into my jaw-dropping beauty.
It's real hard, you guys,
and I do it every day.
Every day.
I've never known Pony Head
to be so horrible.
[both] At least
we have each other.
Yeah, we don't need
no stinkin' Pony Head
to have a good time.
We can show you how
a real pony head parties.
Now you look fierce.
Thanks, Pranciss.
Yo, Star,
check this out.
Oh, cool.
Fun trick.
Huh? What do
you think?
I wasn't done.
[groaning]
I'm not sure
what just happened there.
You should be honored.
She only does that
for her sisters.
You're totally like
one of the family now.
- I am?
- [all] Absolutely.
Oh, yay! I've always
wanted sisters.
You know what's the most
awesomest thing about
having sisters?
Arguing over the remote?
That's a good guess,
but it's actually a secret.
Do you like secrets?
Usually.
Do you like
projects?
Yes.
Cool, 'cause we've got
this super secret project
we've been working on,
and we'd love to get
your thoughts on it.
Sweet!
Check it out.
Wait.
Teta on ice?
I thought Teta ran off.
Oh, baby, we're
hatching a plot
to depose Pony Head
as heir to the throne.
[giggles]
No.
Yeah.
[laughs].
You saw how she is.
She's unfit to lead.
Yeah, look, we've
got it all figured out.
Pony Law states that
if a pony princess
puts one of her sisters on ice,
she can never be queen.
So we're putting
Teta on ice,
and framing
Pony Head for it.
On ice?
Well, that sounds fun.
No, no, no, no, no, honey.
We mean...
[all] On ice.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, you guys, ice
is supposed to be cool,
and what you're talking
about is bad ice.
Not really.
We're just gonna
pretend Teta's on ice.
Ain't that right, Teta?
Yep. They got a new life
set up for me and everything.
I have a mustache!
What you think, Star?
I got...
a lot of questions.
I know Pony Head
has got some issues,
but don't you think
maybe framing her is a bit much?
[exasperated sigh]
Everyone knows
Pony would be
the worst queen ever.
She just won't
admit it to herself.
This way, the right pony
gets to inherit the throne.
Me!!
Wait a minute.
Who said you were
gonna be queen?
I thought I was
gonna be queen.
[both] Pamanda, really?
No, you're right.
I should be queen.
No, I should be queen.
I'm perfect.
No, I should
be queen.
I think I'd
do a good job.
That makes no sense.
You're supposed to be dead.
[Pamanda]
We talked about this...
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
- Oh, oh, me, me?
- You weren't planning on
telling Pony Head,
now, were you?
No!
Of course not.
Never. No.
'Cause, uh, we can't allow
you to snitch, sugar booger.
You're one of us now...
sister.
And if you betray
your sisters,
you're gonna get
disappeared, too,
- just like Teta.
- [Pony Head whinnies]
Bam, you are busted.
Pony, what is going on?
Star, you beautiful angel,
I'm so sorry
you've been put through
this trauma.
I knew these no class-having
wannabe queens
were up to somethin';
I just didn't know what.
And I have it all on video.
This way, the right pony
gets to inherit the throne.
Okay, thanks for having me.
Because I definitely feel
like I've been had.
Oh, unbelievable.
Yeah, so anyway,
thank you, Star,
for coming over.
I know you probably
feel used,
but I couldn't
have done it without you.
Thank you so much.
What, are you kidding?
Pony Head, this is one of
the most stressful experiences
of my already
very intense life.
I'm sorry.
My sisters
are totally insane.
- Oh, totally insane.
- Whoa, hold on.
You cannot just be
sitting up here talking
about my sisters like that.
You just said it yourself.
Star, I love my sisters.
We do this every meal.
I guess I just don't
get the whole sister thing.
You have one of the best
sisters a girl could ever need,
'cause you
got me, B-fly.
Oh, girl.
Star, you weren't
trying to leave without
saying good-bye, were you?
[whispers]
Take me with you.
[all] Bye-bye, Star!
Bye!
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through
the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when
it's night 'cause ♪
♪ She will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly! ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪