♪♪
[upbeat music plays]
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird,
gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here,
I'm from another-- woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows,
I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puh-puuuhh♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[Marco panting]
You stop right there,
young... old man!
Globgor!
Aah! [panting]
Hey, Buff Frog,
sorry about Glossaryck.
He gets fussy
around, uh...
nap time?
Oh. Uh, guess he has
today off.
-[snores]
-Come here, you.
-Hmm.
Guess I'll bring this to--
Ohh! Aah!
I looked at someone's mail
without their permission!
-Wait. What?!
-[snoring]
Oh, beans.
[sighs]
I don't know.
I feel so weird.
I have so much
on my mind,
and I can't talk
to my parents about it.
I don't think I can
talk to anyone.
[awkward]
Oh! Yes, you can!
You can talk to me!
Right? Yeah.
Yeah, th-th-that's
a thing that boyfriends
do, right?
Listen! Yeah!
I'm all ears.
I mean, technically
I'm mostly eyes. [chuckles]
Just talk to me.
[sighs] It's just that--
-[door opens]
-[Marco] Star!
-Buff Frog is gone!
-What?!
I found this letter
for you in his office.
Look.
Wait a second.
This letter is legible!
Buff Frog didn't write
this note!
Exactly!
We gotta find him.
I'll get my wand.
Yessss! Weapons!
I'm gonna try
the lance this time!
Marco. Marco.
My man. My dude.
Hmm?
Um, how about I go
with Star on this one?
What?!
No, no. I'm her squire.
It's my job.
Okay, okay, yes,
but also, as her boyfriend,
my job is kinda
to spend time with Star.
Time you kinda
just interrupted. Soo..
Okay, true, but also,
Buff Frog's my friend, and--
Okay! That's enough bickering.
C'mon, Marco let's go!
[whispering]
Please.
[snoring]
Oh! What do you know!
Glossaryck
is escaping again!
That nimble
little rascal!
[Glossaryck] Globgor!
Uh, I gotta go catch him
before he starts trouble!
Sorry, Star! Tom can
go with you instead!
[Glossaryck]
Globgor.
Whatever, fine!
C'mon, Tom! Let's go!
[insects chirping]
Buff Frog?
[gasps]
This doesn't look right.
Buff babies?!
I've got a really
bad feeling about this.
Well, we tried.
Guess he's not home.
Do you wanna
get a cornshake?
Are you
for real right now?
We are just
getting started.
All right, well,
maybe we could ask
someone in the village
if they've seen him.
Ah! The Monster village!
Great idea!
Oh, yeah.
Better than something
Marco could come up with?
[wind blowing]
Hello!
[echoing]
I don't think anyone's here.
This just doesn't
make any sense.
[thud]
What was that?
[flies buzzing]
This is troubling.
C'mon, let's
keep looking around.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait!
I want to get me
some of that meat.
What?! Are you serious?
That's Monster food.
[mumbling "I don't know"]
You are gross, dude.
What if someone
rounded them up?
A rogue band
of Mewmans maybe.
[gasps]
Or worse-- Mina!
Oh, no, no, no, no,
everywhere I look,
things are getting
worse and worse!
I don't know,
maybe everyone is out
grocery shopping
or on a picnic or something.
I mean, that's
what peasants do, right?
Hey, what's that thing
on your neck?
What? I don't have
anything in my neck.
What's that on your arm?
What? I don't
have anything on...
[sound of Tom falling]
[drowsy] Hey... what--
What are you doing
on the ground?
What am I doing
Oh, gee! Oh! [panting]
My face is itchy.
Why is my face itchy?!
Because you're
in a burlap sack.
Aah! Don't sneak up
on me!
Ow! Sorry.
-What happened?
-I don't know.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Who did this?!
Star, I know
exactly the same amount
as you do right now,
which is nothing.
Somebody really
does not want us to know
where Buff Frog is.
Okay, let's get up,
ready?
On the count of three...
one, two...
[groaning]
[grunts, screaming]
Tom! Tom! Are you okay?!
I think I just found out
I'm claustrophobic,
and I might be panicking
a little!
Me, too!
I think I'm close.
Just stay where you are.
I'll come to you.
-No, Tom, stay put!
-[whimpering]
-Tom! It's all right!
-[screaming]
I'm right here!
-Aahh! Aah!
-[thunk]
[Star] Tom, stop
being so difficult!
Huh? [straining]
Uh, I accidentally gored a tree,
and, well, now I'm stuck.
A tree! Aha! Now we know
we're in the woods!
[roars]
[Star] Run!
Woo-hoo! Okay, I don't know
what I just did,
but I think
it was pretty awesome,
and I am very proud
of myself for it!
Oh, no!
I have message for you.
Those that search
for little lost frogs
will find themselves
at bottom of swamp!
What does that mean?
Stop looking for Buff Frog!
And to make sure
message is clear,
-break his horns!
-Aah!
[Tom screams]
What is going on here?!
Buff Frog?!
Oh! You're okay!
Hello, Princess.
-[happy croaking]
-Oh!
[whisper yell]
Babiiiess!
I was so worried!
That letter
freaked me out.
Letter? I know
nothing of letter.
Excuse me. The person
who wrote the letter was me.
Aw, Katrina got li'l arms!
Oy yi yi. How many times
must I tell children,
to become spy, they must
not to leave paper trail?
Is like number one rule.
Kids these days.
But your house...
it was a mess.
When you are single parent
of pile of kids,
I would like see your house!
I just want Star
to know we were leaving.
Leaving? Where are you going?
Grocery shopping?
No. We must leave
this dimension for good.
We cannot stay
on Mewni anymore.
What are you--
What are you
talking about?
[sad music playing]
What? No, but--
No, no, no!
No! You can't leave!
I need your help
to bring Monsters
and Mewmans together!
We're so close!
Sorry, Star, you tried,
but it not work.
This not problem
you can solve.
[Tom] Fools!
Beg your pardon?
You heard me. You're all being
a bunch of fools right now.
How can you say things
will never change?
Things are changing.
I mean, Buff Frog, you work
at the castle now, right?
Star did that.
True, yes, but everyone
in castle still scared of me.
Plus commute is terrible.
What do you care,
Your Highness?
What? Why wouldn't I care?
-'Cause you don't know...
-...what it's like!
Being treated differently,
day in and day out.
I do know what
it's like, because...
I, too, am a Monster.
Yeah! Wait, what?
-What? Are you serious?
-I had no idea.
What?!
Well, technically half Monster.
I got these eyes, horns,
-tail.
-[rip]
Okay, that's new.
And lets not forget
this face!
-Look at it!
-[Monsters scream]
Please, please.
Not in front of children.
Yeah, but I mean,
you're a rich guy.
I mean, ri-- right?
He's... he's rich.
Doesn't count.
Okay, you're right.
I am very rich.
Uh, but when I get
on an elevator with a stranger,
I'm a Monster
just like all of you.
I'm a rich Monster, yeah,
but I'm a Monster.
Thank you for pretty words,
purple boy.
But for us to stay,
we need more than words.
Star Butterfly,
you are good person.
You tried your best,
but it was not good enough.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no,
Buff Frog,
please wait!
I can try harder!
We have to
stick together!
Goodbye, Star.
Perhaps when it is your time
to rule, we will come back.
My time?
But how will you know?
Princess, please,
it's me, Buff Frog, master spy.
Trust me, I will know.
Babushkas, come say bye.
-[croaking]
-[laughing]
You sweet
little baby angels.
I'm-a miss you so much!
Okay, no more
with the sentimental.
Time to go, everyone!
After you.
No, after you.
No, no, after you.
Together!
Okay, now you babies.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten,
11, 12.
Where is Katrina?
I made you something
so you don't forget me.
Aw, Katrina!
I actually got something
for you, too.
My toy!
[portal hums]
[croaking]
Oh, Tom, I-- I can't
believe they're gone.
I feel like I've
only made things worse.
Have a little faith, Star.
I'm a Monster,
you're a Mewman.
If we can make it work,
then there's hope for everyone.
Aw, thanks, Tom.
You're welcome.
So did I do better
than Marco?
All right, we'll just pop in
and pop out real quick,
'cause I've got that Royal
Squire mixer this afternoon.
Aah! I caught the bouquet!
I caught the bouquet!
I caught
the bouquet!
So... what kind
of party is this?
Bird... Bird Day?
Bird Day? Is that a thing?
Bird Day?
Doesn't it say
on the invite?
Star!
I'm a squire of Mewni.
I don't have time
to read invites!
Seems to be some kind
of kid-washing party.
-What?
-Yeah, a "baby shower."
Eh, guess someone's
having a baby.
A dirty baby
it sounds like,
seeing as to how
they're gonna wash it.
Marco!
Hey, Mom!
So, who's having the baby?
Can't you tell?
[gasps] Mom?!
You're gonna be... a mom?!
When did this happen?!
Oh, while you were
out on Mewni.
And you're going
to be a big brother!
Say hello
to your hermanito--
Marco Junior!
Ohmigosh, ohmigosh,
ohmigosh, ohmigosh!
Wait. What?
You're naming him
Marco Junior?
After you.
That's not how it works!
You don't name your son
after your son!
But he's got a little mole
just like you, Marco Senior.
Wow... a brother!
How have I not heard
about this until now?
It's okay.
You've been busy.
Point is,
you're here today.
Now, give your mom
a hug!
Oh, yeah, okay.
I spent 37 hours
squeezing you
out of my body,
and this is what I get?
Oh, I just didn't want to--
Give your mother a hug.
Okay.
Now come on! We have
a baby to shower!
[people chattering]
Whoa! I felt him kick!
We might have to find
a spot for this little guy
on the Mewni Kings guard!
[laughs] No, I think
stealing one of our sons
is enough for now, Star.
Oh, oh, oh!
He's kicking? He's kicking?
Why, yes, Marco,
you may touch my stomach.
I don't feel anything.
He must have stopped.
You think that's because
he doesn't like me?
I think his brain
is the size of a grape.
Which reminds me,
I'm gonna eat a bag of grapes
before we open presents.
-[panting]
-Presents?
Yeah, it was in that
invitation you didn't read.
Oh, Gustav, you've
outdone yourself again!
Oh, my gosh!
I didn't get a gift
for Marco Jr.
I'm a terrible big brother.
Shh shh shh shh!
Calm, Marco Sr.
I know! Why don't we
pop on over to Quest Buy
and get him
a little present?
Quest Buy? I don't know.
-Sure! Come on!
-Whoa!
Well, we were so lonely
that we decided,
"Hey, why not have a baby?"
Marco, where are you going?
Uh, I'm gonna, uh,
run out and grab some ice
for the party.
But we have plenty of ice.
Yeah,
but I'm gonna get
fancy ice they harvest
from a glacier.
Oooh! Glacier ice.
Well, don't be gone
too long.
We'll be
opening presents soon.
-No problem-o.
-Get out of here,
tap-water ice!
You are not needed anymore!
Are you...
just gonna hold your drink
until Marco gets back?
For glacier ice?
I will wait.
[elevator music playing]
Seriously?! None of this stuff
is safe for a baby!
How about Baby's
First Hidden Poison Capsule?
What's safer
than not having enemies
because you poisoned
them all?!
I am not giving
the baby a pacifier
filled with magic poison.
Well, there's always
a gift card?
[female voice] You have
8.5 minutes until expiration.
Aah!
No! Aaah! Please! No!
[laser blast]
No.
This gift has to be
the perfect reminder of me
since I might
not be around much.
Oh, I know!
[Marco] "Atelier
de Cobalt Ferrero."
He works
in the basement?
Mr. Ferrero?
[impatient] What?
Oh, your portraitness.
Eh? Whaddaya want?
My friend Marco here
wants one
of your legendary portraits.
Is that right, Marco?
Yeah. I'm starting
to think this is a bad idea.
Oh! Rich Pigeon?
Sorry didn't see you there.
-Uh, Marco, that's a portrait.
-What?!
That piece?
Not even finished yet.
Wow, he's so real,
I can almost smell him!
That's just
the perch he posed on.
That's fowl.
Get it?
'Cause he's a bird.
It's the perfect gift!
A portrait that realistic,
it's like I'll be there
with my family
even when I'm not!
I know, I know.
I'm very talented.
But we got a lotta work
to do before
the painting begins.
I have to study
you closely.
I have to live with you,
breathe with you,
eat a lock of your hair.
The process takes weeks,
maybe months.
Can't you do
something faster?
No! I never compromise
my work.
-650 Cash.
-Sold.
You need
one of these things.
A scantron?
And one of these.
What? I don't have time
for a pop quiz!
It's an Essence Test,
wise guy.
The abridged version of me
studying you for months.
"What kind of socks
do you prefer with loafers?
A: tube socks, B: ankle socks."
How is this supposed
to help with a portrait?
Whatever! I don't
have time for this!
[humming]
[music playing]
Uh, Mr. Ferrero? All done.
Let's make some art!
-[ding]
-Let's.
[dramatic music playing]
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Time's running out
and my legs are asleep!
-Hmm.
-[snaps]
Mwah!
She's done.
Bye, great party!
And, uh, congratulations!
Marco,
what took you so long?
You missed
the whole party.
Yes, and where is
the glacier ice?
What? Oh, uh,
they were all sold out... of it.
Oh, I see.
I know I'm not always here,
so I got Marco Jr. this gift
to make up for it.
Aw, how sweet.
Aw, how nice.
You got us a...
-painting!
-Ohh!
You paid money
for that?
What are you talking about?
Whoa-ho-ho!
What the heck?!
This doesn't
look like me at all!
It's like he got
the proportions all wrong
and then tried to fix it
by adding more detail
and more detail
and more detail.
But, Marco,
it did not fix it.
Well, it was a nice thought.
And then just as I
take off Marco's diaper,
he pee-pees
all over my shirt!
-[all laughing]
-Remember?
C'mon, Marco,
I thought you loved it
when Dad told stories
about when you were a baby.
No, I'm fine.
Uh, Marco, what's
that on your face?
Huh? Oh.
Did I get it?
Um... yeah,
no, no, not exactly.
Marco?
Your face!
It looks like-- [gasps]
It looks
like the painting!
Oh! Ha ha, guys. I get it,
the portrait stinks,
but, y'know,
I was just trying to do
something that Marco Jr.
could remember me by
when I was-- mrrf mrrf mrrf.
[mumbling]
[garbled]
What's happening?
[whimpering]
What's happening?!
Oh, I knew it was a bad idea
to rush a magical portrait!
[mumbled shouting]
Marco, don't use
that kind of language
at the table.
[mumbles sadly]
Oh! Maybe if we destroy
the painting,
it will break the spell.
[Star]
Laser-beam blast!
Anything?
I think it's getting worse?
[mumbled]
It's getting worse?!
Well, guess there's
only one thing left to do.
[Cobalt]
Very nice.
Now if you could just turn
your cheek a little to the--
[Star] Cobalt!
Look what your painting
did to Marco's face.
[speaking angrily]
It's getting worse!
The painting
is just a reflection
of his answers
in the Essence Test,
and if there's
any discrepancies,
the painting will adjust
you to match the portrait.
No extra charge!
Okay, there's gotta be
some way to fix this.
We tried destroying
the painting,
but that didn't work.
True art can never
be destroyed. [chuckles]
You'll need to take
the Essence Test again,
and you must answer
the questions truthfully.
[mumbling]
[cracking]
[dramatic music playing]
I got it!
What the...
[cracking]
[whimpering]
Oh, no! He can't take
the exam like that!
C'mon!
Don't worry, we'll
take the test for you.
After all who understands
the mind of a teenage boy
better than his own parents?
Mrmpf!
-[groans]
-[all screaming]
He's becoming the canvas.
You'd better hurry.
Okay! Question one--
"Which do you prefer to ride?
A: a bicycle B: a unicycle
C: a tricycle
D: a Dragoncyc--"
What's a Dragoncycle?
I don't know.
Remember
when Marco was little
and had that red tricycle?
[Mr. Diaz]
He loved that!
That's it!
The answer is C: tricycle!
Mrs. Diaz!
We don't have much time!
We have to be really careful
these answers are perfect!
That's what we're doing!
If you could get off
the [straining] sheet!
-Oi!
-Sorry, dear!
I am not bleeding.
It is okay.
That's great!
But I don't know
if your answers
really capture
the Marco of today.
Of course not.
The Marco of today
is very frightening.
[whimpering]
No, I just mean
he's grown up--
Sure,
but I know my own son.
Sorry, but The answer
is D: Dragoncycle.
Marco?
[sadly]
Mrf. Uh-huh.
Oh, I was wrong
about my own son?
This is sad.
Star, get this test done.
All right,
let's do this thing.
Okay.
"How old are you?
A: zero to 15
B: 16 to 25
C: 26 to 35."
-Um...
-Hmm...
You two have
some catching up to do.
Okay, "Have you ever worn
a dress? A: Yes.
Do you prefer cornshakes
or corn malts?"
Malts, duh. Next question.
And, done!
[panting]
Huh?
Oh, Marco,
you're beautiful again!
Thanks, Star.
Mom, Dad?
I guess we have
some catching up to do.
My beautiful son
is all grown up!
I should
have visited more.
I don't want Marco Jr. growing
up without knowing who I am.
Visit anytime, sweetie.
I mean,
those scissors work
both ways, right?
Snip, snip?
This is
a beautiful family moment.
And I just happen to be runnin'
a special on family portraits.
Uh... that'll be a no!
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Ohh,
there goes a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining sta-a-r ♪