♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Mmmm.
Hm.
Oh, just eat one already!
There's only ever
one chip worth eating.
Besides, if this is
too boring,
you could be practicing
your magic.
Fine!
What are we
learning today?
Why don't you pick one?
Pick anything.
And my mom would
be cool with that?
Yes, there's a lot I do
that your mom isn't cool with.
Well, how cool would she be
with this?
( evil laughter )
The table of contents?
A thrilling choice.
Why is that
in the middle?
- Ehhh?
- Pedestrian.
- Ehh?
- Boring.
- ( barks )
( laughs )
The perfect chip.
What's this?!
- Oh, no, no.
- Hey, you said anything.
It's the most dangerous
chapter in the book.
It shouldn't even
be in there.
Your mom would
totally freak out.
Okay, okay,
you sold me.
I wanna read that.
Oh, I don't
know, Star.
It could taint you.
Perfect chip!
Unlock it.
Hostage-taking.
Classic Butterfly.
Unlock it or else.
- You wouldn't.
- Uh-uh-uh.
Okay, okay.
Chip.
( crunching loudly )
Okay, so...
- Yes, yes, but, um...
- Hey!
This wasn't the deal.
Oh, well, I'm so sorry.
But you're without
your bargaining chip.
Fine. I am standing here.
Open it.
Now, I'm going to show you,
for a split second.
( loud buzzing )
Bureaucracy of Magic.
Yes, this is he.
- Tell 'em you're busy.
- Kind of a bad time.
- Are you listening to me?
- You're busy right now.
- This is not a good time.
This is the worst time.
- Star, I'll be right back.
- Just hang up.
Don't turn the page.
( shrieking )
Uh, Glossaryck?
Oh, hi, Mr. Glossaryck.
Sir?
Sean. Oh.
Sorry. The transporter's
on the fritz today.
But there's free muffins
in the lobby.
Look, Sean, I was
in the middle of something,
and it was of
ultra cosmic importance.
Yeah, but you see,
the Magic High Commission
wants to see you, too, and...
( laughing )
Uh, is everything
all right?
I don't know.
Is everything all right?
Did you get on the right flight?
Are you running late?
Are you cracked,
are you confused?
Are you mad?
( blubbering )
Oh, Mr. Glossaryck,
you're so crazy.
But you still have
to go up and see
the Magic High Commission.
Hand me your radio.
( loud blaring sound )
Radio's on the fritz, too.
You're gonna
have to go up.
Very well.
Great. Up the elevator,
all the way to the top.
Wait, wait, wait.
No magic in the building.
You'll have to walk.
Fine.
Have a magical day.
Glossaryck.
Glossaryck, Glossaryck,
He is not waking up.
Time to call Mom.
Uh, never mind.
Please step through
the magical detection machine.
Oh, come on.
Are you carrying any articles
of magic, sorcery,
or occult objects
of a mystical nature?
Uh... no.
Just step this way, please.
- ( beeps )
- Thank you.
Okay, Mr. Glossaryck.
Your turn.
( alarm blaring )
Wait. Hold on.
Are you kidding?
That other guy
just walked right through.
Technology, right?
I miss
the simpler days.
I think
we're done here.
- Have a magical...
- ( alarm sounds )
Sean, work with me, please.
Cosmic ultra importance.
( beeps )
( alarms sounding )
That stays with me.
Hello. Hold the elevator.
Oh, hey, Mr. Glossaryck.
Which floor?
We've done this.
Top floor.
Uh, what's going on?
The elevator's not moving.
Uh, elevator's
on the fritz, too.
Sorry.
But there's muffins
in the lobby.
Which part of "cosmic
ultra importance"
do you not understand?
( bell dings )
Now we have to stop on
every floor.
( maniacal laughter )
Sean. Stairs.
( exhausted sigh )
( panting )
Hey, Star, check it out.
I'm getting my first
chest hair.
It's pretty small,
but if you look at it
in just the right light...
Uh, Glossaryck?
What's up with him?
He's on the fritz.
Wait a sec.
Are you doing something
you're not supposed to?
Glossaryck said
not to turn the page.
But he didn't say
you couldn't.
( panting and muttering )
Stairs are
on the fritz, too.
( angry groaning )
Now, now,
Mr. Glossaryck.
No magic in the building.
You're probably wondering
why you're here.
Children, the only thing
I wonder
is why you waste my time.
Don't call me children.
You're the children.
I've got chest diamonds
bigger than you.
Rhombulus.
Rhombulus, you still mad
about my last visit?
( bleating )
Excuse me, sorry.
Don't mean to be rude.
Getting stronger, though,
huh? That's good.
You always do this!
So you bring me here
while I'm at work.
Doing my job.
Yes, Glossaryck.
That's exactly what
we're here to talk about.
My liege.
The commission
has discovered a problem.
Something somewhere
is sapping the power of magic
from the universe.
Yes, that would explain
the fritz.
That's what I've
been saying.
Hey, the time-out corner
is not on the fritz.
Stupid Glossaryck.
Stupid time out.
Omnitraxus has been
searching for the leak's cause.
Omnitraxus, what have
you learned?
- ( muffled speaking )
- Hello!
Omni?
Can you hear me?
- Check the inputs.
- You out.
Yeah, whatever.
I'll crystallize myself.
Would you miss me? No.
( bleating )
Whatever's causing it,
I want everyone
to be on their toes.
Especially Star.
I need you to accelerate
her training.
Yeah... no.
Why all the riddles?
You were always very direct
when you were training me.
Well, it finally happened.
Every queen wants to tell me
how to do my job.
"My training was different."
You know what
Glossaryck hears?
Me-me-me-me-me!
"I'm going to pull my mentor
away from his job
so I can be in
the spotlight again."
The only Butterfly
to leave me be
was your great-great-great
great-great-great-great
great-grandmother,
Eclipsa,
the queen of darkness,
whose chapter, coincidentally,
you left Star alone with
when you pulled me into
this wonderland of red tape.
Turn the page,
turn the page!
I'm gonna turn
the page.
Turn the page, Marco!
( anguished bleating )
You all did this because
you don't trust me,
and what's worse,
you don't trust Star.
My queen. My queen,
your training was different
because Star is different.
You have to have faith in her
to make choices
that are best for her.
And my job
is to train Star
to be a queen.
Oh!
- So?
- Yeah.
You read the whole thing?
Yeah.
And?
It wasn't all that.
I mean, I get it.
Power of darkness,
forces of evil,
eternal suffering,
blah, blah, blah.
But honestly, didn't
really affect me that much.
- Just wasn't my thing.
- Yes!
But Marco,
on the other hand.
Yikes.
( evil muttering )
Luckily, there's
a spell
to fix that.
Oh, Minnesota.
Fancy.
Okay, you got this.
Today is the day.
- Hey, Marco.
- ( gasps )
Today is the day
for what?
Oh, uh...
Today is the day...
I was going to
ask you a question.
Okay.
Jackie, I was wondering
if you'd like to go out
and get me some paper towels
for Marco's sweaty pits.
- Uh...
- No, no, no, no!
That is not
what I meant to say.
What I meant to say is,
the sweat is gushing
down Marco's back
- like a waterfall.
- ( nervous laugh )
Now it's crossing the border
into Marco's undies.
Aaaah!
Okay, well, Jackie
is going to go now
and get Marco
some paper towels
for his wet body.
( whimpers )
That was so stupid!
Hey, hey, now, Marco.
It's not
that big a deal.
I heard what happened.
Everyone's talking about it.
Well, looks like you should
just give up on dating forever.
Thanks for
the vote of confidence.
I'm not gonna let
being tongue-tied stop me.
Pen me.
Jackie, will you
go out with me Friday night?
Hey, uh, Jackie.
Oh, hey,
there you are.
I got your paper towels.
Oh, uh...
( nervous giggle )
Thanks. Here's
some paper for you.
"Marco can't grow
hair on his chin,
but he can
on his back"?!
- Ha!
- What?!
( reading quickly )
( giggling )
Bro, my jacket.
Oh, sorry, Chet.
No worries. It's just
a material possession.
Marco thinks Chet
should punch him.
- What?
- No, no, no.
I mean,
if Marco were Chet,
he'd totally punch Marco.
It's just a jacket, dude.
Marco would lose
all respect for Chet
if Chet didn't
punch Marco.
Don't... don't make me
do this, bro.
What happened
in there?
I don't know
what got into me.
Every time I'm
around Jackie,
I keep blurting out
the wrong thing.
Every night when
Marco goes to sleep,
he shapes his pillow in the form
of Jackie Lynn Thomas.
and kisses it
good night.
Did you say something?
( muffled speaking )
( groaning )
Marco,
what's happening?
Wait. Let's see
where this goes.
( anguished screaming )
( all gasping )
Hello.
( yelps )
Oh, you made
a little Marco Junior.
'Sup, Marco Junior?
Janna, that's not his hand.
That's...
Oh, oh, oh.
Marco Diaz covers the mirror
when he showers,
because, because, because,
because Marco is ashamed
of his own body!
Oh, it's
so adorable.
Are you crazy?!
How am I ever gonna
ask out Jackie like this?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Did any of you get
the English homework assignment?
Marco thinks...
Oh, I can
show you, Jackie.
Come with me.
That's it. I remember
where I've seen you before.
Hey, where'd you get
my combination?
From your diary.
What is
that stuff?
Just some of
my personal things.
I've seen Marco Junior
somewhere before.
Stop calling
it that!
Here. The Naysaya.
"The Naysay grows out of
the neck of its victim."
Yes, that is Naysaya
when Naysaya was younger.
"It reveals itself when
the afflicted
attempts to woo
their true love,
exposing the victim's
deepest, darkest secrets
for all to hear."
And to judge.
What the heck
is that thing?
JANNA: Oh, that's a demon.
The Naysaya is
a total demon curse.
( groans )
A demon.
Dude, I'm so sorry.
I totally put
that curse on you
to prevent you from
asking out Star.
Why would you do
something like that?
That was before
we started hanging out.
You haven't asked out a girl
since the Blood Moon Ball?
That's way more embarrassing
than that thing on your neck.
How do I
get rid of it?
Just let it
run its course.
Once it's shouted
all your worst,
most shameful secrets,
it'll wear off.
And how long
will that take?
It depends.
How insecure are you?
Oh, no.
Good luck, dude.
( knocking on door )
STAR: Marco?
What did Tom say?
Tom says Marco will have Naysaya
for the rest of his life,
because, because, because
Marco is so insecure.
You should
get back to school.
You're missing class.
Well, aren't you coming, too?
I won't be going
to school anymore.
What?
Marco, it's just
a demon curse.
Don't let Naysaya keep you
from what you want.
( sighs )
Okay.
The door is cutting off
the circulation to my finger,
so I better get going.
Ooh, tingly.
She's a good friend.
All right, dude,
what do you want
to keep your mouth shut?
What?
What do you want?
Marco wants to know
what Naysaya wants?
But no one has ever
asked what Naysaya wants.
Well, dude,
it's your lucky day.
What do you want?
May Naysaya have
whatever he pleases?
As long as you let me
ask Jackie out,
you can have
whatever you want.
Then Naysaya would like...
cereal.
Seriously?
You can have cereal.
But... but...
Naysaya would like
to enjoy cereal
in Naysaya's own mouth.
Ahhhh.
Will... will...
will it hurt?
Just make sure you chew
with your teeth.
Some more.
Some more!
Okay, so you promise
to keep your mouth shut, right?
( swallowing )
Naysaya is in your corner.
( bell rings )
That is so cute,
you guys.
( sighs deeply )
Hey, Jackie.
Look. Is that Marco?
He's going for it.
Hey, Marco.
Are you cold?
What's going on here
with the scarf?
Oh, you know,
sometimes I...
ski to school.
No way! I snowboard.
Awesome!
Yeah, yeah, there's probably
a lot of stuff
you don't know about me.
That's why I thought
it would be cool
if we, uh, if we,
if you and I, if we...
went on a...
Oh, oh, oh,
this is the Jacqueline
Marco practiced asking out
in the mirror. Oh!
Marco even pretend-kissed you
with his own... reflection.
Naysaya, you promised
you wouldn't do that.
What's a promise?
Look, I gotta go home.
You're... you're
really confusing me.
Jackie, wait!
It's not me
saying this stuff.
It's him.
- Greetings, Jacqueline.
- ( gasps )
That is disgusting.
Is that
a British accent?
Jackie, there's nothing
I can do.
Got this curse thing
on my neck.
But I'd still like
to ask--
Marco hasn't taken a bath
since he saw
that shark movie.
He's right.
I haven't taken a bath
since I saw that shark movie.
I mean, I take showers.
I'm just afraid
of the tub.
Oh, oh, oh,
and Marco wears...
I wear ballet shoes
around the house.
And he never held hands--
I never held hands
with a girl.
- So I practiced
with Ferguson.
- And, and, and--
I always sit
when I go to the bathroom
What? Come on,
there's ladies in the house.
I cry when it rains.
I still got my wubbie
and his name is Esteban.
Until last week, I thought
that the state of mind
was between
Nebraska and Kansas.
I'm a straight-A student,
and I've still got no idea
how to do long division.
Go ahead, someone
yell out a division.
BOY: 724 divided by 7.
I got no idea.
Get a calculator.
Yes, but Marco--
I filled a notebook
with my first name
and your last name,
because I couldn't decide
which looked better--
Marco Diaz Lynne Thomas,
or Marco Lynne Thomas Diaz.
- Oh, oh...
- Oh, yeah,
and another thing.
I kept this drawing
you made of the moon.
I pulled it out of
the trash in art class.
That's supposed to be
a watermelon.
Oh, really?
Looks like a moon.
Well, your watermelon
reminds me of my biggest
fear of all--
that we're all alone
on this tiny blue marble,
floating in the infinite
expanse of the universe,
ripped from the center,
and ejected out
into a black void
for no reason at all.
Players on the stage
of the absurd.
Wow, that was
really... deep.
So there it is, Jackie Lynne.
That's it.
That's all my insecurities.
You know everything now.
Unless I left
anything out.
No, Marco, that's...
everything.
I still think it'd be
really great
if we hung out
Friday night.
Whoo!
You know, a group of us
are all going to a movie
Friday night.
You should totally come.
That would be awesome.
Cool. Well, see you then.
You did it, you did it,
you did it, you did it!
You did it,
you did it!
You know who to call
when you get divorced, Marco.
So, curse fulfilled,
right?
How's this work? You just kinda
dry up, flake off?
You know, Naysaya has never
been to the movies.
Ah!
Don't open the door.
It's not the milkman.
( screaming )
Oh, Marco's very nervous
right now.
After the movie,
you gotta go.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪