♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Honey, you've got to try
the jumbo megafowl.
It's so moist.
It just melts
in your mouth.
You haven't touched
a thing.
What's wrong?
( sighs heavily )
I just can't stop thinking
about what happened to
Glossaryck.
So? He's gone.
Good riddance, I say.
Little guy always
creeped me out.
But Star is all alone
on Earth now
at a crucial point
in her training.
We may need to consider...
bringing her back to Mewni.
What?
Oh, but she's in
the middle of school.
We can't disrupt
her life like that.
Then that leaves us no choice
but to have her evaluated.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
What other options
do we have?
I can't stand
that stupid...
I say no.
No!
Curse you,
you wretched monster!
No, no, no, wait.
Can we talk about this?
I don't wanna go
in the secret closet.
Why is everything
such a mess?
No, Star.
No, no, no!
Oh, hey, Star...
It's time for you
to hide now.
Mystic room
suck transform!
Food's ready.
Great. Put it
on the table.
Whoa. Why is your room
so clean?
I have to make
a good impression.
Not a chew toy.
I'm not ready.
Can't believe
this is happening.
Ready for what?
Being e-v-a-l-u-a-t-e-d.
E-v... Ooh!
Evaluated.
Wait, why are we spelling words
instead of saying them?
Yeah, that sounded
kinda weird when
it came out of my mouth.
Anyway, my mom
is sending someone
to see how far along
in my magic training I am
since I got to Earth.
( nervous giggle )
That doesn't sound so bad.
Oh, sweet, simple Marco.
- If I fail, I could get
sent back to Mewni.
- What?!
Which is why I need to clean,
and you need to cook.
Whoa!
It's her!
- Hello.
- BOTH: Awww.
I'm here to evaluate
a one Star Butterfly.
I'm a one
Star Butterfly.
And you must be Baby.
Oh. Food.
Yes, I prepared this spread
for you, Miss Baby.
Please help yourself...
More, please.
That took me
all day to make.
Please.
I would love
to make you more.
So, Your Baby-ness,
how does
this evaluation work?
How do you think
it should work?
Uh, I don't know.
I could show you my room.
Okay.
So, this
is my room.
Really?
Oh, yeah, and it's
pretty much always
this clean.
I'm super organized.
- What's that?
- What's what?
Oh, that!
You were supposed to hide.
Oh, that's just Beanbag.
Come say hi, Beanbag.
Beanbag, say hi to Baby.
Uh, crud.
Hmm. Interesting.
( nervous laugh )
Uh, yeah. Totally.
Hey, maybe we should go
downstairs and check on Marco.
You know, see how
the snacks are coming.
What's that?
Oh, oh, that.
Oh, no. ( chuckles )
No, nothing.
That's my secret closet.
Boring.
For things that, you know,
I don't want people to...
No, wait! Don't!
Interesting.
You... you think
that's interesting?
Oh, yes.
Very interesting.
Hey, Baby,
wanna see my wand?
Hm. It looks
so different from your mom's.
Yeah, it's cool, right?
Wait right there.
I have something
else to show you.
You're gonna
love it.
This is something I have
been working very hard on.
My own spell book.
Oh. That looks
interesting, too.
Really?
I made it myself.
Huh. Interesting.
Yeah, isn't it pretty?
I only used, like,
five pounds of glitter.
Who wants
refreshments?
How's it going?
Interesting.
What does that mean?
I don't know,
but go get more food.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
More food.
Now, Ms. Butterfly,
how is your spell casting?
My spells?
Oh, they're great.
My spells are awesome.
Good.
Would you bring me
that apple, please?
What apple?
- Oh, sure.
- No.
I mean, bring me
that apple, please,
with magic.
Oh, right. No, of course.
( blows raspberry )
Star.
Narwhal blast.
- Not quite.
- Oh, no?
I want a whole apple,
not an apple
with a hole.
Try again.
Oh! Oh, oh, oh.
Gotcha.
Oh, totally.
No problem at all.
Totally. That is totally
something I am capable of doing.
Winter storm hyper blow.
Did you want that
damaged or undamaged?
Undamaged it is.
Right, of course.
Makes sense.
Mystic suck portal.
All right, that's enough
practice.
Here it comes.
This time for real.
Wet ceiling.
( speaking indistinctly )
Okay, seriously.
I swear.
I can do this.
It just does that
sometimes.
Let me try again.
No need. I've seen
everything I need to see.
Thank you.
B-b-but, hey.
How'd I do?
Mm-hmm. Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, you failed.
Good-bye.
What? Failed?
So this was all
just a waste of time?
Princess, would you like me
to read you
the results of
my evaluation?
Let's see.
Tells me you have
a closet full of secrets.
But what does that
have to do with...
While under your care,
your wand,
the single most important
heirloom of the
Butterfly dynasty,
was broken.
You lost the sacred
book of spells,
and replaced it with
a college-ruled notebook.
And lastly,
your spell casting
is so undisciplined
and unstructured,
that you're incapable of
performing basic magic.
You can't even
bring me an apple.
Who wants sandwiches?
Get out!
Your Highness,
you failed.
No, no, no.
If I failed, that means
I have to go home.
That's not my problem.
Good-bye, princess.
It's perfect.
Does this mean
she gets to stay?
Ah! I knew
you'd do great.
Thanks, Marco.
( sighs )
Well, she has
a closet full of secrets,
a broken wand,
a notebook containing
her own spells,
and she doesn't know
basic magic.
So she failed.
Ow!
No, my queen.
Star is nowhere near
your skill level at her age.
She's far beyond it.
But I haven't seen
anything like this...
since Queen Eclipsa.
Monster love.
( gasps )
( yells )
Not now, puppy.
I should be safe
under here.
( barking )
What?
( growls )
Whee!
( groans )
( makes shooting noises )
I'll get you, tennis ball.
Hey, can I borrow your
dimensional scissors
for a second?
- Yeah, sure. Whatever.
- Thanks.
All right, guys.
Who's ready for
a walk?
Come on, puppies.
Whew. Problem solved.
Hmm.
Here you go.
Sir?
( belches )
Ah, feels good, man.
So far.
What?
Where did
you get these?
Seriously, fleshwad. Talk.
Uh, well,
I'm borrowing them
from a friend
who may or may not
be Star Butterfly.
Wrong answer.
I'm the forger of
all dimensional scissors.
Each pair is made specifically
for the entity who earns them.
Lady, I can't read that.
It's me.
That's my name.
Hek-a-poo.
Hekapoo.
You humans are lame
times a thousand.
Boop.
I don't care
whose name is on them.
I borrowed them
from Star and I'm
returning them.
And how do you propose
you're going to get them back?
Well, I'll earn them
like you said...
( laughing )
That's rich.
I'm serious.
I'll have you know
I have a red belt in karate.
This should be amazing.
Okay. All you have to do
is blow out this flame.
Really? No problem.
What the...
That's one.
Hey.
That's two.
( laughing )
Bye-bye.
HEKAPOO: She doesn't have
the scissors,
and you're gonna have to
blow out a whole lotta flames
to find them.
Are you looking for
these, dum-dum?
( all taunting )
Ow! You're burning me
a bald spot.
I don't have time for this.
HEKAPOO: It may take
days, months,
even lifetimes.
( laughs )
I don't think you have
the goods to do it.
Go home to your stinky
dirt rock, little boy.
I don't care
how long it takes.
I'm getting those scissors.
Oh, dang it.
Good boy, Joffrey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Rainbow diaper blast!
Not cool, bub.
Take it easy, man.
This new dog park
is really confusing.
Dog park?
Oh, Marco!
Why did you...
Oh, no.
He's gone scissor happy.
( dogs barking,
girl yelling )
Okay, puppies,
time to come home.
( barking )
Oh, Marco, Marco, Marco.
Oh!
Oh, this does not bode well.
( vibrating )
Hey, girl,
I'm doing my cardio.
Okay, hold up. I'm gonna
put it on an incline.
Okay, girl,
what's good?
Okay, so Marco opened
a bunch of portals
with my scissors and one
of them looks like this.
Oh, snap, that's bad!
Yeah, that's what I thought.
The red portal is Hekapoo.
You need to get away from it,
and if she asks,
you do not tell her you got
those scissors from me, okay?
Wait. I thought Hekapoo
gave you those scissors.
I mean, yeah, she left
the scissors in the bathroom
at the Bounce Lounge,
and what happened then
was I took them, so yeah,
basically, they're mine.
What? No, Pony,
that's stealing.
Uh, I'm pretty sure
that's called finding.
Okay, so is Marco in trouble?
You know what?
He's probably dead.
That Hekapoo chick
is crazy, man.
Oh, boy. All right,
I'll talk to you later, girl.
Bye-eee!
I'm coming, Marco.
( raucous squawk )
( sneezes )
- Dude, watch it.
- Sorry.
Oh, incoming!
Oh, dude, it's on.
Hey-yah!
Ha ha!
Oh, man.
So it all comes down
to this.
Sixteen years.
A lot of clones.
Seemed to go by...
( snaps fingers ) like that.
I finally tracked
you down, Hekapoo.
Yep, it's the real me.
No more clones, so...
Who's a little boy now?
This is the part where
you blow out my flame?
Ha. You barely escaped me
on the exploding
plains of Flendar.
When I lost your trail in
the mist of the Never Zone,
I thought
I'd never find you.
After spending a few years
infiltrating a cloister
of monks,
I acquired some ancient texts
which led me to
dimensional scholars
who taught me to translate
their language.
After that, it was
a simple matter of surviving
the Afflicted Forest
and ending up right
at your door.
Not bad for a human.
You truly earned these.
I underestimated you.
Hekapoo, where's Marco?
Star!
( groaning )
Unhand me,
beautiful stranger.
How do you know my name?
It's me, Marco.
See?
Marco?!
Marco!
Oh, man, we have
so much to catch up on.
I've learned how
to sword fight...
( Marco continues
indistinctly )
Then I jet-skied
off a waterfall.
- Isn't that cool?
- What?
Oh, check it out!
It took me 16 years,
but I totally earned
these scissors.
Wait, 16 years?
You've been gone from Earth
for, like, eight minutes.
Eight minutes?
Yeah, I forgot to tell you
that time passes differently
in this dimension.
Not sorry.
No, no, no.
This is good.
It means you haven't
missed anything
back on Earth.
Come on. Use your new scissors
to take us home.
Yeah, about that.
I don't think
I'm coming back.
Turns out I really like
my new life here.
I got my sword,
my dragon cycle.
I get to ride around all day
and go on adventures
whenever I want.
It's the journey,
you know.
Yeah, that dragon cycle
is really dope.
No, wait, wait.
What about your parents,
or your friends...
or me?
Don't look at me.
Those scissors are yours now.
You can come back here
any time you want.
Please. Take care of Nachos
while I'm gone.
She's in good hands.
Adios, boo-boo.
Well, old friend, you really
gave me a run for my money.
Likewise.
You're pretty cool.
( laughs )
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Later, H-poo.
Don't call me that!
( yells ) Oh.
No! My hot bod!
Where did it go?
Squish.
Oh, I guess you're back
on Earth's timeline now.
But look on
the bright side.
You still have
your bald spot.
Seriously?! That's the thing
that stayed the same?
( Hekapoo laughing )
You got the mark
of Hekapoo, son!
Okay, bye-bye.
Hey, who cares if
you're 14 again?
That just means we have
more time to go on
adventures together.
Especially now that you
have your own scissors.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
Of course I am.
Now I'm gonna go
make us some nachos.
"Password"?
I don't remember
my password.
( sighs )
Mmm. Still warm.
( barking
and whimpering )
All right.
Let's go for a walk.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪