♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh
Puh-puh-puh-puuuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
[snoring]
[sniffing] Ahh!
[muttering]
Aah! Ooh-eee! Aah!
Wha--?
[squeaking]
My wand.
Where's-- Where's my wand?
Aah! [grunts]
My hand is a wand?
A wand hand?
I have a wand... hand.
I-- I don't know if I like this.
Wait! I don't like this!
Glossaryck. Where's Glossaryck?
[Glossaryck] I'm right here.
I'm right where you left me.
Right here.
Glossaryck!
Oh, Glossaryck! They--
They turned my hand
into a wand, and you...
you into a pole.
[sobs]
[Glossaryck]
I am not a pole.
Huh?
I'm over here.
Hey-o!
Glossaryck!
[thud]
Where have you been?
What do you mean,
where have I been?
You told me to hide.
I hid!
[plop]
Oh, come on.
What?
I never told you to hide.
Wait. Now, which one of you
am I talking to right now?
Which one?
It's me! Ludo!
Oh, yes. It's you. Yeah.
All right, never mind.
What's going on?
Who trashed my house?
-Uh, you did.
-What?
You defeated
the Magic High Commission.
I did?
Well, not you.
Not you exactly, but, um...
I defeated
the Magic High Commission?
I can't believe it!
[gasps]
This needs to be a chapter
in the Book of Spells!
Then everyone will know
how powerful I am!
[humming sound]
Huh? What?
Butterfly Castle?
Oh, no, no, no, first I write
my chapter in the book,
then I'll take
over Butterfly Castle.
Now, where was I?
[straining]
There we go.
That's not going to work.
You see, only the owner can
write in the Book of Spells.
Yep, that's me,
I'm the owner.
Okay...
Should I write
in my normal handwriting
or try something
fun and fancy?
What should
I call my chapter?
"Ludo the Awesome"!
Mm-mmm.
Nah, nothin'.
"Ludo the Better
Than Everyone Else."
Ooh, yes!
I like the sound of that!
Eh?
No problem. No problem.
Just a little speed bump.
Aah!
I told you,
it's not your book anymore.
Hmph! Okay.
Maybe it just
needs a little space.
Yes, that's it.
I'll just come back
some other time.
[humming]
Aha!
[grunting]
Hah! Ooh ooh ooh!
[grunting and screaming]
Boo-yah!
[shouting]
I gotcha now!
[muttering]
So this is probably not one
of my favorite things
that's happened to me.
[screaming]
[growls]
Oh, I just
don't know anymore.
Is it more heat
and less pudding,
or less pudding and...
Oh, forget it.
Aah! Gotcha!
[Ludo] Ow!
-Hmm...
-Ow!
-[screams]
-Hmm.
Whoo! Aah!
Oh!
You will let me write in you!
[screaming in slow motion]
[groaning]
I hurt in places
I didn't know I had.
You know, there's a spell
in the book that would fix that.
Oh, wait.
Oh, oh, never mind.
Oh, give me a break!
A spell? Of course!
Why I didn't think
of this before!
[humming]
I wouldn't
do that if I were you.
Levitato!
[screaming]
[explosion]
Where am I?
Oh, thanks, Marion.
That's so nice
Barbra? My favorite.
[slurping]
Mmm. Oh, that really
hits the spot.
Say, you got any
of those tiny pillows
for behind my knees?
You know, girls,
it's funny,
I know this
is a bit lolo-- Ha!
but I can't remember
how I got here.
[laughing]
Huh?
That stupid book!
Yaah!
[angry muttering]
-Get my hands on you!
-[mooing]
[grunting]
Aah!
[growling]
So, what's that thing you said
about me not being the owner
of the book anymore? Hmm?
Yes. Well, that's, um...
That's the thing.
-What's the thing?
-The book thing.
You don't--
You don't own it anymore.
That's it.
But that doesn't
make any sense!
I took it!
It's right there!
How can it not be mine?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask the book?
-[pudding plops]
-Ohh!
Hmm.
Book! I demand
that you let me write
in you this instant,
or I'll turn this car
around so fast,
it'll make your head spin!
[groans]
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just that you have
something I want,
and you won't give it to me.
And I want it so much.
You and I aren't really
that different, you know?
We both like magic...
and, uh, other stuff.
What I'm trying to say is
I really appreciate you
and all you've done for me,
so if you're not letting me
write in you
because of something
I did or I said, I-I...
All right, I'm just going
to come right out and say it.
I love you, book.
I do! I love you.
And I'd be honored
if you let me write in you.
[Glossaryck laughing]
[clapping]
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
It's-- It's a book.
You cannot talk to the--
to the book.
[laughing]
I'm sorry. [laughing]
Ahh.
I thought you were in
on the, uh-- Oh, never mind.
Oh, yes. Funny?
Yes, I suppose it is.
Funny that I ever believed
you would take me seriously!
Funny that ugly little Ludo
wants to be
a mighty magical superstar.
What a joke, right?
Ha ha ha ha! Joke on me!
Star was always
your favorite, wasn't she?
The cute little sparkles
on the cheeks.
I'm just a sad little dingus
in a chip bag,
who you never believed in.
Well, if you don't
want me in your book,
then I don't
want me in it, either!
[grunting]
Well, Toffee, looks
like you finally got him
to do what you wanted.
I didn't want this.
This was all Ludo.
But now that you're gone,
I can finally get him
to do what I wanted.
I'd love to chat more,
but it looks like
you're out of time.
Hmm. You know, even though
I knew this was coming,
it's, uh...
it's still kind of a surprise.
Hey! Hey, look!
It worked!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Glossaryck? Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Glossaryck!
What have I done?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I--
No, no, no, no!
No, no, stop. Come back!
I didn't mean it!
[crying]
[humming]
Huh?
What do you mean
it's for the best?
Right.
The book was a distraction.
We don't need it anymore.
We don't need anyone anymore!
[wind whistling]
Butterfly Castle...
I'm coming for you.
[snoring]
Mmm. Good morning, Moon Pie.
[whimpering]
[deep breath]
[harpsicord music
playing]
-[segues to dance music]
- Let us revel!
Look out below!
-[cheering]
-Whoo-hoo!
Ha ha ha!
Hoo ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
[screeches]
Forward!
[screeching]
-[loud crashing]
-[River] Aha!
[monkey screeching]
[snoring]
[groans]
-[screeching]
-Get away.
-[dance music playing]
-Keep it going!
Ha ha ha ha!
Whoa-ho!
[exhausted cheering]
Hot Tub's outta water!
I need this!
Ha ha! Yaah!
[screeching]
[loud crashing]
[snoring]
Aha!
[screeches]
[chattering]
Oh, no.
Well, you're free now,
little monkey.
[chuckling]
[needle scratching]
Hey! Can someone
come and fix my thing?
Looks like I've got to go
wake somebody up.
FoolDuke!
-Wake up!
-[gasps]
Ah, FoolDuke, ha!
My music thing
isn't working.
I need you
to take a look at it.
Where's my monkey?
Oh. Oh, that
was your monkey?
Can't say that I've seen him.
Not to be rude,
but there are more pressing
matters, you see.
-[whirring]
-Uh.
Uh, Star?
Wow, this place is a mess.
Marco!
Oh, hey, River.
Marco, my boy!
I can't believe you're here!
[whispers] Have you seen
FoolDuke's monkey?
Uh... no.
Well, we better keep
an eye out.
-I threw him-- Uh?
-[crunching]
Well, what's this?
Oh, well, they were
Captain Blanche's Sugar Seeds.
It's, uh,
Star's favorite cereal.
You can't get them on Mewni,
so I brought her a box.
Marco, you're not giving
that to my daughter.
It's all smashed.
Probably a good thing
she's not here.
[groans]
Now there must be some other way
to summon forth the music.
We will rock at you.
Look, River, I gotta say
I'm pretty worried about Star.
She left Earth
in kind of a hurry.
She's not in trouble
or anything, right?
No, not at all!
She and her mother
just took a little trip,
and Moon Pie
asked me to keep up
morale in the kingdom
until they get back.
So we've been rippin' it
nonstop for days!
I-- I don't know, man.
Have you looked outside?
What do you mean,
"Have I looked outside?"
What I mean is, morale
doesn't look so high to me.
[townsfolk yelling]
What are you
talking about, Marco?
The people are happy
if their king is happy.
Let me show you.
Greetings,
my gleeful subjects!
[townsfolk grow quiet]
Huh?
Ah! Funny story!
My know-it-all friend,
Marco Diaz here,
seems to think you're
not having a good time.
And I said,
"That's impossible."
Of course
you're having a good time
with all these good times
I'm having.
So tell me,
are you not lifted?!
Whoo!
[Scottish accent]
How's about you lift
some of this garbage
out of the streets?
-[flies buzzing]
-Huh?
Huh?
Is that what that stuff is?
I thought you
were all having a garage sale.
What are
you gonna do about
the burning building?!
Ah, you have to let one burn
every once in a while.
How else will you
have room for a new one?
[cockney accent] Well,
what about the monster
in the cornfield?
-There's no monster
in the corn--
-[growling]
Huh.
Well, I'll be dipped.
Well, I should be able
to take care of that.
[knuckles crack]
Hey, you there!
Move along!
Scram! Get out!
[growling]
[River, faintly audible]
We don't want you here!
[footsteps thudding]
Don't worry!
She'll never make it past
the magic shield.
-[screaming]
-The beast cometh!
There's still the moat!
Yes. She'll never make it
across the magic moat!
The magic traffic cones?
We're about to die, y'all!
-Run!
-[townsfolk screaming]
Hey! Thanks for partyin' us
all to our deaths!
He's right.
I'm not fit to rule.
[stammering]
Uh, wait a minute.
[slams]
Hey!
[crying]
[pounding]
You locked me out!
Oh, no. Now I lock you
on the balcony.
It's okay.
Just unlock the door.
[crying]
I can't do anything right!
[sobbing] I can't
do anything right!
[straining]
Hey! Pull yourself
together, man!
Moon should never
have left me in charge.
"The people love you,"
she said.
"Keep them happy
and safe," she said.
And now, because of me,
the kingdom is defenseless!
[party horn toots]
Moon didn't even tell me
where she was taking Star.
What if something
happened to them?
No wonder I want
to party all the time.
I'm worried sick!
I'm worried, too.
Star just... left.
Do you have any idea
when she'll be back?
It's funny
you should ask, Marco.
Let me show you something.
Whenever Moon goes away,
she always puts together
a few outfits for me,
so I know what to wear
while she's gone.
But-- But look at this!
She's got them
piled up
all the way
to the top of the room.
[chuckles]
So it's probably
she's not coming back
anytime soon, is she, Marco?
[sobbing]
I don't know.
But they
can't ever come home
if they don't have
a home to come home to.
[growling]
Oh, right, yes,
I see what you're saying.
This is the end
of everything.
[whimpering]
No!
It means you have
to go lead your people.
But they hate me!
They've
never hated me before.
It doesn't matter.
You're the only king
they have.
You sound just like my wife.
And that's just what I need!
My people! Please, listen!
[screaming]
We all-- Ow!
Okay, I deserved that.
Look, if the Queen were here,
she'd fix all this
with her magic!
Well, she's not here!
But that doesn't mean
we should cower in fear.
We still have each other,
and together,
we can defeat this monster!
No offense, King,
but you're a terrible king!
You're right.
I stink at this.
But right now,
I'm all you've got,
and you're all I've got.
-[screaming]
-We can't do anything!
We don't have
any weapons or magic!
We don't need magic
to do extraordinary things.
Dentist! Construction worker!
Remember when you two
worked together
to dislodge that tooth-shaped
rock in the road?
Blacksmith! You worked
with the turtle sanctuary
to make iron shells
for the turtles in need!
[clanking]
And you two weirdos
hold the record
for the longest staring contest!
Wha--?
Whoo-hoo!
Aw, man, I lost!
We all can do something
unique and helpful,
and that's Mewni's
greatest strength!
And it's what Queen Moon
loves the most about all of you!
-[all agreeing]
-Yeah, we are pretty good!
Uh, I don't think
any of that's gonna
help us defeat the monster.
[footsteps thudding]
So what do you say?
Let's show that monster
what happens
when it messes with Mewmans!
[cheering]
Huh!
FoolDuke, fetch us
our loincloths!
What?
-Ha ha!
-[townsfolk shouting]
He's near!
Yeah, he's right there.
Hey, monster!
[growls]
Go away!
Go away?
But you're the one
who called me over.
What?
I didn't call you over.
Yes, you did.
You kept motioning,
"Come here, come here."
Oh, no. I was motioning,
"Go away, go away!"
Oh, no. That's,
"Come here, come here."
No, it's,
"Go away, go away!"
Ohh!
So you're telling me
I came all this way
for nothing?
I got, like, a thousand
splinters on this foot.
Help!
You might consider widening
the streets a little.
What a waste of my day.
[townsfolk cheering]
We did it!
Everyone, I'm holding
one final off-the-chain
party at the castle
in honor of all of you!
Three cheers
for King River!
Hip hip, hooray!
-Hip hip, hooray!
-[Ludo, late] Hooray!
-Hip Hip--
-Hooray!
Hip hip, hooray!
[rats squealing]
♪ She's a princess
Winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
The lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
A shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
Flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪