♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Hey, Marco.
Can I get your help
with something?
Can't help right now.
I just found out
there's a Mackie Hand
movie marathon tonight,
- and I can't miss it.
- Ooh. Who's Mackie Hand?
He's the greatest martial-arts
superstar who ever lived.
He died 30 years ago
while performing
one of his own stunts
on...
himself. Accidentally.
Come on, come on,
come on!
( inhales deeply )
Ooh!!
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's sold out.
Oh. I'm sorry,
little guy.
( muffled )
It's okay.
It was just a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
Don't worry. I'm sure
there's a chance you can
still get a ticket.
Good things
don't happen to me.
Hey. What's up?
- BOTH: Tom?
- What are you doing here?
Actually, I was wondering
if we could hang out.
Ugh. No, no, no.
A million times no.
Not with you, Star.
I meant with Marco.
Huh? Uh... no.
Oh. Okay then.
Guess I'll just find
somebody else
to go with to
the Mackie Hand movie marathon.
Huh? What?
Wait, you're a fan
of Mackie Hand?
I'm a super fan.
Why do you want
to go with me?
I really thought
we connected that one time.
Over ping-pong?
You kidnapped me.
Look, I know I've been
a little aggro in the past,
and I'm sorry.
I promise not to
get mad this time.
( grunting )
Star, what is he up to?
I think you should
go with him.
He's obviously trying
to bury the hammer
or whatever.
Hatchet.
Bury the hatchet.
Well, the marathon
is all the way
on the other side of town,
so... are you coming
or not?
Whoa!
Let me just
give you a tour.
Giddy up, skeleton horse.
( whinnies )
So here it is.
We got six
flat-screen TV's,
a photo booth,
karaoke machine.
- Is that a white tiger?
- ( purring loudly )
And up here
is the lounge.
Here. Have a seat
in the throne.
Are you comfortable?
Can I get you anything?
Some cereal perhaps?
Look, you're being
super nice to me right now,
and you're never
nice to me.
What's this really
all about?
Wha... I'm just
a huge fan
of Mackie Hand.
What's your favorite
Mackie Hand movie then?
Uh, it's...
( stammering )
I knew it.
You don't know the first
thing about kung-fu.
I'm outta here.
No, wait, wait.
It's just because
I have two favorites.
Hand To Hand To Hand,
and  Hand To Hand To Hand 2.
Now that I'm saying it,
I'm gonna have to go
with the original.
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
That is the best one.
But not the English version.
I'm talking about
the original in Swedish.
Huh. I guess you do
like stuff.
I'm... sorry.
No, no, no,
I get it, I get it.
It can be hard to
break through people's
preconceptions of me.
That's why I don't
have many friends.
I haven't even been to
a movie marathon before.
( engine revving )
Hey, where did you pick up
your sweet ride?
At a funeral home?
Are you gonna go pick up
someone's dead grandpa
and hold a respectful
service for him?
You think you guys
are fast?
I can guarantee that we'll
beat you to the next light
without even
breaking a sweat.
Yeah. What are ya,
chicken?
BOTH: What?!
- Bro.
- Bro!
- You're on, punk.
( tires squealing )
Oh, I'll show them.
No, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
( siren blaring,
police radio chatter )
Those guys are
going to jail.
( raucous laughter )
Oh, that was...
that was so much more fun
than obliterating people.
Yeah! This whole thing
reminds me of
one of my favorite songs,
"Awesome Feeling."
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that a song
by Love Sentence?
( humming song )
Uhhhh....
Yeah.
Come with me.
No way!
You have a signed picture
of you and Justin Towers?
I also have a vintage
five-disc CD player
with automatic shuffle.
♪ Awesome feeling ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna
take us down ♪
♪ At first
I turned my head ♪
♪ But then you really
turned my day around ♪
♪ Awesome feeling ♪
♪ We started out
as friendnemies ♪
♪ But found that
we have chemistry ♪
♪ And you were like
ooo-aa--ooo ♪
♪ And I was like
ooo-eee-ooo ♪
♪ White tiger's like
ooo-aaa--oooo ♪
♪ All right! ♪
( both laughing )
Man, I can't believe
I'm actually having
a good time with you.
I know. Right?
Heck, I could just skip
that whole movie marathon and--
Oh, my gosh.
The marathon.
- What time is it?
- Don't freak out.
It starts in...
ten minutes?!
What the heck?
Hey, can you unlock the door?
Actually, I can't
let you leave yet.
What? But we gotta go.
We're gonna be late.
Couldn't we just
chill here for, like,
another four-and-a-half
minutes?
No. Seriously,
let me go.
Please.
Just wait
a little longer.
What is wrong with you?
I said let me go!
And I said wait!
( whistle blows )
Sorry, Tom.
That's an instant fail
for you.
Hey, you almost made it
this time.
No, no.
Wait, wait.
You gotta give me
a second chance.
Okay, seriously,
what is going on here?
Dude, I cleaned
your litter box.
Well, Master Tom here
was just about to earn
his anger management
graduation badge.
All he had to do
was spend three hours alone
with the person
he hated the most
without blowing up.
But you,
you had to be selfish.
You could wait another
four minutes and 15 seconds.
All you care about are your
precious karate movie tickets.
- Well, guess what.
- ( gasps )
Mackie Hand movies
are garbage.
Are you kidding me?
You lied to me about
being a Mackie fan,
and pretended to be
my friend
so you could earn
some badge?
Dude, you're a jerk
and a liar,
and that's not even
the worst part.
I was dumb enough
to fall for it!
Marco, wait.
I do like Love Sentence.
That part wasn't a lie.
Too little,
too late.
Which is my second-favorite
Love Sentence song,
by the way.
♪ Oh, girl, you know
I never mean to hurt ya ♪
♪ When you're sad you know
I'd never desert ya ♪
♪ Mm-mmmm ♪
♪ You're my angel ♪
♪ My beautiful dove ♪
♪ We spiraled high
on a gust of love ♪
BOTH: ♪ And I knew
right from the start ♪
♪ Nothing could
tear us apart ♪
♪ Till the day
you broke my heart ♪
♪ And now it's
too little too late ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
( unintelligible chanting )
Eesh, what a drama queen.
It's... it's...
Mackie Hand!
I took quite a tumble there.
How long was I out?
I hope I didn't make us fall
too far behind
shooting schedule.
Mr. Hand, I can't believe
it's really you.
Say, you must be
the new PA.
Kevin, right?
Nice to meet you.
Oh, my gosh. I wish I had
something for you to sign.
Eh, don't sweat it.
I gotcha covered.
Hold still.
There you go.
Tom, I can't believe you brought
Mackie Hand back from the dead
just for me!
That was... that was
cool of you.
Wait, I'm dead?
Three for the Mackie Hand
marathon, please.
What does the sign say?
Wait, but... do you know
who this is?
This is  the  Mackie Hand
in the flesh.
Nice costume, but no one
gets in without a ticket.
Now shove off, grandpa,
before I have to get physical.
Hey! You!
You were right.
This guy's for real.
Yeah. I told you.
I still don't
like you, Tom.
like you, too, Marco.
Is mystery.
How is there hole
in Newman force field?
Maybe better question is,
who make hole?
They find weakness
in Newman magic.
Could be huge advantage
for all monsters.
Help my babies
have future.
You do realize that when
you're writing,
you're talking out loud.
Uh... oh, thank you.
I didn't realize I was...
( groaning )
Hey, rat,
what is this place?
( angry squealing )
( struggling )
There's only
one way outta here,
and it's through me.
Uh, okay, but I did not
ask to leave.
Nice try, pal,
but you're not gonna talk
your way outta here.
'Cause the only way...
out of here...
is through me.
Okay, but...
( groaning )
What is this?
( screaming )
( whistles )
Hm? Oh.
This could feed
a lot of monsters.
So where does all this
delicious corn go?
To the grinder.
Hey, stop the thing.
Why does he
have to yell?
Hands.
I will not.
Okay, I will.
Get to work,
frog man.
What are ya
waiting for?
Get moving!
So tell me,
where does all this corn go
after we grind it?
It goes in the hole.
Why?
'Cause if we don't,
we get thrown down that hole.
No. I mean,
where does it go
It goes in the hole.
Okay, we established that.
But then what?
Then we eat dinner.
No, the corn!
I'm talking about the corn!
Where does the corn go?
Oh, the corn.
It goes in the hole.
( frustrated stammering )
Yes, the corn goes
in the hole.
So you do know
where it goes then.
You know exactly
where it goes.
It goes in your pockets.
( nervous chuckle )
How did those kernels
get in there?
The boss doesn't look
kindly on those who
steal from him.
He wants to see you.
The boss wants
to see me?
- The... boss!
- ( screaming )
No, no, no!
Boss?
Hey, whoa, whoa, no need
to get the boss involved here.
It's just a few
kernels of corn.
No worries.
I got this.
Hey, I'll even make sure to
scream all the way down, okay?
Enjoy the rest of your day.
Bye!
( screaming )
( scream fades,
then resumes )
Must find out
who is boss.
No fun!
( snoring )
( laughing )
This guy has
own cornfield.
own cornfie...
Cornmeal.
( squeaking )
Unicastle...
made of corn?
Oh!
( gasps )
Know why they call me
Meat Fork?
Why?
Because it's
a family name.
I'm not going back
to grinder.
- No?
- No.
- No?!
No?!!
No.
Okay. Then can you please
take me with you?
Corn on the cob
or creamed corn?
Creamed corn.
- Creamed corn
or popcorn?
- Popcorn.
- Popcorn
or boiled corn?
- Popcorn.
- Popcorn or cornbread?
- Cornbread.
- Cornbread
or steamed corn?
- Cornbread.
- Cornbread or
roasted corn?
- Roasted corn.
- Roasted corn
or corned beef?
- There's no corn in...
Green hole.
Did you see that?
It worked!
( maniacal laughter )
Ludo!
Hello, Buffrog.
It's been a while...
old friend.
You're... alive.
Don't act so surprised.
It makes it seem like
you want me dead.
No, please.
I am father now.
I know that,
you idiot.
I'm the one who
gave you those...
You see, girls?
This is why I need that book.
Don't know what I'm
doing with this thing.
- Gotta go.
- He's getting away!
Just swallow it.
But I want him to die.
Uh, fine.
Spit him out.
I was going
to let you die,
but my wand told me to give
you Meat Fork's old job.
Meat Fork?
( groaning )
Yeah.
Meat Fork!
But you don't need
monsters now.
You have wand.
Spider, bird, corn.
Rats.
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
But you know,
there's more to be done.
So what do you say?
We gettin' the band
back together or what?
I'm... I'm sorry.
I think
you've lost your mind.
With wand, Ludo
more powerful than ever,
but more crazy
than ever, too.
He make Buffrog
intriguing offer.
But did I make
right choice for my tadpoles?
Have crazy idea,
but have to make sure
I'm not talking out loud first.
A big black bug
bit a big black bear.
Rubber baby buggy bumpers.
Okay, good.
Must warn Star.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪