♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Cupcake blast!
We've got them cornered.
[roaring]
[footsteps thudding]
How could I have
been so stupid?
[monsters roaring,
pounding on door]
Marco, what the heck
is going on?
This may be
all my fault.
What?! What did you...
What did you do?
Um...
Hold this.
- We're gonna need
to build some armor.
- Marco.
Okay, where does Dad
keep his blowtorch?
[roaring and crashing]
Ha ha, there it is.
Marco!
Marco Diaz!
What is going on?
Look, do you remember when I was
having that really bad day?
[panting]
Wait! Stop!
Look at you,
joggin' to school.
In the zone.
I'm tryin'
to catch the bus.
Keep your focus.
I get it.
Stay in that zone.
Who punched my bus?
Who does that?
Bus never did
nothin' to you.
Ow.
Oh... [laughs]
You kissed a ninja.
[laughter continues]
You have got
to be kidding me.
- School picture day?
- Smile.
[groans]
I wanna go home.
Well, well, well.
Marco Diaz.
Not today, Jeremy.
I came to give you
a black eye for picture day,
but apparently,
there's no need.
I said not today!
Marco, you broke
my skateboard.
- Ooh hoo hoo!
- Jackie, I...
It's fine, Marco.
I'll just live with it.
I think my work
here is done.
I'm sorry you had
a bad day, Marco,
but what does that
have to do with
right now?
I'm getting to that.
Thank you.
I was so bummed out.
You did everything you could
to cheer me up.
Ta-da!
[laughing]
A little fish.
[both laughing]
And then,
you met Oskar.
[screaming]
Make it stop!
No, no, no, no!
Skeeves.
Who is that
fresh of breath air?
Oh, that degenerate
is Oskar Greason.
I'd stay away
if I were you.
That boy
has a record.
Oh, a record.
[playing dissonant notes]
[tempo changes to
rhythmic percussion]
♪ My car is a flying snail ♪
♪ Let's ride him far away ♪
♪ Yeah, to mermaid pools
filled with puppies' drool ♪
♪ And centaurs
pulling candy sleighs ♪
Star!
Can you please keep your
fantasies out of my flashbacks?
- [monster pounding]
- Almost done.
Call me.
[sighs]
I couldn't wait
to talk to him.
I'm expecting
a phone call.
From Oskar.
Why don't you just
give him the home line?
Mmm, I like
your ringtone better.
♪ Space unicorn,
soaring through the stars ♪
[laughs]
So cute.
It's supposed
to be ironic.
- ♪ Space unicorns ♪
- Hello.
Hola, Marco,
it's Grandma.
[line disconnects]
- [monster growling]
- I guess I'm just
not cool enough
for a guy with a record.
Are you kidding?
You're the coolest
girl I know.
[loud pounding]
Anyway, you
were so sad.
It was my turn
to cheer you up.
- Hey, Star.
- [shrieks]
I thought you liked
clowns. Sorry.
Hey, Star, up here.
Ha ha, watch this.
I'm gonna...
[stammers]
I can't do this.
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[spits]
Ta-da!
And that's when
I realized
nothing makes you happier
than when you're
Narwhal blasting a monster.
So I tried to lure one
with your wand.
[sing-songy]
Oh, Star!
So you brought
these monsters here
- to cheer me up?
- Yeah.
I just didn't expect
so many.
But don't worry.
This armor
will hold them off.
[crashing]
Marco!
[shrieking]
Give it up,
Star Butterfly.
You're outmatched.
Ludo, what's with
all these
new monsters?
What? These are
all the same monsters
I always bring.
Mm, I don't know.
I've never seen
this dude in my life.
You mean you've never
met Man Arm?
Hey.
Surely you know
Spike Balls.
We were never
formally introduced.
Hi. I'm Spike Balls.
I'm usually
in the back.
Now that you all
know each other,
get the wand!
Put him in
the Tornado Swarm!
[monsters exclaiming]
I like that again.
You were right, Marco.
I am totally cheered up.
I don't even care
if Oskar calls.
[ringtone plays]
Space unicorn
Ugh, what is that
terrible ringtone?
It's supposed
to be ironic.
[gasps]
It's Oskar!
Well, talk to him.
Oh, right, right, right!
Hello.
Hi. I'm calling
this phone number
on my phone.
Thank you for calling.
- Hi.
[both]
So what are you...
Oh, I, I,
I interrupted you.
[roars]
Oh!
Oskar, can you
hold on for, like, one second?
Hey, I am
on the phone!
You monsters
are so rude!!
Syrup Tsunami Shockwave.
Sorry 'bout that.
[giggles]
Cool.
Okay, bye.
I like your phone voice.
[sighs]
Sticky.
Oh, sticky.
Mmm, thanks, Marco.
You did know
just how to cheer me up.
Oskar called anyway.
[giggles]
Hug.
Yuck.
Whoa.
[guffaws]
Perfect.
Hey, you know the rules.
Keep your stuff on
your side of the counter.
Is it that hard to just be
a little organized?
I'm organized.
My mess is here,
and, well,
that's pretty much
my system.
- [crackles, then fizzles]
- Huh?
What's wrong
with this thing?
Hm, let me check
under the hood.
[gasping and wheezing]
- Oh, no.
- [beeping]
Have you seen my charger?
I know it's
around here somewhere.
Where did you
last see it?
Where is that stupid thing?
Star, calm down.
Star!
This is why
you gotta get organized.
See, with my system,
nothing ever gets lost.
Nothing's ever
out of place.
This is serious.
You have to recharge wands
with magical energy.
If it goes to skull,
it'll be dead forever.
Can't you just buy
another charger?
[gasps]
Of course!
They sell them at
Quest Buy.
Quest Buy?
Come on!
Welcome to Quest Buy!
Attention,
Quest Buy shoppers.
We have a red-ticket
special.
Twenty-five percent off
all things that murder.
Why?! Ow!
- Whoa.
- Sample?
Either take a sample
or leave a sample.
- Up to you.
- Gross.
- [beeping]
- We gotta hurry.
You can talk to
the creepy salesman later.
Gnome repellent?
Extra-strength ghost heads?
How do you find anything
in this place?
It only looks messy.
Legend says that
the founders of Quest Buy
had an ancient cryptic
system of symbols they used
to organize the store.
Some have gone mad
trying to decipher it.
I finally got it!
Housewares is that way.
[laughing excitedly]
[whimpering]
If there's
a system here,
I'm gonna use it
to find the best route
to the charger department.
Lucky for you, I myself
know my way around here
pretty well myself,
if I do say so myself.
I think I just said
too many "myselfs."
Hey, boss,
look what I found.
We're not getting that.
Aw, but you'd look
so cute in it.
Stop trying to sneak
things into the cart.
Same goes for you.
I don't even know what that is.
Look, we're only here
because I need
an electric beak groomer.
Keeps the tip sharp
while brightening my smile.
Oh, clerk peasant.
Bring me your finest
beak groomer.
Sorry, that's not
my department.
I want the name
of your supervising wizard.
Halt!
Those who wish
to pass my lair,
answer my riddles
if you dare.
- I do not breathe--
- A leg.
- But I run.
- And jump.
- A leg!
And... wait. How could you
possibly know that?
- The internet.
- Internet?
You should look it up.
Now come on, come on.
- Open up.
- [sighs wearily]
Thank you.
You ever hear of
the internet, skeleton door?
[silence]
Okay, it should be
right through here.
Gnome repellent?
Extra-strength ghost heads?
We're right back
where we started.
How is this
even possible?
Let's see.
Made a right turn,
another right turn.
Another right turn,
then another right turn.
This makes no sense!
Well, well, well.
Looks like Quest Buy
really does have
everything a monster
could want.
- Ludo!
- Now hand over
that wand,
or there's going to be
a big clean-up on aisle...
uh, what aisle is this?
That's not my department.
Rainbow Avalanche!
Uh, just give me
a sec here.
Uh...
Narwhal Nightmare!
Get me that wand!
Big Boy Diaper Blast!
Oh, no.
This doesn't look
familiar at all.
You know what?
We tried this your way.
Now we're gonna try this
the organized way.
Hmmm.
I think I got it.
That elevator will take us
right to the charger department.
Come on.
Hold the door
there, folks.
Oh, close, close, close!
Thanks, guys.
There it is.
Don't worry, little wand.
We're almost there.
Told ya I'd get us there.
We stopped.
Sorry, folks,
this elevator's
no longer in service.
Welcome to
the booby trap department.
Please step carefully...
- [gasps]
- Don't help me up.
- I get workers' comp
for this.
- [elevator bell dings]
See ya later, guys.
Guys?
- Get 'em!
- [screams]
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Ow. Ow.
Look out.
Blades of doom.
Massacre darts.
A hallway with walls that
smash together periodically.
We made it.
There's so many chargers.
We'll never find
the right one in time.
Oh, yes, we will.
Because this time,
we're gonna get organized.
I'll figure this out.
You go hold off the monsters.
Right.
There she is.
You're not gonna tell
my boss about this, are you?
Well, well, well.
It looks like Mama's
havin' pork chops for supper.
[clucking angrily]
[yelling]
- [gasps]
- [ angry cluck]
Beak 'N' Trim.
I found it.
Ludo, I found it.
Marco, where are you?
I found the charger!
It took me a while,
but once I figured out
they were using
the metric system...
Just give me
the cock-a-doodie charger!
Yes! I got it!
Yes. I've got it!
Finally.
Evil is in
the palm of my hand.
Prince Blast Your Face Off!
Spinning Dizzy
Death Blast!
[frustrated groan]
Ka-pow!
What's wrong with
this thing?
[excited laughter]
[whinnies]
So cute.
Fantastic Exit Beam!
Are you gonna pay for
that charger, ma'am?
My arch-nemesis will cover it.
He kinda owes me.
- You do realize that
we could just walk?
- I know.
I had it right in
my claws.
So you're the one
who's paying for this mess?
Uh, I must've dropped
my wallet in the fight.
[nervous giggle]
[ferocious growl]
Ah, we're back.
You see, Star,
it pays to be organized.
- If you'd just
listened to me--
- Oh, shut it.
On Earth, it's rude
to tell people to shut it.
Yeah, that's rude
on Mewni, too. Look.
- My mini-vac.
- It's possessed.
- I'm gonna touch it.
- No, don't touch it.
Oh, she's touching it.
Just my charger.
My charger?!
Uh... whoops.
I must've accidentally
sucked it up
when I was cleaning. Sorry.
Guess you have two now.
Nah, you keep it.
I've got my wand.
You've got a magic
floating vacuum cleaner.
Now we're both cool.
Whoa!
[sighs]
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪