♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Ooh! Hey. Hmm.
Oh!
- Uh... ha ha!
- CROWD: Oooh!
There's a dessert
on that plate.
Hey, it's back!
( exclaiming )
- Witchcraft!
No, don't be scared.
These are... you're
supposed to like these.
These are trick candles.
You blow them out,
they come back.
- ( screaming )
- Oh.
( wheezing )
Don't be sad.
One hundred years from now,
I'll come back just...
like...
my... candles.
( horn honks )
( school bell rings )
Thanks for agreeing
to go with me tonight, Star.
Dances make me
a little anxious.
What are you
so worried about?
Well, I had a nightmare
that I came to the dance alone,
and everyone laughed
and threw tomatoes at me.
Then all my teeth fell out.
Oh, and then Jackie saw me,
and said I looked pasty.
That's not gonna happen.
- It'll be fine.
- ( Marco yells )
My leg. I can't
feel my leg!
- That's my leg.
- Oh. Sorry.
What happened?
I just saw a huge rat
in the air duct.
Yeah. This place
is a dump.
Star, come here.
Janna Banana!
Did you get it,
did you get it?
I made it.
( gasping )
Cake on a plate.
It's time to find out
if the legend is true.
Will Bon Bon come back?
BOTH: Just like his candles?
( laughter )
This séance
is gonna be epic.
I will see you
tonight at 7:00.
I'll see you tonight
at... wait, what?
Yeah, Bon Bon said he'd
be back on his 100th death day,
and that's tonight.
Oh, I thought it was
tomorrow.
I promised Marco
I'd be his dance buddy tonight.
His teeth might fall out
if he goes alone.
What are you gonna
remember more,
high school dance
or a dead clown séance?
Dead clown séance.
Marco!
Okay, see you later.
Marco! Marco, Marco, Marco!
( squealing )
Are you okay?
Jackie Lynne Thomas
just asked me to the dance.
And I said yes!
Wait! But you and I,
we were gonna go together.
No, no, Marco,
this is perfect.
I totally forgot that
I promised Janna
that I'd resurrect
a dead clown with her tonight.
So you should totally,
totally go with Jackie.
Really?
- Marco, clown séance.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
♪ ♪
Here we go.
One wipe, two wipe,
three wipe, four.
Five wipe, six wipe,
sweat no more.
Yeah, that's it.
A little dab'll do ya.
Whoa! Ugh!
What the heck?
Watch where
you're going, Marco.
Janna, what...
what are you doing here?
We just need a few more
supplies for our séance tonight.
Now my backside
smells like cologne.
Hey!
Ain't nothin'
wrong with that.
It's nice.
Yeah, it's nice.
- Stop smelling me!
- ( doorbell rings )
Oh, my gosh.
She's here!
Uh, okay, okay.
What am I doing?
Where's my...
where's my room?
Oh, yeah.
( stammering )
- Wanna say hi
to Jackie?
- Okay.
I'll get it.
- Me too, me too, me too!
Me too!
( both gasp )
Oh, hey, Angie,
hey, Star.
Come on in.
Oh, my gosh.
You look like the ocean.
( giggles )
Thanks.
Hey, Janna.
Hey.
MARCO: Hi, Jackie.
Ay, mijo.
♪ Darned if I knew ♪
♪ That I'd find you ♪
♪ In the last place
I thought you would be ♪
You look amazing.
You, too.
A-plus!
( giggles )
Uh... sorry.
Smell his butt.
You'll thank me later.
Oh, Star, please take a photo
of my handsome son
and his beautiful date.
Sure.
Uh, smile.
♪ And if I catch your eye ♪
♪ It feels like
I could fly ♪
♪ ♪
MOM: Bye, sweetie.
Come on, Star.
Let's go.
( Mom screams )
So where's this ghost?
Glossaryck?
What are you doing here?
Is that a joke?
Dead clown séance?!
Now lead the way.
I like your natural
headlamp, Glossaryck.
It's not natural,
but thank you.
JANNA: I wonder if
Bon Bon's skull still
has the clown nose on it.
Oh, no way. Maggots
would've eaten it by now.
Maggots don't eat plastic.
- Plastic?
- Yeah.
Glossaryck, all clowns
have plastic noses.
No. Real clowns
have meat noses.
Ugh. What do you
think, Star?
Don't you think it's weird
that Marco asked me
to the dance,
and then totally changed
his mind at the last minute?
That's, like, not cool,
right?
What?! No.
You told Marco
you didn't wanna go,
because you wanted
to see Bon Bon.
You do wanna see
Bon Bon, don't you?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
( tentatively )
Bon Bon.
Huh?
- Meat.
- Plastic.
Janna, Glossaryck,
check it out.
- "I will come back."
- BOTH: It's Bon Bon!
Uh, so, I was just
gonna ask.
What are your hobbies?
Oh, uh,
lots of stuff, I guess.
Skateboarding,
which you know.
I'm kinda into
history books.
I actually read
this really cool one about--
Hm, interesting.
What kind of music do you like?
Uh... I guess
pretty mellow stuff.
I know that's
totally vague.
Next question.
Do you like food?
If so what kinds?
Wait. Hold on.
You just wiped something
on your face.
- It's all...
- What?
It's all blue now.
- Here. Let me see that.
- No, no. No, no.
( sighs )
Dude, you don't need this.
Now come on.
Okay.
Okay, let's see
what's goin' on here.
There's hot wings girl.
Light bulb sisters.
Ugh. Looks like somebody
forgot to cancel
the basketball game.
Oh, there's Brad and Tammy.
They look happy.
Leave room for
Lady Decency.
Greetings, kids.
A corsage for the lady?
Thanks, but
we don't need one.
But it's mandatory.
Aw! It's crooked.
You are
such a disappointment.
( slapping sound )
I think I made
a mistake.
Huh? What do you mean?
I never should've
asked you to the dance.
( sighs )
Yeah. No, yeah, yeah.
I mean, you're right.
You're totally right.
Why would you go
with me to a dance?
I should've just
asked you on a date.
Huh?
Do you wanna go
on a date with me?
Yes... please.
Come on.
Let's get outta here.
( stammering )
♪ Bon Bon
the birthday clown ♪
♪ First he was dead ♪
♪ Maybe he's alive ♪
♪ Does he have a nose? ♪
♪ Maggots in his eyes ♪
Bam! If that don't say
welcome back, clown ghost,
nothing does.
How's the shrine
coming?
- Hey, Star?
- Huh?
The shrine,
how's it coming?
It's, uh, it's
comin' along.
Ugh, it's not.
Sorry, sorry.
My head's
totally loopy tonight.
Take your time, Star.
This'll be a long night.
So as long as we're all
just sitting here chillin',
would it be cool if I got
you guys' opinion on something?
Is this about
Marco again?
What? No.
Yes.
Could you please just
tell me what you think
of this one thing?
Uh, sure.
Notice anything
off about it?
See? Just because
Marco has a mole,
suddenly Jackie has to have,
like, eight of them.
Those are freckles.
GLOSSARYCK: Hey, Star.
Star. Star!
Yes, interrupter.
Are you gonna use this?
- What is it?
- I don't know.
It's, like, a spell.
There's a little drawing
of a rat or something.
Uh, we're kind of
in the middle of something.
So I can do whatever I...
Yeah, whatever. Go.
Oh, whoops. I accidentally
deleted the picture.
Problem solved?
Can we just focus
on the shrine now?
Yes. Shrine time.
Okay, got that?
All right.
- Now stir the cereal.
- Got it.
Stir, stir, stir,
stir, stir, stir.
And then, we add
one, just one,
malted milk ball.
One for me,
one for you.
Are you sure about this?
Jackie, trust the chef.
( laughs )
All right.
( choking )
Marco!
( coughing )
It's terrible.
( retches )
Really? It was good
the last time I had it.
Ugh. ( sputters )
( giggling )
( tentative laughter )
Your face.
( both laughing )
See, Marco?
You're adorable
when you laugh at yourself.
What?
Relax, dude.
I... I'm relaxed.
( stammering )
Seriously, why are you
so nervous?
Uh, I don't know.
'Cause it's a date,
and you're super cool,
and I'm just
afraid of messing up.
Marco, you already
messed up.
- What?
- Yeah.
You puked on my lap
in third grade.
You broke my skateboard.
And then there's
that weird box thing
- you got trapped in
at Star's sleepover.
- Okay, okay.
You sent me anonymous
text messages of cats.
All right.
Point taken.
Then there was
the little neck guy
that came out of
your neck or whatever.
Jackie, I don't wanna
relive that.
Fair enough.
But you know
what I like about you,
is that even after
a humiliating, crushing defeat,
you just pick yourself
right back up,
and you hop right back on,
kinda like skateboarding.
Yeah, well, I don't know
how to skateboard
- What?
- No, I never...
What are you doing?
Whoa! You just
keep that
down there?
- Well?
- No, no, no, no.
- Come on.
- No, no, no.
- Marco, you can do this.
- No, forget it.
Marco, do it for me?
Ugh. Okay.
I'm gonna do this.
Don't look down.
Don't look up.
( stammering )
- Do you trust me?
- Yeah, I trust...
Okay, I'm done.
( snoring )
Janna, wake up!
No, you shut up.
( groans )
I might as well be
spending the night alone
in a graveyard.
If any dead clowns feel like
coming back from the dead
I think now would be
a pretty good time.
Ugh! Should've just gone
to that stupid dance.
( beeps )
Bet Marco's
having a good time.
( dialing, line ringing )
( buzzing )
Hey, it's Marco.
I'm not here right now,
but leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Hey, Marco,
it's just me,
checkin' up on
my best bud.
Drop me a line
when you get home.
Just wanna
check up on you.
If you want to.
If not, that's...
that's cool, too.
Bye.
- ( groans )
- ( dialing )
Hey, it's Marco.
I'm not here right now...
- ( groans )
- ( dialing )
Hey, it's Marco.
I'm not here right now,
but leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Hey, it's Marco.
I'm not here right now,
but leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Hey, it's Marco...
( frustrated groan )
Why aren't you picking up?!
( snoring )
Glossaryck, wake up.
Hey, what's the name
of that spying spell?
( muttering )
Oh. The all-seeing eye,
uh, you're talking about.
- Where is it?
- That would be...
that would be in
Eclypso's chapter.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
You don't wanna go there.
Eclypso...
Dark magic. Not nice
to spy on people.
( laughs )
Glossaryck,
don't be ridiculous.
I'm not using it
to spy on anyone.
Spying leads to crying.
( snoring )
Well, I'm not spying.
( snoring continues )
Aha! Here it is.
I summon
the all-seeing eye
to tear a hole
into the sky.
Reveal to me
that which is hidden.
Unveil to me
what is forbidden.
Whoa!
Don't worry.
I've got you.
Oh!
( growls )
What?!
( yells )
What'd I miss?
- Did I do that?
- Yes, you fell on me.
I know I fell on you.
I was there for that.
There was this eyeball spell,
and Jackie and Marco--
Slow down, woman.
You are not making
any sense.
Shoo! Shoo, shoo.
Get out of here,
you giant rats.
It's happening.
You came back.
Oh, that explosion
did a real number on your face.
( maniacal laughter )
Surprise.
Ludo?
Miss me, princess?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Haven't ate it
like that
in years.
You know, I'm really glad
I asked you out.
Me, too.
Marco?
Is everything okay?
We have to find Star.
Get her, get her!
Shimmering crystal see-saw!
( screeching )
Get her!
Rainbow fist punch!
Syrup tsunami shockwave!
You guys
are ruining my séance.
Mega starfish tsunami!
Mystic Suck Portal.
Not again!
I'm back, just like my...
( screams )
Please have mercy on me.
I would have mercy on you.
JANNA: Help!
Bad vermin. Bad.
Janna.
Aw, looks like
you need a hand, princess.
What do you want with me?
You think I'm here for you.
So selfish.
Ha! Fetch!
- My spell book?
- Yes.
I figured it would be
okay if I took it,
seeing how you're
probably not going to need it
where you're going.
( evil laugh )
As the humans say,
destroying you
will be easy as pie.
I think you mean
piece of cake.
You will pay for that.
I'm on fire,
I'm on fire!
Put me out, put me out!
Oh, great job...
Fetch Spider.
We have what we want.
No, no, no, no!
( rats squeaking )
( straining )
Do you really wanna
waste precious time
chasing me?
I mean, look.
Star!
( Ludo cackling )
Marco, let go.
You're gonna
get pulled in, too.
I'm not letting go.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks to you.
Jackie, are you okay?
Yeah. I'm great.
This is the funnest dance
I've ever been to.
MARCO: Yeah, well, I mean, yeah,
we're in a graveyard, so...
I can't believe
Ludo took my spell book.
It's got everything
in it.
That's my whole
family history.
All the spells,
everything, it's lost.
We'll get it back.
I've lost Glossaryck.
We'll get him back, too.
I promise.
At your service, milady.
I'm not a milady.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪