♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Pretty crazy year, huh?
No more math.
Trying to find someone to give
me a ride to summer school.
So, I was, like,
"Look, Principal Skeeves,
I'll start wearing pants
when you start
winning gold medals."
Know what I mean?
( laughter )
Okay, don't move.
Aw, I dropped it again.
( yells )
( laughter )
Hey, Marco,
whatcha doin'?
Jackie, can I
ask you something?
Why are all these people
acting like everything's normal?
'Cause everything's normal.
Mm, you should try those.
They're delicious.
You know what?
You can have it.
I can't eat.
My gut's... ugh.
All... blah.
You know what I mean?
Is this all 'cause
you're embarrassed
of your parents?
Oh... oh... oh.
That's certainly
not helping, but... no.
Ugh!
Everything's just
all super weird
with Star.
I just want things
to be normal.
You're having
a Marco moment.
Uh, yeah, I'm
having a Marco moment.
Ha, yeah.
All right, well,
you can tell me
all about it
on the way
to the kitchen.
I want some more
of these little
hot dogs.
No.
( inhales deeply )
Be classy.
Hello, friends.
What's up, Star?
You having fun?
Oh, yeah.
Totally.
Hmm.
I just realized,
I have to go to the bathroom.
- Oh, uh...
- You two talk for a sec.
Be right back.
Um...
( both talking at once )
- Oh, sorry.
- No, please.
You go first.
What did you say?
( nervous laughter )
You look well.
Oh, thanks.
I brushed my hair.
Well, great
catching up.
Yeah. See ya around.
Buddy.
( forced laughter )
Whatever.
( both groaning )
Man!
Aww.
( groans )
So, yeah, those are
basically all of the reasons
why I will be
the most reliable
non-flaky
girlfriend ever.
- ( phone buzzing )
- I gotta go. Sorry.
Huh? Hey!
Here are the four lobsters
the young lady ordered.
( shrieking )
( phone buzzing )
Need a time out.
Something just came up.
Cool. Later, Kelly.
See you next week.
( sighs )
( heavy breathing )
Whoa, Starfan13,
you got here fast.
I was here
the whole time.
ALL: Eww!
WOMAN: Welcome to
Britta's Tacos.
May I take your order?
Time to rise and dine!
Uh, who are you?
Please don't take my organ.
Queen Moon?
What are you
doing here?
Give me that.
Where's Glossaryck?
Glossaryck?
Um, he's gone.
( gasps )
So now, Marco and I can
barely make eye contact
because of Roberiot's
dumb song.
I mean, Marco actually thinks
I have a crush on him.
( hysterical laughter )
Yeah, but like,
don't you, though?
What?! No!
- Okay, maybe once.
- ( gasps )
But I don't anymore.
Aww.
I just think
he's kinda cute.
I think lots of things
are cute.
Puppies are cute,
kitties are cute,
tiny peppers are cute--
Star, it's cool.
We believe you.
I just want things
to go back to normal.
What if they never
do, Kelly?
What if they never do?
Girl, don't freak out.
Maybe you two just
need some space.
Like me and Ted,
we're on our third
break this week.
Come on, Star.
Let's ditch this place,
and go to the party
the bad kids are having.
I heard it's
super dangerous.
Oh! Star, you know what?
You love danger.
That is true.
Boom, you're in.
Let's go.
What do you mean,
he's gone?
What did you do
with him?
I didn't do anything.
Glossaryck showed me
something in the spell book,
and next thing I know,
I wake up, and they're gone.
Oh, come on.
You stole the book.
Well, well, well,
Glossaryck said
the book is mine now.
How's that stealing?
And I think we can
all agree,
Glossaryck comes and goes
as he pleases.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
And I suppose
it's just a coincidence
that you've taken up
shelter here
in this ancient
monster temple.
I'm supposed to know that?
This place was empty,
so I moved in.
It's cold out there.
I'm wearing a chip bag,
for corn sake.
What about your wand?
You have half my family's
crystal embedded in it.
It doesn't even
work anymore.
If it's yours,
you can have it.
Face it.
You've got nothing
on me.
All right, this is
getting us nowhere.
Time for Plan B.
No. Wait.
No, we need to find
Glossaryck.
Oh, I...
I saw your family, Ludo.
My family?
Let me tell you about
my family.
ALL: Wow!
"See me after class."
See this after class,
Mr. Kimball.
Oh, burning homework.
So dangerous.
Is that legal?
Don't worry.
It's a controlled burn.
This is pretty cool, right?
Janna's having
a good time.
Burn, burn.
Yeah.
Oh, come on, B-Fly,
you need to loosen up.
Here. Throw this math quiz
into the fire.
Yeah, I don't
feel anything.
You guys were so awesome
to bring me here,
but I just don't think
I'm in a party mood.
No. I'm not like that.
You guys stay and have fun
with your controlled burn.
I'll see you
back at my place.
- Star.
- Huh?
Is that you?
Um... yeah. Maybe.
Do I know you?
It's me, Oskar.
I got a haircut.
Check it out.
Oskar?
You're not leaving
already, are you?
Uh...
- Oh, yeah.
- He's cute.
- Go for it.
( nervous laughter )
Hey, what are
we staring at?
Oh, nothing.
Just thinking about,
uh, stuff.
Marco, it's
the end of the year.
We don't have to
think about anything!
( both laughing )
Let's only think about
you, me, and what we're
gonna do this summer.
Now, what am
I thinking
right now?
Uh...
Come on, Marco.
Read my mind.
Imagine all the time
we'll save
if we learn to read
each other's minds.
Mmm...
You want me to kiss ya?
Um, no.
I just wanted you to
feed me pizza nuggets,
but hey, good first shot.
Now go get us
some pizza nuggets.
Hello. Welcome
to the world.
Oh, Marco,
how are you?
Feelin' pretty great, Dad.
Oh, that's good.
Hey, where's
your partner in crime?
Oh, Jackie?
I guess we are
pretty good partners.
Star, Marco.
I was talking about Star.
- Oh.
- Jackie is no criminal.
Star, however, now
she's a criminal.
I haven't heard
any explosions
or magic sounds.
Is she okay?
Well, uh...
things are a bit weird
between us right now.
What could be weird?
Two teenagers
sharing a home.
One boy, one girl.
Oh. Oh, no.
Well, if things are weird,
it's always good
to talk it out.
I feel great
talking right now,
- and I don't even
have a problem.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Now, go.
Get out.
- What?
I have to make
more pizza nuggets.
- Oh.
- Leave!
Oh, and then,
and then, and then,
when I was, like,
five years old,
my big brother Chudo
was walking me home
from the park,
and he stopped at
this old, burned-down castle,
and he said, "Well, looks like
the house burned down.
Guess we've got to
live outside now"
That must've been
difficult.
But I do know that
Dennis misses you.
He says hello.
How is he?
He's worried about
his big brother.
And so am I.
Worried about me?
Don't you get it?
I lost my army,
my kingdom, my clothes.
And look, still standing.
Yes, but for
how much longer?
You don't look
well, Ludo.
Tell me what's
going on,
and maybe I can
help you.
So I haven't seen you
at school in a while.
Yeah, I dropped out,
to pursue my music.
Oh, you just gonna
play that right now?
( synthesized
rock music plays )
You think maybe it'll
end up on Mars?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, Mars is
pretty far away.
What are you saying?
Oh, no, no.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe. Maybe it'll
end up on Mars.
See, Star, that's what
I like most about you.
You always
believed in me.
Oh, no, I...
I always do that wrong.
You know, that
fist punchy thingy.
What are you talking about?
You can't do it wrong.
Just do what you feel.
Is this okay?
Glossaryck?
Glossaryck!
Glossaryck.
Tell me where
he is!
- ( squeaking )
- You're a liar!
( bleating )
You found Glossaryck?
Blank!
That's not
the real book.
( all gasping )
( evil laughter )
- Ludo.
- Ludo's not here
right now.
But if you'd like,
you can leave a message.
You did not wanna
do that, little man...
That's it.
You can't keep doing that,
Chancellor.
Get him!
( weak bleating )
Chancellor! No!
Hello, Moon.
It's been a while.
Toffee.
( yells )
( laughs )
Tell Star...
I'm coming for my finger.
So you just say stuff
and magic comes out?
Yeah, pretty much.
I've even been creating
my own spells.
- Wanna see?
- Yeah, I'd be honored.
Okay, I haven't practiced
this one too much,
so if your body
explodes, whoops-a-doopsies!
That's a little
magic joke for you.
Oh.
( laughs nervously )
Okay.
( inhales )
Sparkle kitten
fireworks shower!
Whoa! It's beautiful.
Wow. What wonderful colors.
Hey, what's that?
( cats screeching,
people yelling )
Geez, I gotta stop
making cats.
( laughs )
Seriously, how have we
not hung out before?
Well, I'm usually
pretty busy,
fighting monsters
and stuff.
Oh, yeah, with
your buddy.
What's his name?
Mango.
It's always just
you and Mango.
Oh, Marco.
Yeah. Where's Mango?
Well, Mango's going out
with Jackie now,
so he'll probably have
less time to hang out with me.
Well, I'm not doing anything
this summer.
I'd make a great Mango.
Oh, uh...
Yeah.
( siren blaring )
This is the police.
You punks better be having
a study group up there.
I've never read
a book in my life.
That's it,
I'm calling your parents.
Everybody, run for it.
- Whoa.
- Hey, Star.
I had a great time
tonight.
I think we could have
an awesome summer together.
( nervous laughter )
- Yeah, maybe we could.
- Give me a call.
Good-bye.
Good work, Star.
Great work.
That's some
fine work.
You gals stop.
You know, maybe this summer
thing won't be that bad.
We're off to a pretty
great start already.
Yeah. I guess there's
just one thing to take care of.
Again.
All right, Star,
let's get awkward.
Okay, now do me.
Uh, hey, Marco.
Got a sec?
Star?
- I have to...
- We need to talk.
( both chuckle nervously )
Let's go somewhere
more quiet.
Okay.
( inhales deeply )
Marco, I know things
have been "different."
"Definitely different."
I wanted to talk to you
after Song Day,
but I feel like
we've been avoiding
each other.
Oh, I've definitely
been avoiding you.
Yeah, me, too.
I guess I just felt
scared that everything
would change,
and that you didn't
wanna be friends anymore,
and I miss the way
things used to be,
- and, and...
- Star.
I miss the way things
used to be, too.
( gasps )
You do?
Yeah. You're
my best friend.
But... but do you
have a crush on me?
Uh...
No. I don't.
But the song.
Marco, you're my friend,
and I just wanna have
an awesome summer
with my friend.
- Friend?
- Friend.
Well, maybe let's just
forget Song Day ever happened.
What's a Song Day?
That sounds like
a terrible day.
( chuckles )
You know, I think we deserve
a couple of months
where we just
don't do anything.
That sounds great.
Star, it's called summer,
and it's gonna
be great.
( whispers )
Great.
- How did this get here?
- Star!
Demon! Mom?
What... what are
you doing here?
I don't have time
to explain, but
suffice it to say,
we are in danger.
We must leave for
Mewni immediately.
What? Mom, no.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. No!
Yes, I'm afraid you have
no choice in the matter.
You sent me here,
and I didn't
have a choice,
and now, you're just
telling me to leave?
Star, this
is different.
Mom, I've learned that
I get to make choices here.
- I chose to fix things
with Marco.
- Star.
- I'm choosing to have
a crush on Oskar, I guess.
- Star.
And apparently, there's
this thing called "summer,"
- where you just don't
go to school.
- Star.
So I'm choosing
to stay here with--
- Star!
- I'm not changing
my mind.
- Star!
- What?!
Toffee has returned.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry,
Star,
but you need
to leave.
( sighs )
I need two minutes.
( shouting ) Marco!
Loud.
- Star?
- Marco, we need to talk,
just one last time.
Is everything okay?
You shouted pretty loud.
Everybody's just
staring at us.
Yeah, I know.
But some stuff
just came up,
and I've only got
a little time.
Wait. We got
the entire summer.
Marco, I don't know
how to tell you this,
- because you're
my best friend...
- Star?
and that makes this
super weird because--
- What's wrong?
- Because I...
I... I do have
a crush on you.
- ( all gasping )
- Who called it?
I called it.
Boom. I called it.
I didn't want to
admit it,
because I know you
don't feel the same way,
and I thought if I just
pretended the feelings
weren't there,
they'd go away,
but they haven't.
I have to leave Earth,
probably forever,
and I couldn't go
without telling you the truth.
Uh...
- I, uh...
- ( crying ) Good-bye!
Good-bye, everyone!
Star!
Hey!
What do you mean...
Star?