♪♪
[upbeat music plays]
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird,
gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here,
I'm from another-- woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puh-p-u-u-uh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[singing K-pop song
in Korean]
[speaking Korean]
[slurping]
Yeah, how's the girl
supposed to sing
with a cursed body bone?
[burps]
[speaking Korean]
[soft piano music playing]
Mmm, yeah,
I should get a pizza.
Or... Or...
I got an idea.
Why don't you pay me
for the pizza you
already ordered?
You're still here?
Just, like, put it
on my tab or whatever.
Yeah,
I'd love to do that.
The problem is, in order
to put it on your tab,
I need to see your I.D.
[clenching teeth]
It's at the end of the bed!
Uh, this isn't you.
The girl in this picture
has one of those, uh...
What uh?
Uh, fine, here.
Oh, yeah. There's
a weirdo looking
in your window
if you're interested.
[Star humming]
Huh? [panting, giggling]
Okay, guys, I can't
get her to look.
What's Plan B?
You're Plan B!
You need to get
back to that window
and get our sister
out of bed
so we got somethin'
to do, or else.
What, are you threatening me?
No, Star,
we would never threaten you.
[shudders]
All right, you guys
gotta stop doin' that.
Imagine... [sobbing]
...you woke up one day,
and you were so beautiful.
What are you talking about?
What are you
talking about?
All right,
so you know what?
We're goin' with my plan.
Should've done this
all along.
I'm gonna give her
some sweet treats
and just be nice to her.
Did you ever
think about that?
Is that all right
with you, Azniss?
Krysthalle?
Shonda and Shinda?
Where-- Where did
Shonda and Shinda go?
You know what?
I don't care.
I really don't.
[grunts]
Gimme the treats.
Unh!
Look what I got for you.
Ah! Oh, good Mewni,
what's that smell?
[sing-song]
Look, your favorite!
Kitten donuts.
[mewing]
Ooh, whatcha watchin'?
[speaking Korean]
Okay, Pony,
I'm just gonna say it.
You don't have a horn.
Heinous took it from you,
and that's awful.
But you gotta
pick yourself back up
and just move on.
-Don't touch that!
-[TV show playing]
What's the matter
with you?!
See, Star, we told you
she won't get out of bed!
Yeah, she's
being so difficult, uh!
Oh, and believe me,
we've tried everything.
Go away and let me
watch my show in peace!
[inhales]
[woman speaking Korean]
Oh, wow.
Hey, girls,
can we talk for a sec?
Come on. Maybe we should
give her a break.
I mean,
she's lost her horn.
She can't fly anymore.
Uh, excuse me,
I don't have horn,
-and I can fly just fine!
-[window opening]
Hmm!
[gasping] Pony!
[TV show continuing]
Hey, Boo, thanks for showin' up
on such short notice.
You're a good boyfriend.
Your satisfaction
is my number one priority.
Okay. Wow, all right.
Blah blah blah, uh-huh.
I understand you, okay.
Just get me
out of here, please!
[engine starts, tires screech.
[thunder]
Oh, no! She's driving
into that storm!
She's gonna die!
Girls, we gotta save her!
Huh!
Aaaah!
[scream diminishing]
Ugh! Oh, sorry.
Cloudy was
a lot further down
than I thought he was.
We gotta go!
[straining]
Ahhh.
[girls crying
on Korean TV show]
I'm sorry, but tampering
with company property
-is strictly prohibited.
-Shh! Keep it down!
You know the longer
your mouth is open,
the less I want
to be with you!
Uh... [gulp]
[crying continuing
on TV show]
It appears your friends
are following us.
Shall I pull over?
What?! Oh, no, no!
No, no! Lose 'em!
Step on it!
At Reflectacorp,
customer service is
our number one priority.
[speaking Korean]
[Ponyhead sniffling]
I-- I feel you, girl.
Your friends are faster
than Reflectacorp's
top utility van.
Uh! Then start throwing
something at them or whatever.
Geez!
Customer service is
our number one priority.
You're gonna have to do
better than that!
Your friends
are very persistent.
Deal with it!
It is my pleasure to find
you an adequate solution.
[loud bump]
[gasps] Ponyhead!
Oh, no!
My Ponyhead! Ponyhead!
Oh! [groans]
What the-- Ponyhead?!
[printer whirring]
3-D printing! Cool!
[thunder]
[Cloudy] Whee! Ha ha!
Whoo hoo hoo hoo!
This has gone too far!
Let me help you!
[melodramatic music
playing]
[bang]
[muffled] You can't run
away from your problems!
Are you listening?!
Ponyhead!
Come on! Let's end this
and go home!
Caution. There's
a slip stream ahead.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
take that.
Yaah!
[thunder]
Ponyhead, what are you doing?
[gasps]
Oh, my goodness.
He's at the hospital!
[speaking Korean]
[tires screech]
[thunder]
Hey! What's goin' on?!
Why you stopping?!
[thunder]
I am unable to travel
any further
due to hazardous
weather conditions.
Uh, okay, cool.
Then I'll drive.
What? Ugh!
[kiss]
Here we go now.
Okay, this is
a new life on the road!
It's just for me!
Here I come!
And no interruptions, either,
except for commercial breaks!
Mmm, just me and my shows
till the end of time! Forever!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
-[upbeat music playing]
-[Ponyhead shouting joyously]
[car alarm blaring]
[alarm slowly dying]
[thunder]
[TV show playing]
[girls shouting
in Korean]
I can't miss the finale.
[wind whistling]
Oh, girl, yeah.
you been doin' that.
Mmm... I love you, too!
[sobbing]
[singing K-pop song
in Korean]
She did it!
The hot TV people are right!
They're right!
Just because my tour
didn't sell out
doesn't mean
I should hide away!
The world deserves Ponyhead!
I deserve Ponyhead!
There she is!
So dramatic.
We get it.
You had
an emotional journey
and came out
as a changed pony.
Eee!
Girl, thank you!
Okay, I know I can be,
like, a lot to deal with,
like, all the time, like,
tick-tock every single second,
but I really appreciate
you helping me.
Anytime. I'm
just so glad you're okay.
I would also help
during the business hours
of 9:00 am to 5:00 pm.
Oh, my goodness!
I thought you died!
What?
Oh, no, I am unkillable.
However,
I do have a gift for you.
I utilized Reflectacorp's
newest 3-D printing technology
to analyze your needs.
Reflectacorp assessed
that artificial horns
would suit you perfectly.
Oh, wow!
You are so sweet!
That is so adorable!
Thank you so much, Boo!
May I do the honors?
Unh! No!
That is reserved
for my favorite sister.
Ohh! Uhh!
Are you dense?
I'm talkin' 'bout Star!
[gasps]
Aww!
Huh!
[woman singing in Korean]
[whispers] I love it!
Mmm, you know what, though?
I am afraid that it's time
to break up with you again.
Hey, do you think
I can get one
of those horns, too?
Why do you always
have to be at the center
of attention, Hornanne?
Just like,
why?! Why?! Why?!
Why do you need
to do that?
Why are you always
thinkin' about you?
Why?! Why?! Why?!
[ominous music playing]
[crows cawing, pigeons cooing]
Okay, let's just
make this fast.
L-Lord and Lady Pigeon,
I understand your fear
for your people's safety,
but, please, let us
take care of Meteora.
It's safer for everyone
if Eclipsa and I
get to her first.
[cooing]
Well, that's going well.
Let me try.
[cooing]
[Rich Pigeon]
They can't understand you!
You'll have to talk to me!
Oh. Turn around again.
-[mechanical noises]
-Hold on.
You'll have to talk to me!
Rich, we know
that you're upset,
but, please, don't take
matters into your own hands.
Let us deal with Meteora.
[Rich straining]
Look what she did
to our castle!
[buzzing]
[pigeons cooing]
Does it not normally
look like this?
No! Keep looking!
[dramatic music]
[gasps] Oh, my.
Behavior like this
-must not go unpunis--
-[mechanical noises]
[straining]
Unpun-- Come on.
Make a fist.
Unpunished!
Oh! No, no, no, no, no, no!
Stop! [gasping]
Oh, no!
Aah! [squawks]
Rich, are you all--
Get out of my house!
Uh, I'm so sor--
Get out! Out! Out!
Okay, so,
what do we do now?
Oh, I don't know,
Eclipsa.
I was thinking we'd
just, you know,
follow the trail
of destruction.
[flames crackling]
[clicks tongue]
Right, yeah, I...
I suppose that works.
[clicks tongue]
Can you believe
that little bird man?
How upset he got?
He's all,
"Get out of my house!"
You know, you might
want to take this
a little more seriously.
Oh, sorry. You're right.
I get jokey
when I'm nervous.
And just, it's been
such a long time
since I've seen my daughter.
Yes, but this isn't
a rebellious teen.
This is carnage.
Meteora may be
beyond your reach now.
Well, I can try.
Well, of course we'll try.
It just won't be easy.
Even the little monsters
can be a handful.
Now let's keep going.
We're getting close.
[people shouting]
Is that an angry mob
headed in our direction?
[shouting]
Everyone, please!
What's going on here?!
We're out to get the
fire-breathin' monstrosity
with 23 heads and a tail
what come
and smashed up the town!
You said she had a tail?
A tail, which she used
for destroying
me humble cottage!
[sadly] Me humble cottage.
I lost everything!
Me life is ruined!
[sobbing]
Uh, perhaps
you could take--
[sobbing uncontrollably]
Oh, no!
Me bad luck!
I can't believe
me bad luck!
-Oh!
-[thud]
That thing
destroyed our town.
And we intend to do
something about it!
Something violent!
-[all] Yeah!
-Violence!
After what she done,
there's no forgivin'
and forgettin'.
She destroyed
me teddy bear collection!
[first villager]
I love teddy bears!
She gave me this neat hat!
I like it.
[all shouting]
Let's get out of here.
How are we supposed
to find my daughter
before a bunch of villagers
with pitchforks do?
Eclipsa, it'll be fine.
We'll find her first.
[Eddie]
Psst! Hey! Down here!
Looking for the beast,
are we?
-Yes.
-No.
Well, that's
a confusing answer.
But we'll go with yes.
I've been tracking the beast
for quite a while now.
Boy, is she gettin' big!
Imagine the size
of her mother! Ha ha!
Her father deserves
most of the credit.
Can you take us to her?
Well, that depends.
Do you have legs?
Oh, look at that.
Answered my own question.
You both have legs!
Uh, well, follow me.
[ribbiting]
Is this the bog?
Well, it was the bog,
till that beast
drank it up.
-[gasping]
-Every last drop of it.
The true
Bog Beast of Boggobah,
on account of her
drinking the bog.
How big is she?
Well, I must say,
as a Bog Beast expert,
I reckon she's this big.
Not this big!
I mean, this is just her foot.
A footprint!
But, yes, she's big!
And her tracks just keep
getting bigger!
[Eddie] Follow me!
[sniffing]
How does she keep
getting bigger?
Well, if you
drank a bog, you'd put
on a few pounds, love.
But what is she eating?
Ooh! I can answer that one.
[dramatic music playing]
She's been eating
the souls of my family.
At first, I thought I'd
quite like the peace and quiet,
but then I, uh...
I realized I-I do--
I do miss them.
Except for Tim.
I do not miss Tim!
Thanks, Tim!
You're gone!
Oh, dear.
How is she doing that?
-Well, her tracks end here.
-[light snoring]
She must be close.
Let's try to find her.
[hushed]
Eddie, no! Stop!
-Get out of there!
-No!
Wow! She's bigger
than I thought!
You ought to come
look at this!
-[hushed] No, no, no!
-Eddie! Eddie! Eddie! No!
[Eddie] I think I better
give her a nudge.
See if we can
wake her up a bit.
Nudge, nudge!
Yep, I think
that that's worked.
[dramatic music playing]
Oh!
[gasping]
She... has... magic.
Mm-hmm.
We have to stop her.
Wait. You have
to let me try something.
What?
She might listen to me.
What?!
[hushed]
Come back!
[exasperated sigh]
Hello there.
Oh! [stammering]
Before you kill me,
I-- I brought you
something.
Bo-Bo!
Is it really... Bo-Bo?
[whimpering]
Up we go!
Can't believe it!
It's really...
Yes! It's Bo-Bo!
What's a Bo-Bo?
But Mama made Bo-Bo.
Are you my... my mama?
You know,
I think I prefer "Mother."
What?!
You know, "Mama" is just fine.
What should I call you?
Baby Smooth.
Okaaaay.
[sighing laugh]
Mama?
Where have you been?
Well...
some terrible,
terrible people
locked me up
in a dingy old crystal
deep down
in a dark dungeon.
They were a rather backwards,
maladjusted people,
especially their old queen.
Oh!
But that is an era bygone,
and I'm hoping that now
we're together again,
we're going to have everything
we've ever missed out on.
Like what?
I don't know.
Uh, how about ponies?
Bedtimes past 8:00.
Ice cream for breakfast.
I hate ice cream.
Then no ice cream.
What would you like instead?
You can have
anything you want.
The throne of Mewni.
What?
I'm afraid
that's not possible.
[heavy thuds]
You said I can have
anything I want.
But the throne
is not mine to give.
It's ours by right!
A lot has changed
since we've been gone,
and after everything
that's happened
at St Olga's...
I was
a great head mistress!
But you were stealing
the life-force
of those girls
to preserve your youth.
Oh, you noticed.
Look, we have each other now.
You don't need this kingdom.
Are you saying...
no?!
[inhales]
Yes, I am.
-Ugh!
-[stomping]
Young lady, you turn
right back around!
All right, that's it!
Meteora!
You have to stop!
[gasps]
Mama, you set me up!
I don't want to hurt you!
That's too bad, because
that's all I want to do to you!
[groans] Yah!
Ah!
[growling]
[groans]
[screaming]
I love you!
I know you haven't
heard these words
in a very long time,
but I'm saying them
again to you now.
Please, Meteora,
come back to me.
I-I...
[groans]
Aah!
I am ending this.
No!
[screaming]
[sound fades]
[high-pitched tone]
[groans]
[wind whistling]
Moon!
[frightened gasp]
No!
[gasps]
[ominous music playing]
♪ She's a princess
winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Ohh,
there goes a shining star ♪
- ♪ Evil won't deter her
- ♪ No, sir! ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ Star Butterfly ♪
♪ She is a shining sta-a-r ♪