♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't
from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another,
whoo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
[Ponyhead] Okay, you need
to hold still.
One more second.
It needs to be perfect.
Mm. Mm. Mm-hmm!
How do I look?
Super pretty!
[gasps] Oh, no.
What's the matter?
You don't like it?
No, I know I look amazing,
it's just...
I can't go back
to St. Olga's like this!
I gotta come clean!
[spits] Uh-uh!
If you tell those girls
that you have been lying
about being a princess,
they will destroy you.
I still can't believe they want
to give me an honorary degree.
Ugh. I know I inspired
a generation and all,
but I can't keep lying!
Whatever.
It's your funeral.
-[thuds]
-[groans]
Hey, goat, just because
you're invisible
doesn't mean
I can't hurt you!
Oh, we're here. Mm.
Come on, ladies.
[grunting]
You're having
a princess problem.
[sighs] Yeah, I'm having
Okay, stand up straight.
Arms forward!
And exhale!
Exhale!
Oh! Well, you've
obviously done this before.
-[dance beat playing]
-[cheering]
Okay. I can't do this.
[fan] Princess Turdina,
where you going?
-Ahh!
-Sign my poster!
-Sign my cat!
-[cat meows]
Sign my face!
Okay, people,
don't crowd her!
Princess Turdina!
It is truly an honor.
Oh, please,
you don't have to--
We can't wait
to show you what we've
done with this place.
Whoa!
Welcome to Utopia!
[all gasping]
[cheering]
[gasps] Where am I?
Oh, it's so beautiful!
Wow, this is, uh...
really something.
Oh, we got rid of all those
oppressive classes about manners
and "please" and "thank you"
and all that other trash.
We have our own
curriculum now!
Brunch and... party.
When do you sleep?
Oh-ho-ho,
don't worry about it!
You know, sometimes structure
isn't a bad thing!
-What?
-I just think
that rules have a place...
Yeah, but you told us
to never conform!
If you weren't being honest
about who you are,
then this whole school
would be built on a lie!
Oh, what I meant to say
was rules have a place...
in the garbage! Hah-hah!
Oh, hah-hah!
Oh, oh, good one.
That was...
Oh, you had me.
Here's some princesses hard
at work on their brunch final.
We don't believe in grades,
no, we don't, just pancakes.
[chewing noisily]
I love learning!
These are
the whispering gardens,
our designated gossip area,
because a princess's voice
shall not be silenced!
[gasps] Oh, my gosh,
did you hear that Beatrice
and Alfred broke up again?
Oh, no way!
And this is where
we have our party class
to celebrate our freedom
from the reign of Miss Heinous!
I see what you're seeing.
It's cooler at night.
This is the hallway
of Turdina!
Whoa.
This is the very first
Turdina poster we hung up.
All of your T-shirts
and all of your dolls
and a lock of your hair
and a poster of your movie!
Oh, I gotta get
a DVD of that!
This is too much!
Are you kidding?
We owe this whole school to you.
You showed us
that all princesses
don't have to fit
into the same mold.
[squawks]
Pfft. No, I didn't.
And we're gonna show you
our appreciation
by throwing you
the biggest party
this school's ever seen!
A party?! For me?
Uh, Marco, isn't there something
you wanted to tell these girls?
Oh! Yeah, um...
[clearing throat]
It's not criminal
to be an individual!
-She said our catchphrase!
-Yay!
Aw, you are way
much more fun as Turdina!
Oh, my gosh!
It's here!
What's here?
Check it out!
Isn't it amazing?
Whoa.
In honor of the one princess
who changed our lives,
we dedicate this to you!
I'm so beautiful.
I hope you do like it,
Princess Turdina!
It took all year to save up
enough to get it made!
We cleaned toilets
on weekends for extra cash.
But it was worth it
because you showed us
that there's another way
to live.
[cheering]
Hey, hey, it's time
for a group selfie
in front of the statue.
Oh, okay, sure.
Camera phone! Mm!
Are you...
enjoying this?
Hey, this is the first time
he's ever been popular!
Don't ruin it for him.
Well, he should tell the truth
like a decent human being.
Hey, Turdina, can I talk
to you for a sec?
Sure. Uh, bye, ladies!
Marco, I think you're running
out of time to tell the truth.
Don't even listen
to her, Turdina!
These princesses
worship you!
Yeah, but they worship
someone who doesn't exist.
Marco is the most organized,
rule-abiding person I know.
Think of the party!
Yeah, they spent all that money
for the statue.
I can't crush
their spirits!
I'm just worried
you might be letting
this attention
get to your head!
What? That's not it!
This is for them,
not for me!
Princess Turdina,
come on!
It's time
for your ceremony!
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but I'm going
with Pony's advice.
Whoo! Good choice.
[claps]
Oppression!
Eternal darkness!
Suddenly light!
Freedom!
Turdina!
[doves coo]
Thank you,
Princess Gwendolyn,
for that beautiful
interpretive dance.
And now, the moment
you've all been waiting for,
the woman herself,
Princess Marco Turdina!
[cheering]
I present you this honorary
St. Olga's degree.
Wow!
[chanting] Turdina!
Dearest princesses,
congratulations
on this wonderful school.
I know you see me
as an idol,
but today
you're my idols!
You embody everything
that Princess Turdina...
uh, um, that I stand for--
not letting anyone force you
to be something you're not,
living by your true colors,
loving who you are!
I'm proud to have inspired
you to be brave,
even when it's scary.
And when being true
to yourself
might mean disappointing
thousands of people.
Um...
[sighs] That's--
that's why I have
to tell you the truth.
I, Princess Marco Turdina,
-am a boy!
-[words drowned out by saw]
Oh, no.
[humming]
[all gasping,
screaming]
Ooh!
It's Miss Heinous!
Princess Turdina
is a fraud,
and I have
the evidence to prove it.
-It's a tape...
-It's a tape of what?
That's right,
I watched your video
and saw your dark secret!
Oh, that phony confession I did?
Go ahead, show 'em!
It's not real.
Oh, no, it's not...
but this is. Uh!
-[gasps and exclamations]
-Wait! Is that a hair?
Turdina isn't a princess!
She's a boy!
[girls gasping]
How'd you know
about Rodrigo?
Whatever! That doesn't
prove anything!
Princesses
can be hairy!
Yeah! We believe
in you, Turdina!
No.
[girls whispering]
I lied to you.
I am a boy.
[gasping]
Ooh!
Oop! I mean, ugh!
This, princesses,
is why you need me
running St. Olga's.
Look where all
this freedom got you--
living in filth
and championing a "hero"
who's been lying
to you all along!
Henceforth, you must reinstate
me as your schoolmaster!
You need me...
and I need you.
Wait, what did she just say?
Wait, no, why does it matter
if he's a boy?
Nothing he said
was wrong!
Yeah! He can think
for himself and so can we!
He can be a princess
if he wants to!
Turdina's a state of mind!
[cheering]
Silence! Silence!
[gasps]
Oh, I just got her
right in the face!
[neighs]
Come on, girls!
-Yeah!
-Free will!
No! No!
[saw buzzes]
Spare me.
Get in the car!
Turdina lives!
[cheering]
[dance beat plays]
Well, looks like Turdina's
gone for good.
Yeah, because you
took her away from us,
you selfish monster!
You look like you can breathe
a lot easier now.
Mostly 'cause I'm
out of that dress!
That corset
was killin' me!
Could we get a selfie
with Marco Turdina,
Boy Princess?
Sure.
[all] Camera phone!
Oh, Smoochie's gonna be
so jealous of this one!
Where is Smoochie,
anyways?
♪♪
Ah! Oh, yeah,
that's good!
Gemini, we gotta get
more of this stuff.
Oh, yes, but I'm afraid this one
is out of juice, milady.
Camera phone...
[Heinous] I know that,
you fool!
I'm not talking about her!
Well, I'm happy to share
some of mine with you.
No! I want
the good stuff.
I'm coming for you,
Princess Marco Turdina!
I don't mean
to interrupt, milady,
but we say this
all the time.
"I'm coming for you..."
Maybe we should
just stay in tonight
and you can have
a little Gemini fuel.
No. Nobody asked you.
Go get the car!
Uh, of course, milady.
Whoa!
Yeah, that princess merch
is, like, so cute,
but for that price,
I'm, like,
it better do real magic.
[laughs] That is funny
and a good point.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
This one's spicy!
Oh, my gosh, that is
the cutest price tag!
Hey, monster!
You know the rules.
Monsters ain't welcome,
so put the merch back
and get out!
-Whoa.
-Shoo, shoo, shoo!
[sobbing]
Do you think I'd look cute
in this shirt?
-What?
-Or...
Hey, over there!
That goes for you, too!
-Monster!
-Hmph!
Oh! Prince Lucitor.
Sorry. Sorry, sir.
Please don't incinerate
my shop.
-[kisses]
-Hmm.
Circumstantial evidence...
Hmm, okay. Hmm.
[footsteps patter]
-No.
-Hey, Mom!
You know how Mewmans
kind of keep monsters separated
from the rest
of the kingdom?
Yes?
Well, I was
just wondering why!
We keep monsters out
because monsters are dangerous.
You know that.
Well, yeah!
But no! No, no, no, no!
Not all of them,
and what about people
who aren't Mewmans,
but also aren't monsters?
Like Romulus!
He has snakes for hands!
Are his hands monsters?
Heavens, no!
He's on the Magical
High Commission!
And what about
the Ponyheads?
They're a bunch
of floating horse heads!
No, dear, we've had ties
with the Ponyheads
for generations.
And Rich Pigeon?
His kingdom is brand new!
And he's a pigeon
with legs, Mother!
How is he
not a monster?
Well, dear, he's rich.
I don't really see what that
has to do with anything.
And what about
the Lucitors?
I've seen Tom do
some pretty scary stuff.
Somehow he's not a monster?
Okay, and it makes
absolutely no sense
that lizard people
are monsters
but Lekmet, the giant
magical goat-man was not?
Too soon, Star!
But what's the difference?
What the heck
is the difference?
Enough! Look,
I don't make the rules.
The Royal Monster
Expert does!
I'm sorry, what?
We have a monster on staff?
Not a monster,
a monster expert.
Dr. Jelly Goodwell.
Okay, then I'm gonna
go have a little chat
with this "Jelly Goodwell,"
if that even is
her real name!
-Fine!
-Fine! Bye.
[sighs] What am I supposed
to do with this cart?
Jelly Goodwell!
[screams]
We need to talk now!
Oh, you must be here
for the cheese!
What? No!
Don't play dumb with me,
Royal Monster Expert!
Oh! No,
I'm the Royal Muenster Expert.
The Royal Monster Expert
is down the hall to the right.
Okay! Thank you!
Jelly Goodwell!
Hmm?
Wrong office. Sorry.
Jelly Goodwell!
And step... step...
[snuffles]
Excuse me.
Pardon me, is this
Dr. Goodwell's office?
Yes, I'm Dr. Goodwell.
Ah, thank goodness!
Now, you listen up, Goodwell!
The way we treat monsters
around here is outrageous!
We have got
all these dumb rules
saying monsters
can't mingle with humans,
and monsters
can't go here,
can't go there!
Oof! It's gotten to the point
where a monster
can't even go shopping
for a pre-ripped T-shirt!
Well, sister,
I am not leaving here
until you agree
to make some changes.
I've spent my entire life
studying monsters.
Nobody knows more
about them than I do.
I've even lived among them
and observed
their behavior first-hand,
and you are exactly the princess
I've been waiting for!
-Wait, what?
-For years I've hoped
to find a royal
who actually gets it.
The way we treat monsters
in Mewni is,
well, monstrous!
-Exactly!
-Monsters need to be respected.
-Yes!
-And loved!
-And their habitat preserved!
Oh, yes! Yes! Yes!
Excellent. Let me take you
out into the field
and show you
what I've been working on.
Let's go!
Being a researcher
is awesome!
These monster costumes
are great!
Oh! They're
monster camouflage.
Speaking of which,
we should probably go ahead
and apply our monster musk.
Monster musk?
What's that?
-[spritzes]
-Oh, that is nasty!
What's in there?
My own special blend
of various monster secretions.
[gargles]
Bleh, ugh!
Let's get going!
First we need to go
through the Forest
of Certain Death,
then across the Lake
of Endless Suffering,
over the Dam
of Constant Sorrow,
across the Bridge
of the Inevitable Hereafter,
and here we are!
Wow, sick treehouse, doc!
Oh, no...
[laughs]
It's not a treehouse.
It is
my field research lab.
It looks like
a treehouse to me.
It's not!
Whatever you say, doc.
[grunting]
Oh!
[grunts] Dr. Goodwill?
Whatcha doing?
Shh! There's
a herd nearby!
A herd?
A herd of what?
Monsters!
Whoa.
This hill features
naturally occurring
geographic formations
that almost
look like buildings.
The monsters
were clever enough
to use them for shelter.
Amazing!
Wait, what?
Ooh! Ooh! You've got
to get a look at this!
There's 011358,
and he has
his offspring with him!
Oh, hey, Buffrog!
You know him, too?
I have been watching 011358
since he was a tadpole.
I implanted a tracker
on his ear
and have been keeping
close tabs on him ever since.
[whistling]
[scratching]
Okay, I don't know
about this, Goodwell--
the spying, the costumes,
the monster musk?
Monsters are just like us.
You don't need
all this equipment
to get to know them.
Get to know them?
Oh, ho, sweet, naive Star!
It's not so simple.
When monsters and Mewmans mix,
bad things happen,
usually to the monsters!
Yeah, but that--
I've devised
a plan!
Let me show... you...
Tah-dah!
Ooh!
Nice cartsmanship.
Thank you!
Aw, look at little tiny us
in the treehouse!
So cute!
And the monster village!
What are you planning?
You see that wondrously
mysterious structure
the monsters built?
Uh, you mean "dam"?
I believe it's some kind
of primitive monument
that they built
out of instinct,
but no matter-- we simply
remove a small piece
of their structure
to release
a gentle flow of water,
which travels
down the chasm,
covers the lowlands
around the monster
nesting grounds,
and creates
a natural island!
Voilà!
More like a prison.
I mean, how are they
supposed to get in and out?
Well, they don't!
It's guaranteed total
isolation from Mewmans!
Shall I detonate
the dam?
Listen, we can't just
go around blowing up dams
and imprisoning monsters!
That's crazy!
Mewmans have been deciding
what's best for monsters
for way too long!
But I already did it!
[explosive noise]
Ugh. Unbelievable.
You know what, Jelly?
You doomed these monsters!
You don't like
my explosion?
It's not about that.
I thought you were different.
But you're just like
everybody else here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop complaining.
Look, of course there is
bigger, better stroller.
But you should appreciate
the one we have.
[panting] Hey, Buffrog!
Look, look, look!
Jelly Goodwell blew the dam,
and now the water's
gonna come down
and turn this whole place
into an island!
What?
Hey, Star,
it's not a problem.
That's just
a little trickle of water,
nothing we haven't
seen before.
Oh, you must be crazy dirty lady
that watches us through trees.
Hello. I am
Yvgeny Bulgolubuff.
Well, I'm Jelly Goodwell!
Oh-ho-ho!
-[beep]
-[explosion]
Oh, I'm such
a turd-brain!
I shook your hand
with the blower-upper thing!
No! It's too much water!
It won't create an island.
This will destroy
entire village!
Come on.
Incoming!
Oh, my goodness!
Come on, move it!
This is not drill.
Hey, hey!
Hah!
[video game tones]
Hey, Star!
Incredible!
Mewmans and monsters
working together!
-Here it comes!
-Oh, no!
-Hey!
-Huh?
-Grab a rock!
-Oh!
Great, let's go!
Oh! Okay!
[all] Yay!
How could I have been
such a dumb-dumb?
Here I thought
we should live separately!
But really Mewmans
should live like monsters!
Hah-hah!
Play in the mud!
Act like idiots! Oh!
I'm a monster, ho-whah!
I'm a monster!
[laughing]
[grunts]
There!
Now Mewni has
a real monster expert.
Thank you.
Aw, you're crying.
Oh, the badge.
I think you broke
the skin a little.
Oh, gosh!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, yes.
♪ She's a princess ♪
♪ Winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry
when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she would keep
the lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪