♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh
Puh-puh-puh-puuuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna get
A little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
[clattering]
[puppy yipping]
[Angie]
Did you hear that?
[Raphael] Y-yes. Maybe
we should call the police.
Psh! Police.
-[Angie] Hand me my nine-iron.
-[golf club clanks]
There's only one law
in this jungle.
Mom's law.
-[yipping]
-[sad song playing on radio]
Marco? It's 3 a.m.
Is it?
Honey,
what are you doing up?
Nothing.
Barco Diaz, stop,
we're sad now.
-Act sad.
-[yipping]
I'll take care of this.
Maybe it's time
-we take down
these decorations.
-[music stops]
Mom, that's too soon.
-What if Star comes back?
-[music starts]
I want it to be
like nothing's changed.
Oh, honey,
I know this is hard.
-Look, I--
-[phone dialing]
Raphael,
what are you doing?
I was just going to call
the Teen Sadness hotline.
I told you.
-[music stops]
-I got this.
[music starts]
[Angie] Well, how does
your oatmeal taste?
Like empty nothingness.
Mom, can you
be addicted to crying?
-[bowl breaks]
-[puppy whines]
How about
some Captain Blanche's
Sugar Seeds?
[groans]
Star loved Sugar Seeds.
[playing louder]
I'll pour you a bowl.
I tried, I can't even
find the box.
They're in the cupboard
behind the dog food.
I hid it so well.
[Star]
Behind the dog food, Diaz!
Star would eat all of them.
And now they're both gone!
Its behind the dog food, Marco.
Stop being so dramatic.
Why do you have
to be such a cute idiot!
[carriage rumbling]
[sniffing]
Oh, Marco, yuck!
When was the last time you
washed this thing!
Star!
We need to be quiet!
We don't know
who might be listening.
Sorry, Mom.
Sorry.
It's okay. Can you check
on the Commission?
Yeah, they seem... okay.
-[chirping]
-Still in their stasis.
[cawing]
Oh, looks like ol' Heckapoo
is gonna be an aunty!
So how exactly are we going
to de-balloonify them?
Once we're at the sanctuary,
the Well of Magic should
be able to rejuvenate them.
And Lekmet's gonna
meet us there?
Yes, he'll meet us there.
[Star]
Okay, great. [chuckles]
So what's up
with that warnicorn?
What?
[panting]
[Star] Mom!
Mom, what is going on?
Its the fritz!
It's causing
all magic to...
to weaken and...
fade.
It's okay,
we're all right,
as long as we have
this magical path to guide us.
[lights buzzing]
I guess
we're setting up camp.
[grunting]
[defeated sigh]
I got this one, Mom.
Stop!
It's corrupted!
What? No, no, no, it's fine!
Don't worry about it.
It does this all the time.
Glossaryck never cared.
Glossaryck isn't here,
and, ugh, he's probably
not coming back.
Wait. What do you mean?
Toffee has Glossaryck,
and your wand
seems tainted
by his magic as well.
It's the same magic I saw
when I fought Ludo.
Now let's start a fire,
and we'll head
for the sanctuary
in the morning.
There must be something
helpful in here.
"I corn't wait
to see you again."
Uh, did your father
pack this with nothing but--
Ugh, no.
[groans]
What are you doing?
Starting a fire. Duh.
Did your father
teach you that?
No, Marco did.
Marco taught me a lot,
like how to mope, self-pity,
ya know,
all the cool teen stuff,
and now that's all I have.
What-- Mom!
Shh shh shh!
[rats squeaking]
[sniffing]
[whispering] It looks
like they're just scouts.
We'll let them--
[whispering]
Mom, check it out!
Star! No!
-[squeaking]
-Ugh! Fine!
Stick blast!
Yah!
Star!
[shuddering]
[squeaking]
Aah! I did it! I did it!
Yeah! I did it!
Star, we need to get
out of here immediately.
I can't believe
you would be
so foolish as to--
[squeaking]
[gasps]
The High Commission!
[raspberry]
[panting]
Where-- Where did they go?
They're right there.
[creature howls]
Guess we're goin' up.
Ugh, fine.
Ugh, never listens
to her mother.
C'mon, Mom!
What's the big deal?
The big deal is
your recklessness has
put us in harm's way.
[grunting]
It's just a little danger.
I've been
in way worse than this.
You know
what I'm talkin' about.
[Moon] Mmm! Mmm!
Mmm mmm mmm!
Mom!
Are you okay?
Let's just get
the Magical High Commission
and get out of here.
Okay.
[gasps] The Sanctuary!
[chuckles] Is it, like,
a little Sanctuary guardian?
No, he's the gatekeeper.
Wait, what?
-Wah!
-Rahh!
-Wahh!
She's lost her marbles.
Wah!
[all] Wah! Wah!
Whoa.
Whoa!
-Look at all the Glossarycks.
-Yes, Star.
The queens of Mewni
have been coming here
for generations.
What now?
[straining]
All right. Let's get
the Commission
into their pods
so we can revive them.
Lets go, guys!
All right, I'm going
to open the Wellspring.
Stand clear.
[straining]
Is that stuff supposed
to be all black
and goopy like that?
No, it's not!
[thick bubbling]
Oh, I feel like that's not
how its supposed to look.
[gasps] Its worse
than I'd feared.
Mom?
We'll have
to go with plan B.
All right, plan B?
What's plan B?
We'll talk about that
after we get settled in.
Look at you, you're
covered in scratches.
Let's fix you up.
[gasps]
What are you doing?!
Star, what do
you want me to do?
It's in tatters already.
Uh, Mom?
If the well is messed up,
how are we going
to revive the Magic
High Commission?
We don't need to worry about
that right now, Star.
This sanctuary
is very well hidden.
Now, do you want creamed corn
or corned cream?
-What?
-To eat, Star.
Generations of Butterflys have
come here in times of danger.
We'll be safe
for as long as it takes.
Now, do you have any change?
So we're
just going to hide?
That's your plan B?
That's a terrible plan B!
Your safety is
my priority right now.
Uh, I didn't blow up
my whole life just
so you could give up!
Come on, we could track
those rats back to Toffee
and end this whole thing!
Even if the Magical High
Commission was okay,
we still wouldn't be strong
enough to defeat Toffee.
Our best bet is
to lay low until
the situation changes.
You lied to me.
Star,
what are you doing?
What else have
you lied about, Mom?
I bet Lekmet isn't
even meeting us here!
Lekmet is dead, Star.
And it could
happen to us, too.
Toffee won't stop
until he finds this!
Did you take
that from my closet?
And you're just
carrying it around?
It's too dangerous
to do anything but stay.
No! I am not hiding
here until I am old
and gray like you!
This has
to mean something!
No, Star!
The wands are linked!
He'll find us!
Oh, like he won't find us
with you carrying
his finger around!
I defeated him once,
I can do it again!
Fantastic exit beam!
Star, stop!
Why? What happened
to cool warrior queen Mom?
I was never
a cool warrior queen, Star.
I was a happy-go-lucky
girl like you.
And then Toffee and his monsters
killed my mother.
I thought you sent
Grandma to a grandma farm
to hang out
with other grandmas.
Oh, Star.
Tell me.
I was about your age
when it happened.
I didn't know what to do,
so I spoke to Eclypsa.
Eclypsa Eclypsa?
But she's been dead
for hundreds of years!
No, Eclypsa's alive.
And I made
a deal with her.
[monsters chattering]
[Mildrew] Hey.
I'm sorry,
am I bothering you?
No, Count Mildrew.
I'm just...
Mourning
the loss of your mother?
I understand.
It's been a hard week,
but I'm--
There's
no need to be strong.
Deal with your feelings.
We will handle
everything else.
Uh, Princess?
Uh, I mean, Queen Moon?
There's a... a situation...
in the...
in the situation room.
I swear it wasn't my orders!
[grunting]
You shut up during
your confession!
[door opens]
-[Young Moon] Mina.
What is going on?
[chair squeaks]
According
to this dingus here,
one of his mooks
lammed-off
with half an army,
and they're the ones
who put your mama
in a wooden nightgown.
Ya know, they, uh...
They put her on ice.
Uh, drapes down in funtown.
Thank you, Mina.
Sorry about your mama.
The queen and I were
about to sign a peace treaty
when one
of my generals went rogue.
Rogue wha-- Who?
He's known as... The Lizard.
[stifling laugh]
Sorry. "The Lizard"
-Dude, don't laugh.
-Shut it, both of you!
Put this guy in the caboose
and let's croak those toads!
I think we should go to war!
Now is not the time.
And her magic isn't strong
enough for war yet.
Especially
against the lizards.
They're indestructible.
We need to go to war!
We need
to sign the peace treaty!
Yelling feels
really good right now!
[all yelling]
[Young River] Maybe
we should let Moon decide?
She is the Queen.
She just lost
her mother, River.
She needs time
with her feelings.
[all shouting at River]
I am the queen now,
so I will make the decision.
My decision...
is that I will
make a decision at dawn.
Ugh. Why did I say
"decision" so many times?
Queen Moon! I'm sorry
I spoke out of place.
I got you something.
Uh... what is this?
It's an apology meat.
It's how
we Johanssons apologize.
It was a relief to know
someone believed in me.
Thank you.
Hey! Anytime, pal!
Did I just call
the queen "pal"?
Ugh! Oh, apology meat,
what am I going to do?
[muffled crying]
[crying]
Oh, Glossy,
are you okay?
No!
Your mama's gone!
[sobbing]
I know.
And she's
never coming back!
[sobbing]
No, she isn't.
And I really liked her, too.
I know you're upset--
so am I--
but, right now,
I really need your help.
Things are bad.
I-- I have to decide
between signing
a peace treaty
or waging a war.
Oh, yeah...
[sniffles] that.
I don't know, just pick one.
Sure it'll work out.
That's not helpful at all.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I'm in no condition
to give advice.
If you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go cry
in your mama's chapter.
[sobbing]
[Rhombulus] Eclypsa's
been crystalized
for hundreds of years.
I've got no idea what's gonna
happen when we open this up.
I can handle it.
Hoo. Okay, I'm out.
Call if you need me.
[gasping breaths]
Oh, my gosh,
I killed her!
[whispering] B... 4.
What?
B... 4
"Before"?
Before what?
B...
4.
Oh, wait.
You want the candy?
B4, B4, B4, B4!
O...kay.
[straining]
Aah!
Mmm mmm mmm!
How long have I been here?
Uh, like, 300 years.
[coughs] 300 years?
[munching]
So, you're the new queen?
Yes, what of it?
Well, it's just
you're far too young
to be queen, unless...
Oh, no.
Unless, your mother,
is she...?
[sniffles]
I see.
I lost my mother, too,
when I was not
much older than you.
Ever since Mom...
um, since I became queen,
everybody's
been looking to me
to end the war
and make all
these big decisions,
but I'm just a kid!
I can't decide
the fate of Mewni!
I can't even decide
which boy I like!
I know how you feel.
But that's
not why I'm here.
I need you to teach me
one of the spells from
your Forbidden Chapter.
Forbidden? Is that what
they're calling my chapter?
Yeah, sorry,
I didn't name it.
But the point is
I need a spell
that can destroy something
that's immortal.
Are you sure
that's what you want?
It's my only hope.
Well, the spell you seek
requires a magical contract.
I can give it to you,
but once your enemy
is killed,
you must give me
something in return.
Okay, what do you want?
My freedom.
What?
Oh, I know
it's a lot to ask.
But I've
just been here so long.
All by myself.
I want to buy
my own chocolate.
Or those little
shrink-wrapped muffins
at the bottom. Mm!
But these are
Rhombulus' crystals.
I can't free you.
A contract
between two queens is
stronger than any crystal.
Now, do you want
to learn the spell?
Come close. Now...
[whispering]
And aim it directly
at his heart.
What was that for?
I'm just doing my job,
Your Majesty.
Evil queen,
gotta freeze it.
She didn't seem so evil.
The queen is late.
Look!
[goat bleating]
She's gone mad
with grief!
She was so young!
[sobbing]
She's not dead yet,
you fool!
Uh, can we help you?
I wish to speak
to the general.
-The general?
-[laughter]
[Toffee] Silence!
Hello, Princess.
I presume you're the one
they call "The Lizard"?
Yes,
but you may call me...
Toffee.
Toffee?
How is that any better?
What do you want?
I want you and your army
to leave immediately,
or face the consequences.
Your mom couldn't defeat us,
and neither can you!
I was hoping you'd say that.
We're not afraid
of your little girl magic!
We're invincible!
Just watch!
No, wait!
I already know about the--
-[crunch]
-Ugh!
[grunting]
[cheering]
I call the darkness unto me.
From deepest depths
of earth and sea.
From ancient evils unawoken,
break the one
that can't be broken.
To blackest night,
I pledge my soul
and crush my heart
to burning coal.
To summon forth
a deathly power,
to see
my hated foe devoured.
Aah!
Enough of this.
Have you learned nothing?
[all gasp]
It's not growing back!
[screaming]
[grunts]
Queen Moon!
You did it!
Oh, my gosh! River!
Thank you.
What did you just do?
I did my job!
And as your queen,
I will continue to do my job
of protecting this kingdom.
I will hunt down
the remains
of the monster army
and scatter them
without country
or leadership.
Now, are there any questions?
I didn't think so.
♪ She's a princess
Winning battles ♪
♪ Through the break of dawn ♪
♪ Don't worry when it's night ♪
♪ 'Cause she will keep
The lights on ♪
♪ Oh, there goes
a shining star ♪
♪ Evil won't deter her ♪
♪ 'Cause magic
Flows through her ♪
♪ She is a shining star ♪