Boy howdy! I got my work cut out for me.
That there's the biggest bumper crop
a' apples I've ever laid eyes on.
Yep. Too big for you to handle on your own.
Come on, big brother!
You need to rest up and get yourself better.
I haven't met an apple orchard yet,
that I can't handle.
Oops. Sorry.
I'll take a bite out of this job by day's end.
Bitin' off more than you can chew
is just what I'm afraid of.
Are you sayin' my mouth is makin'
promises my legs can't keep?
Yep.
Why of all the... This is your
sister Applejack, remember?
The loyalest of friends and
the most dependable of ponies!
But still only one pony. And one pony plus
hundreds o' apple trees just doesn't add up to...
Don't you use your fancy
mathematics to muddle the issue!
I said I can handle this harvest
and I'm gonna prove it to you.
I'm gonna get every last apple out of those
trees this Applebuck Season all by myself!
Well, I better get kickin'. These apples
aren't gonna shake themselves outta the trees.
Hey!
Oh no!
STAMPEDE!
Heeey...! Thiiis maaakes myyy
voooice sooound siiilly!
Pinkie Pie! Are you crazy?! Run!
Everypony calm down!
There is no need to panic!
But Mayor! What ever shall we do?
Look there!
YEEHAW!
Other side, Winona!
Put 'em up, girl!
This is the best rodeo show I've ever seen!
Come on, little doggie! Herd!
Winona! Put 'em up!
Gotcha!
Attagirl!
Now what was that all about?
Oh my! Begging your pardon, Applejack.
But Mooriella here saw one of those nasty snakes.
And it just gave us all
the willies, don't you know?
I completely understand. Just next time,
try and steer clear o' Ponyville.
We certainly will, Applejack. So long, Winona!
Ride 'em, cowpony!
Applejack was just... just...
Appletastic!
Exactly! We must do something to thank
Applejack for single-hoofedly saving the town.
I know!
A party!
-We all ready?
-Just one last thing.
Now we're ready.
-Is Applejack all set?
-Actually, I haven't seen her all week.
Not since the stampede.
But she'll be here for sure.
Applejack is never late!
Welcome, everypony!
Today we are here to honor...
...a pony we can always count on
to help in matters great and small.
-A pony, whose contributions to...
-Did you see Applejack's slick moves out there?!
What an athlete!
This week she's gonna help
me with my new flying trick!
And I know it's gonna be SO AWESOME!
Exactly! And...
This week, I get to run Sugarcube
Corner for the first time!
What does that have to do with Applejack?
Oh! Applejack, one of the best
bakers ever, is gonna help me!
Applejack makes everything great.
So free samples for everypony!
Okay, that's great. Now if I could just
make a point without being inter...
-Twilight...
-...rupted.
Twilight, I'm so sorry, but I just
wanted to mention that Applejack...
...is also helping me this week
with the official bunny census...
...where we count up all the new baby
bunnies that were born this season.
She's gonna help gather them
using her wonderful herding skills.
Anyone else? Anyone?
No?
Well then, as I was trying to say...
ARGH! Never mind!
And so, with no further ado...
...it is my privilege to give the prized Pony of
Ponyville award to our beloved guest of honor...
...a pony of the utmost trustworthiness,
reliability and integrity...
...Ponyville's most capable and
dependable friend: Applejack!
...way to go, Applejack,
that was awesome! I mean...
Awkward.
I'm here! I'm here!
Sorry, I'm late. Whoah... I was just...
Did I hurt your tail...?
Miss Mayor. Thank you kindly for
this here... award thingy.
It's so bright and shinin'.
I sure do look funny here.
Oookay. Well, thank you, Applejack, for
saving us from that scary stampede.
And always being there for everypony.
Yeah. I like helpin'
the ponyfolks and... and stuff...
Yeah! Thanks!
Was it just me or did Applejack seem a little...
-Tired?
-Dizzy?
-Messy?
Well, did you see her mane?
She seemed fine to me!
What on Earth is that pony doing?
Whoops.
Hey Applejack!
Applejack! Applejack!
APPLEJACK!
-Howdy Twilight?
-What is all this?
It's Applebuck Season.
Apple-what Season?
It's what the Apple family calls harvestin' time.
We gather all the apples from
the trees, so we can sell 'em.
But why are you doing it all alone?
'Cos Big Macintosh hurt himself.
What about all those relatives I've met when
I first came to Ponyville? Can't they help?
They were just here
for the Apple family reunion.
They actually live all over Equestria and
are busy harvestin' their own orchards.
So... I'm on my own.
...which means, I should really get back to work.
Ahem... hint hint? Get back to work?
Fine.
-Could you step aside, Twilight?
-I just did.
Applejack. You don't look so good.
Yeah... don't any o' you three worry
none, I'm just fine and dandy.
Do you want some help?
Help? No way, no how.
But there's no way you can
do it all on your own.
-Is that a challenge?
-Um... No?
Well, I'm gonna prove to you that I can do it!
Now if you'll excuuuse me...
I've got apples to buck.
There you are!
I'm a might sorry, Rainbow.
I was busy applebuckin' and I guess I...
I closed my eyes for a second and...
...when I woke up, I was late.
Now, what's this new trick of yours?
-See this contraption?
-Uh.. Yeah?
Well, I'm gonna stand on one end, then
you're gonna jump down from that platform...
...launching me into the air faster than I could
take off on my own. Once I'm in the air...
...I'm gonna do some AMAZING flips and spins
that are sure to impress the Wonderbolts.
Isn't that a mite dangerous?
Not for a pony who can fly!
Well, alrighty then!
Oh my!
Ready? One... two... THREE!
Um... maybe I wasn't clear.
You're supposed to land *on* the other end.
Got it!
Applejack, what a hay is going on?
I mean, I though I was working
with Ponyville's best athlete!
You are!
I'm okay! Really! I have an idea!
Watch this!
Ta-da!
Oh... Maybe not.
Okay, one more try!
I'm sure to get it this time.
Here I go!
Wait, Applejaaaaack...!
You're welcome!
Can I help you?
I think somepony else needs your help.
-Applejack?
-Yep.
Applejack, can we talk?
CAN BEES SQUAWK?! I DON'T THINK SO!
No! Can we talk?
TWENTY STALKS?! BEAN OR CELERY?!
No! I need to talk to you!
YOU NEED TO WALK TO THE ZOO?!
WELL, WHO'S STOPPIN' YOU?!
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU!
OH! WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?!
WHAT'S YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT?!
RAINBOW DASH DROPPED
IN TO SEE ME TODAY!
THAT'S QUITE NEIGHBORLY OF HER!
YES, EXCEPT THAT SHE
CRASHED ONTO MY BALCONY...
...AFTER YOU LAUNCHED
HER INTO THE AIR!
Oh, yeah. I wasn't feelin'
quite myself this morning.
Because you're working too
hard and you need help!
WHAT?! KELP?!
I don't need kelp. I don't even like seaweed!
HELP!!! YOU NEED HELP!!!
Nothin' doin', Twilight. I'm gonna prove to you...
to everypony, that I can do this on my own!
Ow!
Now if you'll excuuuse me, I've
gotta go help Pinkie Pie!
Now, Pinkie Pie, are you sure you're up for baking
the muffins and running the store this afternoon?
Yes siree bob, Mrs. Cake!
Plus, I have Ponyville's prized pony to help
me out. Why, she's the best baker ever!
Right, Applejack?
No, you're not the best baker ever?
What?! On, no!
I mean... Don't you fret. I can bake anything
from fritters to pies in the blink of an eye.
All right. Well, see you later, girls!
Stop with the shakin'! It's time to get bakin'!
Alrighty! I'll get the sugar and the eggs.
Can you get me some chocolate chips?
W... What was that?
Chocolate chips!
Chips... Got it!
Tater chips. All salty and dry.
Okie dokie.
What next?
Baking soda!
Soda... Perfect! That'll get
the tater chips nice and wet.
Now what?
A cup of flour!
A cup o' sour? Well, lemons are sure sour.
A cup o' sour, comin' up.
-Anything else, Pinkie?
-One last thing. Wheat germ!
Wheat worms...? Oh! That must be
fancy talk for earthworms!
Now that's gonna be delicious!
If you say so...
Free Muffin Sample Spectacular!
Yeah! Muffin spectacles!
Get 'em while they're hot!
We came as soon as we heard!
Oh, thank you, Twilight.
We need all the help we can get.
Oh no! What happened?
It was a mishap with some of the baked goods.
No... Not baked goods... Baked bads...!
Applejack!
Want one?
Applejack? We need to talk.
Oh. It's you, Twilight.
I know what you're gonna say,
but the answer is still no.
Not to upset your applecart, but you need help.
Hardy har... No, I don't!
-Here. Let me help.
-Help?! No thanks!
A little more... Little...
There.
I'll prove that this apple
can handle these apples.
Come on... apples... Fall off!
AJ... I think you're beating a dead...
...tree.
I knew that.
Actually, Applejack, I had something
else to talk to you about.
I just came back from
Ponyville urgent care and...
You know? I'm a little busy to
get lectured right now, Twilight.
But if you'd just let me help...
No no NO!
How many times do I gotta say it?
I don't need no help from nopony!
That pony is stubborn as a mule!
-No offense...
-None taken.
Oh Applejack! Thank you so much for offering your
herding skills for the annual rabbit round up.
Why are we doing this?
Well, lots of new baby
bunnies have been born...
...so it's my job to get a count
of all the new families.
Fine. Can we just get on with it?
Certainly. But remember, these are
bunnies we're dealing with, not cows.
They are timid bunch and
need to be treated gently.
I do NOT need any direction on
corrallin' critters. Right, Winona?
Okay, little bunnies! I need you
all gather here in the middle.
That's right! Let's go, bunnies.
In the center. Hop to it!
Swell. Just swell.
Put 'em up, Winona!
Applejack! Winona! Stop! You're scaring them!
We know what we're doin'.
Get along, little bunnies!
Oh no.
STAMPEDE!
The horror...! The horror...!
That was awful!
A disaster! A horrible, horrible disaster!
I don't get it.
Our gardens! Destroyed!
Every last flower devoured.
By... By... THEM!!!
Oh my! Oh... Please stop, little bunnies!
No no! Please, let's go home! Oh my goodness!
All right. Enough is enough.
Must... keep... buckin'.
Just... a few... more...
Must... finish harvestin'.
All right, Applejack. Your applebucking
hasn't just caused you problems.
It's over-propelled pegasus, practically
poisoned plenty of ponies...
...and terrorized bushels of
brand new bouncing baby bunnies.
I don't care what you say. You! Need! Help!
No, I don't. Look! I did it!
I harvested the entire Sweet
Apple Acres without your help.
How d'ya like them apples?
Um... How do *you* like *them* apples?
...plejack? Applejack!
Oh, good! You're okay.
Now, Applejack, I completely
respect the Apple family ways.
You're always there to help anypony in need.
So maybe you can put a little of your stubborn
pride aside and allow your friends to help you?
Okay, Twilight.
I am not taking "no" for an answer... what?
Yes, Twilight. Yes, please!
I could really use your help.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"My friend Applejack is the best
friend a pony could ever have."
"And she's always there to help anypony."
"The only trouble is, when she needs
help, she finds it hard to accept it."
"So while friendship is about
giving of ourselves to friends..."
"...it's also about accepting
what our friends have to offer."
"Your faithful student, Twilight Sparkle."
How about y'all take a little break?
I got some fine apple juice waitin' for ya!
Girls, I can't thank you enough for this help.
-I was acting... a bit stubborn.
-A bit?
Okay. A might stubborn!
And I'm awful sorry.
Now, I know the town gave
me the Prized Pony award...
...but the real award is
havin' you five as my friends.
Phew! That applebucking
sure made me hungry!
And I've got the perfect treat!
Eeeew... Spike, I threw them all away!
Where'd you get them?
From the trash!
Just a little nibble? Come on.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000