Let's quiet down, please. We have
a very important lesson to get to.
Thank you.
Today, we are going to be
talking about cutie marks.
Boring.
You can all see my cutie mark, can't you?
Like all ponies, I wasn't born with a cutie mark.
My flank was blank.
Awww, the's tho prethious!
Then one day, when I was about you age...
...I woke up to find that a
cutie mark had appeared!
Look at her hair!
Yes, I know. But honestly, that's how
everypony was wearing their mane back then.
I had decided to become a teacher.
And the flowers symbolized my hope that
I could help my future students bloom...
...if I nurtured them with knowledge.
The smiles represented the cheer I hoped to bring
to my little ponies while they were learning.
Now, can anyone tell me when
a pony gets his or her cutie mark?
Oh, oh, oh!
When the dithcovers that thertain
thomething that maketh her thpecial.
That's right, Twist.
A cutie mark appears on a pony's flank...
...when he or she finds that certain something...
...that makes them different
from every other pony.
Discovering what makes you unique isn't
something that happens overnight.
And no amount of hoping, wishing or begging
will make a cutie mark appear before it's time.
What?
Apple Bloom!
Are you passing a note?
What could be so important that it
couldn't wait until after class?
It's blank!
Reminds you of anypony?
Want thome thweet? I've got thome peppermint thticks.
I made them mythelf.
They'll make you thmile!
No...
I don't know why we had to sit through
a lecture about getting a cutie mark.
I mean, waiting for your
cutie mark is so last week.
You've got yours...
...I just got mine.
We all have them already.
I mean, almost all of us have them already.
Don't worry, you two. You're still totally
invited to my cuteceañera this weekend.
It's going to be amazing.
It's a party celebrating me
and my fantastic cutie mark.
How could it not be?
Bump, bump
sugar lump rump!
Gimme a break.
See you this weekend...!
Blank Flanks!
It's not fair! It's just not fair!
Oh, don't get your mane in a tangle.
You'll get your cutie mark.
Everypony gets one eventually.
But I don't want one "eventually".
I want one right now!
I can't go to Diamond Tiara's
cuteceañera without one. I just can't!
'course you can!
You know, I was the last pony in my class to get
a cutie mark. And I couldn't be prouder of it.
I knew my future was to run Sweet Apple Acres
and these bright shiny apples sealed the deal.
Come to think of it, Granny Smith
was the last one in her class too.
Same with Big Macintosh.
I really don't see how that's
supposed to make me feel better.
That probably means that being the last one in
your class to get a cutie mark runs in the family.
Runs in the family...?
Runs in the family!
RUNS IN THE FAMILY!
You've got apples for your cutie mark...
Granny Smith has an apple pie...
Big Macintosh has an apple half...
My unique talent must have
someth'n to do with apples!
Apples! Apples! Apples!
Apples.
Get you delicious, nutritious apples here!
Delicious and nutritious! And so many uses!
You can eat 'em...
Play with them...
Hey, watch it!
Create fine art for your home with them...
You have to be crazy not to get
a bushel of your very own.
She's so creative...!
You, sir!
Care about some apples?
Uh... no thanks.
Why not?
I have plenty at home.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm pretty sure...
You're *pretty* sure.
But You're not absolutely, positively
completely super-duper sure. Are you?
Uh... if I buy some apples,
will you please leave me alone?
Awright!
You forgot your change!
That's how you sell some
apples and get a cutie mark.
So, what does my cutie mark look like?
A shoppin' bag full of apples?
A satisfied customer eatin' an apple?
Maybe I gotta increase my sales figures first.
You touch it, you buy it!
We take cash or credit.
I'm sorry, ma'am...
Ma'am!
Now, Apple Bloom, you can't just...
That'll be four bits.
I didn't put those in my bag!
Likely story... Four bits, lady!
Apple Bloom!
I am really, really sorry about that. She's new.
Here, take these. No charge.
And these.
Ya'll come back, now, ya hear?
What?
Sorry, little sis, but your
applesellin' days are over.
What?! But how else am I
gonna get my cutie mark?
Home! Now!
Listen, sugar cube. I know it's hard
to wait for your very own cutie mark.
But you just can't force it.
Besides, your not that grown up just yet.
Ain't there other fillies
in your class without one?
Well... Twist doesn't have hers yet.
Do you think it'd feel better
if you went to the party with her?
Well, there you go!
Bet you and Twist will have
a great time together.
Now run along and find your friend.
You're sure you don't want me to stick
around till the end of the market?
Hey! Who's been using my racket?!
Yeah. I'm sure.
Oh. What'th up, Apple Bloom?
So I was thinkin'.
Maybe we could go to Diamond
Tiara's cuteceañera together?
I don't have a cutie mark, you
don't have a cutie mark...
Well, um...
Ithn't my cutie mark thwell?
I've alwayth loved making
my own favorite thweets...
...but it took me thome time to dithcover
that it wath my thuper thpecial talent.
Pretty thweet, huh?
Yeah... Pretty... sweet.
Hey... This doethn't mean we can't
go to the cutetheañera together.
You're thtill gonna come to the party, aren't you?
Of course she will.
It's not like being the only pony there
without a cutie mark would be, like...
...the most embarrassing thing ever.
Whoa...
Looks like somepony's got a dark
cloud hanging over her head.
Let me do something about that.
What's the matter, kid?
Theresacuteceañerathisafternoonandeverypony
inmyclasswillbethereandtheyallhavetheircutiemarks...
...andIwannagetmycutiemarkbutImnogoodat
sellinapplesbutIreallywannagototheparty...
...buthowcanIgotothepartyifIdonthavemycutiemark
whichmybigsistersaysImgonnageteventuallybut...
I WANT IT NOW!
Cutie mark? I can get you a cutie mark like that.
Applejack says these things take time.
I have to just wait for it to happen.
Why wait for something to happen
when you can make it happen?
But Applejack says...
Hey, who are you gonna listen to?
Applejack...
...or the pony who was first in
her class to get a cutie mark?
I always liked flying n' all but
I was going nowhere in a hurry.
It wasn't until my very first race that
I discovered a serious need for speed.
And KAZAM!
This sweet baby appeared as fast as a lighting.
That's right!
Stretch out those legs. Gotta be nice and loose.
The key here is to try as many things
as possible as quickly as possible.
One of them is bound to
lead to your cutie mark.
Are you ready?
I'm ready!
I said...
ARE YOU READY?!
I'M READY!
Jugglers, go!
Hang gliding, go!
Karate, go!
Kite flying, go!
Ultra-Pony Roller Derby, go!
Tried that one... tried that one... tried that one...
Your new outfit is, like, perfect for the party.
I know. It totally shows off my new cutie mark.
I love being special.
Can you imagine how embarrassing
it must be to be... not special?
I don't even want to, like, think about it.
Tried that one... Huh, tried that one...
I'm doomed. Doomed! I'll never find somethin' I'm good at.
You look like you'd be good at eating cupcakes.
Eatin' cupcakes?
Eating cupcakes?
Eating cupcakes!
I really appreciate all your help, Rainbow Dash.
You're really great coach and
I've learned a lot from you...
...and I'm sure I can learn a lot more, but...
I've got some cupcakes to eat!
See you at the cuteceañera!
Hold on, Pinkie Pie! I'm comin'!
I can't believe I didn't think of this.
A cupcake eatin' cutie mark. It's so obvious!
Now, where are those cupcakes?
I'm ready to chow down!
I don't have any cupcakes.
Oh.
But you look like you'd be good
at helping me make some!
I guess, uh, "makin' cupcakes"
cutie mark could work too.
All you have to do is take a cup of flour,
add it to the mix.
Now just take a little something sweet, not sour.
A bit of salt, just a pinch.
Baking these treats is such a cinch,
add a teaspoon of vanilla.
Add a little more and you count to four
and you never get your fill of...!
Cupcakes, so sweet and tasty!
Cupcakes, don't be too hasty!
Cupcakes! Cupcakes, cupcakes, cupcakes!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Those look much better than the last batch.
Guess I'm not cut out to be a baker either.
I just have to face it.
I'm gonna have a blank flank forever.
What about that?
What about what?
Is there someth'n on my flank?
Is there, is there, is there?
A cutie mark! It's up!
A... a measuring cup? No.
A mixin' bawl? No.
Are those cupcakes?
A tower of cupcakes, maybe?
Flour! It's flour!
Yay! I guessed it! What game
do you wanna play next?
Please say bingo, please say bingo...
Whoa...! What's been going on in here?
We've been making cupcakes. Wanna try one?
No, thank you. Not that they don't look...
...delicious.
Twilight! You have to help me!
What's the matter?
Tiarascuteceañerastodayandeveryponyinmy
classwillbethereandtheyallhavecutiemarks...
...andIwannagetmycutiemarkbutImnogood
atsellinapplesorhangglidinormakincupcakes...
...butIwannagotothepartybuthowcanI
gotothepartyifIdonthavemycutiemark...
...whichPinkiePiesaysIcantjust
makeappearbutIneedittoappear...
...RIGHT NOW!
I don't follow.
How can I help you?
You can use your magic to
make my cutie mark appear.
Oh no, Apple Bloom.
A cutie mark is something that
a pony has to discover for herself.
Please, Twilight. Just try.
I'm sorry, but...
Oh please, please, please, please, pleeeaaase!
Alright, alright.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you!
Yes! I knew you could do...
...it.
I'm sorry, sweetie. But I told you...
Try again! Try again!
Told you that not even magic can make
a cutie mark appear before it's time.
It's hopeless. Hopeless!
I just won't go to the party. I can't go!
Everyone will just laugh at me and
make fun of me and call me names.
It'll be the worst time of my life.
I'm sure it won't be as bad as all that.
Forget it. There's no way I'm going to that...
...party.
How could I've forgotten the time?
How could I've forgotten
Pinkie Pie was hostin' the party?
it was at Sugarcube Corner?
Don't forget you party hat...
...Forgetty Forgetterson.
I have to get out of here
before anypony sees me.
Hey!
It's my cuteceañera.
I'm supposed to get the first bite of cake.
Okay, Apple Bloom. Almost there...
Apple Bloom! You made it!
After I heard about Twist, I was
afraid you wouldn't show up.
I sure am glad you came to your senses
about this all cutie mark thing.
These things happen when these
things are supposed to happen.
Tryin' to rush it will just drive you crazy.
I'll let you be. Looks like your
friends want to talk to you.
Well, well, well. Look who's here.
Nice outfit.
Just someth'n I, uh, pulled together last minute.
It really shows off your cutie mark.
Oh, wait. That's right. You don't have one.
I have a cutie mark.
What? Since when?
Since, um... earlier today.
Oh really? Let's see it.
I shouldn't. I couldn't.
My cutie mark is so unbelievably amazing.
I'm afraid that if I showed it off...
...everyone would start paying
attention to me instead of you.
Outshined at your own cuteceañera?
Can you imagine how
embarrassing that would be?
Uh, forget it.
I didn't really want to see it anyway.
Okay! Well, I'm gonna go mingle.
Enjoy your party!
Oh no!
Wow, that IS an amazing cutie mark.
Nice try...
Blank Flank!
You got a problem with blank flanks?
I said, you got a problem with blank flanks?
The problem is, I mean, she's,
like, totally not special.
No, it means she's full of potential.
It means she can be great at anything.
The possibilities are...
..."like, endless".
She could be a great scientist...
...or a amazing artist...
...or a famous writer.
She could even be
mayor of Ponyville some day!
And she's not stuck being stuck-up like you two.
Hey! This is MY party,
why are you two on HER side?
Because...
You don't have your cutie marks either?!
I thought I was the only one!
We thought we were the only two.
I for one think you are three very lucky fillies.
Lucky? How can they be lucky?
They still get to experience
the thrill of discovering who they are...
...and what they're meant to be.
And they've got all the time
in the world to figure it out.
Not just an afternoon.
-Wow, Apple Bloom.
-Do you really think you can be a mayor?
-I wish I could be a scientist.
Maybe I got my cutie mark too soon?
Hey, what's everypony doing?
This is my party, everypony's supposed
to be paying attention to me!
Whatever. We still think you're
losers. Right, Diamond Tiara?
-Bump, bump, sugar lump...
-Not now, Silver Spoon.
Name's Scootaloo.
And I'm Sweetie Belle.
Apple Bloom.
This thong is tho thuper!
So I was thinkin'. Now that we're friends...
I mean, we are friends, right?
How could we not be? We're totally alike.
We don't have cutie marks...
Diamond Tiara and Silver
Spoon drive us crazy...
Totally crazy!
Now that we're friends...
...what if the three of us work together to find
out who we are and what we're supposed to be?
We could form our own secret society.
I'm liking this idea!
A secret society! Yeah.
We need a name for it though.
The Cutie Mark Three?
The Cutastically Fantastics?
How about...
The Cutie Mark Crusaders?
It's perfect!
-This is gonna be so great!
-We're gonna be unstoppable!
What do you say we celebrate
with some of these delicious cupcakes?
Not the cupcakes! Trust me.
Let's see if there are any cookies!
-Yeah!
-Come on!
"Dearest Princess Celestia."
"I am happy to report that
one of your youngest subjects..."
"...has learned a valuable
lesson about friendship."
"Sometimes the thing you think will cause
you to lose friends and feel left out..."
"...can actually be the thing that
helps you make your closest friends..."
"...and realize how special you are."
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000