(birds chirping)
Oh, good morning little friends,
your singing is oh so pretty.
Yes, it is a very
beautiful day today,
certainly something
worth singing about.
♪ There's music in the treetops
and there's music in the vale. ♪
♪ and all around me
music fills the sky ♪
♪ There's music by the river
♪ and there's music
in the grass ♪
♪ And the music makes your
heart soar in reply ♪
♪ Aahhhh!
(growl)
♪ Aaaaahhh!
♪ Ah ha ha! Ah ha ha!
♪ Aaaaah!
♪ (ends on a sweet high
note) ♪
(cheers)
Oh, thank you so much.
You're too kind.
Pinkie Pie: WOW!
Oh. You um, you didn't
hear me, um ...
Singing in the most
beautiful voice ever?
Uh, yeah we did!
(whimper)
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
HoH version
Wow! I've never heard you
sing a solo like that before.
It was like a little
slice of heaven.
With ice cream on top!
Fluttershy, I cannot believe
your spectacular voice
isn't part of the
Pony Tones Quartet!
Um...well...I...
Especially since you're
having us perform
for your Ponyville Pet Center
Fundraiser tomorrow night!
Well, you see, I...
This simply must be rectified!
You must share that
stunning voice at the event.
Yeah! It will be so amazing!
You'd be there on stage,
basking in the hooflights,
the center of attention,
a shining star...
With everypony staring
at you, judging you,
jealously noting how they
could be WAY better than you.
Why wasn't it them?
And then, when you choke,
they'll turn on you
becoming a seething angry mob
and you'll be horribly
humiliated,
never able to show your
face in Ponyville again!
Pinkie Pie! Don't
be ridiculous!
But I'm so good at it!
Come, Fluttershy.
You will join the group making
the Pony Tones Quartet
the Pony Tones Quintet!
No!
Pardon me?
I love the Pony Tones.
I'm one of their biggest fans.
But I do not want to
perform with them.
Why not, Fluttershy?
Well you see, I...I
have...um...I-I have...
Spit it out!
I have...stage fright!
(gasp)
Is it contagious?
Stage fright isn't
a disease, Pinkie.
It just means that Fluttershy
is scared to perform
in front of everypony.
I'm very thankful
the Pony Tones
are singing at the Pet
Center Fundraiser.
And I'm really looking
forward to the performance.
But I'll be watching
safely from the audience.
Well, I think it's a terrible
waste of an exquisite talent,
but I understand that
you're not comfortable.
Thank you.
Ooh! Angel's right!
We better get going!
There's a lot of work to
do before tomorrow's event!
♪
Ahem!
All right, Pony Tones, let's
run through that again!
(pitch pipe tone)
♪ (doo wop bass notes)
♪ (vocalizing in harmony)
♪ Everypony's saying you should
learn to express your voice. ♪
♪ But if talk doesn't seem
like it's the answer ♪
♪ luckily you have a choice.
♪ When you find you've got the
music, got the music in you. ♪
♪ Find you've got the music
got the music in you. ♪
(sigh)
Whoo hoo! Yeah!
Rarity, you were awesome!
Thank you, Spike, but
this is an ensemble.
Enh, the rest of you
were pretty good, too.
Oh, I thought you were all
amazing, Pony Tones.
Thanks, Fluttershy!
Now, Pony Tones, I want you
all to rest your voices
for the remainder of the day.
We'll do a final run-through
tomorrow before the big event.
All right?
Eeyup.
Sounds great!
Oh, Rarity, the Pony Tones
are really going to make
the Ponyville Pet Center
Fundraiser so special!
Thank you so much for
helping me help the animals!
Oh yes. It is wonderful
when a plan comes together
without any sort of
drama, isn't it?
(giggle)
(owl hoots)
(rooster crows)
♪
Morning, Fluttershy.
Good morning,
Pony Tones!
Actually, we're the Pony
Tones minus one tone.
Big Mac is
inconveniently late.
(panting)
Well, there you are!
Have I not told you
about punctuality?
Ah! I don't want
to hear it!
♪ (pitch pipe tone)
♪ (no doo wop introduction)
(gulp)
Big Mac! Can you please
start the song?
Nnope.
Big Mac!
Did you lose your voice?
(gulp)
Eeyup.
(gasps)
♪
Whatever did you
do to cause this?
Well...
Howdy, everypony!
And welcome to the 12th Annual
Ponyville Turkey Call!
(cheering)
(gobble)
Who will take the
title this year?
Will it be somepony new?
Or will the Turkey Call
champion of six years
defend his title to make
it lucky number seven?
We'll find out if
ya stop yer gabbin'
and git on with
the gobblin'!
All right, everypony!
Let's talk turkey!
Big Mac, yer up!
(takes a deep breath)
A Turkey Call?
You lost your voice
doing a...Turkey Call?
Lost his voice and the title!
(Pinkie gobble)
Now we can't
perform tonight.
Wait! What? No!
You have to perform!
Otherwise the fundraiser
will be a disaster.
Well, we cannot perform
tonight with only three voices.
Why not?
It would take rearranging
all the music
and we just don't have time.
I'm sorry, Fluttershy,
but I have no remedy
for this situation.
(gasp)
Of course!
A remedy!
Follow me!
(hoarse) Ahhhh!
Hmmm.
Aaahh.
I can cure this
pony that is hoarse,
but it will take
a longer course.
Come again?
Hmmm.
I can mix a brew that
will work just right,
but it cannot heal
him by tonight.
Oh no!
Where are we ever going
to find a deep voice
to replace Big Mac's?
(chuckle)
Pardon me, Zecora,
but this is no laughing matter.
We need a bass voice for
the harmonies to work!
Without it, the
performance will be ruined!
Please forgive my
strange elation,
but I was not laughing
at your situation.
Then what?
Remember when you pony folk
stumbled into Poison Joke?
Miss Fluttershy had
an unusual change,
deepening her vocal range.
(very low voice) I don't
want to talk about it.
Yes, yes!
Your voice became really
low, making it sound like...
Flutterguy!
With these leaves,
I can mix a brew
creating the same
effect on you.
Zecora, that's fantastic!
Yes! I'll do it!
I'd do anything for the animals!
Why, you'd even
appear on stage!
Oh, except that.
I just can't bring
myself to sing on stage
in front of everypony.
What if you sang NOT
in front of everypony?
Huh?
What if Big Mac was on
stage moving his lips
while you're behind the
curtain singing his part?
It would be just like
singing in your house.
Nopony would know it was you.
Even still. I just don't think
I could sing in front of--
You must! For the animals!
(squeaks)
Oh, OK, then...mix it up.
♪
Now do it just
like we practiced.
(gasp)
(crowd
chatters)
Good evening,
citizens of Ponyville!
I want to thank you all
for coming out tonight
and generously supporting
the Ponyville Pet Center!
Thanks to your kindness, pets
are finding loving homes
and we are sure to meet
our fundraising goal!
Where's Fluttershy?
Prob'ly hidin'.
You know how much that
pony hates the spotlight.
So, with no further ado, please
welcome...The Pony Tones!
(cheers)
♪ (pitch pipe tone)
(big inhale)
(hoarse inhale)
♪ (bass doo wop intro)
♪ (harmony vocalizations)
♪ Hot outside can
you see the sunshine. ♪
♪ Something's in the
air today. ♪
♪ Sky is clear and
you're feeling so fine. ♪
♪ Everything's going
to be a-ok. ♪
♪ You listen carefully
♪ on every corner there's
a rhythm playing. ♪
♪ Then it happens suddenly
the music takes you over ♪
♪ and you find you
got the music. ♪
♪ Got the music in you.
♪ Find you've got the music
got the music in you. ♪
♪ Ohh!
♪ Everypony says that you should
learn to express your voice ♪
♪ But if talk doesn't
seem like it's the answer ♪
♪ luckily you have a choice.
♪ When you find you've got the
music, got the music in you. ♪
♪ Find you've got
the music ♪
♪ Got the music, got
the music in you. ♪
(cheers)
Pony Tones! Pony Tones!
(galloping)
Pony Tones!
That was truly amazing!
And you sounded better
than ever, big brother!
(snort)
Fluttershy, you were on the
wrong side of the curtain!
You totally missed the show!
Just like a true professional,
Fluttershy was back stage
making sure everything
ran smoothly.
And it was perfect!
That was fantastic, Pony Tones.
My new puppy and I thought it
was super duper crazy good!
Why, thank you!
And we were wondering if you
would consider performing
at my daughter
Zippoorwhill's Cuteciñera.
Will you? Will you?
We'd love to!
When is it? Next week?
Next month?
Tomorrow!
Oh, gracious, I'm
terribly sorry.
That's just much
too last-minute.
Oh no!
Well...I understand.
♪ (sad tune)
(deep voice)
Oh, Rarity.
We can't disappoint
that sweet little filly.
Are you sure
you're up for it?
♪
♪ When you find
you've got the music, ♪
got the music in you
♪ Find you've got the music,
got the music in you ♪
♪ Got the music, got
the music in you. ♪
Whoo yeah!
Yeah! We got the Pony Tones!
We got the Pony Tones!
Amazing Pony Tones!
And it would be even more
amazing if you could perform
at my ribbon-cutting
ceremony tomorrow!
Oh, Mayor, we would
love to but...
Will you excuse us
for a second, Mayor?
Certainly.
(softly) Don't
worry, Fluttershy.
You don't have to
perform again.
(deep voice) But we wouldn't
want to disappoint the Mayor.
Well then Mayor,
the Pony Tones will happily perform
at your ceremony!
♪ (doowop introduction)
♪ It's hot outside and
you see the sunshine. ♪
♪ Something's in the
air today. ♪
♪ Sky is clear and
you're feeling so fine. ♪
♪ Everything's going
to be a-ok. ♪
♪
You wouldn't want to
disappoint the spa patrons.
♪ (singing continues)
♪ If you listen carefully
♪ on every corner there's
a rhythm playing. ♪
♪ Then it happens suddenly
the music takes you over ♪
We wouldn't want to disappoint
the school ponies.
♪ and you find you
got the music. ♪
♪ Find it in your heart, you can
♪ Find it, oh yeah ♪
♪ Got the music in you now ♪
♪ Got the music! Got
the music in you! ♪
(cheers)
Fluttershy! We
must talk to you.
Big Mac's voice
is all better.
Eeyup.
Now you can bathe in the
Poison Joke antidote
and sound like your
lovely self again!
It's just...I didn't know
that last performance
was my last  performance.
Fluttershy! Stop!
Would it be OK if Fluttershy
sang for you one last time?
Yup.
♪ (Fluttershy improvising)
Hey-o, you can find it, find
it in your heart yeah yeah!
♪ Find the music yeah yeah,
♪ it's in you right now,
oh yeah, ♪
♪ you can find the music,
I love the music yeah! ♪
All: Fluttershy?
(teeth chattering)
(screaming cheers)
(horror sound effects)
(frightened shouts)
Big Mac!
You got some 'splainin' to do!
Turkey call?
Eeyup.
Trash yer voice?
Zecora remedy?
Eeyup.
Not quick enough?
Nope.
Needed a deep voice?
Eeyup.
Poison Joke?
Flutterguy?
Eeyup.
Better now?
And that shy filly was living
her dream in the shadows
because she couldn't
bring herself
to come into the
spotlight?
Eeyup.
Well, for corn's sake!
Let's go!
Twilight: Fluttershy?
You in here?
Yes.
I'm here.
Pinkie: That was
totally unbelievable!
I mean, the curtain came
up, and there you were,
singing in front of everypony!
And, you know, I don't think
any pony was jealous
cause there certainly
wasn't an angry mob!
But it must have been horrible
standing there on stage!
All eyes glued directly on you.
It's like you were living your
own personal worst nightmare!
(sobbing)
It was!
(frantic sobbing)
What? Too much?
(crying)
What Pinkie meant to say was
that you were really great.
Wait! Didn't I say that?
Hardly!
Whoops!
YOU WERE GREAT!
You totally blew
my mind!
Incredible!
Though, no offence, you
kind of sounded like a dude.
(sobs)
A great sounding dude!
Well, thank you all.
I'm glad you enjoyed it...
...because I'm never going to
sing in front of anypony
ever again.
(gasp)
Oh no!
Are you kidding me?
Can we please
stop running!
(panting)
I just don't understand
why, Fluttershy.
After all, you're the one
that wanted the Pony Tones
to sing for every silly
thing that was requested of us.
You mean, you knew I
really wanted to perform?
Of course I knew!
Oh.
And for all her babbling, Pinkie
Pie was right about one thing.
Only one?
When that curtain fell, and
everypony saw you singing,
you lived your worst nightmare.
Was it really that bad?
Yes!
Well, what was so bad about it?
The thunderous
applause?
The praise for your
fantastic singin'?
The SCREAMING FANS?
♪ There's music in the treetops
and there's music in the vale ♪
♪ and all around the
music fills the sky. ♪
♪ There's music by the river and
there's music in the grass. ♪
♪ And the music makes your
heart soar into flight. ♪
When you find you've
got the music,
♪ You've got to look
inside and find. ♪
♪ Find you've got the music
♪ The music deep inside you.
♪ Find you've got the music.
♪ Cause when you look
inside you'll see it. ♪
♪ You're going to find,
you're going to find. ♪
♪ Got the music, got
the music...in you! ♪
(cheers)
You did it,
Fluttershy!
See? That
wasn't so bad.
And you didn't look completely
petrified by the fact
that we're all staring
at you at all!
How do you feel?
Surprisingly OK!
Rarity: Fantastic!
Because the Pony Tones
have been booked for the
Apple Family's Zap Apple
Jam Extraordinaire!
Oh no! I couldn't
do that!
Why not?
How come?
Seriously?
I'll get there someday.
But for now, baby
steps, everypony.
Baby steps.
Fluttershy: Sometimes
being afraid can stop you
from doing something
that you love.
But hiding behind these fears
means you're only hiding
from your true self.
It's much better to
face those fears
so you can shine and be the best
pony you can possibly be!