You know the worst thing about
you being the Princess of Friendship?
The dishes.
Thanks for taking
care of that, Spike.
After three events in one week,
I really needed to
relax with a good book.
It's kinda funny, isn't it?
All these ponies coming to you
for advice about friendship.
What's funny about that?
Well, you know, cause
you used to be famous
for being such a bad friend.
What are you talking about? I
had good friends in Canterlot.
Come on, Twilight,
look at the wall.
Do you see any photos from
before we moved to Ponyville?
And look at you now. The
Princess of Friendship.
This is a disaster!
All my old friends. I can't
remember any of their names
right now, but do you
really think that they think
I'm a bad friend?
Well, I only meant that
you've come so far.
You're a great friend now and--
Oh, I feel terrible! I've
got to make it up to them.
Pack a bag, Spike! We're
going to Canterlot!
And make a list of
my friends' names.
Aw, me and my big mouth.
Regular subtitles by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Come on, Twilight.
You're getting worked
up about nothing.
The only logical place to
start is at the beginning.
Whoa...
It's exactly
how we left it.
Look! It's "Predictions
and Prophesies!"
And it's still opened to
the Elements of Harmony!
And here's that present I
was gonna give Moondancer!
Eh, guess she won't be needing that.
Hey, look! The rest
of it's still here!
How could I have
let this happen?
Come on, Twilight.
Princess Celestia gave
you an assignment.
No pony could blame
you for that.
But look at the way
I left this place.
It's a total mess!
Just like how I
left my friendships.
I've got to make it up to-
Oh, uh, Minuette,
Twinkleshine, Lemon Hearts,
Lyra Heartstrings,
and Moondancer.
Yeah. Them.
Spike! Come on!
We've got work to do!
Have you been awake all night?
I did a little research
and I think I know
where we can find Minuette.
That is one of my
friends, right?
Uh, it's not too late to
forget I opened my big mouth.
No, Spike. I'm glad you
opened your big mouth.
These ponies have
probably been suffering
ever since I left, wondering
why their supposed friend
would treat them so badly.
Minuette?
Twilight Sparkle,
you old so-and-so!
What are you doing
here? Hey, Spike!
Look at these wings, huh?
Hey, grab a picture of me
and the Princess, will you?
I tried to tell my coworkers
we used to be friends
back when, but they've
never believed me.
Wait wait wait; really
fluff 'em up, huh?
So what are you doing here?
I mean, I know you're
here all the time,
but you never come to see me!
Hey! I just had
the greatest idea!
You want to go see Lemon
Hearts and Twinkleshine?
Of course! My old friends!
It'll be great!
Come on, let's fly!
Get it? Heh-heh-heh.
This is perfect!
I can apologize to all
three of them at once!
Let's hope they're not as
traumatized as Minuette.
She did! Twinkleshine
literally spit out her oats
when she heard you were the
Princess of Friendship!
We saw you at the coronation.
That was some shindig!
You did?
Sure! We see you all the time.
You remember our old
friend Lyra, right?
She lives in Ponyville, too.
We're always over
there visiting her
or she's coming over here.
We've thought about
asking you to join us
from time to time,
but we just sorta
figured you'd moved on.
Oh.
So what brings you by, anyway?
All those times you've
come back to Canterlot,
you've never had
donuts with us before.
Well, uh, you see...
I came to apologize.
For what?
Before I left Canterlot,
I didn't really
appreciate my friends.
And that's because I didn't know
how important friendship was.
But I've learned so much
since I moved to Ponyville.
I learned what it means
to be a good friend
and that I certainly wasn't
one to the three of you.
So, for all the pain I caused
you, I am truly sorry.
Aw, come on, Twilight!
Sure, it might've stung a
little bit when you ran off
to Ponyville without
saying goodbye,
but it's not like we weren't
used to that from you!
Yeah, we didn't
take it personally.
But it's really
good to see you now.
Hey! Anypony up for a
blast from the past?
It's our old science lab!
I have so many great
memories of this place.
Remember when Lemon
Hearts got her head stuck
in that beaker?
...but according to this book,
you're supposed to add the
sodium chloride first.
I read ahead and to
make a proper salt lick,
you need to add
the molasses first.
Well, I read ahead
too, Moondancer,
and I'm sure it said
sodium chloride first.
Oh, I've got the wrong
book. That's so hilarious.
Whatever happened to Moondancer?
Moondancer?
Yeah, you know,
our other friend.
Oh right, Moondancer!
I remember her!
I wonder what she's up to.
Yeah, I always liked her.
We just sort of lost
touch after you left.
I think she went to live out
by the stadium, didn't she?
Well, let's go see!
I think this is the place.
Didn't used to look
like this, though.
Moondancer?
What do you want?
I'm trying to study.
It's us! Your old friends--
Ugh!
That's old
Moondancer, all right!
She always did like her books.
Hey, kinda like you
used to be, huh?
Exactly how I used to be.
Come on, Twilight, we've been
watching her for three days!
Library, house. Library,
house. That's it.
Nopony looks at
her or says hello
or even gives her a smile.
It's like she
doesn't even exist!
Was she always like this?
Well, she always
was a little shy.
But for a while there she
was really starting to
come out of her shell.
Remember when she
threw that party?
Oh,right. I think you might
have been busy that day.
There you are, Twilight!
Moondancer is having
a little get-together
in the west castle
courtyard. You wanna come?
Ooh, sorry girls. I got a lot
of studying to catch up on.
Thought she might finally
be letting her guard down
a little with that party.
We invited her out a
few times after that,
but she was always
too busy studying.
So eventually we
just stopped asking.
I had no idea that party
was so important to her.
I've got to find a way
to make it up to her!
Oh my gosh! Moondancer? Is that--?
SSSSSHHHHH!
Moondancer? Can I talk
to you for a min--
SSSSSHHH!
What is this?
Eh, a bubble of silence.
I haven't seen
you in a while
and I thought it might
be nice to catch up.
For what purpose?
You know. Cause we're friends.
SSSSSHHHHH!
I'm really sorry to bother you.
I was just hoping we could go
outside and talk for a bit.
I'm sorry I skipped your party.
AAH!
SSSSSHHHHH!
Why won't you leave me
alone? I'm trying to study!
You've got the wrong pony.
I don't have parties.
You did once.
And I was so caught
up in my own studying
that I didn't take your
feelings into account.
Look, Twilight Twinkle--
Sparkle.
Whatever. I just need to be
alone so I can study
without some crazy pony trying
to make friends, all right?
Fine.
Wait.
How did you get into
my book like that?
I've been studying a
new studying technique.
I can only do it
for a few minutes,
but you'd be amazed how
much you can pick up
when you're
actually in a book!
That's one of Haycart's methods.
You know Haycart?
Of course! He's a genius!
I have a copy of his "Treatise
on Ponies," you know.
What is this place?
This is where I used to live.
You mean I never had you over?
A first edition of
"Principles of Magic"!
Hey. Didn't I
give this to you?
Maybe?
I did! Look, I even wrote
something:
"To my friend,
Twilight Sparkle.
Thanks for introducing
me to the classics."
I can see by the fact
that you left it here
that it meant a lot to you.
Look, I didn't
bring you over here
for even more poignant reminders
of what a bad friend I was.
I brought you here
to give you this.
You can come here
whenever you want
and study to your
heart's content.
Really?
But first you've got
to do something for me.
What?
Have dinner with our
old friends tonight.
I can't; I'm reorganizing
my biology scrolls.
I've been spending a lot of time
with Minuette, Twinkleshine,
and Lemon Hearts since I've been
back. They really miss you.
Look, I already told you,
the last thing I need
is a bunch of ridiculous
friend-making
keeping me from studying.
Moondancer, wait!
A wise pony once taught me
that there's more to life
than dusty old books.
I tried friendship and
it's just not for me.
Now if you'll excuse me.
What if I taught you
Haycart's method?
So, uh, what are you
studying these days?
Science. Magic. History.
Economics. Pottery.
Things like that.
Yowza! You plannin' on being
a professor or something?
No.
So you're just...studying?
Can I go now?
Moondancer, please.
It's all right, Twilight.
We're having a good
time. Right, everypony?
So, uh,Spike, tell
Moondancer that story about
how Twilight had to read a
book about doing a sleepover.
"Slumber 101"? I've read that.
Oh, heh-heh, really?
Well, uh, did you know
Lemon Hearts here works
at the Canterlot palace?
Yeah, it's true. I do
the big events, mostly.
State dinners, that
sort of thing.
Ugh!
Moondancer! You've got to
give friendship a chance!
I gave friendship a
chance a long time ago.
It didn't work out then. It
isn't going to work out now.
Twilight? Are you all right?
No. No, I'm not.
Wh-where are you going?
I don't know, Spike, I really
messed this one up.
That party was
everything to her.
I can only imagine what
it must have felt like
when I didn't show up.
Hey, Moondancer! Look
at this spread, huh?
Thank you so much for coming!
Of course! We wouldn't miss one
of our best friend's parties!
Is Twilight coming?
Oh. OK.
Hey, we'll still
have fun, right?
Sure.
If there was only a
way to undo the damage.
I know what I need to do.
And I know just who can help me!
Huh. Guess they must have
gone back to Ponyville.
Wheeee!
Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
That was AWESOME! We gotta go
flying more often, Twilight!
There you are!
I thought you threw in the
ol' towel and headed home!
I did head home, but not
to throw in the towel.
I went to get my secret
weapon. Minuette, meet--
Hey, Pinkie Pie!
Hi, Minuette!
Twilight, you didn't say
Minuette would be here!
You two know each other?
Oh, sure! She was one of
Cadance's bridesmaids.
We hang out all the time
when she's in Ponyville.
Didn't you know that?
Hah! And you call yourself
the Princess of Friendship!
Twilight briefed me
on the way here.
We'll need fifteen
bags of confetti
and as many hooves
as we can get.
Let's go! We can pass by
the donut place on the way!
And what are we gonna do?
Just come with me.
Oooh, "A Brief History
of the Wagon Harness"!
"The Life and Times of
Marwari the Maneless"?
What is this?
It's a party. For you.
SURPRISE!
Come on in!
Uh, thanks, but no thanks.
I don't do parties.
I know. And I think
it's my fault.
Back when we were
in school together,
you invited me to a party.
I was so focused on my
studies that I didn't show up.
Big deal.
It was a big deal.
And now that I realize how
important friendship is,
I'd like to make up for my
mistake with a new party.
A party in honor of
my friend, Moondancer!
Please, you've got to let
me make this up to you.
And you think this is
going to do it, huh?
Er, Yes?
Well, sure, why wouldn't it?
That was only the first time I
ever put myself out there
and then you didn't
even bother to show up!
Then you left town
without saying goodbye,
even though we were
supposed to be friends.
I was humiliated! I felt
like I wasn't important!
I never wanted to let myself
be hurt like that again!
Those three finally convinced
me that I had value!
That other ponies might like
me and want to be my friend!
And YOU! DIDN'T! SHOW! UP!
You're right; this party can't
make up for the way I hurt you.
But please, don't let my
mistake be the reason
you can't be friends
with anypony else.
We were your friends then,
and we'd be honoured
to be your friends now!
What? That's the librarian,
the book seller, my sister!
You've got a lot of
friends, Moondancer.
I'm sorry, Moondancer.
I've faced magical creatures,
the end of Equestria...
all sorts of things.
But seeing how my
actions affected you,
that was one of the worst
feelings I've ever had.
Thank you, Twilight.
I never realized how much
I needed to hear that.
Now come on, everypony!
Let's party!
Right?
Right!
I think it's time for
us to go, Moondancer.
Thank you for helping me
make some new friends.
Even if they are
my old friends.
We'll come back and visit soon.
That would be great!
You've still got to teach
me that Haycart technique.
Deal.
Um, Moondancer? It
got kinda banged up,
but here's a little
something I wanted to give you
back at your first party.