Pinkie: Five hundred
and sixty-six,
five hundred and sixty-seven...
five hundred and sixty-eight!
Phew!
Look at that, Pound Cake.
I am so close to breaking my
personal cupcake icing record!
My goodness! I can't believe
what I'm seeing here!
Pretty impressive,
if I do say so myself.
Pinkie, would you mind
watching the counter
while I pop to the supply room?
We've just received
a very special order
and the ingredients
need to be perfect.
Okie-dokie-lokie.
Thanks, dear!
A baby?
[pop]
Shining Armor and Princess
Cadance are having A BABY?
This is the best news ever! I
can't wait to tell Twilight!
Oh, and Pinkie? Uh, it's
a Top Secret surprise!
Shhhhhhhh!
A Top Secret Surprise?
But that means I have to keep
the exciting news... [gulps]
... to myself!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Even though I
didn't technically
make a Pinkie Promise
to Mrs. Cake,
I can't tell Twilight
or anypony the big news.
That would make me a... a...
big ole' surprise ruiner!
Right, Gummy?
Did you take that
from Pound Cake again?
Don't you know it's wrong
to steal from a baby?
What's all this
about a baby?
What? Who? What? Who said
something about a baby?
You did, Miss Pie. Just now.
What were you talking about?
[pop]
Twilight: Great, everypony's here!
Now I don't have
to wait any longer
to tell you all
the wonderful news.
Somepony special is
coming to visit Ponyville!
And I need your help
getting everything ready.
[excited chatter]
It's...
[Both at once] Shining
Armor and Princess Cadance!
Yes, and they're coming--
Tomorrow!
Yes, on the--
Friendship Express rather
than the Crystal Empire train
so as not to cause
too much of a scene
when they skip
town to come visit?
Yes.
Aaaaaand?
And that's it.
Oh.
Uh, how did you
know all that?
Hehe, heh, uh... Pinkie sense?
So, you said you needed
our help with something?
Follow me.
Sweet posters! Is
that Smash Fortune?
It sure is.
When Shining Armor said he
wanted to come to the castle
and visit, I started
collecting things he liked
when he was a colt
as a surprise.
Surprise?
[nervous giggle]
I've been so excited that it's
been hard to keep it to myself.
I have no idea what that's like.
Aww, look at the
cute little ant farm.
[screams]
And check out all
these old comic books!
Be careful; they're
mint in bag.
[whoosh]
[casual whistling]
What's this?
This is Brutus Force!
Shining Armor used to carry
him around like his baby.
Yeah, ha ha, really
cute, [forced laughter]
It is a bit juvenile
for castle decor,
but it is very sweet of you.
I'm sure Shining
Armor will love it.
Me too. But, there's a few
more things I'd like to add
before he gets here
and I could really use
a hoof collecting them.
Whatever you need, sugar
cube, we'll help Yeah get it.
[agreement]
Thanks, everypony.
I just can't wait till they
walk in and see everything!
Totally understandable. Watching
somepony else be surprised
with something is almost
better than being the one
who's getting the surprise!
But what if the surprise is
something so incredibly exciting
that a pony can't
keep it in any longer
and she has to tell the pony
who's standing next to her
what it is or she might explode?
I would say... no.
The pony who ruins a
surprise for somepony else
has to live with that
guilt... FOREVER!
[nervous laugh] Gotta bounce!
[pinball bumper bells clanging]
So, I know the bar
is set pretty high...
but does anypony
else think Pinkie Pie
was acting weirder than usual?
[zoom]
[panting] Phew! That
was close! Too close.
I almost spilled the beans.
Beans that would be
really hard to clean up.
I obviously can't be around
my friends right now...
or anypony for that matter.
Hmm. That's it! If
Shining Armor and Cadance
are coming tomorrow, then all
I have to do is lock myself
in my room away from
everypony until they arrive.
Then I won't ruin anything!
Oh, good. You're back.
Mrs. Cake needs my help but
these deliveries can't wait.
I can't thank you enough
for agreeing to be my backup
delivery pony, Pinkie!
I did?
Maybe I should hire somepony
to be my backup delivery pony.
Pinkie: I'll do it!
Really?
Sure! There's no possible way
that I could ever have anything
that might interfere
with doing that task-
like a gigantic,
emotionally-exhausting surprise
that would make it super hard
to be around other ponies.
Great! You're sure you
won't change your mind?
No way. Cross my heart, hope to
fly, stick a cupcake in my eye!
Oh, yeah. I
Pinkie-promised I'd do it.
And I never break a
Pinkie Promise. Never!
Well? Thanks again.
You're a real cake saver!
[groan]
Maybe it'll be a quiet day and
I can just avoid everypony.
♪♪
Hi, Pinkie Pie!
Heard any good
gossip today?
Yeah. We're bored.
Please say you have
some interesting news!
Nope!
[whoosh]
Oof!
Fluttershy! What a surprise!
I mean, not a surprise.
You were in such a rush earlier!
Twilight wanted me to ask you
if you would bring some snacks
to the castle for Shining
Armor and Cadance's visit.
Definitely. Got it! Pinkie
Promise. Yeah. Uh huh.
You know, maybe
some baby carrots...
Ha ha ha! What did you say?
Baby carrots! They're
Shining Armor's favorite.
Mine too! Baby carrots are
like big carrots but smaller,
kinda like how foals are tiny
versions of their parents
but smaller and cuter and...
Albino squirrel!
Where? Is it Albert?
♪♪
It's time to kick this
operation into hyper hoof.
And avoid all ponies
by any means necessary.
♪ [lively accordion and tuba] ♪
♪♪
It didn't feel good ignoring
my friends like that.
Maybe I can tell just one
little pony the surprise?
The pony who ruins a
surprise for somepony else
has to live with that
guilt... FOREVER!
You're right, spooky
reflection of Rarity
that I know is actually
my own imagination!
I can't tell anypony at all.
[sighs] Then they
would tell Twilight
and she wouldn't be surprised!
And it would be all my fault!
[sigh] Finally! I'm
all aloney on my owney.
[rustling]
Wow, great idea.
I'm starving too!
This apple is delicious.
What are you having, Gummy?
Oh, no!
It's the list that Twilight
helped me make yesterday
so I wouldn't forget all of
my Pinkie Promises today!
And I have three
more things to do.
Four if you count bringing those
snacks to Twilight's castle.
I've been getting liberal with
those Pinkie Promises lately.
♪♪
Ooo! I want a flamingo!
I want a goldfish!
Surprise me!
[baby cries]
Is that a baby bottle?
Aaah! No! It's a...uh...puppy.
Haha. Woof woof! Haha!
Are you sure? Because
it looks like a--
Next!
A baby pony, please.
Unless, of course that
would be a royal pain.
Interesting choice of
words, Featherweight.
Was it?
I don't know. Was it?
Uh, maybe you'd better
just make me a giraffe.
[clanging drawers]
My! Your friends weren't kidding
when they said you had a
great filing system, Pinkie.
You are Ponyville's
best kept secret!
No, I'm not!
Speaking of secrets...
have you ever known
somepony else's secret?
No.
A surprise that was
so big and exciting
that it was all you
could think about?
Nope!
Oh! Me, neither!
Oh, ho ho ho! That's just
what I wanted. Thanks, Pinkie.
You're welcome!
Oh, by the way, could
you help spread the word
about the big crib
sale I'm having?
"Treat your foal like royalty"?
Ha ha ha ha.
Pretty good slogan, huh? I
came up with it all by myself!
[screams]
Well, I thought it was clever.
♪♪
Those look yummy,
Pinkie! Let me help you.
But we'd better cover them
up so they don't get spoiled.
Why would they
get spoiled?
We're all going to
eat them super soon.
Oh, didn't
anypony tell ya?
Shinin' Armor and
Cadance are held up.
They might not arrive
until Saturday.
WHAT?
[hyperventilating]
You mean... I have... to
wait... another whole day?
I don't know if I can!
Pinkie Pie, do you have
something you need to say?
You seem like you've been
keeping something in.
Aaaahhhh!
We're here to listen.
Well, go on then, sugar cube.
We're not going to
judge you, darling.
You'll feel so much better once
you get it off your chest!
[deep breaths in and out]
Come on. Whatever it is. You
can tell us. We're best friends!
Friends, friends,
friends. Tell, tell, tell.
OK! OK! You win!
SHINING ARMOR AND CADANCE
ARE GOING TO HAVE A--
... an awesome weekend
with the best little sister
in all of Equestria!
[giggles] Hi, everypony.
[sighs heavily]
Shining Armor!
Cadance! You're early!
I thought something had come up
and you weren't going to
make it until Saturday!
So did we. Turned out we
weren't needed in Maretonia
until next week.
And the summit we were
supposed to attend today
had to be
rescheduled so...
we got here even
sooner than planned.
Surprise!
It's wonderful to
see you all again.
[happy chatter]
I'm so glad you're here. I
have a big surprise for you!
Oh, yeah?
[chatting excitedly]
Lucky we came
when we did, huh?
I'm guessing you saw the scroll
we sent to Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
Hey, I'm impressed you've been
able to keep our secret this long.
So you're gonna
tell Twilight now?
[chatting excitedly]
You're going to have to wait
just a little bit longer.
We have something
special planned.
It'll be worth it, I promise.
It'd better be.
So do ya think Shining
Armor liked his surprise?
Didn't you see him? He
couldn't stop raving about it!
Where did Shining Armor and
Cadance say they'd meet us?
I'm starving.
In the town square.
I wish they'd waited
to walk over with us,
but they said they had something
to take care of first.
They're going to have a lot
more to take care of soon.
What?
Nothing!
That's odd. Usually
they're quite punctual.
Ughhh, I need a hayburger
in my belly right now.
What's this?
[gasp]
What does it say?
A scavenger hunt! Shining Armor
used to set these up for me
when I was a filly.
At the end, there was always
a big prize like a new book,
or several new books, or--
We get the picture!
You like books!
So what's the first clue?
I hope it's something
about eating lunch.
"You've got a scroll,
you're on a roll.
Why don't you take a peek, where
young ones spend their week?
A piece of paper will
continue this caper."
I've got it!
"Where the young ones
spend their week!"
I'm not quite followin'...
[clanging bell]
It's the Ponyville Schoolhouse!
Good enough for me! Now
where's the next clue?
[sniffing]
Ah-choo!
EXTRA! EXTRA! Get your Ponyville
News! Read it in the paper!
EXTRA! EXTRA!
"A piece of paper, will
continue this caper".
It's in the Foal Free Press!
Ooh! Look at that dress
Mayor Mare is wearing
in the social report.
Why, it's stunning!
Uh, didn't you make
that, Rarity?
Yes. What is your point?
FOCUS, EVERYPONY!
You know, there's
really no time limit
on these scavenger
hunts, Pinkie.
AHA! There!
"Though this hall
is rather small,
in it you'll find
files of all kinds.
Take a look on the back, of the
birth certificate of Applejack!"
I don't like where
this is goin'.
[galloping hooves]
Baby! A ROYAL BAA---
Ahem!
Does anypony know where the
birth certificates are kept?
Ooo! I do! I do! Go down that
hall, then you take a left,
and then a right, then another
right, then a slight left,
then it's the third
door from the right.
Wow, Pinkie. I never knew you
knew so much about Town Hall.
There's a lot of
things I know...
that you don't know I know!
Oh, you're so
cute! [giggling and cooing]
"This next place is where,
you can buy a table or chair.
Or some comfy beds to
rest little heads."
Gah! Really? None of you?
It's obviously the furniture
store! Go in, go in, go in!
I don't know...
AHHHH! Fine.
[crashing]
Wow. You're scary good
at this, Pinkie Pie.
"It seems we've saved
the best for last,
we hope that you
have had a blast.
Now it's time to take a break,
where you can get
a slice of cake!"
Sugarcube Corner!
That was an easy one.
[bell jingles]
Surprise! Twily! Did you
like the scavenger hunt?
It was perfect.
Just like old times, except
even better because this time
I got to share it
with my best friends.
There's just one thing
missing, isn't there?
What's that?
The book prize at the end!
[chuckle] There's still a prize.
But it's a little
different this time.
Oh. I don't understand.
Hee hee hee.
All the places we sent you
today had something in common.
First we went to
the schoolhouse...
...and then we read
the Foal Free Press.
After that we found Applejack's
birth certificate...
...and then the last
clue was under a crib...
Hmm. School, foal, birth
certificate, and crib...
[gasps] Can it
be? Are you two...
WE'RE HAVING A BABY!
A baby, Twilight!
It's a baby! Woo hoo!
You mean... I'm
going to be an aunt?
♪♪
This is the best prize ever!
[laughter]
Ooh, I love you guys.
And I can't wait to
meet your little foal!
Neither can we.
[excited chatter]
I DID IT! I DID IT!
[pop]
Go, Pinkie.
[happy chatter]
You did it, Pinkie Pie!
You kept it a surprise.
Thank you. Was it much trouble?
Piece o' cake!