Rainbow Dash, I simply don't understand
why you can't just play the guitar you have.
Now I understand.
- How about this one?
- No.
- Lookie here!
- Super groovy!
- No, Pinkie.
- Well, whatcha looking for?
- That's the problem!
I need something that looks as awesome
as I'm gonna make it sound.
Hands off my guitar, Trixie!
I touched it first, Rainbow Dash!
Sounds to me like this is
a makin' for a nice, friendly competition.
All right!
Let's see who plays best!
A shred-off?
Shred on.
Check me out!
Uh, she can have it.
Turns out this is the one
that really speaks to me.
The Great and Powerful Trixie
always wins in the end!
I doubt it.
Twelve-thousand dollars?!
You'll pay for this,
Rainbow Dash!
No, silly!
If you want it, you have to pay for it.