♪♪
[thunder crashes]
-[all scream]
-Oh!
[quacking]
-[thunder crashes]
-[startles]
Aw, come on, a little lightning
never killed anyone.
Statistically speaking...
[all gasping]
See? Nothin'
to worry about!
-[clicking]
-What about
that flashing red light?
Huh?
That's just probably
the "everything is fine" light.
Okay, but hypothetically,
what if
it's the "everything
is not fine" light?
[gasps] Oh, no!
-[quacking]
-[screaming]
[roars]
Where are we?
According to the JWG,
we're off the tip of Greece,
and... wait.
This can't be right.
-I thought it was a myth.
-What? What is this place?
-Ithaquack.
-What?!
[all gasping]
-It's gorgeous!
-Look at that!
No. No, no, no.
We gotta go now!
Get this plane
in the air!
Sorry, Mr. McD,
gotta figure out
what this
flashing light means.
I always say,
better safe than...
whatever the opposite
of safe is.
Yeah. I do say that.
When have you ever said that?!
Hmm. Might as well
take a look around.
[cheering]
-No!
-Everyone stay on the plane!
-[cheering]
-Get back here!
-See ya!
-Bye-bye!
We're here!
We did it!
Yeah! Wait,
why did we do that?
-Dewey, this is Ithaquack.
-I'm sorry?
Home of legendary
Greek artifacts?
Oh, Greek--
What, what, what?
-Like the Spear of Selene--
-Selene! I knew it!
My mom's note to Scrooge
said she took
the Spear of Selene.
If we can find the spear--
Maybe we'll find out
what happened to her
and uncover Scrooge's
greatest mystery!
To the naos!
That's Greek for temple.
Okay, stop assuming
I know things.
Like, baseline,
assume I know nothing.
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ DuckTales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making DuckTales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some DuckTales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making DuckTales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring,
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, DuckTales! ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
[tropical music playing]
You're in my light!
No...we have
to get back
to the plane.
You don't know
what's out there.
What could be dangerous
about a beautiful Grecian
vacation island?
Hmm! Ha-ha! Hyah! Ha-ha!
Huzzah!
Kyah! [laughs]
Oh, glorious day!
May the fates sing
of your return,
friend Donald,
sailor of the seven seas!
Hiya, buddy.
[gasps]
Be these colorful creatures
your kin?
By Hephaestus's Hammer,
half-grown heroes in the making!
Um, who are you?
Your uncle must've told tale
of Storkules!
Colossus of Corinth,
hero of Heliopolis,
and, my proudest
accomplishment,
best friend
to Donald Duck!
[imitates explosion]
The Storkules
of Greek legend
is your best friend?!
Uh, more like
an acquaintance.
Ha-ha! Thine tongue
be as quick and mighty as,
well, me.
[quacking]
Donald! Get the boys onboard!
We can't let him
know we're here.
Can't let who
know we're here?
[thunder crashes]
[powerful voice]
Scrooge McDuck!
You dare defy the will
of Zeus?
The king of the gods?
Get out!
So many questions.
Do you control all storms,
or just lightning?
Does being immortal also
make you impervious to pain?
Do you cry?
[gasps]
You know where I can find
a good gyro?
[whispers]
Always ask the locals.
The myths are real!
This place is amazing!
It used to be amazing,
until Scrooge
and his mortal riff-raff
showed up and ruined it!
-What?!
[Webby]
"Dear Scrooge,
"I've taken
the Spear of Selene.
I'm sorry. Della."
We're close to the truth.
I can feel it.
What if my mom explored
this very path?
What if I'm literally
walking in her footsteps
right now?
[inhales deeply]
I can still smell her feet.
So we know Della
took the Spear of Selene
and betrayed Mr. McDuck
and Donald.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We don't know
she did something bad.
That note can mean
lots of things.
"I've taken
the Spear of Selene
to get cleaned."
I'm sorry
I spilled soup on it."
"I've taken
the Spear of Selene
back to the store.
I'm sorry
you already had one."
Happy Birthday!"
Oh! Or "I've taken
the Spear of Selene
from your money bin,
I'm sorry
I betrayed your trust."
Or--or probably
one of your things. Heh.
The only way to know for sure
is in...
the Temple of Heroes!
"Of Heroes"? Aha!
Pretty good sign
my mom wasn't a traitor.
[Zeus] Ithaquack was
the secret vacation spot
for gods and heroes.
And I was
the god of hospitality.
The King of the Beach!
Everyone loved me.
Then Scrooge showed up.
Defeated the unkillable Gorgon.
Found the lost treasure of Troy.
Was really good
at building sand castles.
Bah!
-Seems pretty fun.
-'Twas.
No, it twasn't!
Scrooge showed up
like he was so cool
and ruined it!
Och, jings.
Leave it to an immortal
to whine about
the good old days.
So, where is everyone?
They all left
when you did.
Said they didn't want
to party with a "lame god"
who couldn't even best
a lowly mortal.
There may have also been
a year-long lightning storm.
But now that you have returned,
Storkules, noble Donald,
and his fiery sister--
Halt! Where is Della?
I see.
Then we shall embark upon
a rousing adventure
to honor our fallen compatriot!
I don't adventure anymore.
What?! But adventure
is the very blood in your veins!
Well, we must at least
hold a feast
to celebrate your return!
-[cheering]
-What?!
Father, surely
the god of Hospitality
would not cast out
a crew of weary travelers.
Well, no, I guess not.
Ha ha! It shall be
a bacchanal for the ages!
-Beach party!
-[whooping]
[noisemaker toots]
[soft harp music]
Mmm! These are
the best graves ever!
[crunching]
A little salty.
Dip not good enough
for you, mortal?!
You offend Olympus!
Maybe people didn't leave
because they liked me,
but because
they didn't like you.
[whistling nonchalantly]
Ha-ha! Perhaps
some festive beach games
will lighten the mood.
Yes! A contest!
Your family versus mine
in a series of heroic trials.
Yea, all will know that we
are the superior party hounds
and return to the island!
This is exactly why
we stopped vacationing here.
But guys, epic trials!
Zeus!
Delicious grapes!
[thunder crashing]
You're not going anywhere.
-Whoo!
-Ah, phooey.
Careful!
According to legend,
the artifact in this chamber
holds a terrible curse
when removed from its pedestal.
Of course!
Scrooge must have
been cursed by the Spear!
"I'm taking the Spear of Selene
to de-cursify you.
I'm sorry
I probably won't survive."
She was a her--whoa!
This place is filled
with booby traps.
We have to be careful.
If my mom can make it across,
so can I!
[clank]
[whimpering]
It's okay. Shh.
It's okay.
We only have to do that
one more time to get out.
[gasping]
It was all worth it to find
the Sword of Selene!
Wait, what? This isn't
what we're looking for.
Where's the Spear?
It's a big temple.
We must have
the wrong antechamber.
Then we'll just have to find
the right one.
Nothing will stand
in our way!
[rumbling, crackling]
[low vibration]
The curse! Put it back!
Put it back!
[exclaims]
I love these tunics.
So breezy, so comfortable.
And surprisingly
slimming.
Storkules may have
brute strength,
but he's also an idiot.
You lads can use that
to your advantage.
I believe in you all!
Okay, son.
If you beat
Scrooge's family,
I'll be back on top.
Admired. Respected.
Blindly obeyed!
And why do you not compete
directly against Scrooge?
Well, obviously, people
would lose respect for me
if I were to lower myself
to his level.
Never mind that.
To your positions!
Whoever claims
Aeolus's Bag of Winds
first wins.
Understood?
Five or six questions--
On your mark, get set--
[thunder crashes]
[quacks]
[wind whooshing]
[Donald cries out]
We're never gonna beat him
like this!
Too breezy! Too breezy!
Idea!
Ha ha ha!
Well done, nephews of Donald!
What ingenuity!
From henceforth,
you shall be known as Hubert,
Tamer of Winds,
and Llewelyn,
Fighter of Storms!
-Awesome!
-Please do not say
my real name out loud.
Heh-heh. Satisfied?
Doesn't count!
They cheated!
Best two out of three!
[roars]
Ha-ha!
"Scrooge, I'm taking
the Spear of Selene
"to challenge
the gods of Olympus,
"but will probably
be eaten by a sea  monster.
I'm sorry. Della."
That's a possibility.
-[both yell]
-[roars]
You hideous monster!
I will avenge my mother
by killing you
with the very spear
you're sworn to protect!
You shall never get
the Spear of Poseidon!
I'm sorry.
The Spear of who, now?
The Spear of Poseidon!
Man! We got the wrong chamber
again!
We're looking for
the Spear of Selene.
Oh! Huh.
You're gonna want to go back
down the hall,
past the Harpy Aviary,
third door on your left.
Garden of Selene.
Can't miss it.
Oh, hey, thanks.
Sorry about calling you
a hideous monster before.
I'm sure you're very attractive
by sea monster standards.
Not really.
Thanks, though.
[both grunt]
Yahh!
Ha-ha! Huzzah!
[grrrr]
[horse whinnies]
[Donald cries out]
-[both] Whoo!
-Ha ha!
[groans]
Hmm.
Hmm?
Enough!
[thunder crashes]
Now comes
the ultimate challenge.
Steal the golden fleece
from this small child.
This is your
ultimate challenge?
There's no way we're gonna beat
Storkules on this one.
Steal? From a child?
But if I were
to do such a thing,
could I ever truly
be called a hero?
Donald, I am in need
of your wise counsel.
Donald?
Donald!
Oh! companion Donald,
where are you going?
Ah, look.
You're a nice guy, but...
The most nice guy,
for I am Storkules,
pure of--
No, no, no! I'm through
with adventure!
Someone always gets hurt!
But getting hurt
is part of the adventure!
What would
fierce Della say
is she could hear you now?
Well, she can't!
Ahh. Someone always gets hurt.
[Webby gasps]
A perfect 1:125th scale replica
of Ithaquack.
And look! There's a tiny chimera
on the hillside!
It's so adorable
I just want to slay it!
Focus. We're so close
to solving this.
The truth about my mom.
And one of the greatest
mysteries of Clan McDuck.
So, do we look
in the tiny houses, or...?
[loud clank]
[whirring]
[rumbling]
[both gasp]
[both] The Garden of Selene!
What's it say?
That Della Duck was a hero
who died nobly
trying to protect her family?
"Whomsoever
claims the prize inside
"shall find great riches,
but incur
the terrible wrath
of the gods."
[gasps]
It all checks out!
Della stole the spear,
angered the gods,
and brought their wrath down
upon her innocent family,
which explains why
Mr. McDuck and Donald
didn't want to land here. Ha!
That can't be true.
My mom would never
do that to her family.
[stone moving]
I guess we'll find out
for sure in the garden.
Let's go!
No.
-What are you doing?!
The door is closing!
-We're not going in.
But all the answers
we've been searching for
are in there!
I don't care!
My mom was a hero!
If I do not steal the fleece,
Father shall be incensed.
But if I steal
from a small, innocent child,
how can I ever
face myself again?
Just grab it already!!!
-I got it!
-Louie!
What? I'm also
a little kid.
It's fine.
-[sings haunting melody]
-Plug your ears!
No good ever came
from a creepy child singing!
[continues singing]
Oh! The child is actually
a mind-controlling siren!
Did I not mention that?
Storkules, finish them!
[siren continues singing]
Uh-oh!
-Ahh!
-Aah!
Please! The answers
are right through there!
-You can't stop me now!
-Don't have to.
Just have to hold you off
until the door closes!
You wouldn't!
I'll save you, tiny chimera!
No! My fists betray my heart!
Father! Stop this madness!
Mm-hmm?
[grunts]
[all cry out]
Just lay off, man!
It's not my fault
I best you at pretty much
everything I do!
Not helping!
Let me through, you no-good--
-[crackles]
-Aaaah!
Never--aaah!
adventure--ow!
again!--aaah!
-[Huey/Louie] Help!
-What?!
[stammering]
I must apologize in advance
for crushing your tiny bodies.
I want you to know
that as my best friend
Donald's family,
I consider you
my second-tier
best friends.
Farewell!
[Donald] Hey,
you big palooka!
Nobody gets hurt today!
[both grunting]
Aaah!
-Ha!
-Aaah!
Ha-ha! Whoa!
Dodge!
[quacking]
I'm gonna get my hands on you!
-[quacking]
-[grunting]
We're so close to the truth!
Why won't you let us find it?!
Because...
what if my mom
was a bad person?
-Okay.
-What?
This is one mystery
we don't have to solve.
Hmm.
[both grunt]
I need to know the truth--
whatever it is.
[both] Aaah!
Ha! Gotcha!
Heeeey, you're not Della.
You know Della?
Where is she?
Please tell me she wasn't
an evil family betrayer
and spear stealer!
Who are you, anyway?
Dewey, that's Selene,
the goddess of the moon.
Hi, I'm Webby.
I heard Scrooge and his family
were on the island,
so I wrote a super-spooky
prophecy on the door
to lure my friend Della.
It usually does the trick.
So, where's
the Spear of Selene, Selene?
-What spear?
-The one Della took
from your garden.
You mean the Sphere of Selene?
Why does no one
get what I'm saying?!
The Spear of Selene!
I've never had a spear.
Do you mean the Sword of Selene?
That's down the hall--
No! The Spear of Selene!
The one my mom took!
The one that's our only clue
to finding her!
Ah, your Della's kid!
I shoulda realized--
you're just like her.
I'm sorry. I haven't
seen her in years,
and I don't know what
the Spear of Selene is.
So we're back to
"she stole Scrooge's spear
and betrayed the family" then.
-Great.
-What? No way!
She loved her family
more than anything
in the world.
Della wasn't just a good person,
she was the greatest.
And she made
everyone around her better.
Maybe the spear
isn't an artifact.
Maybe it's something else!
Your mom did love
a good mystery.
Here. It's not a spear,
but it is a treasure
even Della never found.
Don't give up, young duck.
Your mother never did.
Mmm.
-[quacking]
-Know that I regret this
most bitterly.
Seems like old times,
eh, lad?
-[siren singing]
-Yeah!
-We gotta stop the singing!
-I'm on it.
[singing in ancient language]
What a magical voice!
Do you have any idea
how much money I could make
on a voice like yours?
Zeus just wants to use you.
I want to use you
to make us both rich.
What do you say?
[low, gruff voice]
You've got a deal.
Great.
[both grunting]
Huh?
Donald!
You have saved me!
Oh-ho-ho! Come here.
Don't hug the enemy!
What are you doing?!
They're best friends.
Acquaintances!
Perhaps we've been letting
our pride get in the way
for decades
and it's our families
who suffer.
What do you say?
Peace?
Does beating me
really mean that much to you?
Yes, absolutely.
Oh, fine.
One final challenge.
Winner gets all the glory.
Oh, I--oh, I cannae believe
I choked on the last round.
Yes! I win!
In your face, McDuck!
♪ I win, say it out loud ♪
♪ I win, you love it,
yeah, go, I win! ♪
[thunder crashing]
You may think
you're done with adventure,
but it will never
be done with you.
You're a hero,
whether you want
to be or not.
I do not. But thanks,
friend Storkules.
He called me his friend!
He said it back! Ha ha!
This is the most glorious day
of my entire life!
There you two are.
Right, let's get back
to the plane
before he comes up with
another cockamamie contest.
Thanks for pushing me
back there.
I promise I'll never stop
until we find the truth.
With this sphere
as my witness, I--
Ohh, no!
-No!!!
-[thunder crashing]
The wrath of the gods!
We should go now.
Okay. I think I found
the problem.
♪♪