♪♪
I'm Johnny,
the brains of the outfit.
And I'm his twin brother,
Randy, the handsome one.
And we got ahead
by building furniture.
For your feet.
Welcome to our...
This show is so dumb.
You could always
turn off the telly.
The remote's
way over there.
Oh, forget it.
Any big plans for today?
Thought I'd move to
the big TV in a few hours.
You know...
( belches )
Aahh! Do we have
any more Pep?
You've got six
full cans right here.
I only like
that first sip.
Peak carbonation.
Never mind, I'll call Beakley.
Oh, man,
my phone's dead.
Guess I gotta
buy a new one.
Just charge it.
Eh, this one's
three months old anyway.
Who cares? We're rich.
No. I'm rich.
That's it, laddie.
You are coming to the office
to learn the value
of a hard day's work.
Whatcha doin'?
- I'm not breaking in;
you're breaking in.
- Busted.
You think I put glitter
on my top-secret notebooks
just because it's pretty?
Well, sure,
it's a perk, but...
I'm sorry.
I was just looking
for information
about my family.
You shoulda asked.
What do you want,
shoe sizes,
horrible dark secrets
known only to
your Uncle Scrooge
that could change
the fate of the world
as we know it?
- What do you know
about my mom?
- ( gasps )
What do you know
about your mom?
Uncle Donald just told us
she was gone.
The only thing
we have of her is this photo.
Photographic evidence!
I've gotta add it to
my Della Duck file.
You have a whole file
on my mom?
Seriously? This is it?
I've been looking
into her for years,
but there's nothing.
No photos, no records.
No one even talks about her.
One time, a piece of
junk mail with her name
on it showed up at our door,
and a day later,
Scrooge bought the post office,
and I never saw
our mailman again.
Maybe he retired?
Bad things happen
to people who ask
about Della Duck.
So who are we gonna ask?
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duck Burg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck blur ♪
♪ Might solve a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Duck Tales
Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do,
bad and good luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
You have arrived
at your destination.
Be back at 6:00,
Launchpad.
We've a long, hard
day of work ahead of us.
Gotcha, Mr. McD.
Thanks for letting us
tag along, Uncle Scrooge,
but I suddenly very much
have to use the bathroom.
Oh, and I will show you
where to go to that place.
Oh, no, you don't.
( bell dings )
What is this place?
The private library
of Scrooge McDuck.
If there's info
about your mom,
it's in here.
Go away, Webby.
For the last time,
Mr. McDuck's archives
are strictly off-limits.
Except to
his family.
Meet Dewey Duck.
Behold, heir of
Clan McDuck,
the Archives!
( bell dings )
( gasps )
The money!
You want me to count
the gold?
Can we go out
and spend some gold
to make sure
it doesn't expire?
There's more to money
than just money.
Gold is a beautiful thing,
but even something
as small as a dime
can have meaning.
For instance...
Are you out of your head?
You'll crack your skull open.
But you swim in money
all the time.
Yes, but I worked hard
to perfect that skill,
building muscles
and dexterity.
If you want something,
you work hard to get it.
SECRETARY: Mr. McDuck,
the board is here to see you.
We don't have
a board meeting today.
No matter.
Come, lad.
Welcome to the fast-paced
world of business.
As you know,
revenues are down
in our international
markets--
Dawson, Lillehammer,
Eldorado, and Culebra.
We feel that--
Shut up, everyone.
I've done something brilliant.
Ah, Gyro.
Gyro Gearloose,
my head of
research and development.
- I'm sorry, but we--
- Apology accepted.
Now try to keep up
with my mind-numbing genius.
Gyro, what did we say about
interacting with other people?
The cards. Fine.
"Hello, Mr. McDuck,
and others.
Are you tired of all those
single-use gadgets
cluttering up
your junk drawer?
What a mess.
There's got to be
a better way!"
Meet Lil' Bulb,
the tiny,
all-purpose robot
that does it all.
Wait, what does it do?
It all.
Lil' Bulb is an artificially
intelligent
personal robot helper.
He can make toast,
find your keys,
serve as a book light
for your late-night reading.
You'll never have to do
anything yourself again.
Mm-hmm. And how do you
ensure this one
won't achieve sentience and turn
evil like all the others?
Only half my inventions
turn evil.
The other half
are just wildly misunderstood.
( buzzing )
What's it doing?
Waving. It likes you.
Request denied.
( sighs )
Keep at it, Gyro.
I know you'll come up
with something great.
Lil' Bulb
is something great.
I'll show you.
I'll show you all!
And maybe wait until
you're out of the room
to say that next time.
A robot that does
everything for you?
How could you
say no to that?
Part of hard work
is knowing how
to work with others.
My board are the only people
cheaper than I am.
I trust them completely to make
good financial decisions--
Indeed. Which is why
we've called this meeting
to discuss cutting
your unnecessary spending
here at the Money Bin.
Unnecessary?!
I'm Scrooge McDuck.
I don't spend one penny
more than I need to.
It's says here you're spending
$15 million
on magical defense.
Do you have any idea
how many vengeance curses
I have on my head?
Think I'm just
gonna go
and get a drink.
Yeah.
The Collected
Treasure Maps of Peruvia.
The Topographical Atlas
of Plain Awful.
Scrooge's Favorite Smells,
Volume 12.
Fresh cookies.
I knew it.
Focus, Webby.
We're here to find out
about Della Duck.
So the blue one seeks
to learn of his past.
But is he strong enough
to learn the truth?
Yes.
Wrong! You must first
prove yourself worthy
by passing the trials!
( coughing )
This is my new
favorite library.
( bell dings )
A dollar ten?
Who keeps dimes on them
anymore?
Sweet. Scrooge has
an emergency dime.
I'll pay you back later.
But how do you justify
spending $5,000
on a velvet pillow
for a dime?
That dime deserves
its own velvet pillow.
It's my number-one dime.
The first dime
I ever earned.
I was a young shoe shine
in Glasgow
when a man came in,
his boots cemented in mud.
I worked and worked until
those boots sparkled.
In return, he gave me
an American dime.
That dime inspired me
to move to America
and find my fortune.
It means more to me
than every bit of bullion
in my Money Bin.
( slurping )
( gulps )
Uh...
I gotta go. Bye.
Gotta get the dime,
gotta get the dime!
( sighs )
( panting )
( music playing
over headphones )
No, no, no, no...
( bell dings )
57?
Oh, boy.
( panting )
Come on!
Hey. Wait.
The dime!
Ahh!
Okay. Easy.
Break in, grab the dime,
sneak back downstairs,
Oh, maybe stop at
the vending machine.
Well, I'm dead.
WOMAN: Today we're gonna teach
you how to pick a lock.
First you need a small,
thin object, like a dime.
If I had that,
I wouldn't need the video!
No, don't switch to an ad.
This week on
Ottoman Empire,
we're working on an ottoman
for Flintheart Glomgold.
He wants an ottoman
with storage
by this afternoon!
( laughs ) They're never
gonna get that ottoman
tufted in time.
Focus!
Aw, there's gotta be
a better way.
Fools! They'll rue the day they
overlooked us, Lil' Bulb.
Ding!
Wait, hold the elev--
( groans )
So what do you know
about my mom?
Was she really
an adventurer?
Silence!
Behold your first test.
You must decipher the ancient
and mysterious code within.
Yes! I love codes!
Dewey, you start with
a Number Shift Cipher
while I try
a Monoalphabetic Substitution.
Pretty sure this is
just a library card catalogue.
Mystery solved.
Oh, yeah? If it's
just a card catalogue,
then how does it
know your name?
Come on!
( panting )
Hey, Gyro Gearloose.
If this is about
the Gearloose Magnetic backpack,
I specifically said
they should not be used
as school bags.
Blathering blatherskite,
one teen gets stuck
to a moving school bus.
No, no, no, no, no.
Louie Duck,
Scrooge's super-rich nephew.
Keep talking... sir.
I can't believe Scrooge
and that tired old
board of his
didn't see the potential
in Lil' Bulb here.
I'd love to invest,
but I'm gonna need
to test this little guy
out first.
Do you mind if I borrow
him for the afternoon?
Anything you say,
rich nephew.
Lil' Bulb, you be good.
Don't you rise up
against your masters.
Ha ha. Just a little
robot humor.
Wait. I need to go...
up!
( imitating Scrooge )
Put in a hard day's work.
I think I'm so much
smarter than--
Louie! Where
have you been?
Trying to get out
of work again.
What? No.
I just, um...
filled up my notepad
with all that precious
business wisdom,
so I went to go
find another.
Good lad.
You're free to take
as many pads as you want.
Or are we not allowed
to use those either,
ye penny-pinching
buzzards?!
No, but really.
Make sure to use the front
and back of every page.
And write small.
And that's how
you unlock a door.
- Good job, Louie.
- ( buzzing )
Finding one specific dime
in this mess
is gonna be
a pretty big job.
You better get to it.
It's, like, a dime.
Ah, you'll find it.
Ready to put your feet up,
Mr. Glomgold?
You call this
an ottoman?
It does not even
have my face on it.
Do it again!
( laughing )
In order to gain knowledge
from the Archives,
one must first
offer up knowledge.
Look, Quackfaster.
Normally I would be super-into
a mysterious conspiracy quest.
But couldn't you
at least give me
a tiny piece of
information on my mom?
Dewey, don't question
the ancient methods.
I'm just saying,
these are feeling a little
less like trials,
and a little more
like stalling.
It is not for us to understand
the ways of the Archives.
That is literally
your job.
I'm out.
She doesn't know anything.
No. None shall leave
once the Trials are undertaken.
There are those who would
destroy you for the knowledge
you seek.
( whispers )
Just like the mailman.
Who's gonna destroy me?
Scrooge? The government?
The Unicorn Illuminati?
- Me.
- Wait.
- What?!
GLOMGOLD: You expect me
to put my feet up on
my own face, you loons?
Do it again!
I used to hate this show,
but now, I kinda love it.
It's like every ottoman
tells a story.
Hey, you found it.
Great job... little buddy.
( shrieking )
If you can find me 3,000 gallons
of silver polish for cheaper,
I'd love to hear about it!
This is getting us nowhere.
If you won't make
your own cuts,
then we're forced to fire staff
at the Bin to save money.
The obvious choice
is the archivist.
Fire Quackfaster?! Never!
For 50 years, that woman's
level-headedness
has kept my archives
secure and orderly.
You disrespect the Archives,
you shall become
one with the Archives!
This isn't working.
Here. Knowledge is
the greatest weapon of all.
Fine. Quackfaster stays.
But Gyro is definitely
unnecessary.
Are you insane?!
Gyro Gearloose is
one of the most brilliant minds
of our time.
You miserable
piece of rust.
I am man,
you are machine.
Do as I command
or I will pull your plug.
Aaah! He's turned
against me.
He's sucking up
all the dimes. Help, help!
Oh.
If you're going to fire
all the employees,
why don't you just go ahead
and shut the whole Bin down?
You do have a perfectly
good office downtown.
Do you really need
a Money Bin?
I think we lost her.
Foolish child.
You do not know
what you think you know.
I don't know
anything,
and it's really
frustrating!
- Louie!
- Louie, over here.
( screams )
Uh, never mind.
Look, a distraction.
Lazy Tuesday
was an afternoon of TV.
Hard working
was giant robot attack.
Great life lesson, Scrooge.
No!
You are not evil.
You are good,
Lil' Bulb.
Good.
You cannot
get rid of the Bin.
You may think they're
crackpots and weirdos,
but they're the ones
who push innovation,
and creativity, and spur
this company ever forward.
Just a little malfunction.
Definitely not evil.
Look, they're all mad as loons,
and if you fire them,
they're definitely
going to seek revenge.
All in favor of
keeping the Bin
and everyone in it
far away from our offices.
ALL: Aye!
No!!
Come on!
( panting )
No. No, no, no, no, no!
Mine, mine. Wait!
Wait, wait, mine!
Of course.
Book throw,
book throw.
Throwing books.
This is our last book.
Make it count.
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer,
or the book gets it.
I will crease
this corner, man,
so back off.
Tell me about
my mom.
Why don't you
see for yourself?
This is it.
This is it!
This is...
nothing.
Wait. I've seen
that number before.
Follow me.
Just a dime,
just a dime.
Oh, a quarter!
Wait, there it is.
Oh, I know
what went wrong.
This is a 75-watt bulb.
Lil' Bulb's only built
for 50.
Ha ha, he just went
a little mad with power.
Whoa, what the...
So you write me a check or...
( growls )
A pleasure as always.
I'll be in my office
if you need me.
Please don't need me.
I don't understand.
It should be here
somewhere.
Wait. These books.
They're all
out of order.
Quackfaster's a lot
of things, but
she's not sloppy.
QUACKFASTER:
Use your training.
The most valuable knowledge
must be learned.
Okay, how much of this
is about us doing
your work for you?
About 50%.
Curse me kilts!
Come on, come on,
you got this!
Oh, there you are.
( panting )
I can't catch my breath.
Don't be so dramatic.
A little work
never killed anybody.
Okay, here goes.
Ow!
What is up
with this stupid library?
COMPUTER VOICE:
Duck family DNA recognized.
Wow!
Mom...
Why would this stuff
be hidden?
- I gotta show
Huey and Louie.
- Wait. What's this?
DEWEY: "Scrooge, I've taken
the Spear of Selene.
I'm sorry. Della."
Wait, what did she take?
Why is she sorry?
Did she betray
your Uncle Scrooge?
We can't tell anyone
about this until we
find out what it means.
I'm proud of you, lad.
You put in
a full day at the office.
I think you've
earned this.
You're giving me
your number-one dime?
It's not my lucky dime.
I never let my dime
out of my sight.
That was just a decoy.
I'm not an idiot.
This place is
full of lunatics.
A dime sure means more
when you have to work
for it, eh, lad?
Maybe I'll get my own
velvet pillow for this baby.
Oh, hold up.
Noooooo!!
Gyro creates robot.
Robot gains free will.
Robot turns on Gyro.
Gyro controls robot.
Gyro is robot.