♪♪
[Jack-in-the-box melody plays]
[sizzling]
[explosion booms]
[cackling]
Child's play!
-[glass shattering]
-Huh? Huh?!
No!
I will avenge you,
my bulby brethren!
Who would dare?
[Darkwing Duck]
I am the terror
that flaps in the night!
[chattering]
I am
the little roller skate
at the base
of villainy's staircase.
I am Darkwing Duck!
[Quarterjack]
Playtime's over!
Then I gotta get
a shorter intro.
Let's get dangerous.
-[sizzling]
-[grunting]
[both blubbering]
Big day, Dewey.
Mustard stain
or ketchup stain?
Mustard-- looks
less like blood.
What is this weird show?
Whoa, what?
Darkwing Duck?
The greatest TV show
of all time?
Ha! Maybe
when you were a kid.
This hero guy doesn't fly
or shoot lasers or anything.
That hero guy
is Jim Starling.
He was an old-school actor
who did all his own stunts.
Sure, he got
a little banged up
in later seasons.
[grunting]
Keep rolling.
But that just made him
even more heroic.
Why didn't he just use CGI?
[chuckles]
Real heroes don't need
high-tech
special effects
or basic
safety precautions.
So, how do I look?
Remember, Dewey,
a true hero thinks
with his gut
or not at all.
Right, D.W.?
Let's get dangerous.
What's the special occasion,
anyway?
I finally got
my driver's license.
-[engine starts]
-Uh, wait, what?
Aah!
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
-♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
-♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
[slow motion yelling]
[grunts]
How have you been a driver
without a driver's license?
Hey, come on. I've got
a pilot's license, don't I?
Wait, don't I?
Ugh! Aren't you worried
Scrooge will find out?
You kidding?
I had them mail the license
straight to him
so he'd be first to know.
Ah, he's gonna be
so proud of me.
[chuckles]
Wow.
[Dewey] The Bin,
The Bin, The Bin!
Slow down!
[tires squealing]
-[heavy breathing]
-I bet Mr. McD's got
some kind of party
planned for my big day.
Wouldn't want to
ruin the...
-[elevator dings]
-Surprise!
Huh.
Surprise!
Supplies?
Boy, he's really
getting my hopes up.
The payoff is
gonna be amazing.
Surprise!
-Shh! Quiet.
-Shh!
The Gearloose
Monophonicrail
converts aural input
into kinetic propulsion.
[Dewey and Launchpad]
Huh?
Sound-powered train.
-[both] Buh.
-Ah, sorry, Mr. McD,
but I thought you
might wanna hear--
I don't want to
hear anything.
This sensitive prototype
runs on noise.
Observe.
[humming]
Illumination,
Dr. Gearloose!
Alphanumerical
substitution!
The categorical
reorganization
of letters
to prime digits.
[sizzling, whirring]
Aah! My blueprints!
Sorry, Dr. Gearloose.
Intern, try to think.
But that's all I do
all the time.
Well, do it better.
Eh, you probably
couldn't fit a driver
in that tiny train
anyway.
Uh, say, speaking
of drivers...
Gyro, the board
needs results.
Ever since
Bulb Tech backfired
you need an invention
that, well...
Won't turn evil
and kill us all.
Due respect, sir, innovation
doesn't work that way.
I can't just wake up
one morning and say--
How about
a self-driving robot car?
-A what, now?
-Wah! Too many variables.
A self-driving robot car
would turn evil like that.
-Nobody could.
-Well, Mark Beaks did.
He just posted that he's
having a demo later today.
What?! That hack couldn't
even program a microwave!
[chuckles]
We'll see about this.
Okay, cool.
I'll just tell you
my big news later.
Launchpad,
I almost forgot...
-Yeah?
-Stop having mail
delivered to my office.
That's for incoming checks
and death threats only.
Wait, what does
"Smiley face, anvil,
roadkill" mean?
-Crushed it!
-[crowd cheering]
It's a hectic world
posting things online,
checking to see
who liked your post.
Couldn't you use
a little time for yourself?
Couldn't you use a BUDDY?
That's the "Beaks Unmanned
Driver Drone Yay!"
BUDDY will drive you anywhere
quickly, efficiently,
and cheaply!
BUDDY is compatible
with any vehicle,
making traditional drivers
a thing of the past.
The Waddle BUDDY system.
Because machines
are the new man.
And hold for applause!
-[applause]
-Boo! Bad!
-Do not like!
-Agreed.
Very negative feelings,
indeed.
Whoa, Scrooge's driver
and his chief inventor
are threatened
by my BUDDY here.
Well, that is
how you know it's
a good product. [laughs]
-[crowd murmuring]
-Uh, how can you ensure
that this machine
won't turn evil?
Huh. I've never
said that out loud.
Top secret Beaks tech means
this baby's 100% obedient
to its master.
-Next question, please.
-Oh, yeah?
Can you program a robot
to brave the unknown
and laugh at danger?
-Yes.
-Can a robot greet you
with a kind word
at the end of a long day?
-Yes.
-[BUDDY] That's a nice
gray cardigan, Mr. Beaks.
You are killing it today.
Huh. Yeah, well, can a robot
pull you from the wreckage
of a crash
with a reassuring smile
that tells you
everything's gonna be okay?
Well, no, because
it can't crash.
Wait, what, now?
I'm sorry, what was that?
BUDDY, show him.
[Beaks]
BUDDY's patented sensors
mean a smooth, crash-free ride.
No matter the situation,
you can count on BUDDY
to get you
where you're going safely.
Any more questions?
This automated marvel could save
McDuck Enterprises a fortune!
You're not seriously
gonna buy one of these things.
I mean, not when
you have plenty of good
driver/pilots already.
I may buy a whole fleet!
Unless anyone has
any brighter ideas.
[groans]
-A race.
-[both gasp]
What are you doing?
Thinking with my gut.
Me versus the bot.
Winner gets free candy
for life.
-[indistinct whispers]
-Oh, that's better.
Winner is named
the ultimate driver.
A race would give me a chance
to see how BUDDY performs
in a real-world scenario.
Ooh! Dramatic!
In! In!
In! In! In!
May the best man--
Ooh! Aah! Robot hand!
Very strong robot hand.
[suspenseful music]
-Aah!
-Aah! Look out!
It's a headless
man-horse!
He broke in to hoof us
all to death!
[Gyro] What?!
Don't be dumb.
I'm just trying out
some new interns.
Don't tell
my existing intern.
Manny, dispose of them
violently.
I can't have
any distractions.
No, wait.
I need help.
See, I have this friend.
Let's call him,
"Not Launchpad."
And he kinda challenged
a robot to a race.
Pretty common scenario.
Now, Not Launchpad definitely
isn't afraid of losing
and his boss replacing him
with a robot,
but he has a friend--
let's call him,
uh, "Launchpad"--
who is very worried about that.
So, I-- he-- they--
uh, thought you could help
figure out how to take
this robot down, yes?
Oh, in this scenario,
you're still you.
Dummy! There's some dummies
here to see you.
At your beck and call,
Dr. Gearloose.
I heard everything.
Everything.
I'm happy to prove my worth
by aiding Mr. McQuack.
Dr. Gearloose is working
on an innovation
that will better
all of mankind
both literally,
and figuratively.
Behold!
Operating passcode:
-Blathering--
-No!
That... [chuckles]
is not ready yet.
-Go to your room!
-Aah! Ohh.
Forgive Dr. Gearloose.
He's a little more
deranged than usual
trying to figure out
how Beaks beat him to
the self-driving car.
That won't be a problem once
I put that tin can in its place.
In the recycling,
where the garbage goes.
Woof. We'll work on
smack talk later.
Right now we need something
to help Launchpad
get the edge on BUDDY.
Step into my laboratory.
Your lab is in
the bathroom?
Dr. Gearloose says this is
the perfect place for my work.
I'm just now realizing
that remark
may not have been
entirely complimentary.
No matter!
So, how are we going to
soup up your car?
Frictionless tires?
Oscillating overthruster?
An engine that can bend
the very fabric of space itself?
Yes! All of that.
Eh, I don't know
about all these gizmos.
Can't you just give me
a couple pointers
on how to beat that robot?
Reprogramming a man's brain
to compete
with a sophisticated
auto intelligence.
Reprogram Launchpad?
What about thinking
with your gut
and getting dangerous?
Well, if Mr. McD thinks
this un-crashable robo-me
is so great,
I have to prove
I can get dangerous
in the safest way possible.
That's sure to get
Dr. Gearloose's attention.
[Intern] It could work!
[splashing]
I'll clean that later.
[Intern]
Don't go over 32 miles per hour.
And hit all turns
at a safe
35-degree bend.
And increase velocity
by 15% on straightaway.
These visual cues will trigger
psychosomatic synaptic reflexes
to improve your performance.
Did you get all that?
Yes.
Welcome to the
Waddle test track!
Time for the ultimate contest
between man and machine.
First around the block wins.
Don't worry, Mr. McD.
-I got this.
-Good lad.
Beat this bionic blackguard,
and I can probably
talk Beaks down on price
when I buy
a fleet of them.
Anyway, good luck!
Hey, you're the best
personal driver
I've ever had.
You got this!
[intern] Follow the tips,
and you have
a 51% chance of winning.
And whatever you do,
play it safe.
Don't crash!
Wait, don't crash?
Racers to your marks!
Let's get dangerous!
Get set...
[imitates lasers]
Hmm?
That means go!
And we're off.
Hands at ten and two.
Keep it in first gear.
Or was that hands at ten
and one and second gear?
Where's the index?
Oh, no!
[both]
Don't crash. Don't crash!
[grunts]
Gotta catch up!
Uh, check your six.
Carry the two.
[grunting]
Huh?
[panting]
17, other number, Q!
[BUDDY] Adjusting
for hazardous conditions.
[Launchpad grunts]
[Launchpad blubbering]
Whoa!
[straining, grunts]
Oh! He's gonna do it!
Go, you bumblebee-like savant!
-Go!
-[groans]
Whoo!
[groaning]
[grunts]
-[race horn blows]
-[sighs]
Ha ha! Yes! Did it!
Take that,
everyone who's not me!
Impressive display, Beaks.
You have really
built something here.
[Gyro] Or did he?
I couldn't be sure
until I saw how it performed
under pressure.
The precision,
the deadly grace.
Oh, yes,
I've seen it before.
Ha ha!
Beaks Tech
is actually Bulb Tech!
That's how he beat me
to the punch.
He stole my technology!
Officer, arrest this man!
-Is this true?
-Of course not.
I didn't steal it from him.
I stole it from
a public online forum,
then "Beaks'd" it up.
How would one
of my inventions
end up online?
[gasps]
-Oh, wow!
-You!
You circumvented
the kill switch.
Why didn't anyone else
on the message board
figure that out?
You posted
my top-secret plans
on the Internet?!
You were having so much trouble
keeping your inventions
from turning evil,
so I turned to the Net
to crowdsource a solution?
Rah!
-[Intern blubbering]
-[Dewey] Easy! Easy!
Gearloose,
calm down!
Fired!
No.
Uh, back to town, Mr. McD?
That's all right, Launchpad.
We'll ride
with Beaks and BUDDY
to sign the sales paperwork.
Come on, Dewey.
So, how did you keep
Bulb Tech from going bad?
-Say what, now?
-The morality circuits.
You modified them
to keep them from going evil.
No, I just made them
look less dorky.
They're
dumb robots, right?
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
[all screaming]
Room for one more?
[both sigh]
I have so many ideas,
but I try too hard
hoping at least one of them
will stand out.
[distant screaming]
Just vomiting them out
at random like,
"Blah. Solve world hunger.
Blah. Infrared toothbrush."
I just wanna help people,
you know?
-[distant screaming]
-Make them better.
Why? Even if you
try to be better,
there always someone
better than you.
Maybe with built-in Wi-Fi.
You'll just be ignored.
Best to stop trying.
Man, is there anyone
having a worse day than us?
[all screaming]
Churlish child locks!
Please remain seated.
Take that,
you pneumatic monstrosity!
Buckle up for safety.
Sanctimonious seatbelts!
Oh, we need a logic puzzle
to fry its circuits.
-Uh, robot, what is love?
-That's stupid!
Robot, could I
invent an element
so heavy even I
couldn't lift it?
[chuckles]
I definitely could.
No, you couldn't!
-Aah!
-[gasps]
Give it a rest,
geniuses!
[horn blowing]
Yes, you've replaced me
with a cool robot car.
I get it.
[group screaming]
BUDDY's gone glitchy.
-They're in trouble!
-What?
I may not be Mr. McD's driver
for much longer,
but he can still count on me
to get him where he's going.
I'll keep him busy.
You figure out a way
to get them out of that car.
I think I got
something for that.
You try corralling them
into a ravine, or--
I'll probably just
crash into it.
[engine revs]
Isn't that really,
really unsafe?
Tried playing it safe,
old friend-- didn't work.
-Let's get dangerous.
♪♪
Launchpad!
Give me your hand!
-[phone line ringing]
-Come on!
Pick up, pick up, pick up!
[phone ringing]
[hoof tapping]
Manny! Salvation!
I know we've had
our differences in the past,
but now we must put them aside
for the greater good
of scientific endeavor.
What say you?
It's me!
Fenton Crackshell Cabrera.
Just put the phone
up to the floor!
Operating passcode:
Blathering blatherskite!
[Launchpad straining]
Manny, did anything happen?
Whoa!
Please keep your hands and arms
inside the vehicle
at all times.
[grunts]
Aah!
Dewey!
[screaming]
-[gasps]
-Gotcha!
[laughs]
Wow!
Hold on, I'll get you
out of here... somehow.
Oh, good, another robot.
[suit]
Calculating options.
Activating shoulder blades.
I suggest you hold very,
very still.
[Scrooge groaning]
Oh, hey!
[Beaks, Gyro exclaim]
-[suit buzzes]
-Come on!
[suit]
Incoming threat.
Come on, suit, do something!
Defense mode activated.
Whoa, look out!
[Scrooge]
Who the blazes are you?
Call me...
Gizmoduck!
-Gizmoduck?
-Gizmoduck.
Suit, make it stop.
Make it stop!
Suit, help!
Activating gluteal grapple.
Ack, miss!
Uh, something else!
Activating pectoral parachute.
[Gizmoduck]
Stop, stop!
Brakes! Brakes!
Aah!
Huh?
-[gasping]
-You were a robot
this whole time, huh?
-Neat.
-I'm not a--
Warning, incoming threat.
Move!
[tires squeal]
-Aah!
[tires screeching]
For your safety,
please stop the vehicle
and return
to the passenger seat.
Looks like the only way
to survive is to crash.
Too dangerous!
[all laughing]
Take that,
you bucket of bolts.
Oh, I'm sorry, is that
offensive, or--
-I'm not a--
-[rocks crumbling]
[all screaming]
[suit]
Activate helmet-copter.
[laughs] Whoo-ooh!
I'm alive!
This is awesome!
Aww, looks like
somebody's first crash.
Have a good day, Mr. McD.
Nice work today, Launchpad.
See you tomorrow.
You're not gonna
replace me?
Replace you?
Don't be daft.
Where would I ever
find a driver
as crazy and dangerous
as I am?
Oh! Dewey told me about
your driver's license.
Congratulations.
[grunts]
Aww, your approval is
all the driver's license I need.
Come on.
[straining]
You should really
keep the license.
Sir, I was
cleaning out my desk
when suddenly
the prototype armor
burst from the chamber like
so many split atoms, and--
Eh, save it.
You're not fired...
Gizmoduck.
[sighs] Scrooge
is always complaining
my inventions
are dangerous.
This armor's gotta be
100% idiot proof,
and, well, you're just
the idiot to prove it.
Oh, thank you, sir!
You won't regret this.
This project stays top secret
till it's out of beta.
I won't tell a soul.
[Launchpad]
Bye, Gyro!
Bye, Gizmoduck!
From now on.
[sighs] Gizmoduck.
What a stupid name.
Gizmoduck--
I must have him.
[theme music playing]