Hoof-biting action overload!
She was like a stunt superstar.
Flying higher and higher...
...and then Rainbow Dash
swoopped down SWOOSH...
...and right before she hit the ground,
SHOOM she pulled up WROOM!
And then she looped around and around like
WHOO WHOO WHOO WHOO
WHOO WHOO WHOO...!
Rainbow Dash!
Pinkie Pie? Not again...
-Rainbow Dash!
-Not now, Pinkie Pie!
But... but Rainbow Dash!
I'm in the middle of something!
-But...
-I said NOT NOW!
I was gonna tell you to
look out for that mountain.
Hi! I'm looking for Rainbow Dash.
Have you seen her?
Hi there! Have you seen Rainbow Dash?
...Okay, thanks anyway.
Twilight! Have you seen
Rainbow Dash anywhere?
Isn't she right up there?
Rainbow Dash!
That was close...
Hi!
Hi again!
I need a favor, Rainbow Dash.
Oh, forget it.
I toootally promise it
will be toootally fun!
Oookay.
Over to the right.
No no, a little-little left... Wait! Back to the right.
Now a little leftish while staying rightly.
STOP!
Maybe a few inches to the south!
Now a couple centimeters north...
Okay... one more smidgemeter to the...
PINKIE PIE!!!
I mean... perfect! Now wait for my signal.
Oh, Rainbow Dash. We startled
Spike into getting a hiccup!
Good one, Pinkie *hic* Pie *hic*! You're
always pulling a fast one *hic* on me.
Oh no! You're not hurt, are you?
Na*hic*ah... Don't be *hic* silly *hic*!
Dragons are *hic* fireproof!
Oh. Okay. Good.
I wish the same thing *hic*
were true of scrolls.
Have you ever seen anything more hilarious?
I can think of one thing.
I didn't take you for a prankster, Pinkie Pie.
Are you *hic* kidding?! *hic* I LOVE
to pull pranks! It's all *hic* in good fun.
And Pinkie Pie lo*hic*oves
to have *hic* fun! *hic*
You know, Pinkie Pie? You're
not as annoying as I thought!
You wanna hang out?
That'd be... *HIC* I'd really... *HIC* When do...
*HIC* I mean... *HIC* Where would you...
A simple nod will do.
-Is she even home?
-I don't know... There she goes...
There she is!
Land sakes!
Is someone over there? Who're we gonna
squirt, who're we gonna squirt?
-Fluttershy.
-WHAT?
Nononononono...! We can't prank
Fluttershy, I mean, she's so sensitive.
It'll hurt her feelings.
Even the most harmless prank.
Yeah, you're right.
Huh. We need another victim,
who's made of tougher stuff.
So... who's it gonna be?
Oh! I've got someone in mind.
The toughest around.
Oh, awesome! Who? Who? Do I know them?
Oh yes! You're very close.
Good one, Pinkie Pie!
Rise and shine, Rainbow Dash! It's a brand
new day and we got a lot of pranking to...
Morning, Pink!
Gilda, this is my gal pal Pinkie Pie.
Hey. Whazzup?
Pinkie, this is my griffon friend Gilda.
What's a griffon?
-She's half-eagle, half-lion.
-And ALL AWESOME!
Gilda's my best pal from my days
at the Junior Speedsters flight camp.
Hey, remember the chant?
Sure. They made us recite it every morning.
I'll never get that lame thing outta my head.
Sooo...
Only for you, Dash.
Junior Speedsters are our lives.
Skybound soars and daring dives
Junior Speedsters, it's our quest
To someday be the very best!
Oh, that was awesome! And it gave
me a great idea for a prank!
Gilda, you game?
Huh. Well, I groove on a good prank
as much as the next griffon.
But Dash! You promised me we'd get
a flying session in this morning.
Yeah... Um... Well... Pinkie Pie,
you don't mind, do you?
Gilda just got here.
We'll catch up with you later!
Oh! Um... Sure, no problem!
Have fun, you guys! I'll...
just catch up with you...
...later.
Wow! That was sweet! Just like old times.
Yeah! Only faster. So now what?
-Hey there...!
-Huh?
...it's later...!
...and I caught up...!
Pinkie Pie, you are so random!
Hey Dash! Think you got enough gas
left to beat me to that cloud?
A race? You are so on!
One... two... three... GO!
Hey...!
-I win!
-As if! I won, dude!
-No way!
-Yes way!
Oh, come on! I was way ahead of you!
Wow, guys, that was really cool!
But I think Rainbow Dash beat you
by a teeny-weeny itty-bitty hair.
Or a teeny-weeny itty-bitty feather.
See? Good thing, Pinkie Pie's
here to keep you honest, G.
Okay, Dash! Last one to that cloud
up there is an oily dragon egg.
GO!
I think the high altitude is making you dizzy.
Wait! Guys!
Wow! You guys almost got
away from me that time.
So Dash. Got any new moves in your
tricktionary or are you 100% old school?
New moves? Hah! Sit back, G.,
this is gonna take a while.
-Hey, Pinkie. Come 'ere.
-Yeah?
Don't you know how to take
"get lost" for an answer?
Dash doesn't need to hang with
a dweeb like you now when I'm around.
You're dorkin' up the skies, Stinkie Pie.
So make like a bee and BUZZ OFF!!!
Try matching that!
Hey! Where's Pinkie Pie and
her crazy contraption?
Eh... She left. Something about
being as busy as a bee.
So, Pinkie Pie, are you sure that this
friend of Rainbow Dash is really so mean?
Um... Yeah! She keeps stealing
Rainbow Dash away...
...she popped my balloons and
she told me to buzz off!
I've never met a griffon this mean.
Or actually, I've never met a griffon at all.
But I bet if I had, she wouldn't
be as mean and grumpy as Gilda!
You know what I think, Pinkie Pie?
-Well, I think... you're jealous.
-Jealous?!
Green with envy. Well,
in your case pink with envy.
Well, yes. Jealous.
Listen, Pinkie, I don't wanna upset you...
...but just because Rainbow Dash has
another friend doesn't make Gilda a grump.
I mean, perhaps it's you, Pinkie,
who needs to improve her attitude.
Improve MY attitude?!
But I... It's Gilda that...
Are you serio... ARGH!
Maybe Twilight is right. Maybe Gilda
isn't a big mean grumpy mean meanypants.
Maybe I'm just a big jealous
judgmental jealous jealousypants.
That was sweet!
Uh. I gotta take care of a few weather
jobs around here. Shouldn't take long.
Just hang out in town and I'll come find ya.
That's cool, I guess. I'm gonna go chow down.
Later!
A rattler! A rattler!
Run for the hills! Everybody protect yourselves!
This stuff ain't fresh, dude!
Aw, poor Granny Smith! She didn't know
it was a joke! How mean!
No, no! I can't misjudge her!
It *was* kind of a funny prank.
...I guess.
I *did* misjudge her! She's not only
a meanie meanpants! She's also a thief!
Nonononono... She might get it back!
It's just a joke!
All right, little one. This way. This way.
Mama Duck, you're free and clear.
Hey!
-Please excuse me.
-I'm walking here!
Oh... Um... I'm sorry.
I... I was just trying...
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry."
Why don't you just watch
where you're going, stupid?
B... but... I... I...
Please. All these lame ponies are
driving me buggy. I gotta bail.
She's a grump AND a thief AND a bully!
The meanest kind of mean meanypants there is!
I can take it, but no one
treats Fluttershy like that!
NO! ONE!
This calls for extreme measure. Pinkie Pie style!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Who's this Gilda I've heard nothin' about?
I hear she's an old friend of Rainbow Dash.
A griffon. So rare...
You've met Gilda, right? What's she like?
Oh! Um... Well...
I'll tell you later, Twilight.
Welcome! Welcome!
Um... Pinkie Pie, about this party for Gilda...
Um... Do you really think
it's a good idea? I mean...
Don't worry your pretty little
head about mean old Gilda.
Your auntie Pinkie Pie's
got it all taken care of.
I'm a year older than you.
GILDA!
I'm so honored, to throw you
my signature Pinkie Pie party!
And I really, truly, sincerely hope you
feel welcome here among all of us ponyfolk.
Oh, Pinkie Pie! The old hoofshake buzzer!
You are a scream!
Yeah... Good one, Pinkie Pie!
Come on, G. I'll introduce you
to some of my other friends.
Right behind you, Dash!
I know what you're up to.
Great!
I know what you're planning.
Well, I hope so! This wasn't
supposed to be a surprise party.
I mean, I've got my eye on you.
And I got my eye on you!
Everyone, I'd like you all to meet Gilda,
a long time dear friend of Rainbow Dash.
Let's honor her and welcome her to Ponyville.
Please, help yourself.
Banana lemon drops. Don't mind if I do.
HOT!
G.! The punch!
Well, whaddya know?
Pepper in the vanilla lemon drop and
the punch served in a dribble glass!
HA! Priceless! Priceless!
Yeah! Hilarious!
Hey, G.! Look! Presents!
Spittin' snakes. Somepony pulled
that prank on me last month.
Ha ha. I bet I know who THAT was.
You do?
Cake time, everypony!
Hey! Can I blow the candles?
Why don't we let Gilda blow the candles, Spike?
She is a guest of honor after all.
Exactly!
Relighting birthday candles,
I love that prank! What a classic!
Now I wonder who could have done that.
Yeah, I wonder.
Who cares? This cake is amazing!
-Spike!
-What? It's great. Try some.
Hey, G.! You're not upset about
some silly candles, are you?
No way, Dash! Like I said,
I'm down with a good prank.
Come on then. Let's have some cake.
Hey! I'm watching you! Like a hawk.
Why? Can't you watch me like a griffon?
Hey y'all! It's Pin the Tail on the Pony!
Let's play!
Oh, my favorite game! Can I go first?
Can I have the purple tail?
Well, I am the guest of honor.
And I'll have the purple tail.
Yeah! Gilda should definitely go first!
Let's get you blindfolded.
Hey...! Wha... What are you doing?!
We're spinning you around and around and
then you can pin the tail on the pony.
Now just walk straight ahead and pin the tail!
"Now just walk straight ahead and pin the tail."
Huh. Yeah, right.
This is another prank, isn't it?
I'm going this way.
Wait! The poster is this...
Uh... Gilda? You pinned the tail
on the wrong end.
This is your idea of a good time?!
I've never a lamer bunch
of dweebs in all my life!
And Pinkie Pie, you!
You are Queen Lame-o
with your weak little party pranks.
Did you really think you can
make me lose my cool?
Well, Dash and I have ten times as much
cool as the rest of you put together!
Come on, Dash!
We're bailing on this pathetic scene.
Come on, Rainbow Dash!
I said: we're leaving!
You know, Gilda? I was the one who set up
all those "weak pranks" at this party.
What?!
So I guess, *I'm* Queen Lame-o.
Come on, Dash! You're joshing me!
They weren't all meant for you specifically.
It was just dumb luck that you set them all off.
I should have known!
That dribbled cup had
Rainbow Dash written all over it.
No way. It was Pinkie Pie!
She set up this party to trick me up.
To make a fool of me!
Me? I threw this party to improve your attitude.
I thought a good party might
turn that frown upside down.
And you sure didn't need
any help making fool of yourself.
You know, this is not how I thought my
old friend would treat my new friends.
If being cool all you care about...
...maybe you should go find some
new cool friends someplace else.
Yeah? Well, you... you...
You are such a... a flip-flop!
Cool one minute and lame the next.
When you decide not to be
lame anymore, give me a call.
Not cool.
Wow. Talk about a party pooper.
I'm sorry, everypony, for bringing Gilda here.
I didn't know how rude she was.
And Pinkie Pie, I'm really sorry she ruined
that awesome party you put on for her.
Hey! If you wanna hang out with party
poopers, that's your business.
I'd rather hang out with you.
-No hard feelings?
-No hard feelings.
Hey, Pinkie. Sorry I accused you
of misjudging Gilda.
Looks like I'm the one who misjudged you.
It's okay, Twilight. Even you can't be
a super smart smarty smartpants all the time.
Come on, everypony! There's still
a whole lot of party to finish!
"Dearest Princess Celestia..."
"Today I learned that it's hard
to accept when somepony you like..."
"...wants to spend time with
somepony, who's not so nice."
"Though it's impossible to control
who your friends hang out with..."
"...it is possible to control your own behavior."
"Just continue to be a good friend."
"In the end the difference between a false friend
and one who is true will surely come to light."
"Your faithful student, Twilight Sparkle."
"Dear Twilight Sparkle,
my most faithful student..."
Oh! Wrong ink.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000