This meteor shower tonight's gonna be amazing!
Awesome!
You know, this shower only happens
once every 100 years.
A centennial celebration!
We better get a move on!
Don't wanna be late!
There.
Spike, did you grab my quill and ink?
Check!
Scrolls?
I've also packed a telescope,
apples, bananas, fruit punch...
...and my freshly baked home-made
triple-decker nut-crazy vanilla cream cookies!
I can see that.
Once again you read my mind, Spike.
And that is why you are my number one assistant.
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you.
That is why you are my number one assistant.
Missed that! Huh...?
I said...!
Come on, let's get going.
Wait! I almost forgot.
I wanna bring the "Astronomical Astronomer's
Almanac to All Things Astronomy".
The Astronomo-lomo homono what?
You know that really old big blue book
on stars, moons, planets, the Universe...?
Right. Check!
Hey! What's taking my number one assistant so long?
I was sure I put the astronomer's guide back.
The book would have helped me identify
different planets and stars tonight.
Well... Maybe someone borrowed it?
Besides, you don't need that book.
You can already name
all the planets and stars, cause...
...you're super smart and...
...astronomically awesome!
Thanks, Spike. You're such a flatterer.
Yeah, I'm a sweet talker.
And a number one assistant, right?
Check!
Wow, Twilight! You're lucky
to have such a rad assistant.
I wish I had someone to do whatever I told them.
Ooh! Ooh! Me! Me! Me!
I'll do whatever you want, Rainbow Dash!
Oh yeah, pipsqueak?
How about taking out the trash?
Yes, ma’am!
Do we have Spike to thank again
for this amazing spread?
Isn't he simply amazing?
Oh, come on.
I said come on.
Little Spikey-wikey!
Who knew that big ferocious dragon
started off so cutesy wootsy?
Spike, you are such a little star,
that I had to make a little bow tie for you.
Gosh. You guys are embarrassing me. Stop it.
Twilight, your turn.
Spike, that's enough.
All right. That's enough.
Hey, everypony! The show is starting!
Wow...
Huh?
Wow! These cookies are deeleesh!
Spike made them.
Speaking of, Spike, can you bring us some punch?
Spike?
Ooh, poor little thing.
Aww... He's worked himself to the bone.
And now the punch has been...
...spiked!
Goodnight, Spike.
Sweet dreams, number one assistant.
"The Study of Comets."
"Comets are small, irregularly shaped bodies..."
"...that are made of non-volatile grains
and frozen gasses. They..."
"...have body structures
that are fragile and diverse..."
Shoot!
Oh... This is a job for Spike.
If only he were awake...
Hoo!
Wait! Don't go!
Don't be afraid.
Thank you for returning my scroll.
Hoo! Hoo!
Uhoo.
Gosh, it's cold tonight.
Say, would you like to relax in here
and keep me company while I work?
Hoo! Hoo!
Now, where was I?
Oh, yes. "...fragile and diverse with
a surrounding cloud of material called a coma..."
"...that grows in size and brightness
as the comet approaches the sun..."
I overslept!
I know it's already ten, but...
...I'm scaly-tailed and bright-eyed...
...and ready to work twice as fast.
Oh please, don't be upset, Twilight.
And what do you want for breakfast? Oatmeal?
How about a sunflower smoothie? Grass pancakes?
Spike, don't worry.
But my morning chores...
It's okay. Owloysius did them for you.
Who?
He's our new junior assistant.
He's gonna help out with your chores
so you won't be so tired all the time.
Wha... Wh...
What do we need a junior assistant for?
I'm not tired. I do fine on my own.
I don't need sleep, I...
Spike, don't worry.
He's just here to help out a little.
Now, I have to go out. So why don't you
introduce yourself to Owloysius?
He's in the library.
Worried? Do I look worried? I'm not worried.
Who's worried?
Hello?
Hellooo!
Whoa!
Dude, that's creepy.
Uh... Hi there!
I'm Spike. I'm sure Twilight
has told you all about me...
Hoo.
Uh, Spike? You know, assistant number one?
Hoo?
I'm Spike!
And who are you? And what are you?
Hoo!
-Who?
-Hoo!
I thought your name was Owloysius!
Hoo?
Okay, "Who", "Owloysius", whatever.
I'm Spike, okay?
Look! All you need to know
is that I'm number one...
...and you're number two. Got it?
Hoo?
So, a man of mystery, huh?
I'm keeping my eye on you!
I've got eyes in the back
of my head too, you know?
Well, not really, but...
You know what I mean!
That bird is out for my job.
He wants to be number one.
I'll prove to Twilight that
I deserve to be number one.
Not Freaky Feathers over there.
I won't let him have my job
if it's the last thing I do!
Oh, what a fantastical,
fluffelicious feathery little friend!
I'm... HOOked!
He's just wonderful.
"He's just wonderful."
Uh, yes. Wonderful.
He's quite...
...the charmer.
And Owloysius's just such a star...
...I just had to make this little bow for you.
What's he all saddle sore about?
He's probably just jealous of Owloysius.
Maybe Spike feels threatened
or worried that Owloysius will replace him?
Replace him? Hah! It's crazy!
Spike knows he can't be replaced.
They're trying to replace me!
I better step it up and make sure
that Twilight and Owloysius...
...know that I'm still number one...
Hey, Spike! Can you fetch me that book
called Two-headed Myth...
...Mythological Mysteries!
I know where it is.
Thanks, Owloysius.
Hey, Spike, no worries.
Owloysius flew up and got the book for me.
Oh, and gee!
I guess I need Ferrets of Fairyland too.
Hey!
Climb down from there before you fall.
Shoot!
Yes, sir!
My last writing quill. It's broken.
Never fear, Spike, your
number one assistant, is here.
Quill... quill... Where is it?
Not here...
Quill...
Quill, where is it...?
Hoo.
Where am I gonna get a quill?
Spike, wait! Wait!
But the store is called "Quills and Sofas".
You only sell two things!
Sorry, Junior. All outta quills until Monday.
Need sofa?
I swore I had one here somewhere.
Ah, here it is!
A quince!
Not a quince. A quill!
Right. A quail?
A quilt!
A quesadilla?
Aha!
A quiche!
Not a quiche. A quill!
Nope. Sorry. All outta quills.
Shoot.
Come on, chicken!
Here, chicky chicky chicky!
Here, chick chick chick chicky!
Come here!
Spike...
...to the rescue.
Oh, Spike.
I was calling out for you when you were
turning this place upside down.
Owloysius gave me one of
his feathers to use as a quill.
That's just great.
Perfect!
Sweet!
I think I'll just, uh...
...finish up the rest of my chores!
Or did Owloysius already do them?
Oh, no no. There are quite a lot of them.
Well, that's fine. Because I can just
stay up all night and finish...
Poor Spike.
He'll come around.
He's genuinely a good little guy.
Spike. What is this?
You said this book was missing.
Well, Owloysius found it right where it belongs...
...but like this.
How did it get this way?
Uh... Well, um...
You see, I...
I just didn't wanna disappoint you and, uh...
Have you ever seen a dragon sneeze?
I've seen a dragon lie.
I'm very disappointed in you, Spike.
You set me up!
Well, two can play that game.
Hoo!
Not "who"! Two!
Owloysius is out to take my place. I just know it!
I've gotta stop him.
But how?
Ah...
Come along, Opal.
Let's hurry up and get to Fluttershy's tea party.
So lifelike.
And when Twilight discovers it
shredded up on her floor...
...she'll think mouse-eating Owloysius is to blame.
And I'll be number one...
...again!
That poor little field mouse!
Torn to pieces!
It must have been Owloysius!
You know, since owls eat, you know, mice.
What a terrible, terrible bird!
He must be punished!
Right?
Spike! I don't know what upsets me more.
That you deliberately tried to set up Owloysius...
...or that you actually thought
this pathetic attempt would work!
You've let your jealousy get the best of you, Spike.
I am truly disappointed.
This is NOT the Spike I know and love.
She...
She doesn't love me anymore.
Twilight hates me.
I'm cold, hungry, tired and lonely.
Could it get any worse?
I guess that's a yes.
Hello?
Hello!
What is that?
If this is what running away is all about...
...I never wanna go home!
Gems! Mmm... Woohoo!
Even if my tummy's full...
...the rest of me is still empty.
I miss Twilight and the pony gang.
But she doesn't love me anymore.
So, I'm better off here.
All by myself.
Wow. Seems to be getting warmer.
The steam is great for my complexion...
...but it's sure getting hot in here.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN MY CAVE?
AND WHY ARE YOU EATING MY GEMS?
Heyah bro!
I didn't know this was your cave.
And I didn't know these were your gems, but...
...we're cool, right?
Whoa, whoa!
Hey... We're like brothers, you know?
I mean, you're a dragon, I'm a dragon...
It's us against the world, right?
You don't scare me!
So you're big.
Really big.
And your claws are super sharp.
Tail...
...extra spiky.
But, uh...
You don't scare me! Ha!
How'd you like that?
Uh...
I'd love to stay, but gotta go!
See ya! Wouldn't wanna be ya!
Uhoo!
Spike! Over here!
Am I glad to see you!
Hurry! Hop on!
It's too dark! I can't see!
Hoo. Hoohoo!
Spike. We were so worried about you.
*I* was so worried about you.
Why did you run away?
I thought you didn't need me anymore.
And that you didn't love me anymore.
Spike. Sure, I was disappointed...
...but you are my number one assistant!
And friend.
And you always will be.
It's just that sometimes I need some help at night.
I can't ask you to stay up late.
You're a baby dragon and you need your rest.
Owls are nocturnal. So I asked Owloysius to help.
But not to take your place.
No one could ever replace you, Spike.
Not even when you are being a jealous numskull.
I'm sorry, Twilight.
I've never should have been so jealous.
And I'm sorry too, Spike.
I should have been more sensitive.
And Owloysius...
I know now that you weren't out to take my job.
Forgive me?
Hoo?
Me. Forgive me, Spike.
Hoo!
He forgives you, Spike.
Hey! How did you guys know where I was?
It was your ketchup covered feet.
Owloysius discovered your footprints and
we followed them all the way to the cave.
Oh yeah, the ketchup.
It looked pretty real though, didn't it?
Uh...
I know Princess Celestia will wanna
read about what happened today...
I'm ready when you are.
Hey, Spike. Why don't you
write to Princess Celestia?
And tell her what you've learned?
Really?
Why, that's a big responsibility!
I know.
But nothing my number one assistant can't handle.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"This is Spike, writing to you
about my adventures."
"This week I've learned that being jealous..."
"...and telling lies gets you nowhere in friendship."
"I also learned that there's plenty of love
for every friend to share."
"So from here on out,
I promise, that I, Spike, will..."
Oh, Spike.
Hoo?
Who? Spike! You kno...
Oooooh...
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000