Discord: Oh ho! But
that's not all!
When I went to look for them
again, they were on the ceiling!
Oh, Discord, I've never known
anypony as funny as you.
I love that story about the
time you tried to train your right paw...
...to fetch your left leg!
Oh, I do love our Tuesday Teas.
And I can't wait for you to
meet my friend, Tree Hugger.
She's going to love you, too.
Tree Hugger? Ah ha ha!
I met her on a trip
to see the Breezies.
She's a member of the Equestrian Society
for the Preservation of Rare Creatures.
How nice for you.
[crunch]
We're all going to have so much fun
together at the Grand Galloping Gala!
Oh! I was wondering when
you were going to ask me!
I'd love to!
Oh! Oh no.
Um. I'm afraid I've already
asked Tree Hugger.
I'm sorry, Discord.
I assumed you'd have your own ticket since
you and Princess Celestia are friends now.
Were you not invited?
Who, me? It probably got
lost in the mail.
No BIGGIE, as the foals say.
Well, gotta go!
But we haven't had any
of our Tuesday Tea cakes.
Well, I guess we're just goingto have to
EXCLUDE them from our party this time!
Oh! Oh, did I say that out lou--
I mean, ta ta.
Hearing Impaired Subtitles by YayPonies
We have Muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
[snoring]
Aaaaahh.
Gah, aah!
Where's Twilight?
Uh, she's in Canterlot, helping
Princess Celestia with the Gala.
[frightened whimpers]
Rarity: Oh, your first
Grand Galloping Gala!
The excitement,
the anticipation!
I wouldn't miss this for
all the jewels in Equestria!
We're going to the Gala!
All right y'all, keep it down.
It ain't like it's a life
changing experience or nothin'--
My little sister's
all grown up!
[sniffles]
Hey!
[giggles]
This is going to be
the best night ever!
Aaaah!
I don't suppose that uh, these adorable
little cutie pies have their own tickets
to the Gross Gruesome
Gala, do they?
[raspberry]
To answer your
rather rude question,
they're going as
our dates.
Our plus ones!
We're plus ones!
Yes, yes, yes.
I believe I got that!
Yeah!
Have a wonderful,
special, fantastic day!
Oh, hi Discord!
Want some cake?
I can give you a list of all
of the flavors we have
in order of most delicious
to incredibly,
unbelievably delicious!
Actually, Pinkie Pie, who
are you taking to...
I mean, do you...
Oh, you know what?
I AM famished!
I'll take all the cakes!
ALL OF THEM? HE WANTS
ALL OF THE CAKES!
Well, I'll need all my energy
when I'm dancing at the Gala...
IF I decide to go, that is.
Oh, by the way, are
you bringing anypony?
Oh, of course!
I WAS going to ask my mom
because she's, you know, MY MOM,
but it turned out she
didn't want to go,
so I started asking around and
around and around
and I couldn't think of anypony and
I was about to just go by myself
but then I realized OF COURSE!
Who loves fancy, exciting
affairs more than anypony else?
My sister MAUD!
You know what?
Cancel my order!
You want NONE of
the cakes now?
Oh my, you are funny.
I guess every being in
Equestria is funny today.
Oh, how rude of me.
Tree Hugger, this
is Discord.
Discord, Tree Hugger.
Radical to meet you.
Really digging your vibe.
My vibe?
It's a compliment.
Oh well, I'm
sure it is!
Well, I must be off!
It has nothing to do with
seeing you or not seeing you,
you can rest
assured of that!
Have fun at the Gala!
Righteous.
Oh, Tree Hugger, you're
such a great friend!
So much funnier than
unfunny old Discord!
No no, here, take my plus one!
I insist!
Before somepony else
thinks he's my friend
and expects to be
asked instead!
What's that?
You're worried Discord
might be upset?
Not a problem!
I can make more new
friends any time I want!
It's not as if any of
this actually mattered!
I don't even want to
go to the Gala anyway!
[screams from outside]
Are you perhaps looking for ME?
Are you...
..."Discord or
current resident?"
I can't find any street
numbers in this place.
My ticket to the
Grand Galloping Gala!
I WAS invited after all!
Why is this so late?
Well, I got a little lost after
I escaped the flying badgers.
Can you point me in the
direction of the bottomless pit?
I think I can make my
way back from there.
Oh, over there somewhere.
Just, just go over there.
Looks like I'll see you at the
Gala after all, Fluttershy.
But I can't show up alone.
She'll think that
she's my only friend!
Who could I bring on
such short notice?
[laugh]
I must say, it's been very nice
having you take over some of the
planning responsibilities
for this year's Gala.
Anything I can do to
make it easier on you.
Thank you, Twilight.
I am quite looking forward to
just enjoying the Gala for once.
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
Announcing, the spirit of
chaos, Discord, and his guest,
the...uh...
[whispering]
...the Smooze!
[gasps]
Good evening, everypony!
What a glorious affair!
He does have a yen for
shiny things, the rascal!
I'll take care of this.
What are you doing
here with...that?
Now, now, now!
The Smooze may be an "it" but
it's an "it" with a heart of,
well, blob.
This night is extremely
important to me, Discord.
Keep it under control.
Yes yes yes, of course.
Tell me, have you seen
Fluttershy anywhere?
We're here! We're here!
We made it to the Gala!
[soft giggling]
Really?
...the aura coming off the
waterfall was so alive!
So like, magic in
manifestation...
Wow.
Oh, Fluttershy!
I didn't see YOU there!
How did you even know to look
for an aura on a waterfall?
[clears throat]
[clears throat louder]
Discord!
I thought you weren't coming!
No, I actually
never said that.
But funny how you
remembered it that way.
Anyway, good to see
you...Tree... Friend, is it?
Your name is slipping my
mind right now. How strange.
Nice to meet you;
I'm Tree Hugger.
Blessings.
You have met me
before, actually.
Cool.
Like in another
life, maybe?
You've got to be kidding!
You don't remember me?
Ha ha. I meet a LOT of
different creatures.
Each one of them
perfect and unique.
Yes, well, as I was saying,
it's just great to be here
with my oldest, bestest friend.
Am I really your
oldest, bestest friend?
YOU?
Of course not!
You think I don't
have other friends?
I'm CENTURIES old!
I was talking about the Smooze!
Smoozeface, the Smoozenator.
Well I mean, that's what we
called him back in college.
Smooze, I would like you to
meet Fluttershy and um,
Tree... what is
it...oh, Tree Embrace?
Oh, I like that.
It's so in rhythm
with my life force.
Maybe I'll change it!
[giggle]
I can't believe I've never heard
you speak of the Smooze before.
It sounds like you
two are so close.
Well, I'm glad you got that,
because that's what is true.
We ARE very close.
That's wonderful!
The four of us should go
out to dinner sometime!
We should all go out
to dinner sometime?
Have you no heart?
[distant scream]
Oh, oh. It looks like
somepony wants to mingle!
We'll be back in a bit.
Oh, Okay.
Treezy and I would love
to talk to you more later.
TREEZY?
Really?
Sort of a juvenile
nickname, don't you think?
[distant scream]
Smoozie!
Wait up!
Now listen, Smooze, I need
to make this a party of one
for a little while.
Just stay out here
until I come for you.
[laughter]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What's so funny?
Exactly!
Uh...I think we're gonna
go hit the dance floor.
Fluttershy, tell the Hugs here
about the time that we went to
the store and came back with
TWO cakes instead of one
because that's how crazy we
are when we're together!
Um, we went to the
store and got two cakes.
Oh. Well, you kind of
left out all the fun and frivolity there,
but I'm sure you
got it, Tree Hugger.
I got that you
really like cake.
We like each other.
THAT was the point!
I'm actually pretty
lukewarm about cake.
[scream]
Let me in!
[gasping]
That creature took my jewels!
Discord!
I thought I told you to keep
your friend under control!
Oh please, I have
better things to do
than to watch that
THING all night.
What I mean to say is, that
thing is a dear, dear friend
and I'll make sure
that the ooze
that he can't help but secrete
doesn't get on anypony else.
Thank you.
It's all right, everypony!
Let's just get back to
enjoying this magical evening!
You are making me look like a
fool in front of Fluttershy!
I'll be back when
the Gala is over.
♪♪
Oh, Tree Hugger!
I've never known
anypony as funny as you!
[microphone feedback]
Check, check, check.
Is this thing on?
Good evening,
fillies and germs.
I just flew into Canterlot
and wow are my
inter-species parts tired!
I've only got these tiny
mismatched wings
and even I can fly better than
Twilight Sparkle, am I right?
Hey!
[giggle]
Well, perhaps you're into
more observational humor.
Did you ever notice how
you always materialize
out of thin air?
Why not thick air?
What's the deal there?
[cough]
Tough crowd.
What is he doing?
I think they're... jokes?
Maud! Jokes!
My favorite.
Knock knock!
You're supposed to
say "who's there!"
This is the most basic
of jokes!
[splat]
You're the most basic of jokes.
Good one, Maud!
[laughter]
What is that?
[screams]
[grunts]
None of my magic
works on this ooze!
Can you stop it?
I'm afraid not!
Discord, how could
you bring him here?
Oh, he's not that bad.
Oh! My shoes will be
ruined forever!
That's what you're
worried about? Really?
This is kind of
a bummer.
Isn't it, though?
And to think, it never
would have happened
had I come to the Gala as
somepony else's plus one.
Seems like something might
have harshed his flow, ya know?
Like his senses are agitated.
You don't know anything
about rare creatures.
I've known
Smoozeface for ages!
He's not agitated;
he's partying down!
All he needs is some, like,
calming auditory therapy.
I know I always feel
really at peace
when I'm being bathed
in positive vibes.
Maybe he'll calm down
with some sonic bliss.
Do you even KNOW
what you just said?
Ommmm! Eeeeeeee.
Ommmmm. Eeeeeee.
[continues]
Let go, Smooze. Bliss out.
Eeeeee!
Ommmm.
Ommmm! Eeeeeeee.
It worked!
[cheers]
Way to go, Tree Hugger!
That was the most magical thing
I've ever seen done with animals!
Oh thanks, everypony.
It makes perfect karmic sense
your magic doesn't work on him.
He only responds to vibrations
that peace out his energy fields.
Discord: Stop it!
Stop it!
That's it!
I am done with you, Tree Hugger!
Oh, man.
You're really bummin' me out.
Can you just like, lower
your voice a skosh?
A skosh?
A SKOSH?
[rumbling]
Whoa, dude. What is THAT?
Relax, I'm not
going to hurt you.
I'm simply going to send
you to another dimension.
I can't have you interfering
in my relationship with
Fluttershy anymore.
Fluttershy: Discord?
Stop!
I will!
Just as soon as she's gone!
Then we can have a good laugh
about this whole affair
over our regular Tuesday Tea!
Don't worry, Fluttershy,
we'll stop him!
[screams]
I'm doing her a
favor, Fluttershy!
It's a lovely dimension!
White sand beaches, an
attentive waitstaff.
I mean, OK, the
humidity isn't great,
but where isn't that
the case these days?
I don't understand
why you're doing this.
We were all getting
along so well!
As well as we could,
considering you've already
stomped all over our friendship
by inviting her to the
biggest night of the year
as if I didn't matter at all!
Did you really think
I'd abandon you
just because I
have a new friend?
Yes!
Because that's
what you did!
No, Discord.
I invited a friend
to a party.
I didn't abandon you.
What if you had a friend that you could
discuss chaos-based magic with?
Would that mean we
weren't friends anymore?
No, I suppose not.
It would just mean that
I'd have different friends
for different things. Oh!
Oh dear.
It looks like I've perhaps
overreacted just a skosh.
More like a lot of skoshes.
Tree Hugger, could
you give us a minute?
I'm just so new at this
whole friendship thing!
It's so much more
complicated than it looks.
Do you think maybe you
owe somepony an apology?
Not ME!
Oh, oh.
Ahem, Yes, right.
Tree Hugger, I'm sorry that you
got caught in the middle of my,
you know, wrath.
Oh, it's all groovy.
Um, I need like a few minutes
to clear out my chakras
before I can hug you from a
place of authenticity.
Oh, your chakras, yes.
Fair enough.
I owe you an apology, Smooze.
I spent the whole evening
thinking about my own feelings
and never thinking about yours.
Well, friends!
I think I may actually grow to
like this multiple friend thing!
I like it too.
Hey, it's not a party until
somepony spreads magic-resistant
ooze uncontrollably
over the ballroom!
Come on, Smoozinator,
let's dance!
♪♪
I'm sorry,
Princess Celestia.
I thought I could give
you a break tonight,
but it turns out I
was in over my head.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
This has been the most
fun Gala in years!
I know, it
was a-- WHAT?
But there was ooze
all over the place...
and one of the guests threatened to
send somepony to another dimension.
I know!
Can you imagine how dull it would
have been if I hadn't invited Discord?
Come on!
The night is still young!