♪♪
Oh, Sassy Saddles,
don't you just love
my new Femme Mystique
Chic line of gowns?
Sequins and sashes,
Rarity, they're exquisite!
Where in Equestria did
you find the inspiration?
Ooh. I modeled them after The
Adventures of Shadow Spade.
Her stories are always full
of mystery and suspense.
And best of all?
Fabulous costumes!
They're perfect.
What are you doing?
Oh, uh, just making
some minor adjustments.
♪♪
Shadow Spade believes
it all comes down
to attention to
detail. And so do I.
There! Now it's perfect!
Hey guys! How's it-- [crash]
[whimpers]
Heh heh heh. My bad!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Sorry I messed up
your dress thingie.
Nothing we can't
fix in a stitch.
What are you doing
in Canterlot?
I'm here for Princess Celestia's
Royal Garden Opening tomorrow.
Oh, yes.
Rumor has it the gardens are
especially lush this season.
I've heard that the Wonderbolts
will be kicking things off
with an aerial display.
You heard right.
And Rainbow Dash is
here to fly with them.
So exciting!
Well, kind of exciting.
Technically I'm not flying.
I'm just the lucky
reserve who was called in
to be the back-up flier in case
a Wonderbolt can't perform.
Oh, don't be so modest!
Out of all the reserves,
you were the one chosen.
It is pretty sweet.
And I do get to
stay in the castle,
hang out with
the Wonderbolts,
and eat awesome food
at the dinner tonight!
Speaking of the dinner,
you're still coming right?
Heavens yes!
A chance to dress up, be
charming and show off
my newest femme
mystique couture?
I wouldn't miss it
for all of Equestia.
Great. See you tonight!
[slam]
[rumbling]
[crash]
Ooh, the rhinestones
I ordered!
Oh, my, oh, there's
been a mistake!
I ordered dragon cut stones
and these are hoof-polished.
I'm sorry, but I've got a full
load of deliveries today.
I'm not sure I have
time to redo your order.
[sweetly] Of course you don't!
Your job is so difficult.
Honestly, I don't know how you
keep all those orders straight!
It is pretty tough, what with
the boxes all being box-shaped.
Oh, yes, and I very
much appreciate it.
But if there was any
way you could squeeze in
one more little delivery, I
would be eternally grateful.
Ha ha ha. Well, for you,
Rarity, I'll see what I can do.
Rarity, you could sweet
talk a filly out of candy!
Oh, it was nothing. No
pony minds a compliment!
Now, you simply must help me
pick out an outfit for tonight.
Something from the new
collection, of course.
[crowd chatter]
Let's grab some grub!
[sniffing] Mmmmm. Is that
Juniper Phoenix I smell?
No, it's broccoli!
Yeah, Juniper Phoenix is one of
my favorite stallion colognes.
Mine as well. It's
masculine, and yet soft,
with the barest hint of
floral notes and a --
Rarity, don't you
know who this is?
♪♪
A gentlepony with fabulous
taste in colognes and scarves?
It's Wind Rider!
Oh! So nice to meet you.
You didn't let me finish!
He's a living legend!
He holds the Wonderbolt record
in the Mustang Marathon.
Well, that was a
long time ago.
Honestly, I can't believe
I still hold the record.
Wind Rider, I see
you met Rainbow Dash!
She's one of our most
promising reserves.
She just might
beat your record!
Really now?
Oh, I'm nowhere
near as good as you.
I mean I'm fast, but I
don't have the endurance
to go long distances.
Don't be modest.
A little practice
and you'll be beating
records in no time.
Heh heh. Well, it's nice
to meet you fillies.
[sigh] Not as nice as
it is to meet you, sir.
I can't believe I
just met Wind Rider!
Yeah. He's coming
out of retirement
to take the spot of honor
in the center of our
aerial flower
formation tomorrow!
Really? That's incredible!
♪♪
Guess I'll just watch
Wind Rider being awesome
from the sidelines.
Practice tomorrow is
gonna be so boring.
I don't suppose I
could keep you company?
You could!
They always let friends and
family come watch practices.
Oh!
Sorry about that. Let
me help clean that up.
No no. It's almost impossible
to get stains out of silk.
But not to worry...
I've come prepared.
That dinner was absolutely
divine! Thanks for inviting me.
Ooh! You're staying
in the east tower?
Those rooms have the
best view of Canterlot.
How lucky are we?
Well, we better get some
shuteye before practice.
See you tomorrow, Rarity!
Good night!
♪♪
Thanks for keeping
me company, Rarity.
If you weren't here...
well, I don't know who I'd
be talking to right now.
You'd be talking to me.
Rainbow Dash, Spitfire's
mom sent a message
that she was sick. She had to
leave to take care of her.
Oh, no! I hope her mom's OK!
Me too. In the meantime, we
need you to fly in her place.
L-l-like in the actual show?
Unless Spitfire comes back, yes.
I won't let you down, Soarin!
AAAAH! This is the
best thing EVERRR!
Oh, my gosh oh my gosh
oh my gosh oh my gosh!
♪ I'm gonna get to fly with Wind
Rider! And the Wonderbolts! ♪
♪ Cause I'm the bestest! And I'm
awesome! And they know it! ♪
Uhhh. Rainbow Dash?
Sh sh. Let her
have this, darling.
♪♪
Hello, there. Friend or family?
Family. My daughter's
a Wonderbolt.
But I don't see her up
there. Do you know Spitfire?
Oh, you're Spitfire's mom?
But I thought you were sick!
What?
Well, Spitfire got
a note from you
saying you weren't
feeling well
and she went home
to take care of you!
I didn't send a note.
That's so strange.
Stormy Flare? Aren't you
supposed to be sick?
OK, what's happening?
I don't know, but I do know I
didn't send my daughter a note.
Could somepony have sent
Spitfire a fake note?
Who would do such a thing?
Somepony who wanted her
out of the show, I suppose.
Why would anypony want that?
Maybe so that they
could take her spot.
♪♪
Me? I would never
do that to Spitfire.
Why would you think it was me?
I did see you and Spitfire
leave the dinner together.
We were room neighbors
in the castle!
And you did say you would do
anything to fly with Wind Rider!
Yeah, but I didn't
mean anything!
Spitfire came by my room
and told me she had to go see
her mom at around midnight.
Where were you then?
I was asleep at midnight, having
this totally amazing dream.
There I was at the arena,
flying with Wind Rider
and the Wonderbolts, like
I've always wanted to--
Never mind. Not helping.
[accusing whispers]
Rainbow Dash, if you can prove
that somepony else is behind
Spitfire's disappearance
before the start of the show,
then you can still fly with us.
In the meantime,
Misty Fly, Blaze,
head over to Stormy Flare's
house and try to find Spitfire
and bring her back.
I have to warn you, if
you sent that letter,
the bylaws are clear;
I'd have no choice
but to ban you from the
Wonderbolts forever. Understand?
[sigh]
I understand. But how am I gonna
prove I didn't send a letter
that I didn't send?
With me!
Detective Rarity is on the case!
And we're going to get
to the bottom of this
faster than my
costume change!
Yeah, what's
with the get-up?
Obviously, I am
channeling Shadow Spade
through these
gorgeous garments.
And she would say that
the best way to prove
that you didn't send the letter
is to find out whoever did!
First stop, the
scene of the crime!
♪♪
Rarity: We had a long road ahead
of us, Rainbow Dash and I.
Well, not too long because
we didn't have much time
but the point is, I was
up for the challenge.
There I was, surveying
the crime scene
and looking tres
chic while doing it.
This must be the envelope
for the letter Spitfire got!
[sniff sniff]
Hmm, these look like
hairs from a rainbow mane!
[gulp] That's not good.
Rainbow Dash was getting antsy.
But I had faith I
could clear her name
and find the real culprit.
What are you doing?
Huh, oh what? Oh,
just thinking thoughts.
Rainbow Dash was right. In
order to solve the mystery,
we had to be focused, driven,
one hundred percent in the--
Ooh!
The damask pattern on these
curtains is exquisite!
Oh, and this velvet
rope holder, oh it's--
We don't have time
to look at the decor!
They're gonna kick me
out of the Wonderbolts
unless we solve this thing!
I know, Rainbow, and
I am on this case
like a charm on a bracelet.
Here's what I'm thinking:
somepony had to bring
Spitfire that letter,
which means somepony
must have seen them!
I just have a few
questions for you
and I'm sure once we get some
things cleared up, we'll--
C'mon, Rarity; we
don't have all day!
Where were you on the night
of last night at midnight?
We were here, guarding
the hallway entrance
like we were supposed to.
A likely story.
I'm telling you, we
were there all night
and no one went in or
out of that hallway.
Except for you.
What are you trying to say?
Just that there are only two
rooms in the northwest wing:
yours and Spitfire's.
So the only other pony who had
access to that wing was you.
The waters were getting choppy.
Rainbow Dash's tactics
were... well, horrid.
It was time for
another approach.
Perhaps I should
take it from here.
You castle guards have
such a difficult job.
I'm guessing that at times,
it can be rather boring.
[softly] It is. I've counted all
345 bolts in the ceiling tiles
293 times.
And of course, being a castle
guard can be thankless work.
I'm not saying you did,
but if you took a break,
you more than deserved it.
Aw, you're right, we don't
get a lot of recognition
for what we do.
Except for last night when
somepony was nice enough
to leave a cake for us.
So we did take one little
break when we ate that cake.
What kind of cake was it?
Cherry with a
custard filling.
Was the frosting
vanilla or chocolate?
Chocolate.
Was it decorated with
buttercream rosettes?
It was!
Ugh. Who cares how
it was decorated?
Rainbow Dash was
questioning my methods,
but I knew what I was doing.
Do you?
Oh. Did I say that
one out loud?
I mean, even I think I'm
guilty at this point.
I really did want
to fly in that show!
What if I wrote that
note when I was asleep?
Do you know what I do when I
sleep? Because I sure don't!
Oh, calm down, Rainbow Dash.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
There's only one
bakery in Canterlot
that makes a chocolate cherry
cake with custard filling
and buttercream frosting
rosettes, and that's...
...Cinnamon Chai's
Tea and Cake Shop!
[British accent]
Hello, how can I help you?
I've heard you have the best
chocolate cherry custard cake
with buttercream frosting
rosettes in town!
Oh! You travel in
the right circles.
We have the only chocolate
cherry custard cake
with buttercream frosting
rosettes in town.
Oh, no! But somepony's
already bought it.
Who was the lucky pony?
I can't even say!
Why? Because it was
somepony famous?
No! Because it
was hard to tell.
She was wearing a trenchcoat,
sunglasses, and a scarf
around her head that
covered most of her face.
But I do remember she had a
really deep, raspy voice.
Rainbow Dash: What do
you mean raspy?
Well, kinda like yours.
If there's anything else
you can remember, dish!
Well, have I got
a story for you!
The pony who bought the
cake threw a big fit
when she accidentally got
chocolate ganache on her scarf.
That's terrible! What
color was the scarf?
White. No, maybe
more of an ivory.
You don't say!
I can't believe you're talking
fashion at a time like this.
Rainbow, don't panic.
I need you to trust me.
Trust you? You've spent
more time changing clothes
than trying to help
me. I'm doomed!
No, you're not. Come on!
♪ [muted jazz trumpet] ♪
Rainbow Dash was obviously upset
but I had all my ducks in a row,
except for one.
She was not going to like it,
but there was only one way
to find out if my
suspicions were correct.
We looked everywhere,
but Spitfire wasn't
at her mom's house.
Where could she be?
[thunderclap]
I've found the culprit!
Somepony sent Spitfire away and
framed Rainbow Dash for it.
And that pony was none
other than... WIND RIDER!
[thunderclap]
[gasps]
Rarity, I can't believe you
would accuse Wind Rider
of framing me.
He's a living legend,
for pony's sake!
All the evidence points to him.
What evidence could
you possibly have?
All you did was ask
about cake, admire decor,
and change outfits
a gazillion times.
Let me explain.
I never believed you
would send Spitfire away.
And when we found the rainbow
hairs in Spitfire's room,
I could tell they didn't
fall out; they were cut!
No pony loses hair in a chunk.
And look at the ends;
it's a straight line!
They were clearly
cut with shears!
Which means somepony planted it.
Then, when we were examining
Spitfire's room...
...I smelled something on the
envelope. Juniper Phoenix!
Wind Rider's cologne of choice.
Then, in the castle hallway,
I noticed some of the damask
curtains fell out of
their velvet rope holder,
indicating that somepony had
been hiding behind them,
perhaps after they dropped
off the fake letter.
Juniper Phoenix is a
very popular fragrance
and anypony could have
moved those curtains.
Precisely why I questioned
the castle guards.
They were at their post at
the entrance to the hallway
all night except for
a small window of time
when somepony brought them cake.
A cake that was ordered by a
girl pony with a raspy voice.
Whoever ordered the cake
got a chocolate stain
on their ivory scarf, and
I couldn't help but notice
Wind Rider's scarf is tied
in a tight Windsor knot
instead of its usual
loose slipknot.
And why is that? Is it to
hide... the chocolate stain?
[gasps]
This is preposterous.
Wonderbolts, you don't
believe a word of this, right?
Just admit it! You're as
guilty of framing Rainbow Dash
as you are of ruining
that ivory scarf!
Fine. You caught me! I did it.
But why, Wind Rider?
Is it because I took
the last broccoli
at the dinner and you
really really wanted it?
No. It was because he was afraid
that you would break his long
distance Wonderbolt record.
I heard him when Spitfire said
you were close to
breaking his record.
He said and I quote, "heh heh."
That's the polite but
disingenuous laugh you make
when you want to seem happy
but really you're not.
I thought if I could
get Rainbow Dash
kicked out of the
Wonderbolts forever,
my record would be preserved.
Really? That is so not cool.
I thought you were the coolest
Wonderbolt ever until now.
I did what I had to do
to protect my record.
Sometimes, you gotta play
dirty to be the best.
That's not what being a
Wonderbolt is all about.
She's right!
Wonderbolts look
out for each other.
Which reminds me,
where is Spitfire?
I sent her the letter
pretending to be Stormy Flare.
I told her I had Pegasitus
and the only cure
is the Ice Iris in
the Crystal Mountains.
No wonder she's
been gone so long.
Ice Irises are almost
impossible to find in spring!
The Crystal Mountains are too
far for anypony to make it there
and back before the
Royal Garden opening.
Rainbow Dash, we need you
to fly in Spitfire's place.
But Spitfire shouldn't have to
miss this. I'm gonna get her.
Well, you'll never
make it in time!
Then there's no time to lose!
♪♪
Rainbow Dash is still gone!
Oh, don't panic.
If I know Rainbow Dash,
she'll come through.
[door opens]
[panting]
Spitfire, you're back! I
can't believe you made it!
Oh, I wouldn't have, if Rainbow
hadn't found me so fast.
Gave me enough time to fly back!
Rare, I couldn't have
done it without you.
And I'm sorry
I doubted you.
But why didn't you tell
me what you were doing?
Well, I didn't want to get your
hopes up until I was sure.
And I couldn't be sure until
I saw that chocolate stain.
Thank you for believing in me...
...even when I was doubting
you. I'm some friend, huh?
Actually, you're
quite a good friend.
You went to get Spitfire,
even though it meant
you couldn't fly today.
[sigh] I'll get
my chance one day.
Or today. How'd you like Wind
Rider's spot in the show?
What? You can't
do this to me.
I'm one of the greatest
Wonderbolts there ever was!
Not anymore. For attempting
to frame Rainbow Dash,
I hereby strip you of
your Wonderbolt status!
So would you like
to fly with us?
Would I? Woo-hoo!
Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!
Uh-huh, Uh-huh!
Yeah! Oh, YEAH!
Uh, Rainbow Dash?
[sheepish]
Coming!
Rarity: So my friend got
her moment in the sun.
Or the center of an aerial
flower as the case may be.
And as for me? I got a
chance to show off my
Femme Mystique Chic collection!
Stormy Flare:
That's nice, dear.
Oh. Did I say
that out loud?