If somepony had told me when I
was a blank-flank that one day
I'd give a speech to a class
at Celestia's School of Magic,
I wouldn't have believed it.
But...
I hope that I have
been up to the task
because I can tell
that all of you are,
and that the future
of Equestrian magic
is in good hooves.
Wow. That was even better
than the first eleven times!
I don't know, Spike.
I'd like to be able to get
through the whole speech
without looking at the cards.
Come on, Twilight, you can't be
nervous about giving a speech
to a bunch of magic students.
Oh, I'm not nervous, Spike, but
I do have to set a good example,
especially for
magic students.
That's why this
speech has to be...
Perfect?
Exactly. Let's go
through it one more time.
Ahem.
When Princess Celestia asked
me to speak to you today,
I was honored to
have the opportunity
to talk about my favorite
subject - magic.
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Obviously the long-term effects
of the simultaneous acquisition
of cutie marks has yet
to be determined, but...
Ahem. Next slide, please.
...I can speak from
my own experience
that the power of cutie
mark magic is very real.
And in the instance
of my friends and I,
it can be traced
to a single event.
Without Rainbow Dash's race
to defend Fluttershy's honor,
this Rainboom wouldn't
have happened.
Fluttershy might never have
discovered her love of animals.
Applejack might
never have realized
that she belonged
on her farm.
And Pinkie might never have
decided to leave hers.
It might be hard
to imagine Rarity
without her sense
of fabulousness.
But it's even harder to fathom
what my life would be like.
Without this Rainboom,
I might not have gotten
into magic school;
Celestia wouldn't have
taken me on as her pupil
or sent me to Ponyville
to meet my friends.
And the most powerful thing
about cutie mark magic
that I've found is the
connection I share with them.
But, um...
the real question
about cutie mark magic is
who it seems to affect.
Starlight Glimmer?
I was sure I saw her, Spike,
but when I looked
again she was gone.
I'm just worried what
she could be up to.
Nothing good, I bet.
I heard she wasn't very happy
the last time you saw her.
Forcing everypony in her village
to have the same cutie mark
wasn't right. We
had to do something.
And now she's coming
back for revenge.
Or she was just really
interested in your speech.
Honestly, Spike, I'm not
really sure what I saw.
But as long as I
have my friends,
I know everything
will be all right.
Maybe I was just
more stressed
about that speech
than I thought.
Yeah, that sounds better than
Starlight Glimmer coming back
with an evil plot for revenge.
Well, when you say it like that,
it does sound kind of silly.
Or it's totally true!
Welcome home, Twilight!
What are you doing, Starlight?
I'd tell you, but I don't
want to ruin the surprise!
Won't be needing that
anymore.
Where'd she go?
I don't know, Spike. But I
think we better find out.
I guess we could
start with this.
Spike, no! Don't touch that!
Huh.
Cloudsdale! Starlight
doesn't even have wings.
Why would she come here?
I don't know, Spike,
but it looked like she
could fly with just magic.
Keep your eyes open. We don't
know what she has planned.
Isn't that Rainbow Dash?
Did Rainbow Dash look
really young to you?
And I didn't see a cutie
mark. You don't think.
We travelled back in time
to when Rainbow
Dash raced the bullies
who made fun of Fluttershy
and performed her
first Sonic Rainboom?
Spike, only Starswirl
the Bearded
could do
something like that.
And even his spell
just went back a week.
How could Starlight do more
than the greatest
wizard in Equestria?
With this.
Starswirl's spell. Oh, no.
Come on let's go!
Go where?
To watch the race! I don't
want to miss the Rainboom.
Whoa!
Later Rainbow Crash!
Hey!
Aw, sorry about this.
Hey, what gives?
What did you do?
You are about to find out.
I don't know what
Starlight's up to yet,
but we'd better figure it
out before it's too late.
Um, Twilight, I
think it already is.
Uh Twilight,
where's your castle?
The map pulled us back,
but whatever Starlight did in
the past changed things here.
But why? And how did we get
here? And where's here?
More like when.
What do you mean?
Starlight altered Starswirl's
spell, then somehow used it
on the map to travel into the
past and change something.
Once she did, the map pulled
us back to the present.
So we're back where...
I mean, when we started?
Not exactly.
Everything's different.
Look, the map doesn't
even make sense anymore.
The Crystal Empire takes
up half of Equestria.
Plus there's the whole
missing castle thing.
Right.
This is too big to
handle on our own.
You think?
We need to find our
friends and get help.
I'm getting a bad feeling
about this, Twilight.
I know, Spike.
But this is Ponyville.
How bad can things be?
Is that Sugar Cube Corner?
I don't understand.
Rarity?
I don't think she's
here, Spike.
I'm not sure anything
we know is the same,
but I know one place
that could never change.
Applejack?
What can I do for ya?
It's so good to see you!
We couldn't find
Pinkie or Rarity
or Fluttershy
or Rainbow Dash,
but I just knew
you'd still be here.
Of course I am.
This is my home.
But who in tarnation is
Pinkie Bow and Flutter Dash?
Or you for that matter?
You don't know who I am?
Nope. Honestly, the only
name I recognized is Rarity,
but she left for
Manehattan years ago.
Probably to become a world-
famous fashion designer, I bet.
Not
that I know of.
Last I heard, she went
to help with the cause
like everypony else.
The cause?
The war against King Sombra
and the Crystal Empire?
What?
Where have you
two been?
Actually, it's when.
I know this is hard to believe,
but you and I and those other
ponies I mentioned are friends.
Did you bump your head on a
crate of cider or somethin'?
I'm telling you the truth and if
you come with me, I'll prove it.
Well, I'll admit, I've lived in
these here parts my whole life
and I've never seen this before.
There's also supposed to be
a castle that goes with it.
But I still don't see
what this has to do
with you and I
being friends.
Another pony named Starlight
Glimmer used this map
to travel through time and
change things in the past.
For some reason, the
map's here,
but everything
else is different.
Different how?
Well, for one thing,
where we came from,
there's no war with King Sombra.
Maybe you could tell
us how the war started.
Then we can figure out
when everything changed.
That's easy enough.
When the Crystal
Empire returned,
it brought King
Sombra back with it.
And it didn't take long
for him to force
every one of his subjects to
fight for him against Equestria.
And even with Princess
Celestia leading the charge.
It still takes every
last pony in Equestria...
...doing their part...
...working day and night
to keep up the fight.
I just can't believe it.
We stopped King Sombra.
You and me and all
of our friends.
But we aren't friends.
At least not here.
Right.
Look, I hope all this helped,
but I really need to get
back to canning those apples.
Thank you. We're going
to set things right.
I hope you do.
So. How are we going
to set things right?
I DON'T KNOW!
The only thing we know for sure
is that Starlight
stopped the Rainboom.
And that the
map's still here.
Spike! That's it!
The map is connected to
the Tree of Harmony.
It must sense that
something isn't right.
That's why it's still here.
I'll just use Starlight's
version of the spell
and go back a little earlier
and stop her before she
even knows we're there!
Aaaah!
All we have to do now is
find Starlight and st-
Well, finding her
will be easy.
But stopping her's going to
be harder than you think!
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I created that spell
to send myself back in time.
So even when you cast it, I
still get sent back here.
It wasn't difficult to
change Starswirl's spell;
he'd already done the hard part.
But figuring out I could use the
map to go to any time or place
and pull you along with me?
Ha ha! I even impressed
myself with that.
I knew you'd try to stop
me. You're so predictable.
Why else would I leave
the scroll behind?
Touching it triggered
the map to whisk you here
and watch me erase
the one thing
that linked
you with your friends.
My village was a
sanctuary of equality
where no pony's cutie mark
allowed them to feel superior.
It was a special place, and you
and your friends took it away.
Now it's my turn to take
something special from you.
Without the Rainboom, you and
your friends will never form
your special cutie mark bond.
Cutie marks for cutie marks.
Sounds like a fair trade to me.
Twilight!
Whoops!
Thanks.
No problem, Spike.
At least now we know
exactly what we have to do.
OK. Keep your eyes peeled.
Right.
We have to stop Starlight
as soon as Rainbow Dash
and those bullies race by.
Um, Twilight...
So be ready.
I know, but...
Because she could
pop up anywhere.
Like over there?
Just remember
how you'd feel
if someone said
those things to you.
What's going on here?
Oh, I was just reminding
these two colts
how hurtful teasing can be.
Well, don't!
Huh?
I mean... You were?
Of course. In a world where
every pony is unique,
some are bound to feel
more special than others.
But that isn't a licence
to be cruel is it?
No. Of course not.
Isn't it a shame
we don't live in a world
where everypony is equal.
No one would ever tease anyone
there. Wouldn't that be nice?
Mm hm!
No. It wouldn't!
I mean, it'd be nice not
to be teased, of course,
but that's not the same thing.
Come on, Fluttershy.
Maybe I can help you get
through the course this time.
Well, I sure could
use the practice.
I know you only convinced those
bullies to not tease Fluttershy
to stop the Rainboom.
Oh, that's not true. I convinced
them not to be bullies
because everypony
should be equal.
Stopping the Rainboom
is just a bonus.
Look!
This isn't over yet!
If you say so.
Hi!
Um, hi.
You think you can
stop for a minute?
Sure!
I hear you're pretty fast.
Pretty fast? Please. I'm
even faster than that.
OK, so, um... Hey
you wanna race?
Um. That wouldn't
really be fair.
I mean, you're
a full grown pony.
And, wait, are
you an Alicorn?
Come on, I thought
you were fast.
Actually, I just remembered I
have somewhere I need to be.
OK, listen. You don't
have to race me.
I just need you to fly fast
enough for a Sonic Rainboom.
What? I can't do
that. Nopony can.
It's not even a real thing.
It's just an old mare's tale.
But it's not! I
know it's not.
I've seen you do it.
In the future!
OK. I'm gonna go now.
No! Wait!
Gee, Twilight.
What's the matter?
Couldn't convince her to do the
impossible? That's too bad.
Well, that
didn't work.
This is going to be
harder than I thought.
We'll have to try again.
Hey, Twilight.
I don't want to live in
that awful future we saw.
I don't think you'll have to.
Pinkie? Fluttershy?
SILENCE, CHANGELING!
All servants of Queen
Chrysalis found in these woods
must be destroyed!