OK. Library... library... Where
did they put the library?
[sigh] This Castle looked a
lot smaller from the outside.
Morning, Starlight.
Whoops!
Sorry, Spike! I guess I'm still
trying to find my way around.
You don't happen to know
where the library is, do you?
Next door on the left.
[slam]
Oh. Thanks.
Acceptance, mm-hmm,
Altruism, definitely.
Starlight! Good
morning! Come in!
Sorry I'm late. I got
a little turned around.
I still can't believe you're
letting me stay here.
As your pupil. After
everything I did.
Well, I'm not one to dwell on
the past and neither should you.
The castle is your home now and
as far as being my pupil goes...
I was just trying to figure out
what your first friendship
lesson should be!
Oh. Well, it looks like you're
really narrowing it down.
Oh, these are just the As. After
this, I move on to the Bs!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
Eat all muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Starlight: I know I'm just
learning about friendship,
but I didn't think there were
this many lessons for anything.
How do we choose?
Maybe I should pare things down
a bit before we go through them.
Why don't you join the
others in the throne room?
They're planning our trip
to the Crystal Empire
when Shining Armor and Princess
Cadance have their baby.
Throne room. Got it!
Um, which way is
the throne room?
[sigh]
Rainbow Dash: Well, I think
we should leave ASAP!
I don't want to miss
the Crystalling!
But, um, shouldn't we
wait for the invitation?
Frankly, I'm not exactly
clear on all the customs
and traditions of
the Crystal Empire.
Especially when it
comes to a Crystalling.
What's a Crystalling?
Well, that's just
it, Darling.
Princess Cadance and Shining
Armor's baby is due any day
and we're still not sure.
The Crystal Empire was
gone for a thousand years.
A lot of their customs
are a bit murky.
We know it's got something
to do with the new baby.
And a party!
And the Crystal Heart.
And some kind of cool energy.
And...
A PARTY!
Spike: It's not
hard to understand.
Most things in the
Crystal Empire aren't.
Like how I'm a big hero
there, for example.
Plus, I've had to help Twilight
do a lot of research
on Crystallings.
Whenever a baby is born
in the Crystal Empire,
the parents bring it
before the Crystal Heart.
They get the purest shard
of crystal they can find,
then pick a Crystaller
to present the baby
to everypony who comes.
Then they all share the
light and joy they feel,
feeding it into the crystal
that joins with the Heart
and increases its power.
And this is going to
be a Royal Crystalling,
so pretty much the whole
Empire will show up.
That hasn't happened
in a millennia.
What do you mean it increases
the Crystal Heart's power?
The energy it uses to protect
the Crystal Empire, I guess.
Protect it from what?
I didn't help Twilight
with that part.
Hey, Twilight, can
I ask you something
about the Crystal Empire?
Ha! Funny you
should mention it...
Because I just narrowed your
first friendship lesson
down to three options.
And one of them is in
the Crystal Empire.
Really?
I found out that's
where the first pony
you ever cared about lives!
Sunburst?
Of course that's just one idea.
We could also go to
Griffinstone.[voice fades]
Making friends with a Griffin
is a challenge all by itself.
Or we could tag
along with the CMCs
the next time they help a
pony who can't figure out
Starlight, is something wrong?
What? Oh, no. Those
all sound great.
I know! I guess you
were right.
It is going to be
hard to choose one.
[nervous laugh]
Yeah.
[crash]
[slam]
Ugh! I am never going to find
my way around this place!
Gee, Starlight, what's wrong?
I don't know, Spike.
Twilight's figuring out what
my first friendship lesson is
and I guess I'm not exactly
thrilled with the options.
Well, with one of them.
Which one?
Reuniting me with
my first friend.
What's so terrible about that?
[sigh]
When we were foals,
Sunburst knew everything there
was to know about magic.
He always knew just what to do.
[bubbles]
And he was always
there to help me.
[whoosh]
I guess it's not surprising that
Sunburst got his cutie mark
in magic and went off to
Princess Celestia's school.
But when he left...
You blamed cutie marks and
stripped a whole village
of theirs and when Twilight
and the others stopped you,
you went back in time and
almost destroyed Equestria.
[poof]
Not really stuff I'm super
eager to tell Sunburst about.
I mean, he's probably some
big, important wizard now
and I can't even find my way
around Twilight's Castle.
Well, if Sunburst is
that good at magic,
maybe he'd appreciate
your [ahem] exploits.
You should talk to
Twilight about it.
I'm sure she'd want to
hear what you have to say.
I know, but I don't want her to
think I'm not ready to learn
or that I'm not grateful
for everything she's doing.
Twilight: SPIKE! COME QUICK!
[whistling wind]
♪♪
It's a Crystalling invitation!
Shining Armor's a
father! I'm an Aunt!
Well, this settles it.
Since we're going to
the Crystal Empire,
your first friendship
lesson is going to be
reuniting with Sunburst!
Great.
[train chugging and whistle]
[yawn]
Um, Applejack, what is that?
Oh, just a little
something for the young'un.
Made from genuine Sweet
Apple Acres apple trees.
We make 'em for all the Apples
and anypony related to Twilight
is practically family.
Yeah. It's OK, but it's no
Cloudsdale Mobile...BAM!
Oooh! Pretty!
Well, a mobile is real nice...
as long as you have something to
lay in so you can look at it.
And a fetching blanket
to keep you warm.
I'm sure Shining Armor
and Princess Cadance
will love all our gifts, but
I think they're more happy
we'll be attending the
baby's Crystalling.
Ooh! I can't wait to see
all that light and love
make the Crystal Heart even
more sparkly and shiny!
Actually, Pinkie,
the Crystal Heart
is an ancient and
powerful relic.
Without its magic, the
Crystal Empire would be lost
to the Frozen North.
Wow. This Crystalling
sounds pretty important.
I'd understand if you
wanted to, you know,
wait to do a different
friendship lesson
when we get back.
Are you kidding?
This trip is perfect.
Not only do I get to see the
baby and take part in a ceremony
that helps maintain the
magic of the Crystal Empire,
but I'm starting
my new pupil off
with the most amazing friendship
lesson ever. I can't wait!
Right. Me neither.
Actually, Twilight,
I am a little worried
about meeting Sunburst.
Oh, trust me, I know what
it's like to see old friends,
but I'll be right there
to help things along.
I've broken the whole lesson
down into a few easy steps
to ensure this reunion
goes off without a hitch.
[nervous giggle]
[clattering train wheels]
[squeaking brakes]
Step one, head to Sunburst's
house and get you two started
on the right hoof.
Step two, get to the Castle with
enough time to visit the baby.
[gasp] Shining Armor!
Twilight!
I didn't know you
were meeting us.
Of course I am. It's me.
Right here. Here I am.
Why wouldn't I come
meet my sister?
Though we have met before.
Are you all right?
Never better! Being a father
is amazing and wonderful
and amazing and
confusing and amazing...
But surprising too, you know?
I mean, not that you'd know. You
wouldn't know, I know. You know?
Sorry. I haven't really slept
since Cadence had the baby.
Come to think of it,
she hasn't either.
It sure would be
great to get a break.
Oh. Of course. I don't
know what I was thinking.
You two probably need
all kinds of help!
I'm sorry, Starlight,
but I guess combining
your first lesson with this
visit wasn't such a good idea.
Oh, don't be ridiculous!
You're an aunt now.
That's way more important
than some friendship lesson.
I just wish there
was a way to do both.
Maybe there is.
You've already done the
work for Starlight's lesson
with this list.
All we have to do is follow it.
Spike, you're a genius!
Yeah. Genius.
Then it's settled.
Shining Armor and I will
head straight to the castle
and you two can head
straight to Sunburst's.
Aye, aye, princess.
All right, big brother.
Let's go see this
amazing baby pony.
[snoring]
I know you're a little
worried about this reunion,
but I'm sure Twilight's
got everything covered.
Everything except how I'd rather
do absolutely anything else.
I bet she's taken
that into account too.
It's all part of the
lesson. Trust the lesson.
Right.
Hey, is that you?
Oh. Yep. It sure is.
Now... according to the
list, Sunburst's house is--
Why is there a statue of
you in the Crystal Empire?
Because Spike, the
brave and glorious,
saved all of us
from King Sombra.
And then again during
the Equestria Games.
Really?
Really! Big fan.
Um, when were you going
to tell me about this?
Oh, it's no big deal.
IT MOST CERTAINLY IS!
That's it.
We're not going anywhere
until I get the whole story.
Before we go in, I should
probably tell you,
seeing the baby might
be a bit of a shock.
Come on, big brother,
I've met babies before.
I expect meeting this one
won't be any different.
[gasp]
[cooing]
Of course, I could be wrong.
♪♪
[cooing] iiiiiaaa, ahhh, GNAGRN
The baby is an Alicorn?
It looks that way.
But! but!
But I thought Alicorn
wings had to be earned
by accomplishing some great
princess-worthy deed.
Yeah, how can you just
be born with them?
The birth of an Alicorn
is something Equestria
has never seen.
It is beyond even
our understanding.
That's not very reassuring.
Wow, a unicorn and a Pegasus!
So, she could be a super strong
flyer and have crazy baby magic.
Well, I know all about
super strong flying.
And I can help keep
tabs on her magic.
[starting to sneeze]
[achoo/crash]
It appears her magic
is more powerful
than that of a newborn unicorn.
The crowds have already
started to gather.
This Crystalling is
gonna be some party!
[pop]
Do you think we
should call it off?
Um, we've all faced a lot
worse than baby magic.
I can't imagine cancelling
such a beautiful and
important ceremony
over something so
potentially adorable.
Yeah! Of course! Come on!
In light of the little
one's abilities,
this Crystalling might be
more important than ever.
Perhaps you should
address your subjects
and remind them of that.
[snoring]
Shining Armor, do you
have everything you need
for the ceremony?
Huh? Oh! NO! I still have to
interview the Honor Guards,
chose the Purity Crystal
and pick a Crystaller!
All right. Take it easy.
Pinkie can stay here with me
and keep an eye on the baby.
And we'll all help you
with everything else.
[snoring and muttering]
That is if you can stay awake
long enough to tell us how.
And that's how we found
the Crystal Heart,
defeated King Sombra
and saved the Empire.
Yay! We love you, Spike! Yeah!
Tell the one about
the Equestria Games!
Well, as much as I love
reliving my heroic deeds,
Starlight and I have an
important lesson to do
by order of the
Princess of Friendship.
AWWWWW!
Oh, come on, Spike. I want to
hear about the Games, too.
I know you're nervous
about seeing Sunburst,
but it says right
in step three to,
"deal with your fears by facing
them," not by putting it off.
Ugh. Let's go get
this over with.
♪ [tense music] ♪
Wait!
What?
Knocking on the door isn't
the next thing on the list.
Seriously?
I know Twilight can
be a little nitpicky,
but this is your first
lesson as her pupil
and it's important
that we do it right.
Fine. What's the next
thing on the list?
"Before they see each other,
make sure to highlight
the importance of the meeting."
I'm pretty sure
we can skip that.
I don't know!
I mean, if we skip it, the
whole lesson could go south.
And then you might end up
taking a giant step backwards
instead of forwards.
Maybe you'll never be
able to learn anything
about friendship at all.
It's almost like your whole
future depends on this moment.
"Highlight the importance
of the meeting." Check.
I can't believe you
wanted to skip that.
[knock knock knock]
Sunburst?
Yes? What can I do for you?
It's, it's me. Starlight.
We used to be friends?
Oh, of course! Starlight. My
goodness, it's been a long time.
What, what have
you been up to?
Me? Oh, you know, some
of this, some of that.
Different stuff.
Right now I'm sort of,
Twilight Sparkle's new pupil.
The Princess of Friendship?
Heh. Yeah. That's actually
kind of why I'm here.
I mean, I know you're
probably very busy.
What do you mean?
Well, I figured
after Magic School,
you'd go on to do important
wizard work, but...
Oh. No. Yes. Oh yes, that's
me. Yep. Important wizard.
Really busy with lots of,
uh... wizarding stuff.
Right, well Good to see you.
[door closes]
Huh. Maybe we
should have skipped
"highlighting the importance
of the meeting" after all.
Well? I guess that's that!
Starlight, come on!
We have to at least explain
what Twilight wants!
Ugh.
[knocking]
Dearest Citizens, I am sure
you are all just as thrilled
and ready for this Crystalling
as myself and Shining Armor.
[cheers]
[gasp] I'm not ready!
Take it easy.
Just pick whoever looks the
most like Honor Guard material.
Right. Right!
I'm sorry;
fatherhood is way more
stressful than I ever thought.
I can only imagine.
Now, I know choosing
the crystal of purity
is a very important decision,
so I have gone through the
trouble of arranging them
in order from incredibly
pure to outrageously pure.
Um, Rarity? Don't they
all sort of look the same?
Oh well, to the
untrained eye, perhaps.
What do you think,
Shining Armor?
I DON'T KNOW!
[whispers] I hope
Twilight and Pinkie
are having better
luck with the baby.
Well, at least she's having fun!
[baby gurgling happily]
Pinkie, hold her still!
I'm trying!
So, the Princess of
Friendship wants you and I
to be friends again?
I know. Weird, right?
I don't understand.
Did something happen to you
after I left for Magic School?
What? No! I don't see what
that has to do with anything.
Why would you even ask that?
I mean, did something
happen to you
after you left for magic school?
What? Um. No. Like you said,
I'm a [ahem] important wizard.
I'm sure there's something
on Twilight's list
that can help here.
[gasping]
OK. I chose the Honor Guard,
picked the Purity Crystal
and I know exactly who I
want to be our Crystaller.
So, all we need is...
The baby?
We're here!
She's a really strong flyer!
[whimpering]
[wail]
[cracking]
[shatter]
♪♪
I'm guessing that's gonna make
it hard to do the Crystalling.
It's worse than that...
Without the Heart, the Crystal
Empire is about to be buried
under a mountain
of ice and snow!
♪ [dramatic] ♪
[gurgle]