We're so happy you
could come have lunch
with your father
and me, Fluttershy.
I'm so glad you asked.
And it was super awesome
of you to invite me too.
Things have been so busy
with the Wonderbolts lately;
it's great to get a chance
to relax someplace quiet.
That's exactly what I intend
to do now that I've retired.
In fact, I converted
the back house
to showcase my
cloud collection.
I have my clouds; your
mom has her flowers;
you've got your animals
and your brother...
Zephyr Breeze has
his... interests.
I'll say. Remember when he
was convinced square clouds
were gonna be the next
big thing?
He's matured a
lot since then.
Actually, it's funny
you bring Zephyr up.
Oh, no! Not again.
It's just for a
little while, dear.
Till he gets back
on his hooves.
Wait. You don't mean?
Guess who's home?
That's right, big sis,
it's your one and only,
favorite little
brother... moi!
Awww.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Hi, Flutter-butter!
How's the bestest
big sister ever?
Hey, where's the love?
How about a little excitement
to see your baby brother?
I'm just surprised.
When you left, you said mane
therapy was your calling.
Oh, it is, sis. It is. You would
not believe how much stress
ponies hold in
their manes.
Everything gets limp
and unmanageable.
No offense, but brushing alone
won't solve the problem.
What went wrong?
Nothing went wrong
per se.
It's just "the powers that
be" were so locked into their
"required styles"
and you know me.
I've got my own style
and I think they were
a little threatened.
Oh, this is lovely, dear.
Ugh.
Well, if it isn't Rainbows "the
best flier that ever was" Dash.
Oh, this ought be good.
Sorry, I shouldn't
tease ya.
I know the whole "super awesome
flyer" bit's just to impress me.
Still, thanks for showing up for
my homecoming, it's, it's sweet.
I kinda thought there'd
be more ponies here.
I mean, what about your party
planner friend? Sprinkle Pie?
She coulda turned this into a
real house par-tay, am I right?
I mean, this place
could use it.
♪ Dra-ahb! ♪
I, I ...
We have been meaning
to redecorate.
Dad, please, when I get all my
stuff back in here, you won't
even remember what this
boring old place looked like.
Um, Mom, Dad? Can I talk
to you for a second?
What is it, honey?
I'm not so sure letting Zephyr
move back home is a good idea.
I know you both
want to help,
but don't you
remember last time?
Zephyr's just trying to
find his place, dear.
I know. It just seems like
his place always ends up
being your place.
And then he sort of makes
you do everything for him.
Well, we may not be as
bold as you, Fluttershy,
but don't you worry. We know
how to stand up for ourselves.
And they were all like, "We
love your free spirit, Zeph
and it would be wrong to cage
that. Go follow your dreams."
Zeph was just telling me
all about the ins and outs
of Mane Therapy School.
It's all so political. I
just could not take it.
Well, maybe if you stuck with
it for more than a few weeks?
Sorry, sis, but when
something's not the right fit,
this pony's gotta fly!
Anyway, good talk, Rainbows.
I am so touched you
came to see me, really,
I hate to deprive
you of my presence,
but this Breeze needs his Zs.
You know it's the middle
of the day, right?
I know. SIESTA!
I'm just gonna assume
you made up my room
the way I like
it, right, Mom?
Ooh, I almost forgot. All
my stuff is out front.
Wanna grab that for
me, Pops? Thanks!
Same old "Zeph."
I know you weren't expecting
to see your brother,
but you've been kinda
quiet. Even for you.
I'm sorry, but I am just
so... so peeved right now!
Excuse my language.
Rainbow Dash! Fluttershy! It's
me, Pinkie Pie! Your friend!
Oh, um, sorry about that.
We just had lunch with
Fluttershy's parents
and you'll never
guess who showed up.
Ooh, Mayor Mare? Cranky Doodle
Donkey? Cheese Sandwich?
Miss Harshwhinny?
Zephyr Breeze.
Oh, that makes more sense.
And from the look
on your face,
I'm guessing it's for another
one of his 'extended' stays.
She's a bit peeved.
Zephyr is my brother
and I love him,
but he's never learned to
do anything for himself
and I don't know why my
parents keep letting him
trot all over them.
Well, if your parents won't
stand up for themselves,
maybe you need to
stand up for them.
You know, you're right.
Zephyr Breeze!
Oh, hey sis! Come to see me work
my magic and turn this place
from drab to fab, huh?
Well, watch and learn!
Can't you see what
you're doing?
Yeah, I'm getting
rid of this old stuff
so I can turn the back
house into my art studio.
I've decided I'm going
to be a sculptor!
I'm talking about
Mom's flowers.
She's gonna move them so I can
have my meditation patio here.
She loves replanting
stuff, don't you, Mom?
And Dad's been collecting
his favorite bits of cloud
from the factory since
before you were born.
The very best from
every production run
since my first day
on the job.
But why hold onto
the past, really?
You can't just fly in
and change everything
Mom and Dad have
built here.
But this is the only
place big enough
for my studio/meditation
garden.
Ooh, unless I do it
in the living room!
I know speaking up for yourself
can be hard, believe me.
But Zephyr will never stand on
his own if he can lean on you.
Don't be so
dramatic, sis.
Mom and Dad just want
to let me be me, right?
I can do plenty on my own.
I agree. Which is why
you should move out.
Oh. Well, I mean,
I totally would.
But I don't think that's
what Mom and Dad want.
It's not, is it?
Uh...
You know we love you, son.
But your sister has a point.
Sure. I mean, I really
just came back here to keep
you guys company. But
whatever's best for the family.
I just...I just gotta
grab a few essentials.
And you definitely have
somewhere else to go?
Of course! There's plenty
of ponies who'd love
for a little Breeze
to blow their way.
So, where's Zeph
gonna go now?
I'm not sure. Oh, I hope
I did the right thing.
Are you kidding?
One hundred percent!
Hey sis, your new
roomie's here!
OK, maybe like
seventy percent.
Um, Zephyr?
When Mom and Dad told you to
find someplace else to live,
I don't think
they meant here.
Well, it's not
their house,
so by definition
it's someplace else.
Am I right, Rainbows? Stop
oogling me and help settle this.
You know what? I totally
forgot that I promised
to help Pinkie Pie...
sprinkle... something.
You said you had
plenty of places to go.
Fine! You can stay here--
You're the best! We're
gonna have so much fun--
--on one condition.
Totally. Anything.
You have to get a job.
Crackin' the whip, huh? You
always were kinda bossy.
Zephyr Breeze!
Kidding! Get a
job. Absolutely.
Where are
we going so early?
You have no idea how bad
morning sun is for your mane.
Remember how we talked
about you getting a job?
It was just yesterday. And
it's totally on my to-do list.
But you can't expect
me to find something
befitting my
awesomeness overnight.
I thought you might
say that.
So I did it for you.
What?
These fabrics all need
to be dyed those colors.
Do you think you
can handle that?
Um...I don't know.
You get started while
Fluttershy and I
head to the store
for more supplies.
Ta-ta!
Good luck!
Thanks for giving
my brother a job.
I just hope he's
up to the task.
Oh darling, dyeing fabric
is the simplest thing.
You just dip cloth
in a bowl.
Rarity! You're back!
What did you do?
Since you talk to
animals all the time,
I just figured it
runs in the family,
so why not outsource
this stuff, you know?
Turns out the animal
communication thing
isn't genetic.
Zephyr! I asked
you to do this job,
not to pawn it off on
innocent woodland creatures.
OK. I guess you have some
feelings about this,
but you should know it's
basically your cat's fault
for walking by and
giving me the idea.
But I'm actually
kinda into this look.
So, I guess what I'm saying
is... you're welcome.
Wha-- Oh, uggh.
Zephyr, this is
just unacceptable!
Wow. I guess I know when my
efforts aren't appreciated!
Whoa, those are tall.
I'm glad you noticed because
they're your new job.
Wha-?
You said you were taking me
to tea with the princess.
Actually, I said I was going
You're going to work.
Sis, c'mon!
Don't worry, Zephyr.
It'll be easy.
I just need a Pegasus pony to
fly up and wipe each window down
from top to bottom.
And I'm here to make
sure you do it right!
Wow, Zephyr, this
looks amazing!
Well, you know, like
you said, it was easy.
Where's Spike?
Up here!
You were supposed to supervise,
not do all the work.
I was supervising! And
then Zephyr asked me about
different cleaning techniques
and which one was best
and if I could--
Hey! I did all
the work.
Don't let him fool you, ol'
Spike is quite the taskmaster.
Oh, come on, sis.
I had to ask Spike to make
sure I was doing it right.
You didn't do it at all!
Well, I guarantee there
won't be any fooling around
on the next job.
Next job?
That's right, Zeph.
You're coming with me.
You don't have to come
up with some excuse
to hang out with
me, Rainbows.
Let's just go for a fly and
see where the day takes us.
Ugh, we're going to
Wonderbolts' Headquarters
and I am going to give you a job
so simple and straightforward,
not even you can weasel
your way out of it.
And the second you try,
I'm going to zap you with
a storm cloud. Got it?
Oh, I got it. I can already feel
the electricity between us.
Rainbow
Dash is crazy, OK?
She expects me to do stuff right
when she asks me to do it!
It's insane!
So you just quit? Again?
Escaped is more like it.
Besides, what was
I supposed to do?
Keep trying? Finish
something for once?
Maybe that way, you'd actually
find something you like to do.
That all sounds fine for your
friends, but it's just not me.
Then I'm sorry, Zephyr, but I
don't think you can live here.
Fine. I'll just go
live in the woods
like my foreponies before me.
Guess the only breeze this
Zephyr can count on is his own.
Aww cheer up, Fluttershy.
I know it was hard, but
you did the right thing.
You couldn't let Zephyr
pull the same stuff on you
that he's always
pulled on your folks.
I guess so.
Oh, hello Constance.
Oh? Oh, dear.
See, Wigford, The Breeze needs
nopony. We've got food...
Shelter...
Just need to put
the ol' kettle on.
Come on, stickie-stickie
make with the sparks.
Ugh! What's a pony gotta do to
find a decent stick around here?
I know he needs to learn to
do things for himself, but...
I can't let him
live like this.
Actually, I don't think he'd
make it through the night.
Fluttershy! Hey! I was just, um,
cozying up in my sleeping bag.
Ready to call it
an early night.
Such an exhausting
day, you know?
It's noon.
You know me: siesta!
UGH! I can't do this.
I can't do anything.
Zephyr, you're
smart and talented.
You could do anything
if you just tried.
And what if I give everything
I have and still fail?
Honestly, I think it's
better not to try at all.
But then you won't
ever do anything.
I don't expect you
two to understand.
I mean, when have
you ever failed?
You've literally helped save
Equestria, like, a dozen times.
And I was worried that
I'd fail every time.
Sometimes you have to do things
even though you might fail.
But failing is the worst!
And quitting doesn't feel
much better, does it?
No.
So here's the deal: You
can come back with me,
but you have to do exactly
what I say, no exceptions.
I will literally do
anything you ask me
if it means I don't
have to stay here.
OK, you know what you
have to do, right?
Beg for help, then quit
when I get frustrated.
Just kidding. Total
opposite of that. Got it.
You think he can do it?
♪ Everypony has times
in their lives ♪
♪ when their hearts
are filled with doubt ♪
♪ Frustration builds up inside ♪
♪ and it makes you
want to shout ♪
♪ But if you just
take that first step ♪
♪ the next one will appear ♪
♪ And you'll find you
can walk, then run, ♪
♪ then fly into
the stratosphere ♪
♪ You've got to give
it your best ♪
♪ so you can
pass the test ♪
♪ Give it everything
that you've got ♪
♪ And we know you can win ♪
♪ You just have to begin ♪
♪ Have to give it
your very best shot ♪
♪ There are times when
you want to give up ♪
♪ when you think that
you can't go on ♪
♪ But if you fight through
with all of your might ♪
♪ You will find that
you can't go wrong ♪
♪ That you could do
it all along! ♪
♪ Everypony has times
in their lives ♪
♪ When their hearts
are filled with doubt ♪
♪ But if you just
give it your all, ♪
♪ you'll start to work it out ♪
♪ And I know I can't give up too
soon, get myself in the zone. ♪
♪ And I find I can
walk then run... ♪
♪ Then flyyyyyy ♪
♪ I can do it on my own! ♪
♪ You can do it on your own! ♪
♪ I can do it on my own!
I can do it on my own. ♪
I did it. I actually finished
something. By myself.
And it looks exactly
like it's supposed to.
I knew you could do
it, Zephyr.
I didn't!
But I do now. Thanks, for
believing in me, sis.
That's what big
sisters are for.
So, Zeph, now that you've
accomplished this, what's next?
Anything I want! I mean,
the sky's the limit, right?
But, you know, I've got
some baby steps in mind.
Thanks for dinner, Mr. and Mrs.
Shy. It was great, as usual.
Thank you, dear, for
not giving up on Zephyr.
After all these years
of pining for him,
it must be so satisfying to
see him on the right track.
Have you heard from
Zephyr? Is he doing well?
I tell you, he's
a brand new pony.
So full of drive
and determination.
That's great.
Guess who graduated from
mane therapy training?
Awesome!
Congratulations, son.
You look so handsome!
I'm so proud of
you, Zephyr.
It was only a
matter of time
before they recognized
my true genius.
But actually doing the
work probably helped.
And I wouldn't have
if it weren't for you.
Oh I just gave you
some encouragement;
you did this on your own.
And honestly, right now I
feel like I can do anything.
Except find a place.
I can still crash here
for a few days, right?