Okay, Granny,
one more time.
When ya accidentally
sold my bass at the garage sale,
who did ya sell it to?
I sold it to the owners
of that new pawn shop.
Uh, Flibbity Flabbity,
somethin' like that.
Welcome to the grand opening of
the Flim Flam Brothers'
Everything Under the Sun Emporium!
- If you want it...
- ...we've got it!
- Need a pogo stick?
- A bowling ball?
- A stuffed clown?
- Whatever this is?
I'd like that bass.
I can give you this bass for a
non-negotiable price of one thousand dollars.
Why, you only paid
Granny Smith two dollars for it!
Yes, well, we have to cover
our overhead and transportation costs.
Listen, Granny never
should've sold my bass.
I'll give ya the two dollars back
and we'll call it even.
Likely story!
It is.
That's my bass.
And can you prove that
this is, in fact, your bass?
Her initials are monogrammed
right on the strap.
That could mean anything.
It could stand for...
"Aardvark Junior"...
- "Anvil Jokers"...
- Or "Animal Jane".
Why, I'll bet you don't even
play the bass, Applejack
- if that is your real name.
- Of course that's her real name!
And she does play the bass!
Perhaps this is her bass.
But there are still
the transportation costs and overhead.
- Don't forget the stocking fees.
- Wouldn't dream of it, brother!
Then again, I suppose
we could make some sort of
trade?
Come on down to the grand opening
of the Flim Flam Brothers'
Everything Under the Sun Emporium.
Since when
do you play the bass?