( theme song )
♪  It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪  Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪  I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪  I'm from
another dimension ♪
♪  Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪  Gonna have a good time ♪
♪  I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪  I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪  Yeah ♪
♪  I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪  I'm talking puppies ♪
♪  Puh-puh-puh-puh
-puh-puh-puh-puuhh ♪
♪  It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪  Gonna get a little wild
I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪  I'm from
another dimension ♪
( theme song ends )
Hiyaah!
( yelling )
( growling )
Hiyaah!
My weak spot!
Yaa!
( shrieking )
Star?
( grunting )
( groaning )
Yes! Yes!
Now somebody
grab the wand!
Lobster claws, you!
Oh, yeah!
I got this.
Go, red boy.
Go, red boy!
Stop flexing your thorax
and get it already!
This is happening now!
( growling )
( yelling )
Booyah!
I got it!
What the--
( gasping )
You got clawed.
Eww.
Ooohh.
Wahh!
Poison Crystal
Cupcake Kiss!
( all grimacing )
( all yelling )
I love cupcakes!
Ahh! ( crying )
Ahhh!
Uhhh!
Uhhhh.
( sighing )
That was fun!
But we gotta go to school.
Oh, you're
on my backpack.
Here.
All right, morons.
Walk of shame.
You know the drill.
( all wincing )
Quit crying and
rub some dirt on it.
Wh-wh-whoa.
Who-whoa.
Where do you think
you're going, hm?
Uh, back home.
To celebrate how close
we came with my bros.
After that performance?
You, sir, are a steaming pile
of monster garbage.
( hysterical )
And you're fired!
Ha ha ha!
Good one!
You really had me going,
boss.
Ugh, you're even bad
at getting fired!
I can't believe
I was friends with him.
What a loser.
( gasps )
( crying )
Earth history is so cool.
Ben Franklin blowing up
that kite monster
with his electric
lightning powers?
Like, whoa.
( laughs weakly )
Yeah. That's not
what happened.
Hey, look.
Ahhh!
You want seconds
on those cupcakes?!
Um, this is the part
where you fight back.
( sobbing )
Go ahead!
Blast me!
Do it!
( yelps )
Um. Are you okay?
Well, uh, the thing is...
( sobbing )
Master Ludo fired me.
I can never show my face
on Mewni again.
Oh, man.
He's taking
this really hard.
This is probably
just a monster trick.
I don't think
he's faking it.
We should do something.
Like what?
I don't know.
But we can't just
leave him like this.
Marco,
why do you even care?
He's a monster!
( squirrels chittering )
Ahhhh!
Monsters
are the bad guys.
I don't have to be bad.
In fact, I've always
secretly wanted to be good.
Really?
Well, maybe
we can show you how.
What?
That's crazy!
Monsters...are...evil!
It's just their nature.
No, it's not!
Look!
( squirrel whimpering
like a dog )
See?
Yeah. ( gulps )
( squirrel chittering )
Okay, lobster claws.
The key to being good is
"Do unto others as you'd
have them do to you."
( grunts )
(  screaming )
Like that?
Actually, that's
100 percent wrong.
You want to do
the opposite.
Now say you're sorry.
That's all right!
I landed on a sprinkler!
This is too hard.
I'm never gonna get this.
Yeah.
You should just give up.
( laughing ) Okay.
Don't listen to her.
Uh, the next time you get
the urge to punch somebody,
just imagine how it would
feel if it happened to you.
I got the urge!!
Wow, that totally
would've hurt.
(   sobbing )
( sobbing )
Aww, what's wrong?
My kitty's stuck
in the twee.
( purrs )
Lobster claws,
this is your chance.
Careful with
my Mr. Mittens!
Ta-da!
Thank you so much,
Mr. Lobster Man!
I knew there
was some good in him.
( cat screeching )
( yelps )
( gagging )
( mews )
Now do you see what
we're dealing with?
Mr. Mittens is fine.
No harm, no fou--
( girl's muffled screams )
( yells )
Okay,
that was my fault.
I assumed you knew
this but...
you can't eat children.
Really?
Not even annoying ones?
Never!
WOMAN:  Help! Help!
Help me!
My baby is still inside!
MARCO AND STAR:
Your baby?
Don't worry.
Red boy's got this.
Wait!
And I'm totally
not gonna eat it!
Cotton Candy
Fire Extinguish!
My baby!
Oh, my baby,
my sweet baby...
( minor notes )
...grand piano.
( hitting minor notes )
Are you scared?
Tell me what you're feeling.
( plays note )
( piano self-playing )
♪ Downtown lady
sing this song ♪
♪ Do-da, do-da ♪
I was wondering
where that piano music
was coming from.
Um...
Where's lobster claws?
(  gurgling )
Well, he's not eating humans,
that's a step forward.
Okay,
here's an easy one.
Help the old lady
cross the street.
( scurrying )
I'll help you, miss.
I'd say he's starting
to get this.
Well, I'm not taking
my eyes off him for one sec--
BOTH:
Ahhh!
Ahh!
Where's a sprinkler?!
LOBSTER CLAWS:
Ahhhhhh!!!
( theme song from television )
NEWSCASTER:  Tragedy today
as a rampaging lobster man
destroyed
four city blocks.
Miraculously,
no one was injured,
but one cyclist mourns
the loss of his new bike.
Oh, it was our first
outing together.
Now I have nothing.
( laughing weakly )
Yeah, you know how
the news sensationalizes
things.
I still believe
you can be good.
But until then,
I'm gonna find some
rubber bands for your claws.
( inhaling to say something )
MARCO: Save it.
Why is being
good so hard?
The problem is Marco
is trying to make you
something you're not.
You're a vile,
repulsive monster.
Why fight it?
Yeah. I am repulsive.
I shouldn't be
helping humans,
I should be hurting them.
You, in particular.
And I wish I could
just get back
to smashing your face!
Maybe there's a way
we can both get what we want.
( snoring )
( knife cutting through )
Shh.
Ludo!
I was just dreaming
about kicking your butt.
I couldn't find
any giant rubber bands,
but...teddy bear mittens!
Guys?
( busts through )
( yelps )
Star!!
They're back?
Yeah.
I lured them here.
To get lobster claws
his old job back.
I'm gonna let him
beat me up. Play along.
( screams )
What?
That's crazy!
All right, Ludo,
I got more than
cupcakes this time!
Uhh, I said, "I got more
than cupcakes this time."
Go, red boy!
Ahh!
Boo-yah, ka-sha!
Don't worry, boss.
I got this.
Raahhh!!
Boss?
Didn't I fire you?
( mimicking
fighting ) Whoo!
Pew pew pew! Zing!
Ahh! Ahh!
Uhhh! Uhh!
Wah wah wah!
LOBSTER CLAWS:
Ahh! Ahh!
You know,
he has gotten way better.
Very impressed.
( gibberish  )
Yes. Yes. I do see
marked improvement.
But I'd really
be impressed if you would
just grab the wand!
He's defeated me!
Ahhhh!!
Hey!
Yeeesss!
( laughs )
Ahh!
Wahhh!
( exploding )
( grizzly voice )
What's happening
to me?
( growling )
Oh, not again!
Being bad feels
so good.
How could you do this?
I was trying
to help you!
( growling )
Whoa.
Don't listen to her.
She's the enemy!
No, I saw the good
in you! Don't do it!
Act like a monster
and give it to me!
Lobster claws, please!
( growling )
( snarling )
Hii...yah!
Ahh!
I always forget
about that karate boy!
Stardust
Daisy Devastation!
( coughing )
Retreat!
Wh-wh-wh-whoa.
You.
You had the wand
in the palm of your claws!
What did it feel like?
It kind of tingled.
I knew it!
I'm so jealous.
Can I touch your claws?
( gushing )
Nice!
After you.
Don't do it, lobster claws!
What about wanting
to be good?
LUDO:
That's my monster!
Ahh. Marco.
You were right.
There was some good
in him, after all.
Not much.
( yawns )
( squawks )
Wha--?
( all squawking )
Huh?
( jungle noises )
Wow, Star's getting
better at her magic.
This is really peaceful.
( creature roaring )
Ahh!!
Help! Ahh!
( creature growling )
Mega Explosive
Crystal Laser!
( screeching
like a cat )
Here, kitty kitty.
( gasping )
Thanks for saving me.
Again, that makes it
28 saves for you,
and four for me,
but... ( laughs )
Who's counting?
Wow, Marco.
I just love what
you've done with the place.
( squawking )
Aw, so cute.
( laughing )
What? I didn't do this.
Well, somebody did.
Somebody?
Birds and rainbows and...
whatever that is.
'Sup?
This has to be you.
Sorry, it wasn't me.
Eh, looks more
like your dad's work.
This was my work.
Ha ha ha ha!
But the rest of this, no.
MARCO:
( snoring )
Huh?!
( gasping )
( shooting off lasers )
N-N-N-No.
( gibberish )
( yelps )
Star?
What are you doing?
( hissing gibberish )
Ahhh! Okay. Oh,
whoa whoa.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Playing messages.
Star. Just calling
with your daily reminder
to behave like the queen-
in-training that you are.
Paper. Tornado.
What?
( screaming )
Ow. Star!
Wake up!
Beanbag. Monster.
Metamorphosis.
( growling )
( roaring )
( yelling )
Star!
( yawning )
Morning, Marco.
Morning,
beanbag chair monster.
Marco! Lightning
to the rescue!
Ahh! Ughh.
( sighs )
( heavy sigh )
You saved me.
That's, uh, 29 to 4.
( snoring )
What happened?
You were spelling
in your sleep!
( battle cry )
That must be why
you don't remember turning
our living room into a jungle.
Oh, no, you gotta fix me,
Diaz.
( inhaling )
Now's my chance
to save you.
With psychology!
Psychology?
Psychology.
Yeah.
What is it?
Psychology is like karate
for your mind.
I'm gonna dig deep
in your brain to see
what makes you tick.
Ohh. Yeah, we have
something like that on Mewni.
( screaming )
Yeah, this
is pretty different.
Now, before we start,
I must transform myself.
Transform?
Ahhh.
Glasses. Paper.
Clothes. Book.
Dr. Marco, Ph.D.
What does Ph.D. stand for?
Pretty handsome dude.
Mom! Go back to bed.
All right,
Miss Butterfly.
I'm going to administer
a series of psychological tests
to uncover what's bothering you.
Oooh. Tests.
Sounds fun!
Oh, wait, no it doesn't.
Test number one.
Role playing.
I want you to pretend
to be someone close to you.
Hi, I'm Marco.
My skinny jeans are awesome!
Ooh, here comes
Jacquelyn Thomas!
I'm gonna impress her
with my karate.
I got this cute
little mole.
( exasperated sigh )
Test number two.
Art therapy.
Paint me a picture
of your childhood.
Mmmm. Such depth.
So many symbols.
What does it say
about your childhood?
I was just drawing
unicorns and monsters
'cause they're cool.
Rawr! Egh! Rawr!
Test three!
Ink blot test.
Tell me what you see
on this paper.
An ink blot!
I win!
Okay, no no no.
What does this
remind you of?
A fat porcupine.
Oh, yes,
that's good.
What about this one?
A little alien guy
in a gnome cap.
( gasps )
Maybe I'm sleep-spelling
because I'm secretly a little
alien guy in a gnome cap.
No. Now what about--
ugh, wait. Hold on,
this is a mistake.
( gasps )
That reminds me
of my overbearing mother
suffocating me
with all the duties
of becoming a queen
for the rest of my life.
I think we may have found
the root of your problem.
You have mother issues!
Yay! I have Mother Issues.
No, that's bad.
Aww.
I have mother issues.
It's okay, Star.
Identifying the problem
is the first step to recovery.
Recovery.
( yelps )
( snoring )
Aw, man.
STAR:  Get away!
( grunting )
Huh?
( yawning )
Wait. What the--?
Ahh! Oof. Ahh!
Undy pants?
Oh, no.
Marco's naked.
No,
I'm in my jam jams.
Look.
I want your face!
Ugh, you weren't
sleep-spelling,
you were just
defending yourself
against that
sleep-goblin-elephant.
Wow! I'm hardcore.
I came here
for your face!
To steal your face!
You hurt me
in my butt!
( shuddering )
Ew.
Could you...
stop yelling?
Well, I'm sorry.
I don't have any ears.
Camera phone.
( clicks )
I'm on the run
from St. O's.
Well, you can't stay here.
I don't want
to go to St. O's!
Oh, you're going
to St. O's.
You see,
we're both big girls.
We got the same
highs and lows,
the same east and west.
You can hardly tell us apart.
Except for
in the face.
Camera phone.
So I'm gonna laser finger
your face off of your head.
Oh, you can have my face.
See, I'm gonna wear
your face
and then you can go to jail.
'Cause you look like me.
It's just a classic
face-switch scenario.
( guffawing )
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
It is not funny.
( screams )
Star!
Don't worry, Star.
I'll save you!
Whoaaa! Ughh.
Ahem.
( laughs nervously )
Camera phone.
Ahhh!
Nose grab.
( evil laugh )
MARCO: Stop!
Whoaaa.
Ahhh.
Be careful on this roof.
It is slippery
from the evening dew.
Let me go,
you weirdy weirdo!
Is Marco small?
Or is he just really
far away? I can't tell.
Laser finger.
( screaming )
Marco!
Nooo!
( grunting )
Whoa. Unhh.
Glasses. Paper.
Clothes.
Book. Dr. Marco, Ph.D.
You don't have
to do this.
I have an 'A'
in psychology.
I can help you.
No, thank you.
Use your mind karate!
Listen to me.
I already told you.
I don't have any ears.
Well, maybe that's why
you're in this mess.
( sad music )
Okay, I do have ears.
But I don't use them
to listen to people.
The only people
I listen to is my mind.
And right now,
my mind is telling me
to steal her face.
But you can't keep
running from your problems.
When you steal
other people's faces,
all you're really
stealing is your future.
But I like my future.
I don't like my future.
Camera phone.
( laughing )
( growling )
( screaming )
Ahhh!
Wow, Marco.
You really saved my face.
Yes!
Finally.
I don't get it.
Why is this tally thing
such a big deal to you?
Uhhh...I don't know.
I guess... you're
this magic princess
from another dimension
and I'm just...
( clears throat )
Star, Ph.D. Marco,
you are awesome.
We don't need to get
caught up in who saves who.
All that matters
is that we have
each other's back.
Yeah.
But this time,
I totally saved you.
Woohoo!
Whoa.
You're right.
We shouldn't keep
track anymore.
♪  I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
That's saying something 'cause
've been through outer space ♪
♪  I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪  I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪  I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪  I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪  I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪