♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Of course, very few are
aware of this serious matter
so I'll be traveling afar
to give an all-day lecture
explaining
the proper throne posture.
Slouched shoulders
are an epidemic
among nobility
these days.
Blah, blah, blah,
posture.
back problems.
So this is what it's like
to be bored to death.
Star! Are those
dimensional scissors?
Uh... no,
of course not.
Just normal Earth scissors.
See?
Good. Because
you're not to leave Earth.
[giggles nervously]
I would never think of it.
Glad to hear it.
I'm sorry. Your mother
and I must cut you short.
I have lecture
things to do.
Oh, him and his lectures.
Okay, bye.
Star, we're about
to celebrate my parents'
anniversary. Come on.
Oh, no, I didn't
get them anything.
Don't worry about it.
My gift can be
from both of us.
I want to get them something
just from me,
'cause your parents
are actually cool.
Cool?
Cool.
[giggling]
Ahem!
Oh, hello, kids.
Happy anniversary,
you guys.
[both] Ooh!
Wow, Marco.
More fanny packs.
Okay, I know you guys
are non-believers,
but these are way cooler
than last year's.
They have
everything you need,
like a dilemma whistle,
non-drowsy antihistamine,
and a space blanket
made for two.
Oh, yes, you know how much
we love to travel
and see the sights.
Oh, Marco, you put
so much thought into this.
Gifts are such a great way
to show how much you really
care about someone.
I didn't think
it was possible to
love you more
than I do right now.
And I'm giving you
a trip to Mewni.
[both] We're going to Mewni!
And we can use
our new fanny packs.
- We go now, right?
- Right now?
- I want to go right now.
- Can we go right now?
Welcome to Mewni!
Is this where
you grew up?
No. I live there.
[all] Ooh!
Higher.
[all] Oooh!!
[all]  Oooh!!
Let's go there.
You don't wanna see
that lame, cheesy,
touristy stuff.
What you want
is the real Mewni experience.
[babies crying,
sheep bleating]
[screaming,
giggling]
Oh, hello, little boy.
[chewing,
screaming]
[nervous laughter]
Yum-yum.
Um... oh, look,
an open-air market.
Get your hydra
trail apples.
Half off shrunken
goblin heads.
Want pickled
giant's toe? Is good.
I got what you need.
I'll take
the wind chimes, please.
[gasps]
- Dad!
- Mmm?
Star, what the...
- My dad's here.
- Your dad?
Yes. I don't know
what he's doing here,
but if he sees me,
I am dead.
Breathe.
Just tell my parents
the fanny packs are
from both of us,
and we can go home.
But they're actually
enjoying my gift.
I don't wanna
ruin this for them.
Okay, uh, next,
I wanna show you...
oh, Mewni's
natural beauty.
Sounds thrilling.
We love nature.
"Forest of Certain Death"?
Oh, don't read too much
into the name.
Hurry up.
So it's really
kind of important
to keep moving.
There's a bleeding
willow tree.
- [both] Ooh.
- Whoa!
Here's a carnivore
blossom.
Are you guys
seein' any of this?
See it? Can't take
our eyes off it.
[both] Best anniversary ever,
best anniversary ever!
Best anniversary ever,
Wait. Come back!
Oh, yeah.
Nice try.
Hey, guys, did you see
what I just did
with that bubble gum?
[Star] Wait.
Come back!
Of course not.
Oh, wow.
These flowers
are lovely.
Not as lovely
as you, dear.
Wait for me!
[blows whistle]
Hmm, it worked.
Come on, my dear.
Let me capture
your beauty-ness
on this magnificent
adventure.
[giggles]
Wait. Come back.
Okay, you can stop being
so cool now.
Okay, now,
hold still.
[screeching]
Ah, they're still alive.
- These tracks
are fresh.
- [gasps]
Pegasus feathers,
he's on to me.
Nothin' makes you feel
more like a man
than goin' to the bathroom
in the woods.
We gotta go.
It's not safe here.
- Look. My dad is
right there.
- This way.
Let's just get
your parents
and go home.
Okay, Mr. and Mrs. Diaz,
that concludes the tour.
Hope you've
enjoyed your...
Mr. and Mrs. Diaz?
Where did they go?
Look. Footprints.
Look. It's
their stuff.
But where are they?
[gasps]
[roaring]
[screaming]
Let's get outta here.
No, that thing
ate your parents.
Look out.
Let her go!
Super Rainbow Blast!
There.
A dead end!
Quick. Under here.
Wow! What else
do you have in there?
I pretty much used up
everything
when I was schoolin'
the forest of certain death.
Well, everything except
for this miniature  miniature
book of knots.
So cute.
Did you say knots?
Yeah. Why?
- Bet you can't catch me.
- Over here!
Hey, you.
Yeah, you.
You can't catch me.
Over here.
Come and get me.
Whoo-hoo!
[trumpeting yell]
Star!
My parents are still
inside that thing.
[all cheering]
We're free!
They're not here?
Quick, to the large
intestine,
before they're
fully digested.
[squishing sounds,
Marco gagging]
[giggling]
There's nothing like
a steamy bath
after a long day
of exploration.
- Mom, Dad.
- You're alive!
And you're only wearing
the fanny packs.
Ah, King Butterfly.
Care for a dip?
[clears throat]
As inviting as
that sounds,
I need a minute
with my daughter.
Ow, ow, ow.
Star, you know you're
not to leave Earth.
What are you doing here?
Okay, okay,
but the thing is,
it's not exactly
my fault.
It was an anniversary.
It all started
with the fanny packs.
Hey, aren't you supposed to be
giving some boring lecture?
Uh, yes.
Got a little lost.
The directions were...
It all started with
fanny packs.
[sighs]
There is no lecture.
Being king is exhausting.
Every once in a while,
I need to sneak away
and fight monsters.
It keeps me sane.
And it's good for
my throne posture.
So I get my monster fighting
from you.
Cool.
Cool!
I suppose so.
[both laughing]
Are you gonna
tell Mom you saw me?
I didn't see you...
and you didn't see me.
But just this once.
[both] Hugs!
Farewell.
It's cool that
you guys bonded,
and you got to see
that side of your dad.
[whistling]
I wish I hadn't seen
that side of my dad.
- There she is!
- Hey, Star.
- Hi, Star Butterfly.
- What's goin' on, girl?
Star, will you be
my science partner?
- [explosion]
- You bet.
- Star, I baked you a pie.
- All right!
Star, I ate
the pie.
I knew you would.
Star, I wallpapered
my locker with pictures of you.
That's weird,
'cause I wallpapered
my locker
with pictures of you!
[both] Yeah!
Star, Star.
Please zap me.
Please, please, please.
Oh, yeah.
Gracias,  Star.
No wonder everyone's
your  amigo.
Oh, thanks.
Olé!
Oh, yeah,
hit him.
Ooh, a line.
I love lines!
Why are we in line?
Only for the most
important social event
of the year.
Brittney Wong's
birthday party.
Ooh!
No, no, no.
Yes. No.
Ye... no.
Ugh. No.
You're right. I wouldn't
invite me either.
Yes.
I'm in, I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in,
I'm in, I'm in!
Ew, Star Butterface.
You are invited
when pigs fly.
[laughing]
- [oinking]
- Problem solved.
Anything for
you, Star.
[groans]
Flying pig don't need
this. [snorts]
Hm!
I'm going to
her party.
It's so weird that
Brittney invited us
to her birthday.
And all she wanted
was a flying pig.
- The party bus.
- Party bus?
But I get carsick.
It's not a car,
it's a bus.
Rabid Rocket Blast!
Huh?
♪ I send texts
straight to your heart ♪
♪ So you sit,
I knew it was the end ♪
♪ Sorry, honey,
I have to de-friend ♪
♪ Ooooh ♪
[yelling]
See, that was
way more fun
than taking the stairs.
Ooh, sweet,
a little, tiny hat. Cool.
I can make those.
Star Butterfly,
what are you doing here?
Nothin' yet.
I just got here.
One, two, three.
Marco, what are
you doing?
[gasps]
Jackie Lynn Thomas.
Play it cool.
[bus lurches]
Let me sing you
some birthday tunes
with my mouth sounds.
[spits, vocalizes]
Driver, pull over this bus
at once!
Lady, I can't.
We're in
bumper-to-bumper traffic.
You're gonna have to wait
until the next exit.
[scoffs] This is why
I told my dad
I wanted a party jet.
Hm.
I can't drive a jet.
Okay, now,
to my invited guests,
who wants to watch me
open my presents?
[silence]
I'm waiting.
[all] Me, me, me!
Something tells me
we were not invited
to this party.
That's possible.
Why don't we get off
at the next bus stop?
We can't do that.
These people are miserable.
They need us now.
- Star, we don't have to...
- [bus lurches]
Are you feeling okay?
I told you.
I get motion sickness.
Don't worry, I just
need to sit here,
stare out this window,
and never turn my head.
You do that, homie.
I'ma get
this party started
Who puts a swivel chair
on a bus?
Whoa! With wheels?
Seriously?
[crash]
Ugh, it's not designer.
You're welcome.
Hey, everybody,
I just want you all to know
I can make little hats.
And also dogs.
[girl] Ow!
Check this out.
[kids exclaiming]
Not cool.
There she is, Diaz.
Jackie Lynn Thomas.
You're feeling better.
Now's your chance.
Hey, do these oysters
smell bad to you?
Yep, taste like
they turned.
You better not throw up
on my bus, Barfo Diaz.
This party is a disaster.
Hey, Brittney.
I know how to make
your party more fun.
Rubber Sparkle
Bounce House!
[kids exclaiming
happily]
Walkin' on the moon.
Isn't this fun,
Brittney?
Better idea.
[all chanting]
Hot tub, hot tub.
Foaming Twinkle
Bubble Ripple!
Yeah! Star Butterfly
rules!
[groaning]
Oh, Marco.
It's hard work
makin' everybody happy.
Can you make
my tummy happy?
[bus lurches]
Finally. End of the line
for the princess
and the puke boy.
Now get off my bus!
Oh, thank you.
Fresh air!
[inhales deeply]
Smells just like...
monsters?
Get them!
Ugh, finally.
What is going
on here?
Three-eyed
potato baby.
- Take the wheel!
-[growls]
She says
she wants a jet.
[muttering gibberish]
Will you get
on with it?
[all screaming]
What's your game?
I'm gonna bus-jack
this bus.
Here they come.
Was that them?
Uh, nope.
A particularly
stupid plan, Ludo.
It's a great plan.
Shut up!
Oh, just...
just get her.
[all roaring]
Star's the worst.
I know, right?
I hope you destroy her.
Thank you.
That is so nice.
[speaking foreign language]
[slurping and laughing]
There's a rumbly
in my tumbly.
Oh, no.
Marco, quick,
take the wheel.
[shudders]
[kids cheering]
[monsters groaning]
Why did only
we get hurt?
[retching loudly]
Outta the way.
Hey, party animals.
Oh, this is horrible!
My party is ruined!
Oh, man, Brittney,
hot tub, bounce house.
Laser puppies
and an epic fight.
[all] Best party ever!
It hurts all over.
Just so you know,
I also do quinceañeras.
Ugh!
Man, Star, that party
was the jam.
Please don't
with your puke fingers.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
You know, if I ever
have a party,
you're gonna be
my party planner.
[retching]
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪