♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( deep breathing )
♪ La la la la laaa ♪
Huh?
Hi-yah!
Whoa.
You hate wood, too?
Yeah, crush that wood.
Wood's the worst.
No, I'm practicing
for my upcoming
Tang Soo Do tournament.
Oh.
You see, Star,
martial arts is all
about honor and discipline,
which is why I'm gonna kick
Jeremy Birnbaum's butt!
Jeremy Birnbaum?
Isn't that the talking bear
that used to rummage through
my parents' garbage?
He's just this creep
in my dojo
who's only any good
because his rich parents
buy him fancy equipment
and private lessons.
But Saturday,
he's gonna get
a taste of this.
Hi-yah...
owwwhhh!!!
( groans )
This is a nightmare.
If I can't fight Jeremy,
he'll say I wussed out
and he'll never let me
live it down.
Pigtails?
Ponytail?
Wait a minute.
You have a wand!
You could just
fix my hand.
You know,
that sort of spell
is not really
in my comfort zone.
Oh, but if you like,
I can give you a pretty
wicked set of pigtails.
Pigtails?
( groans )
( gasps )
Unless,
I could look up
a bone-healing spell
in the magic instruction book
that came
with the wand.
What?! This whole time,
you had a magic
instruction book?
Yep, whenever a previous
owner of the wand
mastered a spell, they scribbled
it down in here.
But it's a complete
disorganized mess.
It's gonna take me
forever to find--
Oh! Here it is.
Really?
Hmm.
It's in an ancient
language.
Releasio, Demonius,
Infestica!
Aaah...aaah!
I can feel it working!
My fingers are tingling!
( screams )
( gasps )
Don't worry.
There must be a spell in here
that can change it back.
I can fix it.
( yawns )
( groans )
Ow.
( screaming )
( yawns )
Morning, Marco.
Morning, monster arm.
I was up all night
but I haven't found a way
to reverse the spell.
( indistinct chatter )
LARS: Hey, kid.
I got a joke for you.
What's the most important
meal of the day?
Huh?
It's breakfast.
( laughs )
That's a good one, Lars.
( everyone gasps )
Who did that?
Uh...
No one hits La--
( grunting )
( crying )
I, sir,
am in your debt.
You're a hero!
( cheering )
Can I check out
that arm?
Uh, sure.
I want it to be
my boyfriend.
Me too!
High five!
( breathing heavily )
STAR: Aha!
I found it.
A reverse
tentacle spell.
I think.
Uh, maybe you
should practice
on something first.
Way ahead of you.
Returnio, Armius,
Normalritecus!
( gasps )
Uh, I'm going to bed now.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
Returnius,
Armius, Normalrinny!
Ugh.
STAR: Returnio,
Armius, Normalrino!
( gasps )
Marco!
673,
674, 675.
I did it, I did it, I did it,
I did it, I did it!
Hey, I think
this monster arm
might actually help me
take out Jeremy.
Hi-yah!
Wait.
You're gonna fight
with  that?
That sounds
kind of unfair.
Oh, funny how you
never have a problem
using your magic
when it benefits  you,
but as soon as it
gives  me  an advantage,
you wanna take it away.
Marco, I think that arm's
a bad influence on you.
And I think
you should go.
What?
Fine, but I don't--
( door slams )
Huh. Man,
what does she know?
Don't listen to her,
she's just jealous.
What? You can talk?
You don't need
her anymore.
I can give you everything
you ever dreamed of.
- Really?
- First,
we're gonna destroy
that little punk Jeremy.
Yeah.
Then we're gonna get
Jackie Lynn Thomas
- to like you.
- Yeah!
And then we're gonna
slaughter all humans
and feast on their bowels!!!
Yeah!!!
Wait. What?
I mean, uh,
win the tournament!
Yeah!
STAR: Excuse me.
MAN: Ooh, watch it.
STAR: Sorry.
GIRL: Hey! Ow!
Sorry, sorry...sorry.
Are you okay,
Star?
You look  terrible.
And I have
very low standards.
I've been up
for two nights,
trying to fix
his monster arm,
then he gets mad.
And then I got
to come here
and watch him karate,
you know?
Allow me to introduce
our first competitor,
Jeremy Birnbaum!
( music playing )
Hi-yah!
That's Jeremy?
FERGUSON: That kid can't be any
more than eight years old.
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
We love you, son.
Shut it, Mom!
And his opponent,
Marco Diaz.
( audience gasps )
Now that's
an appendage.
Hey, wait!
He's got a monster arm!
That's not fair!
Yeah! Pretty cool,
right?
Hey-oh!
Whoa!!!
( groans )
Point, Diaz.
Where are your private
lessons now, Jeremy?
Huh?
( laughs )
He's beaten.
- Now, finish him.
- What?
This is what
you've always wanted.
Destroy him.
Eat his bowels.
Not my bowels!
I love my bowels!
Hey, listen, I just wanted
to win the tournament
so he wouldn't
make fun of me.
If you're too weak
to finish him.
I'll do it
myself.
( screams )
Star was right about you.
You  are  a bad influence!
And you
are pathetic.
Whoa!!!
Point, Diaz.
Star?
You can change
it back now.
BOTH: Star!
( both gasp )
Star,
you gotta wake up!
(crying) Star!
Star!!!
Stop hitting yourself.
Hey, wake up!
Here,
try this.
Oh, thank you so much.
No,
on Star.
Oh, right.
MARCO: Star!
Returnio, Armius, Normalrino!
Returnio, Armius,
Normalrino!
Hai.
Whoa!
ARM (laughing):
I could do this
all day.
Ahh! He's too wiggly!
( grunts )
Now!
Returnio, Armius, Normalrino!
You'll never get rid of me!
I'm part of you now.
You can treat the symptoms
but you'll never cure
the virus...
Ugh.
Marco, are you okay?
( gasps )
My arm!
My beautiful arm.
It's back to normal.
( grunts )
And totally broken.
JEREMY: Broken arm?
Ha! Well,
it looks like I win.
Brass knuckles?
Seriously?
Brass?
They're gold.
You boys have brought
shame and dishonor
to this great
and noble sport.
'Tis a sad day
for strip mall dojos
everywhere.
( grunts )
Oh, bravo, son.
Bravo.
Argh. I wish I could
fight  you,  Mom.
What a turd.
Ahh. Sorry.
I should've listened
to you, Star.
I know.
Hey, uh, when the monster arm
said he'd be back,
that's nothing
to worry about, right?
Uh...probably not?
( yawns )
ALL: Surprise!
Happy 47th day
on Earth, Star.
Aaah! A party? For me?
I can't believe it!
You can't?
We've done this every day
since you got here.
Here, Star.
I made you a cake.
And I wrote
you a poem.
Our lives were so small
and puny,
till this angel arrived from...
( doorbell rings)
Ah, thank goodness.
Hello!
It is I, Gustav.
No way!
Ho-ho! Marco,
my American friend.
Look who's here!
- How wonderful.
- What a wonderful surprise!
We've missed you
so much.
Um, hi.
Oh, hello.
I am Gustav.
I was Diaz's exchange
student last year.
What? But I thought
I was your one and only
foreign exchange student.
Not even close.
I mean, who did you think
all these kids were?
Hmm.
I brought gifts
from Scandinavia.
For Mrs. D,
a pair of clogs.
For Marco, the handheld game,
Lederhosen Tycoon.
And for Mr. Diaz,
a genuine Viking helmet.
( gasps )
And for you,
nothing.
I did not know
you existed.
Oh.
Oh, Mrs. D,
you've gotten
so thin.
I need to fatten
you up.
Gustav.
Come, everyone, and I will cook
you my meatballs.
MARCO: Oh, Gustav.
The Scandinavian monsoons
were over,
but the danger
had just begun.
The iceberg was sinking.
Heedless of my own peril,
I disrobed.
I dove into the freezing fjord
and I carried Yuri
back to his mother.
( gasps )
Ooh.
Oh.
Whoa.
Meh.
Marco, think fast.
So, uh, Gustav,
where exactly
are you from?
How much do you know
about Europe?
I know it's a place.
I'm pretty sure.
Oh, well then,
I come from the country
of Scandinavia.
It is a land where Vikings
teach gym class
and everyone
has a pet penguin,
even if you
don't like penguins.
Oop, too bad,
here's your penguin.
MARCO:
Hey, Gustav, I'm open.
Meatball me!
Ooh, Now me, Gustav.
Now me!
( laughs )
Are you sure
those are cooked?
( laughs )
Over here!
Just think,
three more weeks of this!
( yawns )
ALL: Surprise!
Aah! A party for me--
ALL: Happy second day
of your visit, Gustav.
Oh, Diaz family.
You are so full
of pleasantness.
( all chanting )
Gustav, Gustav, Gustav, Gustav!
( laughing )
Huh?
What?
Oh, look at you.
Such a curious girl.
Now, eat your cake
and mind your own business.
Okay.
More cake for everyone!
Marco, listen.
I think there's something
off about Gustav.
I found Scandinavian books
and language tapes in his bag.
Why would someone need
to learn his own language?
Uh...
Why is he always
making meatballs?
Meatballs aren't so great.
I can make things too.
Uh, jealous much?
GUSTAV: Hey, Marco!
Think fast!
I hope he  never  leaves!
( Mom laughing )
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh! That's
a very big bite.
Ugh.
( phone ringing )
Huh?
( snoring )
Oh, Star.
We're about to--
Whaa!
( breathing heavily )
What's going on?
I've been awake for days
spying on Gustav,
and I'm this close
to figuring out
what he's plotting.
What?!
His stories don't add up, Marco.
Penguins, icebergs, polar bears.
What the heck
is a polar bear?
And he's making
phone calls, Marco.
Phone calls!
He's up to something
terrible!
You have lost your mind.
But if you find it,
we're meeting Gustav
for a picnic
at Isolation Point,
where no one
can hear you scream...
with enjoyment.
Oh, Mrs. D,
you've gotten so thin.
Gustav, Gustav, Gustav, Gustav!
Now, eat your cake
and mind your own business.
Meatballs, meatballs,
meatballs.
Isolation Point.
Here is your penguin.
I need to fatten you up.
( screams )
Gustav's not taking them
on  a picnic,
they  are  the picnic!
( car starts )
( tires screeching )
Wait!
Bunny Rabbit Blast!
You're all going to die!
♪ Oh, we're gonna eat some
meatballs in the woods ♪
♪ Yeah, we're gonna eat some
♪ In the woods ♪
♪ Yeah, we're gonna eat
some meatballs ♪
♪ Yeah, we're gonna
eat some meatballs... ♪
( thunder rumbles )
I knew you were up to no good,
meatball boy!
( screams )
Get back here!
( panting )
Dagger Heart Blast!
Glow Worm Blast!
Narwhal Blast!
Ha ha ha!
STAR: Glitter Dragon Escalation!
Give it up, Gustav!
( screams )
Whoa!!!
It's over, Gustav.
I know you aren't
who you say you are.
It's true!
I'm full of lies!
So, you admit you're planning
to eat the Diazes?
Yes, yes.
Wait, what?
No, I don't want
to eat them.
But you said--
I mean, I'm not
from Scandinavia.
Truth is my name
is Charlie Booth,
and I'm just a guy
from Bakersfieldville.
Nobody's heard of it.
( all sigh )
GUSTAV: Back home,
I'm just another boring face
in a  really  boring crowd.
It's not a good place
for a talented guy like me.
But what about
the phone calls?
And the axe?
And those meatballs?
Well, the phone calls
were to my meat guy,
but he wouldn't pick up.
MAN:  I'm the meat guy,
Leave a message.
Bro, it's me.
Come on, man,
I need the meat.
The axe was to cut firewood
for today's feast.
As for the meatballs,
my dream is to become a chef
and open a restaurant
in Bakersfieldville
that uses spices and flavors.
All: Yay!
So that's why I ran away
and moved in with the Diazes.
But what about measuring
the Diazes in their sleep?
Uh...
( horn honks )
Star?
What a pleasant surprise!
You made it!
Yeah, I did.
And I came here to tell you
something about Gustav.
( gasps )
( laughs )
He's made you
even  more  meatballs!
- Yes!
- Fantastic!
Oh, meatballs.
Phew.
Thanks for not blowing
my cover, Star.
If there's ever anything
I can do for you...
Well, as a matter of fact,
Charlie, there is.
Bye!
Bye-bye, Gustav!
ALL: Bye-bye!
( indistinct chatter )
Gonna miss you, bud.
MAN: Hey, get off the road!
See you next year,
Gustav!
Or not,
you never know.
Bye now.
MR. AND MRS. DIAZ: Surprise!
Happy 51st day on Earth, Star.
Ah! A party for me?
Who wants cake?
I'm sorry your favorite
exchange student
had to leave so soon.
You kidding?
You're my favorite.
Aww.
I will miss
seeing him, though.
That guy is just
so...  real.
( doorbell rings )
Bonjour.
Francois!
Hey, what a great surprise.
I brought the baguettes
for everyone!
Aww.
♪ I think Earth ♪
♪ Is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'cause I've been through
outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me ♪
♪ It's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay ♪
♪ A little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers ♪
♪ Are just friends
you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters ♪
♪ And I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking ♪
♪ I could call this place ♪
♪ Home ♪