♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Some of these have
sandwiches in them.
Oh, don't put
your hand in there.
( straining )
Are you sure
this is safe?
I never said that.
Come on, Marco,
you try.
Uh... no.
Suit yourself.
( screams )
Huh? I gotcha,
I gotcha.
( yawns )
( screaming )
Let me just...
Star, we better
get out... Star!
We gotta
get outta here.
Star, pay attention.
Just a little closer.
I had it in
my hands, Marco.
I have no idea
what you were thinking.
I was thinking
of not dying.
( screaming )
We went through
all that trouble,
and this sad little
scrap of sandwich is all
we have to show for it.
That's because it's
not worth dying for
a stupid
piece of food.
I'm going
to my room.
I hate when
you act like this.
It makes me wonder
why we're even friends.
Ugh! Where did
all these flies come from?
( muffled scream )
( snoring )
Don't call me butterfly.
So good.
Marco. I'm sorry.
I was a jerk.
It's just I really
wanted you to try this sandwich.
It's kinda smashed
and dirty,
but it's still delicious.
Marco?
No Marco.
Mr. and Mrs. Diaz.
Uh, what are
you guys doing?
Oh, Star, we were just
looking at Rafael's
old book of
medical illustrations.
Weird. Have you guys
seen Marco?
I think he went
to walk the laser puppies.
Try calling
his cellular phone.
Oh, yeah. Good idea.
( gasps ) The call is coming
from inside the house.
Marco?
There you are.
What's up with everyone
hanging out in the dark
like a bunch of
weird-y weirds?
Uh, Marco,
where'd you put
your legs?
What have you done
with Marco?
If you ever want to see
the boy alive again,
bring the wand to
Ludo's castle tonight.
And come alone.
( laughing )
You're never
going to believe.
The telephone
punched me in the face.
Did you find Marco?
Uh...
And the little fly man
was all, like,
( strange accent ) If you ever
want to see Marco alive again--
I just sounded Irish;
he wasn't Irish.
Write that down.
The thing is,
Ludo's been after my wand
ever since I got here.
He's never gonna get it;
it's, like, my birthright,
from a ba-jillion
generations ago,
starting with my great-great
great-great-great-great...
Do you like magic,
little girl?
I guess.
Me, too.
Heck, I used to go
to Vegas every weekend
for magic.
The thing about
magic is,
if you don't
use it wisely,
you can lose
everything.
Anywho, not much I can do
for you.
If he's not back
tomorrow,
we'll send the bloodhounds
for him.
I told you
he wouldn't get it.
Well, we don't
get it either.
Look, this isn't
your fault, Star.
If anything, we should've
been paying more attention
to the two of you.
I can get Marco
back from Ludo.
Great. We'll take
the minivan.
No, a little fly said to me
to come alone.
- Hey...
- You're wrong,
by the way.
This is my fault.
I'll take care
of it myself.
Oh, Star, come on,
don't be like... that.
Forgot my scissors.
Oh, why bother?
What the...
( clears throat )
Why you bother knocking
when you just walked
through my living room?
I'm sorry!
Go away.
I just wanna talk,
Buff Frog.
Buff Frog not even
my name.
Really? Is it...
Butt Frog?
No, it's not Butt Frog.
Is it Chad?
My name is
Yvgeny Bulgoyaboff.
Oh. So you're foreign.
What do you want?
Okay.
At least let me
buy back your friendship.
You're going to love it.
Quiet.
Fine.
Door is open.
You're not even
going to open it?
BOTH: Huh?
Wait. Was that...
Huh? No.
Marco!
Tadpoles?
Ugh.
Where are my flip-flops?
Where's Marco?
I don't even know
who that is.
She's talking about
Karate Boy.
Please, no more
laser beam.
I swear, I have no idea
where your friend is.
Then why did you summon me
to your castle?
It is no longer
his castle.
He's right.
It's Toffee's castle now.
Toffee?
I have no idea
who that is...
( babbling baby talk )
Ludo gave me babies.
Okay, I'm done.
Wait, wait!
Ludo.
I wanted to say
thank you
for giving me
the gift of fatherhood.
That wasn't a gift,
you ding-a-ling.
It was a bribe.
You see, the plan was,
I'd buy your friendship
with gifts because
we're friends,
and in return,
you'd kick Toffee
out of the castle for me
because we're friends.
( laughing )
But then, Star showed up,
and I don't need you anymore,
you big old meatball.
Well, looks like I've had
all the fun I can have in here.
Oh, wait.
Now I'm done.
All right, you got me here.
What do you want with me?
What?
Tell him what you're
gonna do to him.
Wait till
you hear this.
Do you mind?
( angry buzzing )
Look, if you're
after the wand,
it's harder to get
than you think.
Lots of people have tried.
Eat something.
Could be
your last meal.
Actually, I'm
totally full.
But if you're hungry,
I'm a great cook,
so why don't you let me
out of this chair
and I'll give you a taste.
Okay.
There's two of you?
You really should eat.
I don't want
your stinking sandwich!
You're a disappointment.
Yeah? Well, you're boring.
And you dress like
a lawyer.
At least that idiot
came dressed for a good time.
I feel your pain.
Good luck
getting in there.
Uh, there are keys
in the door.
That's obviously part of
Toffee's plan.
Looks like
these are yours.
Those aren't mine.
Wait, wait, wait!
You have no idea
( panting )...
how powerful Toffee is.
What you need
is the element of surprise.
Lucky for you,
I know this castle
like the back of my hand.
Oh.
I sneak us into
the castle,
and you blast
Toffee in the face.
( malicious giggle )
It's the circle of life.
- What are you talking about?
- So what do you say?
Do we have a deal?
I'm not gonna touch
the hand with the mole on it.
Fine.
Actually, I don't wanna
touch any of your skin
with my skin.
Don't trust him.
I will guide you.
I don't really
trust you either.
I am father now.
I would like my children
to grow up inside castle.
You don't have
to trust me.
But consider alternative.
( muttering in
foreign language. )
Let's go.
( giggling )
Out of the way.
Whoa, whoa.
Before you go inside,
I must tell you,
Toffee is not like Ludo.
He knows about you,
and he does not
like your magic.
Oh, yeah? Well,
I don't like his...
uh...
Uh...
You need to have plan.
What did I say
about the pillows?
I don't need pillows
on my chair.
I'm an adult.
Okay.
No.
Marco! Here's the plan.
We're going in
on the count of one.
That is not good plan.
- One.
- No, wait. Stop.
Chad, wait. Now is
our chance to get the wand.
( scoffs )
You made it.
Supersonic...
supersonic leech bomb.
What?
Oh, hey, Buff Frog.
( yelling )
No.
( gasps )
Marco!
- Star!
- We did it!
Ha, sorry.
I was just excited.
Come on, come on,
let's get outta here.
Oh, no.
( struggling )
Stop.
That's no way to treat
our guest of honor.
No, no, no, no!
( straining )
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
That's not going
to work again.
That crystal's
twice as strong now.
( buzzing )
Don't worry, Star.
I think I got it.
Fine. Take it.
Now let Marco go.
( laughing )
Help, help, help, help!
Do you think
I'm like Ludo?
Just swallow it.
I don't want
your wand.
Destroy it.
What?!
Surprise!
I can't.
I don't even know how.
Yes, you do.
It's the first spell
your mother taught you.
The whispering spell.
Exactly.
Marco's waiting.
Star.
I'm sorry.
( whispering )
( whispering continues )
- Now let Marco go.
- ( snaps fingers )
- Star.
- Run.
Whoa. Oh.
My babies.
Okay, you really gotta
stop shoving me.
It's not over.
Gentlemen.
It's been a pleasure.
- Lawyers.
- Look.
Nature.
BOTH: Eww!
Where's my castle?
It's gone.
And where is
your wand?
That's gone, too.
Everything?
We are no longer friends!
We never were friends.
You are now
my mortal enemy.
This day I vow...
( speaking Italian )
( loud rumbling )
Whoa!
Upgrade.
Oh, Marco, I am
so happy to see you!
Uh, do I know you?
Marco, it is me.
I am your dad.
My dad!
Ooh, ooh, my turn.
Come here... oh... ah!
I'm goin' down.
Just come here
and hug your mother.
This is so awkward,
Mom.
It's not awkward.
Don't make it awkward.
Wait. How did
you guys get here?
They used your mirror.
( whistling ) S-s-s-so,
basically,
just to recap--
- You're not going
to do that, are you?
- What, my dear?
You know that thing when
you talk and every time you
get to a word with an "S,"
you have that little whistle
in your front teeth.
- ( whistles )
- I love you, honey.
I just can't
deal with that today.
Star,
you abused your magic,
frightened Mr. and Mrs. Diaz,
and destroyed your wand.
Did I leave
anything out?
Uh, well, there's a bunch
of other stuff
- you don't know about.
- Sh!
No, I think
that's everything.
But look,
new wand's fine.
- Sort of.
- It's, uh...
I'll take it and get it
cleaned for you.
Please don't be mad.
That looks like
a mad face.
So you're not mad.
Oh, I'm always mad.
But I'm happy
that you're safe.
( whinnying )
Um, Mr. and Mrs. Diaz,
I'm sorry
I made you worry.
We're just glad
that...
everyone's okay.
And I'm on a horse!
- ( loud whinnying )
- ( screaming )
MRS. DIAZ:
Where are you going?
MR. DIAZ: Don't you
ride off with my wife!
- ( shuddering )
- Go ahead.
Mrs. Diaz,
wait up!
I don't know if we're
doing the right thing, River.
Darling.
Glossarick. Hello!
Stop yelling.
I was in the tub...
My lady.
- We can call back.
- No, it's fine.
I'm just doing
a little gardening.
( gasps )
What happened there?
We fear that the wand
has been cleaved.
Cleaved?
Now that's
a funny word.
You can cleave
something apart,
or you can cleave
something together.
- Glossarick.
- If I go like this,
with both my arms,
down goes my bath towel,
cleaved from my body.
( clearing throat )
Glossarick.
Towel, please.
No problem,
Your Highness.
I hope you found
all the pieces
of the wand.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪