♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna
get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another
woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-puh
-puh-puh-pu uuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna
get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
I like red,
I like hoodies.
So I bought
a dozen of them.
JUSTIN: Hey,
it's that magic girl!
( indistinct chattering )
LARRY: Hey,
what's up, Star?
Hi, new friends.
Hi!
Everyone's
so cool here, Marco.
It makes me
wish my parents
had tossed me out
of the castle years ago.
Oh, you haven't even met
the coolest guys.
Alfonzo and Ferguson.
Quick,
here she comes.
Hey, hey.
Are those books?
Where are you going
with those books?
Do you like to read?
Oh, dear.
They're usually cooler.
I need to fix
Ferguson up.
No.
( gasps )
Jackie Lynn Thomas!
Hey, Star Butterfly.
Hi, Jackie!
I need to fix you up.
What?
Oh, come on.
I'm almost as good
at matchmaking
as I am with magic.
I'm good.
Look, look, look, look,
look! It's my name.
It's my name.
With a star
inside of a butterfly
and two hearts and a spider.
As you can see, class,
most of you have
done a pathetic job.
Not me!
I got an "F"
for fantastic!
That's an "F" for fail.
Huh?
What? You don't have
tests on Mewni?
Uh...
So what grade
did you get?
Only the best grade
you can get.
A-plus,
with a smiley face.
Ooh, I want
the best one, too.
Wait, don't!
Oh, Miss Skullnick!
( grunting )
Hey, Skullzie!
Can you please
do me a teeny favor
and turn my "F"
into an "A"?
You're whining
about a lousy grade?
I'd finally got
a guy with a boat,
and he left me
at the dock.
A dock?
The dock isn't
the important part.
I guess I'm doomed
to dry land.
I got it!
I'll cast a spell to
get you the perfect guy,
and you can give me
the perfect grade.
What?
Man--
Wait!
Left arm!
( gasps )
Star,
what did you do?
I think I turned her
into a troll.
Star Butterfly rules!
( cheering )
( screaming )
I'm hideous!
Quick!
Change her back.
Oh, okay...
yeah, right...
Okay, yeah.
Lightning Change Back!
Where are we?
You just zapped us
back to the house!
I wish I knew
how I did that.
It could really come
in handy if I don't feel
like using my legs.
Ludo, Master.
Star Butterfly has come home
from school early today
and she seems distracted.
Distracted?
Excellent!
This is the moment
I've been waiting for.
No one's at their best
when they're distracted!
Finally!
I'll get my hands
on that glorious wand!
When it transforms,
it will match my hat.
And I'll get my big boy body.
Kick down the tower.
Zip, zap, zip, zip.
And I'm a lifeguard.
One, two, three...
Is that CPR?
Silence!
Yes, unfortunately,
I was too late.
Please don't cry,
Miss Skullnick.
Star, we can't
keep stalling.
You're gonna have
to call your mom.
She'll know how
to reverse the spell.
No!
I can't ask for help.
If my parents
find out about this,
they're gonna send me to...
Saint Olga's Reform School
for Wayward Princesses.
It's a terrible,
horrible place
and no one who goes there
ever comes out the same!
( screaming )
Is it all out yet?
Almost.
Okay, I'm done.
Look, Star, you just
need to get the information
without letting her know
what's going on.
You know,
dance around the truth.
I'm a great dancer.
Mirror,
Mirror on the wall...
Call Mom.
MIRROR: Calling Tom.
Star!
No. No.
Oh, wait.
You're here. I'm here--
I said, call Mom,
not Tom.
No, Star.
Don't hang up.
I really got to delete
him off my mirror.
Oh, Star, darling,
what a pleasant surprise!
So, Mom.
Let's just say that
someone accidentally
turned someone
into a troll with a wand.
Not that
I would do that, no,
because that would be
completely irresponsible--
( thud )
Star,
what is going on?
Got to go, bye.
What happened?
She jumped
out the window.
Wow,
good job, Marco.
LUDO: Wow,
Ludo, what are you
doing here?
Catching you
at your most distracted!
What?
I have been way more
distracted than this.
I don't know,
you seem pretty distracted.
Nah, not really.
Oh, well...
What's that over there?
What?
Where?
Get her!
Dagger Crystal
Heart Attack!
Feel the love.
I'm obligated
to warn you,
I'm a green belt
with a stripe.
Rainbow Blast!
Narwhal Blast!
Narwhal blast.
Well, uh, I should
probably be getting back.
Kids ain't gonna fight
themselves, you know.
Maybe I'll see you
around sometime.
Hey, Marco, you can
handle this for a minute
on your own, right?
Oh, yeah, no problem.
Cool, thanks!
Wait...
Oh, Miss Skullnick!
What?
See that monster
over there?
He thinks you're cute.
Really?
Ooh, what should I do?
Wait right here.
Hey there, Monster Guy.
See that troll over there?
Star!
Get him!
Hey, guys!
I think you forgot something.
Get the wand!
Turbo Nuclear
Butterfly Blast!
Not again!
Get up! Get up!
Told you
I wasn't distract--
Wait, did I just
kill that guy?
No, he's not dead.
He's probably just
bleeding internally
and being a total
baby about it.
Open--
Get up you, dipsticks.
MISS SKULLNICK:
Ooh, you're so muscle-y.
So now that I hooked
you up, how about that "A"?
Honey, please!
I'd give you an "A plus"
if I was still a teacher.
I'm setting sail
with Captain Triceps here.
What about my "A"?
Try studying.
So anyway,
long story short,
Skullnick ran off with
this weird man-bull-guy thing
to another dimension.
And now
she is gone forever!
Star Butterfly rules!
( cheering )
Wow, Star,
that is so rad, girl.
Thanks,
but actually it's Marco
who deserves
all the credit.
Really?
That's awesome!
Miss Skullnick?
He dumped me, I think.
I don't know.
I couldn't understand
a word he was saying.
Welcome back,
Skullzers.
Get ready
for the worst pop quiz
of your lives!
TOGETHER: Oh, man.
Sorry, Marco.
I didn't mean to embarrass
you in front of Jackie.
Are you kidding?
That's the most
she's ever talked to me!
Then that means
I'm even better
at matchmaking
than I am with magic.
STAR: Oh, my gosh.
I can't wait. I can't wait.
My very first pep rally.
I am so excited.
When aren't
you excited?
Shh.
And now, Brittany Wong,
who became head cheerleader
on her own
and not because her dad
made a generous
donation to the school.
TOGETHER:
Go, Echo Creek!
Let's try not to get beat!
Go, go, go, go, yeah!
Make some noise
if you love
the Awesome Opossums!
I love opossums.
They carry their babies
on their backs.
You know she's talking
about our football team, right?
We're going up against
the Warriors.
Warriors?
Our rivals
from Silver Hill Prep.
Every year
their team slaughters our guys.
It's gonna be
a bloodbath.
That's terrible!
We must do something!
Well, you could
join the Spirit Committee.
Those kids are relentless
when it comes
to supporting the team.
Opossums!
Relentless.
What a great idea.
We better pick up
some supplies.
As fun as that sounds,
you can go without me.
Okay.
Hey, Sculzy, what's
your favorite weapon?
Battle axe.
And now,
our new mascot,
that I never approved of,
the Awesome Opossum.
All right!
Come on, Opossum--
No.
Where's
the real possum?
Did the Warriors
steal it again?
Those jerks.
Sadly, the real possum
wasn't playing possum.
I hiss, I bite,
I shake my tail like that!
Hey, that's Ferguson!
He's our new mascot.
Oh, no!
That means the Warriors
are gonna steal him!
Oh, that's silly.
The only thing
that's silly
is how the Warriors
are gonna look
when they try
to steal my friend!
So many brave young men,
so many tragic losses.
Alpha Team One,
commencing security sweep
for the Warriors, over.
Oh, Marco.
How can we prevent another
tragic loss to our team?
Well, if I knew
anything about football,
I'd use the element of surprise.
Of course,
of course, of course.
Surprise them.
Bring out
the kitty cat outfits.
Yes!
Maybe even throw
a couple of big bombs.
Bombs!
Yeah, I've got to go tell
that to the Spirit Committee.
Bye.
We have an all clear.
Move! Move! Move!
This is not
the respect a guy
in a possum suit deserves.
BRITTANY:
Don't worry, Sabrina.
The spirit boys
are gonna catch you.
Grow some pom-poms.
What the--
Do these explode?
Maybe we can set them
on fire.
We're kind of
in the middle of something.
You're the leader?
What's the plan?
This year,
we have a secret weapon.
We're gonna distract them
with our booty-shaking
dance moves.
Do you know
nothing of combat?
No Warrior's gonna be distracted
by Chandelle's booty.
What?
Lucky for you,
my mom assigned
the Royal Guards
as my babysitters.
You know
you've done it right,
when you hear the neck snap.
Yay!
I know
on planet Moo-ni,
or wherever
it is you're from,
it may be okay
to be stupid,
but no pesky magical foreigner
is gonna question my leadership.
You are officially banned
from the Spirit Committee.
Fine.
It looks like
it's all up to me.
Okay,
thanks for coming out.
Come back never!
Okay, if a Warrior
tries to kidnap you,
blow on this stranger
danger whistle.
This is ridiculous.
I just wanted to dress up like
a possum to pick up on ladies.
Hey, this whistle's
gonna save your life!
Put it in your mouth!
Do it!
No!
Blow it!
Never!
You get it away from me.
Let me hear you blow.
Get the whistle
away from me.
You guys ready to be
part of my kitty cat offense?
Oh, fine.
Then I guess we got
to do this the hard way.
Kitty!
I got you now!
Why can't I go home?
Dude, it's Taco Wednesday,
it's a day
we eat all the leftovers
from Taco Tuesday!
Because your house
would be the first place
the Warriors would look
when they try to kidnap you!
It kind of feels
like you're trying to kidnap me.
I'd watch that talk
if you ever want to see
your parents again!
STAR: Marco!
Hey, Marco, do you have
any highly flammable liquids?
I don't know.
Check the garage.
Cool.
Thanks.
All right--
Man, I bet I could
get a lot of action
if I had
a real prehensile tail.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, ladies,
you care for a drink?
Two, four, six,
eight, distract them
with our booty shake.
Oh, oh.
It's almost game
time and thanks to me,
no Warriors have even
gotten close to you.
Who's ready for a bloody,
bloody, bloodbath?
What's with that
crazed look in your eyes?
What do you mean?
Watch, Ferguson.
I need to talk
to Princess Cuckoo Pants.
FERGUSON: Stranger danger.
Stranger danger!
( whistling )
Okay, Star,
what are you up to?
Exactly what you said.
I booby-trapped
the battlefield.
What?
Star, the Warriors weren't
actually going to kill our team,
they were just gonna
beat them in football,
which is a game!
Oh...
Oh, no.
Everything's going
according to plan.
Let me guess,
the kitty cat offense?
We have to do something!
All right.
Dude, you're awesome!
Thanks, bro.
( screaming )
Marco!
No, no, no. No!
Mending Heart Hurricane!
Out of my way.
I'm too pretty to die.
Mending Heart Hurricane!
Nuclear Heart
Healing Hurricane!
Come on, fellas,
can't we discuss this
man to possum?
Hey, Marco, you were right,
they were trying to kidnap me!
Ferguson,
get off the field!
What?
I can't hear you through
all the explosions.
Ferguson!
No, buddy!
I'm sorry.
I failed you.
Look at me.
Dude!
I was just playing possum!
Huh?
It's what we do!
You're alive!
This is why you only
have two friends.
I really messed up.
You mean,
we really messed up.
I should have been
watching out for you.
Let's get out of here!
Hey, they just forfeited.
We win!
TOGETHER: Yeah!
Why do I have
this weird feeling
I'm forgetting something.
( screaming and cheering )
That was it.