♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
SYLVIA:
Once every 30 cycles,
when the full moon shines,
the mighty
High Gnee Council
grants one lucky
outsider's request for wisdom
that will help them overcome
even the greatest obstacle.
- Wander giggling )
- What?
You said "heinie."
Wander, please.
Dominator's the most
serious threat we've
ever faced.
and she's got a really
good chance of destroying
the entire galaxy
and everything we love
and everyone we love
and... and...
and the High Gnees--
( giggling )
Listen, I know I'm
being a wet blanket,
but we cannot afford
to blow this.
- The High--
( choking laughter )
These guys are
very  serious,
and  very  uptight.
They place the utmost
importance on manners
and protocol,
and this is not
the time for jokes.
Oh, come on, Syl.
Listen up.
The darkest times call for
the sunniest smiles.
Not today, they don't.
If we offend
the High Gnees
in any way such as
laughing at their name,
we lose our shot at
learning the secret
that could stop
Dominator.
Understand?
Okay.
( exhales )
I promise to put
all my power
into polite pleasantries,
precise protocol,
and perfect posture.
( Sylvia sighs )
Thanks, buddy.
( toilet flushing sound )
MAN: State your name
and business!
Salutations, kind sir.
We, Sylvia and Wander--
Louder!!
Come to humbly request
an audience
with the esteemed
High Gnee council.
( snickering )
Oh, you have got
to be kidding me.
Ahem. A most gracious
thank you, sir.
We desperate,
needy travelers
would be most humbled
if you would see fit
to open your doors to ones
as lowly as we.
Bow, bow, curtsy,
step left, step right,
squat and curtsy, curtsy,
kick, kick, kick.
Well done.
- I am the butler.
- ( muffled laughter )
Please follow me to
the hind quarters.
No way!
Wander, you've got
to keep it together.
Okay, so his head looks
like a giant...
But, but, but, but, but...
No buts.
The fate of the galaxy
is at stake,
so no more cracks.
( muffled laugh )
What was that?
Nothing. Nothing
at all, sir.
Okay, okay, okay.
Time to get serious.
Serious.
Don't fall behind.
( gasping laugh )
And don't forget
to wipe...
your feet.
This shall indeed
be a long night.
( muffled laughter )
Please wait here
until you are summoned to move
into the bowels
of the temple.
Okay, Wander, we need
to get our presentation perfect
if we're gonna impress
these guys.
Bow, bow, curtsy,
step left...
Hey.
How are you keeping
a straight face?
I beg your pardon.
Come on. Don't tell me
you don't think
that their heads
look like giant..
( crashing )
I'm sorry, but...
is there a problem?
No, sir butler of
the esteemed High Gnee council.
My companion is, uh,
hungry.
May I?
Oh, please.
We Gnees like
big buffets,
so feel free to take
a big, juicy bite
of our... rump roast.
Pressed ham.
Hot buttered buns.
Moon cakes.
Roasted halibut.
Sparkling blopberry fizz.
( needle scratches )
Bottomless, of course.
And last but not least,
our galaxy famous
pu-pu platter.
A thousand pardons, sir butler
of the High Gnee council.
We must go do that thing
with the thing real quick.
( guffawing )
Pu-pu platter?!
( gasping )
Okay.
( laughter resumes )
Pressed ham!
Buttered buns!
( raucous laughter )
Oh!
( panting )
Ah, butts.
BUTLER: Excuse me!
Did I hear someone...
laughing?
( coughs )
You!
Is there something funny
you'd care to share with us?
Me? No, no, no, no.
No way.
Why, I'd never even
dream of laughing
at such a solemn
occasion, sir butler,
who looks not even
a little funny.
Guards!
Out with him!
Don't kick me out.
I'm way more worthy
than any of these
bottom feeders.
- Please!
- ( door slams )
I can't stand
brown-nosing.
( gong sounds )
This is it.
Just keep your cool.
Try thinking sad thoughts.
An old man dropping
an ice cream cone.
Acid rain at
Hater's wedding.
Mondays.
Greetings, solicitors.
I am Gluteus,
the High Gnee council's
- number two.
- A bee with
a pollen allergy.
A dog waiting for
his master to come home,
only to discover he's
been sucked through a black
hole never to return.
In a matter of moments,
I shall lead you
into the rear
of the temple,
where you will make
your requests.
We apologize for the delay.
But the Council has been
terribly backed up.
They've been stuck on
their thrones all day,
and they're positively
pooped.
Baby with a broken rattle,
baby with a broken rattle.
Wander!
I'm sorry, Syl.
I'm really trying hard,
but these giggles
have got a hold on me,
and they won't let go.
Wow. I am so, so,
so unbelievably
disappointed in
you, Wander.
We finally got a shot
at stopping Dominator,
and you're about
to blow it.
Sylvia, do you really
think that the High Gnees
are that uptight
and serious?
( crying )
I don't understand.
We did everything
perfectly.
Heel toe, heel toe,
dip, turn, turn.
We're doomed.
Wow, you're right.
If we don't get
the help of the High Gnees,
then Dominator's gonna
destroy the galaxy,
and there is nothing
funny about that.
Really? You mean it?
You're not gonna go in there
and laugh your butt off,
and totally bum me out?
You're behind me
all the way?
I can trust you to
stay serious until
the very end?
No buts about it?
From the bottom
of your heart?
GLUTEUS: The High Gnee council
will now see
Wander and Sylvia.
I present to you
the High Gnee council.
Bow in the presence of
the mighty
Rear Admiral
Keister von Derrière,
Grand Vizier Buh'oo Tay,
Shakaya Rump
the money maker,
the twins, Badonk and Adonk,
and last but not least,
Princess Buttforaface.
You may now present
your pleas for aid.
( light applause )
( clears throat )
Thank you.
Thank you upon
thank you's.
- O magnificent--
- Pardon me.
I am quite stopped up.
( loud farting sound )
( loud raucous laughter )
Oh, man, I can't...
Rump roast!
And... and...
( laughing )
( both laughing
hysterically )
( council members
laughing )
It's about time.
- Someone finally
passed the test.
- ( laughter continues )
Test?
Do you really think
a bunch of people
with heads like ours
would call themselves
the High Gnees?
What does that even mean?
The looks on your faces
are just priceless.
( giggling )
Buns.
Hold it. You did this
for what reason exactly?
( laughing )
Anyone who doesn't laugh
is either lying
or not paying attention.
We are sick and tired
of people kissing our...
( laughing )
faces...
just to get a favor.
You're the first
honest people
we've met in years.
Can you imagine
someone named Gluteus?
( laughter )
My real name's Todd.
Todd.
To help you overcome
even the greatest obstacle,
we offer you
this piece of wisdom.
Lighten up!!
The darkest times call for
the sunniest of smiles.
( laughter )
Wow. Thank you.
It has been a long time
since I've really
laughed my...
Sylvia, that's
just crude.
( toilet flushing )
I get that space
is quiet and all,
but this place
gives me the willies. Ugh!
This place
is amazing!
Just think of the stories
this old time-y orbble
station could tell.
I'd rather you focus
on the present
and help us get
outta here.
Totally out of
orbble juice.
I'll go pay,
you fuel up.
"The Wright Place.
Orbble and Wilmur Wright,
proprietors.
Traverse the universe
one step at a time."
Whoa!
That took no time at all.
Well, Orbble, Wilmur,
thanks for
fueling the adventures,
friends.
Weird. Nobody here.
I left a few credits
on the counter.
Come on, pal, let's ditch
this ghost town.
Bye, Wright Place.
Wish I knew you when.
Ah, forget that place.
We got lots of other
things to see.
Supernovas, astral rings,
a galactic conjunction.
A galactic conjunction?!
That shouldn't be
happening again for
another thousand years.
Whoa, Syl, look.
There's Lord Hater!
And Emperor Awesome.
And me!
Lord Hater,
is that you?
Oh, it's me!
Hi, me!
Wander?
Hold on. Things just
got interesting.
I even packed a picnic!
Did you get time orbbles?
Did I? There were two pumps
not clearly labeled,
I might add.
It's possible that
I may have.
Is it the past?
'Cause we're coming up
on my favorite part.
( straining )
I'm gonna go help me
pass out sandwiches.
You can't just go
over there and help yourself.
With time orbbles,
there are paradoxes
and time shifts,
and that stupid
butterfly effect.
Ooh, butterflies.
Seriously, if we change
something in our past,
it could affect our future,
which is our present
in the future...
Oh, I hate time travel!
We just have to get
back to the Wright place
at the right time,
to the exact moment
we left,
and get regular old
orbble orbbles.
Stop. We're here.
- At the Wright place?
- Yeah.
♪ Do you like
leisurely strolls in the park ♪
♪ 'Cause I do ♪
♪ Cat person or dog person? ♪
♪ I know it's
tough deciding ♪
♪ Think of the pair
we could be if you dare... ♪
This is the big old number
Hater and I did
when you were off
helping Peepers
freeze the ship.
Look at Hater's two-step.
He's come such a long way.
♪ Seems like
a pretty good start ♪
Look, buddy, I know
you're having fun reminiscing,
but we can't just
waste our time
watching past episodes
of our lives.
It could be dangerous.
And boring.
We only have enough
juice for a few more orbbles.
When our time runs out,
our time runs out,
and we'll be stuck
wherever we are,
so can you please just
work with me on this?
Okay, well...
this event just happened,
so we can't be far
from the orbble station.
Just a bit further forward.
Further forward.
Got it.
What? Slow down!
Stop!
Where are we?
When are we?
( growling )
We have to save
Lord Hater.
Wander, this must
be the future.
We can't interfere now.
We'll have to save him
later when the time comes.
But the time is now.
Not yet it's not.
We'll make a note
of this moment,
and come back
when the time is right.
Okay, buddy?
We just gotta get back.
Gotta get back?
Back to the past.
Wander, no!
Okay, I don't have
much to go on.
Just my gut,
a sneaking suspicion,
and a quick eye for detail,
but I think we were
right about here.
Uh, Wander.
You're too late,
Admiral Admirable.
FYI: I knew about this pyramid
before it became a thing.
Another galactic
conjunction?
This can't be
the future, can it?
Nope, this is the past.
A  long  time ago,
in a galaxy far, far,
far away.
Adjacent to the one
we're in now, or then.
I'm really confused.
- Ooh, time travel!
- Look!
Major Threat,
is that you?
Wander, is that you?
It's me, Tumbleweed.
Are you here to watch
the planets align, too?
Look, I even packed
a picnic!
Tumbleweed?
Folks in this galaxy
call me Tumbleweed.
Who am I to say
what's what?
You are a man
of mystery, my friend.
You remember me, right
Tumbleweed.
I travel the galaxy,
I'm about this tall,
wear a hat, and sometimes,
I make this face.
You do this a lot,
don't you?
Whatever it takes
to find the good in the bad.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Not here.
What's wrong?
When are we?
Back off, KL-Bot 85.
This is my bounty.
Never hurts to
help... yourself.
Come on,
you wandering weirdo.
Wander. Huh.
I like the sound of that.
What's wrong, Syl?
I knew you were
a bad guy; I was there.
Yeah, but I'd
rather forget it.
I've come a long way
since then.
I don't wanna live
in the past.
I just wanna keep
moving forward.
Oh, no.
Our last orbble.
If we don't get back
to the orbble station...
Then we're stuck wherever
and whenever
the orbble pops.
Let's do this.
No time to lose.
BOTH: No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no...
WANDER: The end of time.
Too far!
SYLVIA: The beginning of time.
We're here.
The station.
Hello, weary travelers.
I'm Orbble, and this
is my brother Wilmur,
and you are at
the Wright place.
- Yep.
- At the wrong time!
Say, friends, can we
tempt you with our
brand-new invention?
The orbble transporter.
Traverse the universe
one step at a time.
Yep.
Orbbles. Perfect.
We'll take some
time orbbles.
So we can return
to the present.
Time orbbles.
Never heard of those.
- Eh, Wilmur?
- Nope.
- Sounds like
a bang-up idea though.
- Yep.
We'll get to work
on 'em straight away.
- Really?
- Yep.
- Should have 'em
figured out
- in about five--
- No.
- Fifty years.
- Yep.
We're stuck here.
We're not stuck.
We can travel the galaxy
like we always do.
We'll just be
ahead of the trends.
We can't because
the paradox
of the space-time continuum...
Butterflies.
We have to stay put.
Ugh, time travel!!
Sylvia, this is
all my fault.
I was so caught up
in living in the past
that I ruined our future.
You didn't, buddy.
You know what
would ruin our future?
Feeling sorry
for ourselves,
and not living
in the present.
Hey, fellas,
how about we run
the station
while you hurry up
and focus on those
time orbbles?
Fifty years are gonna
fly right by.
Wander, today's the day.
( snoring )
WANDER: Today's the day!
Hurry, Wander.
I'm going as fast
as I can.
I get that space
is quiet and all,
but this place
gives me the willies. Ugh.
This place is amazing!
Just think of the stories
this old-time-y orbble
station can tell.
I'd rather you focus
on the present
and help us
get outta here.
We're totally out of
orbble juice.
I'll go pay,
you fuel up.
Out of order?
Huh. Time orbbles?!
Whoo, close call.
( sighs happily )
We did it, Syl old girl.
They bought regular
old orbbles.
We closed the time loop
so none of this ever happened.
Sorry we had to waste
our time waiting here.
Not a waste of time if I got to
spend it with you, pal.
I almost bought
time orbbles.
Can you believe it?
That could've turned into
a whole thing.
( straining )
SYLVIA:
How long are we gonna...
WANDER: Sh! This
is my favorite part.