♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander! Wander! Over! Over!
Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi dit dit dit ♪
[screaming]
[laser gun blasts]
[door bangs open]
Angela, Mom and Dad
are gonna be worried sick.
What was so important
that you ran off in
the middle of an evacuation?!
Aw, sweetie.
It's alright, Melodie. I can
get us back to the escape ship.
I'll just jump out and be
all like, "Hey, Robodorks!
I'm gonna rewire
your hardware!" Bam! Pow!
That's crazy! We should lie low
and wait for this to blow over.
Maybe we could just, um, ask
the robots to not be so mean?
I'm really liking
my "Hey, Robodorks" plan.
Well, whatever we do, we have to
do it fast or we'll miss our--
--escape ship.
[crying]
I'll scramble
their circuits!
No! I'm too young
for half of me to die!
Jamie! David! Hank!
It'll be OK,
The Hero of legend will save us.
Of course!
Duh!
The Hero will
totally stop Dominator!
What's the matter? You've never
heard the legend of the Hero?
He's a hundred feet
tall!
I heard he ate
a supernova on a dare!
He fights
for what's right!
He's--
Oh no! Stop hat and roll!
What are you kids
still doing here?!
Dominator's gonna
crack this planet
in half any second now!
[babbling]
Don't worry, Ma'am.
"Ma'am"?
The Hero's gonna arrive
to save us! He can
handle anything.
[babbling]
Well, until
that  guy shows up...
maybe  we  get you
to your folks.
[crash]
Boy, we sure are lucky
we found you kids.
Aw, we woulda been fine, mister.
The Hero woulda saved us!
Oooh! Which hero? Prince
Cashmere? Stella Starbella?
Sir Bradley Starlight?
Naw, not those jokers.
The Hero.
He's a mythical furry creature.
I heard he took out
Lord Hater himself!
WANDER: Oh really?
[screaming]
I hereby conquer this planet
in the name of Lord Hater!
The greatest in the galaxy!
[cackles]
[man humming dramatically]
WANDER: Aw is he givin' him
a lovin' friendship hug?
HANK: Nah. He's squeezing
the life out of him!
[screams]
Oh. O... kay.
[stomach grumbles]
[giggles]
Don't listen to Hank.
He's got the Hero  all  wrong.
He's super cool n' edgy.
He won't just save the planet,
he'll make Dominator look like
a dork too!
[scraping]
Plus he was around
way  before Hater.
I heard he took down
Major Threat!
MAJOR THREAT: The Million Year
Darkness is nigh!
Once I've blotted out the
sun, a reign of fear and...
[electric guitar music]
[cackling]
[loud belch]
Oh no.
[explosion]
Aw, sorry Major Threat.
Did I do dat?!
Major bummer! [farts]
Did I mention
he's super witty
and hilarious?
♪ When you're a stupid dummy ♪
♪ And you got
a stupid face... ♪
Agghh! Oh yeah!?
Well, how would
you like... this?!
[laser blasts]
Ahhh heh heh heh haaa!
Oh yeah?
Well, how would  you  like...
mustard or mayo?! Mustard
or mayo?! Mustard or mayo?!
Mustard or mayo?!
Please stop!
You are so totally--
Radical?!
Beedle deedle dee!
Annoying!
[screams]
[farting]
[ fart continues ]
Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit!
[laughs]
But I-I-I don't...
Sylvia,
I would never... I-I-I--
I know, buddy. Some kids
are just really intense.
No way, Jamie!
He's a monster.
He's an outlaw!
- Monster!
- Outlaw!
Please! Stop!
The Hero isn't mean.
He's kind and curious.
He's kinda
like a little kid.
What a neat town this is.
I'll have to remember
to take lots of neat pictures
to remember
this neat town by.
[loud crash]
[screaming]
Wha--?
[roaring]
DAVID:
And he doesn't travel alone.
He's got a big, strong
friend that protects him
from bad stuff
like galactic dictators.
'Bout time.
What?
What? Nothing.
Oh no! There shouldn't
be a monster here.
I'm going to need
help to stop it.
Come in Silver 7.
I need you!
[rocket blasts off]
♪ Silver 7 ♪
♪ Ultra robot fighting force ♪
♪ Super-mechanized
wonder horse ♪
♪ Your monster-smashing
friend ♪
♪ Until the end ♪
♪ Silver 7 ♪
CHILD: Silver 7,
activate Protocol Duchess!
I love you Silver 7!
♪ Silver 7 ♪
♪ Your monster-smashing
friend until the end ♪
♪ Silver 7 ♪
Oh... kay.
Well, according to my
calculations, your planet's
escape ship should be passing by
in the morning, so unless
anybody else has any
non-robot horse theories,
maybe we should all
get a little rest.
"Theories"? Please.
That was cute for fanfiction,
but it's hardly canon.
The Hero isn't like that.
Oh, yeah? How do you know?
Because I know
where he comes from.
- You do?
Oh yes. His true origins
are dark and complex,
with lots of twists and feels.
So  many feels.
At the dawn of time,
there was a race of Star Nomads
who travelled the galaxy
spreading light and joy.
But the youngest and most
innocent Nomad wandered off,
and his uncontrollable
curiosity accidentally released
an ancient evil...
[growling]
...that corrupted his father,
turning him into a creature
of pure hate!
Shocking twist!
Racked with guilt,
the Hero travels the galaxy,
trying to undo
the mistakes of his past,
while  also  trying to find
his long-lost sister
who has sworn revenge
against him! Double twist!
To survive, he'll have
to unlock his inner strength,
compassion, courage,
and the power of the wolf!
[growling]
This horrible curse--
HANK: Wait, I thought
it was inner strength.
MELODIE: Inner strength
can be a curse!
[howling]
It can only be lifted
by his true love...
a secret winged princess.
HANK: Aww, come on!
JAMIE: Are you kidding?
Silence! This is only part one
of a three part trilogy!
Soooo...
So you see, Emperor Awesome's
his half-brother and the Evil
Sandwich is his cousin and...
But he still
crushes villains right?!
Dudes' gotta have
a guitar!
What about Silver 7,
His friend to the end!
[loud stomping]
[electronic scanning noise]
- This is not happening.
- We're doomed!
- We're dead!
What are we gonna do?
The hero's not here yet!
WANDER: The escape ship!
How can we get the kids up there
with Bots focused on the ship?
Easy.
They'll be focused on us!
Hey, fellas, perhaps you would
like a warm, distracting hug!?
Sylvia, activate
protocol Orbit Away!
- Thanks!
- Thanks, ma'am.
- Thank you.
And don't worry! When we find
him, we'll send the Hero back
to help you!
Hey, why didn't you set those
kids straight and tell them
the truth?
Aw, Syl, it doesn't matter if
the stories are true or not.
All that matters
is that they give them hope.
Now ride, Silver 7, ride!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[groans] Nothing!
We have nothing!
No power, no planets, no plan!
Dominator's obliterating
the entire galaxy, and I've
got no idea how to stop her!
And  she won't even
go on a date with me.
Sir, I'm sure being rejected
by your most hated enemy
that you're also in love with
feels... bad?
But we really, really,
really need a plan,
and I can't believe I'm saying
this, but I could really
use your help!
Yes! That's it!
Really?! You know how
to stop Dominator?
Don't fret, C-Peeps,
I have the perrrfect plan.
Oh, thank Grop!
I'm gonna finally go tell
our neighbor
to clean up
his stupid lawn!
[canned laughter]
With all due respect, sir,
we came to Suburbon V
to lay low.
Dominator would never
look for us in this boring
cul-de-sac,
thus making it the perfect place
to hide while we formulate
our plan
to save the galaxy
so we can take it over again.
But that jerk has the messiest
yard on the block
and his leaves
keep blowing onto our...
Rahh!
He's doing it on purpose!
[canned laughter]
May have lost the galaxy but
I'm not gonna let some dumb-wad
neighbor mess with my turf!
Whaddup, Neighbroham?
Awesome in da cul-da-sizzy!
Wha-- What?
[groans]
What are you doing here?!
Oh, uh, totally not terrified
and hiding from D-- Domi--
that lady villain and her
horrifying, universe-ending
onslaught
and her fiery fiery fists,
and don't let her get me! Nooo!
[canned laughter]
Oh, um, [clears throat]
why are you here?
Uh, totally not
what you just said.
Right. So. Wassup?
Well, neighbor,
I just wanted to come by and say
Clean up your filthy leaves!!!
Please. She may be
in charge up there,
but down here,
this is my cul-de-sizzy.
So cross me and it'll be
the end of the road, neighbor!
Watchdogs, eyes up!
Fist fighters, punch it!
No! no powers, no armies,
no fighting,
or we'll be found out!
Sir, is this one of those
things where you obsess
over something
to cover up the real issue?
Of course not! I just refuse
to be publicly humiliated
by Dominator...
I mean, Domineighbor!
[canned laughter]
Our dumb neighbor.
[sighs] And there it is.
OK, listen!
You stay on your side of
the street, you stay on ours,
and for everyone's safety,
shake hands and be neighborly!
[both growl]
[applause]
No!
No "Grrr"!
Inside, both of you!
OK, sir, new plan.
What do we know about Dominator?
[leaf blower blaring]
[chuckling]
Clean enough for ya, neighbor?
[sighs]
[growls]
[chuckles]
You're welcome!
[growls]
Raa! Raa! Raa! Raa!
Raa... raa... raa...
Raa... Raa...
Sir, please,
this is pointless.
We need to get some sleep and
strategize fresh in the morning.
Right right.
In the morning.
[rooster crows]
[bicycle bell rings]
Aw, good morning,
Mr. Hater.
Morning, Jimmy.
[growling]
Go on, Tim,
do your business.
Good boy, Captain Tim.
[canned laughter]
[gasps]
Yes! The plan! The plan!
HATER: Yes the plan.
Now Peepers, how can I help?
Really, you're not gonna...?
What about Awesome?
Ha! I've got a feeling Awesome
won't be bothering us
ever again.
B-but how did he--?
The acid totally--
Sir, now is not the time
for a series of hair-brained
competitive antics!
It's plan time
and I really need your help!
[door slams]
Aww....
♪ Head back to the cul-de-sac
to find a little peace
and quiet ♪
♪ But my next door neighbor's
getting on my nerves ♪
♪ And now sparks
are flying, it's ♪
♪ Bad neighbors
Bad neighbors ♪
♪ Every time I go outside ♪
♪ Bad neighbors
Bad neighbors ♪
♪ Every occupy
for bad neighbors ♪
[speed metal music]
[techno music]
[music plays louder]
[explosion]
[canned laughter]
[cheering]
Awesome!
Mm-hm mm-hm, weld the tradwell
to the fluxxor,
supercharge the
overthrusting oscillator,
reflavven the aximus,
and... and...
Done! I think I finally
solved it, sir! Sir?
[grunting] Stupid wind!
Bat must be crooked!
Ball's not regulation!
Too much gravity!
[glass breaks]
Inside. Now.
To get my bat?
No! To give me your opinion
on my brilliant plan and--
What is that infernal beeping?!
[truck beeping]
A moving truck?
Awesome is moving out!
Yes, I did it!
I win! I win! I win!
Now that I have your full,
uninterrupted attention,
allow me to present
my plan to stop Dominator
and take back the galaxy!
Behold the one,
the only--
[door bell rings]
[screaming]
Oh, Awesome.
I heard you were leaving
and never ever ever ever
ever eeeeever coming back.
Welp, ta-ta,
don't drop by anytime!
The only thing I'll be dropping
is the phattest of beats
at my sick
end of the galaxy barbecue!
That's right. All the escaped
villains will be there.
The cool ones, anyway.
If D... Domin-aaahh--
if  she  is gonna take us out,
we're going down partyin'!
We'll be using all
the parking spots on the block,
including your driveway,
I'm running 14 hot tubs
off your outlet.
It's gonna be crazy loud,
and it doesn't end
until the galaxy does!
[people sigh]
Then everyone will know
that Emperor Awesome
is the greatest...
...in the cul-de-sac.
[applause]
Oh, and just to be 100% clear,
here's your  non  invitation.
[people sigh sadly]
Hasta!
Rrrrrraaaaaa!
No! No "Raaaaa". You are going
to sit down, shut up,
and behold my ultimate plan
to stop Dominator!
Uhhhh...
Gaaahh! I knew it!
This is a terrible plan!
A net?  A net?
She shoots lava!
[cries]
No, Peepers,
this could actually work.
[gasps] Really?
Yes!
If we simply replace Dominator
with Emperor Awesome,
we could totally ruin
his stupid barbecue
and  I  could become
the greatest
in the cul-de-sac!
[screams]
That's it!
Who cares about the cul-de-sac?
The galaxy is in danger!
I've been asking
for your help for days,
but you'd rather waste
your time playing pranks
on a muscle-headed mackerel!
Do you really wanna know
how to stop that guy?
Just throw
a better barbecue!
Set the grill flame
to 456 degrees!
Food-to-guest ratio
equals 3-Y to the n-power!
Execute décor protocol Omicron!
Play "Hater's Chill Mix"
at 64 decibels!
Hot Sauce,
lemonade,
multiple spoons!
Apron!
Turn! Flip!
Turn! Flip! Turn! Flip!
And don't skimp
on the cole slaw!
Dinner is served.
Whoa!
Check out Hater's place!
What? Bros, you can't
ditch me for that poser.
Sorry, loser.
Guess they're having
too much fun over here with  me:
the greatest
in the cul-de-sac!
[canned laughter]
Way to go, Peepers! Couldn't
have planned it better myself.
Wait. Do you mean to say
this whole time,
all your juvenile, pointless
neighborhood one-upsmanship
was all to inspire me,
to break me
out of my planning funk?
You've taught me that whether
it's stopping a powerful
villainess
or throwing the perfect
barbecue, when the chips
are down
sometimes you need a small win
to give you the confidence
for a big win.
Oh, thank you, sir!
Uhhh, yeah.
That thing you said.
Watchdogs, eyes up!
I may not have an exact plan
to stop Dominator,
but I'm confident I will!
Commander Peepers!
[canned laughter]
[bicycle bell rings]
Oh, hey,
Mr. Awesome.
Hey, Jimmy.
[applause]
♪ Where do all
the villains go ♪
♪ When Dominator's
drilled and dried ♪
♪ Send 'em back
to the Bad Guy cul-de-sac ♪
♪ And watch
the sparks fly, it's ♪
♪ Bad neighbors
Bad neighbors... ♪