♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
Wander, the whole galaxy
is gonna get pulled into
this black hole
if we don't find a way
to plug this sucker up.
We'll find the perfect
portal plug.
Don't you worry,
Sylvia...
Wander!
I'll be grop darned.
You did it, buddy.
Perfect portal plug
procured.
( majestic fanfare plays )
♪ ♪
So... now what?
You just gonna
stand there forever?
Nah. I'm positive my hat
can produce a permanent patch
for this pesky puncture.
So, uh, yeah.
Looks like I'll be
standing here forever.
Don't worry, buddy.
I will scour the galaxy
for the perfect plug.
No matter what terrifying
dangers I must face,
and amazing feats
I must accomplish,
I will find a way.
Yeah! Let's go!
Oh, right.
- I'll be back.
- No rush, Syl.
There's plenty of ways
to wile away the time
till you get back.
Just...
wanna... sit!
Come on, come on.
Just a little bit.
( straining )
( shrieking )
Finally.
( contented sigh )
( stomach rumbling )
Aw, come on, tummy.
Not now.
( loud roaring )
Oh. Right. Space.
Oh, sweet, delicious,
delectable and distant apple.
Yes, yes!
Come... to... me!
What's the matter?
Stuck?
Lord Hater!
Am I glad to see you!
You see, this little black hole
is threatening to destroy
the entire galaxy,
so Sylvia went off to find
something to plug it up
permanently.
I've been stuck here
all day.
At first, I didn't think
it would be a problem,
but I tell you, friend,
it's been a battle
with the burden of boredom,
and I don't know if I can
take this anymore!
Any way you can
help a buddy out?
You  need  my  help?
This is a very
interesting situation.
One doesn't get in
a situation like this every day.
- Tell me about it.
- I mean...
you can't even do this.
Look at me, two hands.
Derpity-doo, I can
move about freely.
Whoopity-whoo!
Oh, you hungry?
Thanks. I love apples.
I hate apples.
Oh, man!
Well, hey, since you're
a friend indeed,
how's about helping
your friend in need?
Like maybe zip-zappin'
the hole shut
with some of
your cosmic lightning?
What's the rush?
You said you were bored.
Let's have some fun,
friend.
( squealing )
♪ When you wander
over yonder ♪
♪ And you wear
a stupid hat ♪
Tag, you're it!
Mustard or mayo,
mustard or mayo?
( blows raspberry )
Wander, that was
very rude.
What did you have
for lunch?
Oh, right, sorry.
You're starving.
Okay, this may be
fun for you, but--
( mocking ) This may
be fun for you, but...
Okay, I get it.
Lord Hater, I thought
you came here...
- ...to help.
Sorry, sorry.
Let me see
what I can do.
It's ringing.
Hello.
Sylvia?
Yes, this is
Lord Hater.
Yeah, I know.
Funny hearing from me.
Is she okay?
Has she found something
to plug up the hole?
Yeah, so I'm here
trying to help Wander,
and I was wondering
if you...
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
( laughs ) Oh, grop,
yeah, tell me about it.
What? Oh, sure.
Uh-huh. All right.
I'll tell him.
You, too, you flab-drasser.
Mm-hmm. Bye.
She says you have
a dumb face,
and she doesn't like you
and she never liked you,
and she's never coming back
because your face is so dumb.
( laughter )
What's the matter?
The power of friendship
didn't save you?
Oh, man, that was...
That was really mean,
wasn't it?
Have I always
been that mean?
I'm finally seeing
the error of my ways.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You really need
my help,
and here I am, being
an insensitive jerk.
I'd probably feel
a lot better
if someone just
hugged me right now.
Gosh, if I even got
the littlest hug,
I would totally reform
and not be evil anymore.
( gasps ) Hater,
I'm right here for you, buddy.
Too bad there's
no one here to
make me feel better.
Yo! Right here.
A one-armed hug
still comes with
a wide open heart.
What, no takers?
Guess I'll just stay evil.
Ha! You're finished!
Useless.
Bye-bye, good guy.
You can't even
wander anymore.
You're more like
Stander.
Over therer.
( raucous laughter )
You know what you are?
You're just
a whole lotta nothing.
"Never hurts to help."
Ha!
If I can't even
give a friend a hug,
then what good am I
at all?
( mocking ) Never hurts
to help, never hurts to help.
- Never hurts to help.
- Wait, what now?
Here I was, selfishly
thinking about
how I was suffering,
totally forgetting about
all the folks I'm helping
by not letting
the galaxy get sucked into
this black hole.
And shucks, I'm even
helping you.
Wait, what? No!
Never hurts to help.
Thanks for reminding
me, pal.
That was just
the help I needed.
( shrieks )
Don't you dare find
a positive in this
terrible, horrible thing.
Who's helping now?
Oh, no.
Wow, Lord Hater,
you're saving
the galaxy, too.
I knew there was
good in you.
No. Oh, no. No!
But don't worry.
You kept me company
in my darkest hour,
and I'll happily
do the same for you.
( voice distorting )
Forever and ever
and ever and ever,
and ever and ever
and ever and ever.
So he was literally
doing nothing,
and you could've
just ignored him,
and he would've been
stuck there forever,
and never got in your way
or annoy you,
or ruin your plans for
galactic domination ever again.
Shut up, Peepers.
Okay, I got a genie lamp,
a few dozen magic amulets,
diamond tape,
an interdimensional
soldering gun, a cosmic...
All right.
♪ Who can crush any planet
with a wave of his hand? ♪
♪ Who's crushing rock shows
with his all-watch dog band? ♪
♪ Whose never-ending tour
is never gonna end? ♪
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
Hater! All right!
Whoo! All right!
Yeah. We have been Lord Hater
and the Harbingers of Doom.
( weak cheering )
And before we go,
we have one more thing to say.
One, two, three, four!
- ♪ Who is the universe's... ♪
- Sir, please stop.
You've been playing
the same song for four days.
♪ Who won't stop rockin' till
love comes a-knockin'? ♪
Hater!
Sir, Dominator is not
gonna show up,
and if she does,
she's not gonna see you
as an awesome rock star
and fall in love with you.
She's gonna blast us!
♪ Who's just jealous
and doesn't know
what he's talkin' about? ♪
Peepers!
Have you considered
she might not even
like rock and roll?
( music stops )
Oh, my grop.
Peepers, what if
you're right?
This whole time,
I didn't even consider.
Drop the beat.
Oh, yeah.
Hater time.
Here it comes,
here it comes.
( rapping )
♪ My name's Lord Hater,
and I'm here to say ♪
♪ I'm the greatest dude
in the galaxy ♪
♪ When Dom rolls in,
she'll be lookin' to fight ♪
♪ But instead she'll
be surprised ♪
♪ That my rhymes
are so tight ♪
♪ That's when she'll fall
in love with me ♪
♪ Like I said, I'm the greatest
in the galaxy ♪
Please, sir, stop!
( weak cheering )
- You're right, Peepers,
that was terrible.
- It's okay, sir.
I don't know what to say
other than...
One, two, three, four!
♪ Who is the awesomest dude
in the universe? ♪
Okay, I gotta figure out
a way to stop this insanity.
( singing high note )
( cash register bell
dings )
Would you like to join
Hater on stage?
Really? For really real?
I'd love to!
But doesn't Hater
already have
a lead guitarist?
He's tied up at the moment.
( squealing )
What do you think, Syl?
Can I, can I, can I?
Who can't stand to hear
this song anymore?
Sylvia!!
♪ Who's super strong
and shoots out ♪
♪ Scary green lightnin'? ♪
( Wander screaming
high note )
Wander?
Get outta here or
I'm gonna...
( playing killer riff )
...destroy you.
I command you to play
in drop D tuning,
four-four time. Go!
♪ Who is the universe's
ultimate evil-doer? ♪
Hater!
All right!
No, but, this
should be over.
HATER: One, two,
three, four!
Look, you know
as well as I do that...
BOTH: This will never end.
For their, and our,
own good,
we have to stop them.
( both gagging )
We have been Lord Hater,
the Harbingers of Doom.
And before we go,
we have one more thing to say.
Good night.
( music stops )
Whoo!
Aww.
One, two, three, four!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
Hater!
All right!
♪ Who's gonna catch me
when I leap off the stage? ♪
♪ The crowd! ♪
All right! Here I come,
everybody. Whoo!
♪ Skull ship, laser beams ♪
♪ Conquered planet,
rock star dreams ♪
♪ Lightning powers,
field of flames ♪
♪ Evil lady,
love and fame! ♪
Whoo!
♪ Stupid Peepers,
stupid horse ♪
♪ I'm the greatest,
you're the worst ♪
( screams )
♪ Who's not gonna stop rockin'
till love comes a-knockin'? ♪
Hater!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
Hater!
We have been Lord Hater
and the Harbingers of Doom.
And before we go, we have
one more thing to say to you.
( feedback whines )
One, two, three, four!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer?
( weakly )
Hater.
But how?
I'm exhausted.
How are they
still going?
( bell dings )
( evil chuckle )
Whoo!
One more time!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
- Hater!
- Faster!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
- Hater!
- Even faster!
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evildoer? ♪
- Hater!
-  En Español!
♪ ¿Quién es el más awesomest
malhechor del universo? ♪
Hater!
Now backwards!
♪ !Retah! Reod-live tesmosewa
s'esrevinu eht si ohw? ♪
BOTH: Faster!
Faster, faster!
♪ Who is the...
who is the... ♪
( shrieking )
We have been Lord Harry...
and the Happy Burgers
of Boom, and...
Whoo!
Aww!
Hater, you can't
stop now.
Dominator's not...
...here.
PEEPERS: We're doomed.
I knew this was a stupid plan.
But I gotta
help him, Syl.
He's finally choosing
love over hate.
( weakly )
Who... is...
the universe's...
Wander!
Hater may be
out of his mind,
but at least his heart's
in the right place.
One, two, three, four.
♪ Who is the universe's
awesomest evil-doer? ♪
Hater!
All right!
He's out
of his mind.
( sighs ) At least
his heart's in the right place.
Come on.
Oh, no.
This is ridiculous.
We'll all be blasted
to smithereens.
Or maybe
it'll work.
Either way, it'll be
a heck of a show-stopper.
( groaning )
♪ Who's super strong and shoots
out scary green lighting? ♪
Hater!
♪ Who set the record for
galactic explosions? ♪
Hater!
- She stopped firing.
- It's... working?!
♪ Who's really happy that
his friends will support him? ♪
Hater!
♪ Who's found love
and is on the path ♪
♪ To be a good guy? ♪
Hater!
♪ Who tries to conquer
and rule ♪
♪ Just 'cause
he wants to be cool? ♪
♪ Who pushes and shoves just
'cause he wants to be loved?
♪ Who likes a lady villain ♪
♪ Wants to show her
he's willin'? ♪
♪ I said who's insecure
and lonely ♪
♪ Your sensitive
puppy-lovin' one and only ♪
Talkin' 'bout Hater!
Hater!
( Dominator applauding )
It worked!
( laughing )
♪ Who can't believe
how amazingly stupid this is? ♪
Dominator.
SYLVIA AND PEEPERS:
That totally didn't work.
Did you see?
She was, like,
so into it.
Next time, we need
three... no, six,
drummers.
No!
Hater!