♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
All right!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
( crashing )
Ooh, that's not good.
Oh, man, Lord Hater
just had this thing waxed.
Okay,
no need to panic.
Maybe if we just...
( tires screeching )
( alarm blaring )
Aarrgh!
You Watchdogs
are all useless!
I've never encountered
a more pathetic excuse
for an evil army
in all my life!
Yee-hoo!
Stupid!
Idiots!
Imbeciles!
No!
All I want is for you guys
to finally do something,
anything right
for once!
Is that so hard?
They went to
the wrong conference room.
( screaming )
You!
Why aren't you
running in terror?
Hello?
Pure concentrated
bolts of evil.
I think
this one's broken.
Peepers!
What--
What is that thing?
It appears to be
some kind of present.
But how-- Who would--
What is wrong with him?
( laughing )
I don't know, sir.
I just don't know.
Careful. We don't know
if that thing's contagious.
( giggling )
( tuning fork
vibrates )
Interesting.
I wonder...
( grunting )
( crashing )
( screaming )
Huh? Peepers,
get out of there!
( screaming )
Yeah!
Aah!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
( giggles )
What was that
all about?
It's worse
than we thought.
His cortisol levels
are low,
while his proximity
to the object
has completely altered
the molecular structure
of his prefrontal cortex!
Flab drassit, man!
Enough science
mumbo-jumbo!
Give it to me straight.
The gift has made him...
happy.
( gasps )
Happy?
Happy.
But the Watchdogs have
never been happy before.
Well, they've never
received a gift before.
( screaming )
Peepers, what are
we going to do?
If this spreads,
the entire army
will be ruined!
It's okay, sir.
He's sealed in sick bay,
completely quarantined.
There is no way
this happiness is spreading.
WATCHDOGS: Happy.
Oh!
Shh! Don't attract
their attention.
WATCHDOGS: Happy.
Happy.
That's it.
Easy.
Don't make any sudden
movements or...
( toy breaking )
WATCHDOGS: Happy!
Aah!
( screaming )
( panting )
Oh!
It's worse
than we thought.
Happy.
There's a serial gifter
loose on the ship.
No, no, no,
it can't be.
Not...
( squeaking )
He's infecting
the entire army with joy,
killing any hate
they may have.
We have to destroy him
before he destroys us.
Peepers,
assemble a team.
M-M-Me?
B-B-But, sir...
All right, men,
split up!
Man, Pete, if we make it
out of here alive,
first thing
I'm gonna do
is find that gal
I met on shore leave,
buy her a ring
and ask her to be mine.
Ah, you're crazy, Teddy.
Hater never lets anyone
have nice things...
like dreams.
Teddy? Teddy?
( screaming )
Hang in there,
buddy, I'm coming!
Oh, no.
Teddy!
Happy.
Teddy.
She's gonna love it, kid,
she's gonna love it.
Whoa, whoa.
My dream.
Teddy, Pete,
come in, darn you!
We are on high--
Woo-hoo-ho!
Whoo!
Curses!
Pete has succumbed
to the dance!
( shrieks )
( panting )
( banging )
Who is it?
It's Peepers!
He's coming.
Hurry!
What's the password?
We never came up
with a password!
Please!
It's worse than we thought!
Stop saying that!
It's not worse
than we thought!
This is the most
worst it can be!
Commander Peepers?
C-Peeps?
Happy!
Aah!
Oh, no.
All this happy
isn't happening.
It's just a bad dream.
( screaming )
( continues screaming )
( sighing )
Huh!
Aah!
( gulping )
( panting )
( panting heavily )
( screaming )
( panting )
Oh. Oh.
Dumb snowflake.
Being flakey.
Aah!
Stay back!
No.
No. No!
Perimeter
is on lockdown.
Clear!
Bravo Team!
Secure Lord Hater!
We've got him.
Bone Daddy
is in the Nest.
I repeat, Bone Daddy
is in the nest!
That was the coolest!
You stopped Wander
from infecting me
with the happies...
and this cocoa
is really tasty.
( slurping )
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but you did something
right for once!
Good work, Watchdogs.
Sir, it was
the least we could do
after you gave us all
those thoughtful gifts, sir.
After I gave you?
But I didn't--
Your gifts really encouraged
us to do our very best.
A little positive reinforcement
goes a long way, sir!
We love you, sir!
"You're welcome.
Heart.
Wander."
No!
( snoring )
( groans )
Oh, my grop.
It's today?
It's today!
There's just one
thing I don't get.
What's not to get?
WANDER: Once every
365 Yuletidian cycles,
a cluster of interstellar
temporal neutrinos
collides with a passing
dimensional space vortex,
resulting in a massive
chronal jet stream.
Ooh.
What's in the box?
WANDER: And we
use it to travel
across the universe
in a single day,
giving gifts to everyone we've
met over the past season...
of our lives!
( birds chirping )
( shrieks )
Aah!
SYLVIA: I get that.
WANDER: Then do you not
get that us being nice
to folks makes them
want to pay it forward?
Lolly!
SYLVIA: No, I get that.
I just don't get why
I have to wear these.
'Cause they go
so well with these!
ALL: Yay!
For all your help.
Sorry,
who are you again?
( sighs )
Okay.
That was a blast.
And we delivered
gifts to everyone
we encountered
this past season of our lives.
Almost!
Boing, boing.
We have
to give gifts
to Lord Hater
and the Watchdogs!
We've shared more adventures
with them than anybody.
Even though most
of those adventures
involved them
trying to destroy us?
The guy is a jerk!
I'm just saying,
maybe we should
institute some kind of
Naughty or Nice policy.
There's
an old Slarnian saying...
( guttural noises )
Which roughly
translates to,
"A little nice makes
naughty think twice."
"Sylvia,
this panel is loose.
Hugs and kisses.
Sylvia."
If we give Hater
the perfect gift,
maybe his heart
will grow three sizes
and he'll spread cheer
throughout the galaxy.
Or maybe he'll try
to destroy us.
Again.
I like our odds.
HATER: Watchdogs!
All I want is for you guys
to finally do something,
anything, right
for once!
Is that so hard?
He's gonna be
so excited!
Yeah, that guy's just a barrel
of sunshine waiting to happen.
Exactly!
Hmm.
Was it Conference Room 1
or Conference Room 1-A?
1-A!
Thanks.
Hey, wait a minute!
Who said that?
Show yourselves
or I'll blast you
to bits and even
smaller bits!
It's not just about
giving someone a present.
It's about giving someone
the perfect present.
Observe.
Huh?
What's this?
Read the tag.
Okay, mysterious voice,
but I doubt there's any
new information on this tag
that would
cause me to--
Oh, my grop,
it's for me!
Tim!
The meeting's in here!
Perfect.
He's overwhelmed
with joy!
A little nice makes
naughty think...
Twice.
Slarnian...
( guttural noise )
Yeah, I know.
But if we're caught, we
don't get to deliver gifts.
We get to die.
So just promise me
we'll be careful.
Deal?
Deal.
Let's do this.
( gasps )
Happy.
( sighs )
( gasps )
Happy.
BOTH: Happy.
Perfect.
Eee-yaa.
Happy.
Peepers!
What--
What is that thing?
It appears to be
some kind of present.
But how-- Who would--
What is wrong with him?
( laughing )
The gift has
made him happy.
HATER: But the Watchdogs
have never been happy before!
PEEPERS: Well, they've never
received a gift before.
HATER: Peepers, what
are we going to do?
If this spreads,
the entire army will be ruined!
PEEPERS: It's okay, sir.
There is no way
this happiness is spreading.
WATCHDOGS: Happy.
Aah!
( screaming )
WATCHDOGS: Happy.
PEEPERS: There's a serial
gifter loose on the ship.
HATER: We have to destroy him
before he destroys us.
Peepers,
assemble a team.
( alarm blaring )
They're on to us.
We don't have much time.
Find and secure Hater.
Leave the dogs
to me.
How?
I'll do
what I do best.
Be merry.
All right, men,
split up!
Man, Pete, if we make
it out of here alive,
first thing
I'm gonna do
is find that gal
I met on shore leave,
buy her a ring
and ask her to be mine.
Ah, you're crazy, Teddy,
Hater never lets anyone
have nice things...
like dreams.
Teddy?
( screaming )
Hang in there,
buddy, I'm coming!
Oh, no.
Teddy!
Happy.
Teddy.
She's gonna
love it, kid,
she's gonna
love it.
My dream.
Perfect.
PEEPERS: Curses!
Pete has succumbed
to the dance!
( screaming )
Lord Hater,
let me in!
Please!
( gasps )
He's gonna ruin
the surprise!
Perfect.
Commander Peepers?
C-Peeps?
Boo.
( screaming )
Sylvia, Hater's
running away,
and we've got
to give him his gift,
because if he
doesn't get his gift,
he won't be filled
with the giving spirit!
So come on and hurry up
if you will, please.
Thank you!
I hate today.
( screaming )
( continues screaming )
Ting!
Aah!
Stay back!
No.
I don't think
he wants a gift.
No!
He's just trying
to be polite.
No!
Perimeter
is on lockdown.
Clear!
Bravo Team!
Secure Lord Hater!
Whoa!
That was the coolest!
You stopped Wander
from infecting me
with the happies...
and this cocoa
is really tasty.
( slurping )
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but you did something
right for once!
Good work, Watchdogs.
Man, who knew those pathetic
Watchdogs could be so awesome?
Maybe all they needed
was a little niceness.
Maybe if someone wrote
"From Lord Hater"
on all those
gift tags...
You mean?
WANDER: "A little nice makes
naughty think twice."
So they paid it forward and
did something right for once,
just like Hater wanted!
Which he should be
realizing right about...
HATER: No!
SYLVIA: Hold on.
Wander, do you know
what this means?
HATER: Wait. Yes!
All right, my now awesome
Watchdogs, you know what to do.
Thank you so much
for your thoughtful gift,
which I am totally going to use
to conquer the universe!
Starting with
this pathetic place.
Go, my Watchdogs.
Go be awesome!
( evil laughter )
( gasps )
Hey, Wander.
I've got the perfect
gift for you.
( gasps )
What?
What's happening?
CHILDREN: Yay!
Here you go.
Friendly gifts,
courtesy of Lord Hater.
Gaah!
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
I knew it!
Being kind to others
makes them kind back!
( guttural noises )
Buddy.
Sylvia.
HATER: Okay, guys,
that's enough hugging.
Starting to get
a little claustrophobic.
Aah!
Peepers!
A little help.
Watchdogs?
Wander?
Okay, whose hand keeps
touching my butt?