♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over ♪
♪ Yonder! Wander!
Yonder! Wander ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
Why?
Is it because
I'm not ruthless enough?
I'm ruthless.
Or evil?
Is that it?
You don't think I'm evil?
What do you call this?
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Commander Peepers.
Am I not strong
enough for you?
I can be strong!
You!
Yes, sir?
Pick this thing up
and throw it at yourself.
But sir, my back--
Do it!
See?
I can be all these things.
So why, why, why...why?!
Sir.
Because you can't seem
to do the one thing
I continually ask of you...
capture Wander & Sylvia.
So I hired the three best
bounty hunters in the galaxy.
Brawngraffle the Huntress!
And KLBOT-86.
Wait.
I thought you said 'three'?
Oh, yeah.
The potted plant!!!
Seriously?
You hired a plant
to do my job?
Well, he can't possibly be
worse at it than you, can he?
(Mocking Laughter)
All right,
bounty hunters.
Wander and Sylvia were
last seen on the vacation
planet Phunulon.
One kajillion hate-a-zoids to
whoever brings them to me...
alive.
Only I get to hear
their screams of agony.
I need them
for my torture megamix.
MAN: Ah! No!
Stop. Stop. Please!
I mean this track
is good and all
but I think with Wander
and Sylvia in the mix
it'll really be bangin'.
Now go, go, go!
Oh, I can't believe this.
Those bounty hunters are gonna
capture Wander and Sylvia.
And then Lord Hater's rule
will spread across the galaxy
and evil will conquer
the universe.
But sir, isn't that
what we want to happen?
No!
I'm supposed
to capture Wander and Sylvia.
And then Lord Hater's rule
will spread across the galaxy
and then evil
will conquer the universe.
All because of me!
Uh, where are
you going, sir?
To do my job.
♪ Commander Peepers
Little help?
MAN: Please keep
your hands and arms
inside the ride at all times.
Remain seated, please.
( announcement
repeated in Spanish )
PEEPERS: Well, well, well,
if it isn't Wander and Sylvia.
Looks like I got the jump on
those pathetic bounty hun--
(gasps)
Ow!
Oh, no, you don't.
(gasps)
A winner!
( snoring )
PEEPERS: Sorry, piggie.
(Peepers laughing)
Think you can
mess up my hunt
and save all the glory
for yourself, huh?
Well, I got news
for you, Squinty.
I'm gonna bag those two,
claim the reward,
and you'll be lucky
if Lord Hater keeps you around
to clean
the zero gravity toilets.
Ha!
Grrr...
Zbornak tracks.
The hunt is on.
Huh?
Sorry, Brawny.
It's feedin' time.
♪ Commander Peepers
(Brawngraffle screams)
Looks like the huntress
has become the huntred!
Er... ted.
Hun-ted.
Attention, Lord Hater. Prepare
to receive transmission.
Claws off, toaster face!
They're mine!
Wooo!
Wow!
It's a stunt
spectacular!
Not on my watch,
you bucket of bolts!
I feel like I'm on
a real, live spaceship!
This is
the best ride ever!
You guys really pulled out
all the stops.
Unbelievable!
You're fired.
Who wants to be a part
of my torture megamix?
ALL: Mega-mix!
Mega-mix!
Take them
to my Torture Room.
ALL: Tor-ture Room.
Tor-ture Room.
(cheers and applause)
Yes!
In your face, Lord Hater!
That's what happens
when you send
a pig and a machine
to do an eyeball's job.
And now you two are mine
for the excessively
forceful taking.
Evil will conquer the galaxy.
All because of me!
Oh, zrebdank.
No!
I was so close!
Wow!
This is
the grossest ride ever.
Aw, man.
Blecchh!
Why hello,
Commander Peepers.
I didn't know you worked
on Planet Phunulon.
See? I knew your weren't
such a bad guy after all.
Wander,
it's a trap.
We're going to be
turned over to Lord Hater.
Really?
Wow.
Well then I must say
congratulations,
you finally caught us,
Commander Peepers.
Most of your attempts
to try and catch us are,
please excuse my language,
kinda stinky,
but this plant thing
is just amazing.
It totally took us
by surprise,
we had no idea
you were after us.
And even though
we're sad to be caught
I am just so happy
thinking about how proud
Lord Hater will be of you.
(crowd cheers)
Well, even though
I am a miserable failure
and that bounty hunter
got all the glory,
Lord Hater finally conquered
the entire universe,
and that...
(sniff)
that's good enough for me.
♪ Commander Peepers
Forget that!
Ah!
They're mine!
Mine!
All Mine!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I win! I win!
And the bounty hunters lose!
Thanks for saving us
from the bounty hunter,
Commander Peepers.
Bye-dee-bye!
Watch closely now.
See what
happens here.
This is them,
escaping...
and this is you,
letting them escape.
I know, sir, but--
Ah-ah!
Pay attention.
This is them.
And this is you.
Them.
You.
Getting away.
Letting them
get away.
You see
where I'm going with this?
I get it, sir.
(sigh)
Even so, I guess
you learned your lesson
about using
bounty hunters, right?
That I did, Peepers,
that I did.
I didn't hire
enough of them!
Agh! No! Please, sir.
No. No. No!
Ooh that's good,
that's the perfect high end
my torture mix
was missing.
Agh, no!
Aw, yeah.
MAN: Stop. Stop. Please.
PEEPERS: Agh, no!
MAN: Ouch. Ouch.
BEEZA: I hope everything
at our Relaxatorium
is to your liking?
I'm so pleased you've enjoyed
your stay on Balzaria 9.
We're quite fond of
our peaceful home.
(bell rings)
Well, time to flee
and abandon it forever.
Huh?
Beeza, what the heck
is going on?
Oh,
a thousand pardons,
it's just that
our entire planet
is about to be destroyed.
ALL: Again.
What?!
On eight different planets,
we've built
our perfect civilization.
And eight different times,
we've heard
the Armageddon Chimes,
letting us know
that he's come to destroy
all we've worked
so hard to build.
It's pretty routine
by this point.
Wait, what?
Who's he?
We use to call him
The Worldbuster,
but now most of us
just call him...
Buster.
Ah!
The winds already?
This doomsday is moving
along quite briskly.
BOTH: Huh?
You folks are abandoning your
beautiful home for a new one?
Just like that?
What?
Of course not.
There aren't any planets
left in our system.
We have absolutely no idea
where we're going.
We'll just fly through space
until we run out of fuel.
Or food,
whichever comes first.
How does
one fight off cannibals?
Some kind of pointy stick,
I assume.
Everyone just hold up!
Y'all have put so much work
into this pretty little planet.
Don't you want
to try and save it?
I know
you're scared of Buster.
But if you keep running,
that's all you're
ever gonna be doing.
You have a chance
to change that.
You just have to turn
and face your problems head on.
What do you say?
Eh, sure. Whatever.
That's good enough for me.
Now gather round.
I have a plan.
We got his attention.
Time for phase two.
We did it!
Here's to facing
your problems head on.
Huh. Hey, not bad.
What do you know?
I did not think
I was gonna win.
Uh... folks...
(gasps)
What happened?!
I thought it worked!
Flarf nabbit,
it     diwork.
We threw a dog a bone
and he fetched it.
Oh, darn.
The Sticky Rains
of Terror?
We've lingered
far too long.
Come on.
Time to flee.
Wander, buddy,
we tried,
but these folks seem okay
with just getting out of here.
Maybe we should be too?
Naw-uh.
No way.
I have one more plan.
Everybody!
One more plan!
All right, soldiers.
On my mark... present...
weapons!
Wet...
whistle.
Deep breaths.
And blow!!!
( silence )
It's working!
Don't stop now!
(Buster barking)
ALL: Ah!
Hey, bad dog! Ah-ah-ah!
Wait. New plan.
Everybody!
New plan.
New much better plan.
Everyone.
All new and improved plan.
Trash.
Everybody.
Hit that tongue
with the grossest,
nastiest, worst-tasting
garbage you can find.
Wha--
Why didn't it work?
Wander,
don't you get it?
Dogs love trash.
But, but--
Sorry buddy,
it's time to go.
But, but--
Hey, you guys made it.
That's great.
Go, go, go, go, go!
So we didn't
get a win this time.
But Wander,
sometimes a problem is so big,
you just have to flee.
No!
There's only one way
to stop this once and for all!
Ah!
Come on,
what are you-
What's going on?
Where's Wander?
That little kamikaze's heading
straight for that monster!
Wander.
I know you're upset
that Buster ate the planet.
Heck, so are
the rest of these folks.
Eh, we'll get over it.
But destroying him and us
is not the answer.
We have to flee!
That's what I'm doing!
I'm facing this problem...
head on!!!
Head on.
Yeah.
Have you lost your nut?
Do you realize
what you just did?
Without that ship, these folks
have nowhere to live.
They needed
some place safe from Buster
with trees
and fresh air
and places
for really great spas.
And...
Huh.
Oh, Wander.
Thanks to you, we finally
have a permanent home.
Yeah. See, y'all
always wanted to flee.
But it turns out,
all you really needed to do...
was  flea.
F-L-E-A.
Flea.
You know, bzzt--
like the bug?
'Cause they're
living on the dog.
Look, if you have
to explain the joke--
(cat yeowling)
♪ Mew-mew-mew-mew,
mew-mew-meow ♪
( crash, people screaming )