♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander
Over Yonder! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Wander!
Yonder! Wander! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
( evil laugh )
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
♪ Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪ Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Wander! ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander Over Yonder!
Guhh.
There's got to be something
nice to say about this cold,
drab, dreary,
and empty place.
Hmm. "Though plain and simple,
this cute little planet
has tons of potential
with room to grow!"
( gasps )
You  really  think so?
( giggles )
You really think I'm cute?
Also, it talks.
Hello, planet, I'm Wander.
What's your name?
Oh, um, I'm afraid
I don't know.
I've never needed
a name before.
I do believe I've always
liked the name Janet.
Nice to meet you,
Planet Janet.
Oh, and I'm ever so delighted
to meet you, Wander.
Please forgive
my ghastly appearance.
If I knew someone was coming,
I would have gussied up a bit.
Though why would
I even bother,
it's not like I've had
any visitors-- ever.
Well, that is some
sort of shame.
Those folks don't know
what they're missing!
Oh, Wander.
( giggles )
I tell you
in all our travels,
we've never once come
across a talking planet.
We?
Well, buddy, I have been
all over this cold, drab,
dreary, and empty place
and all I can say is, bor-ing!
Come on,
let's get out of here.
Sylvia! Meet Janet.
Janet, this is Sylvia,
my best pal.
There isn't a mountain too high,
a valley too low,
or a river too wide
to keep apart a pair
of pals like she and I.
JANET: Oh, it's very nice
to meet you, Sylvia.
Talking planet, huh?
Crazy.
Well, nice to meet you,
Janice!
JANET: Wander,
wait, don't go!
( rumbling )
( gasps )
Janet, this is amazing!
Sylvia, come on in!
The water's wet!
JANET: Oh, Wander, I do hope
you enjoyed your swim.
Would you like
to spin dry?
( Janet giggling )
Wander, that tickles!
Come on, Sylvia!
Just roll with it!
( groans )
Ahh. Janet, I don't know how
this day could get any better.
( giggles )
I do.
( rumbling )
( laughing )
Sylvia...
This-- Now--
Look! See!
Uh, hey.
So, Janet,
you think I could get
a boost, or something?
JANET: Oh, uh, sure.
Of course.
( rumbling )
I'm coming, Wander!
Really?
JANET: So, Wander,
what do you think?
Janet, I have seen
a lot of sunsets in my travels.
But yours takes the cake,
the icing
and the cherry on top.
Oh, Wander,
hearing you say
that melts
my already molten core!
Here, have another!
Wow!
And another!
Amazing!
Incredible!
Ooh, Sylvia!
Have you ever seen
anything like it?
No. No, I haven't.
Ooh, Sylvia,
watch out for that bush.
I think it's poison jivey.
Of course it is.
JANET: Oh, Wander,
I can't tell you
how simply
wonderful it's been
to have you here.
You make me feel like
a newly formed celestial body.
Today was like my
Big Bang all over again.
Aw, thanks, Janet.
We had fun today, too.
Right, Sylvia?
Oh, is "fun" the word
we're settling on here?
You know,
the fun doesn't have to end.
You could...stay.
That's a great idea!
We'll stay--
Tonight!
We'll stay tonight.
And then tomorrow,
we really have to go.
Well.
That settles that then.
( coughing )
Thank you for giving me
the greatest day
of my life, Wander.
And don't forget Sylvia.
Oh. I won't.
( rumbling )
Aaah.
Morning, Wander. What do you say
we hit the-- ( gasps )
Morning, Sylvia!
What have you done
with Wander?!
Oh, Wander's fine.
He's right
where you left him--
give or take a mountain.
Listen, you oversized
chunk of carbon.
There isn't a mountain
too high, a valley too low,
or a river too wide
to keep apart a pair of pals
like Wander and I.
What a strangely
specific challenge.
( rumbling )
I accept!
Oh, let's see.
Mountain high.
( Sylvia screaming )
Valley low.
( screaming )
What's next?
Oh, yes!
Goodbye, Sylvia!
( screaming )
Good morning,
my wonderful Wander.
Ahh. Morning, Janet.
Where's Sylvia?
Oh, she went for a climb.
And then a hike.
And then a swim.
Who wants brekkies?
Mmmmm!
Pancakes!
Well, aren't you the hostess
with the mostest.
All for my guest
whom I love the best!
I can't wait
for Sylvia to get back!
If there's one thing
I know about Sylvia,
it's that exercise
makes her hungry.
If there are two things
I know about Sylvia,
it's that she loves
having her snout scratched.
If there's three things
I know about Sylvia--
That's enough!
There will be enough for Sylvia
when she gets back.
Now, how about dessert?
Y'all have pie
after breakfast?
Wander, my darling,
as long as you stay here
you can have
whatever you want.
( laughing )
( panting, coughing )
Okay, that was--
that was almost too wide.
Almost.
That was delec-ticious.
A combination of
delectable and delicious?
Oh-ho-ho! I knew it!
We know each other so well!
I haven't had a meal
that good since we camped out
on Binglebop and Sylvia
made waffles.
Speaking of Sylvia,
I need to walk off
this breakfast belly.
Maybe I'll go take a hike,
see if I can't find her.
Go?
Why would you need
to go anywhere?
D-Do you like it?
You like it, don't you?
Tell me you like it! Please!
SYLVIA: Wander!
Sylvia?
Ohh!
JANET:
Just one second, Wubsy,
I'll be right with you.
Aaah!
I gave you the chance
to leave in one piece!
But you just wuv your
widdle Wander, huh?
Well, now
this...is...happening!
( screaming )
So long, Sylvia.
It was so nice to eat you!
( belching )
Whoop! 'Scuse me!
Uh, Janet, you are a lovely
planet, you really are,
but Sylvia and I should
probably be on our way.
Sylvia, Sylvia, Sylvia!
You know what Sylvia did?
She left!
She would never!
Yes! She left you here!
And now it's just
you and me, Wander!
Until the end...of...time!
( rumbling )
Sylvia!
There isn't
a chasm deep enough.
Come on, Wander,
let's orb!
You are not
going anywhere
with my
Wandy-Wubzy-Woo-Wooo!
She's trapping us
in her orbit!
If getting lava-balled
by a jealous planet is
how we go out, buddy,
well, I'm just glad
we're doing it together.
I couldn't agree more.
I love you, Sylvia.
You too, Wander. You too!
( Janet sobbing )
What happened?
Who the grop cares!
Let's get out of here!
( Janet crying )
We gotta go back.
What?!
Are you crazy too?
Hey, Janet.
Hey.
Sorry I got
a little weird.
What? No!
I was wrong to try
and force you to love me.
All I ever wanted
was a friendship
like you and Sylvia have.
But I guess that's not
in the stars for me.
Hello! I am Maurice,
your moon.
Charmed.
I don't mean
to be forward,
but I find myself
very attracted to you--
JANET: Oh, you!
( giggling )
You, Janet, are my world.
Should we say good-bye?
No, let's let 'em
have their space.
Oh Janet,
your southern hemisphere
is so curvilinear!
JANET: You keep talking like
that you're gonna melt
my polar ice caps!
PEEPERS: Ah, Flendar.
Their fortress city
protects them
from any invasion.
Not!
Lord Hater has attacked
our south gate
when we least expected it!
What a brilliant
and well coordinated invasion!
( screaming )
In my heart, I always knew
our planet would fall
to the military genius
of the almighty Lord Hater.
(soldiers chant)
Hate's great, best villain!
Your plan worked perfectly,
Commander Peepers!
You are a capable
and worthy advisor.
So that's just my little
pitch for the invasion today.
Thoughts, sir?
Sir?
Peepers,
truly your incompetence
knows no bounds.
Did you really think
I would approve of a plan
with such a glaring
and fundamental flaw?
Sir, I don't--
I was very--
Wander!
What are we going
to do about Wander?
'Cause the moment
we try to invade,
that furry freak will
show up and play a song,
or have a picnic,
or challenge me to a contest,
and just ruin everything!
Sir, I know Wander
has caused us issues.
But the chances
of him showing up
every single place we go--
Your plan is bad!
Deal with it!
We need
a completely new idea.
Yeah. Something
fresh and edgy.
Something that really pops.
Something totally
Wander-proof.
Peepers!
Reserve a conference room!
It's time for...
All right, Peepers.
Wow me.
Okay, sir,
how about this?
We don't use the army.
We use...
Doom Dragons.
Air superiority!
Massive firepower!
They won't stand a chance!
LORD HATER: No!
If we attack
with Doom Dragons,
Wander's just gonna
show up and tame 'em
with the power of wuv
or something gross like that.
And now Wander has
an army of Doom Dragons.
Great work, Peepers.
Okay. That's fine.
We don't even go down
to the fortress.
We'll just destroy them
with an electric laser!
Wham, bam, perfect plan!
LORD HATER: Till
Wander takes its batteries.
PEEPERS: We'll bring
back-up batteries.
LORD HATER:
He'll take those too!
PEEPERS: We'll bring lots
of back-up batteries!
LORD HATER: Peepers,
will you just think
for one second
before you talk, okay?
How could he even--
You're being such a--
Okay,
forget the direct approach.
We'll steal their princess,
force her to marry you.
( Wedding March plays )
Then the entire planet
will rightfully be yours--
LORD HATER: Unless
that was simply Wander
disguised as the princess.
And now
I'm married to Wander.
Is that want you
want, Peepers?
For me to marry the person
I hate the most
in the entire universe?
PEEPERS: Fine!
We'll steal the king!
Without strong leadership,
Flendar will descend
into chaos!
( evil laugh )
LORD HATER:
Until Wander shows up
and teaches them
to be self-reliant
and live in perfect
equality and harmony.
And he'll also rescue
the king somehow.
I didn't want to
bring this up.
It's still very experimental.
The Planetary
Mind Combobulator!
Powered by
your own evil energies
it will let you
control the entire planet
with a single thought!
Huh?
Hmm.
No. Banjo.
Banjo?
Banjo.
Now, sir,
I've understood
some of yours
objections, but banjo?
How could a banjo possibly--
The vibrational frequency
of Wander's banjo
will just happen to match
the frequency of the Mind
Comma-lom-bom-bulator--
PEEPERS: It's combobulator.
LORD HATER: Whatever.
Causing it to explode.
The Bob-call-you-later
will zap us,
and we'll wake up
in a fishing village,
no idea who we are
or how we got there.
We'll start over
as simple fishermen and...
life will be good.
That is,
until Rosa shows up.
Our competition
for Rosa's affection
will destroy our partnership.
And she'll end up
with Ron the baker!
We'll both end up
sad old men,
wondering what might
have been.
Why couldn't you just
let me have her, Peepers?
Rosa and I would have been
so happy together!
( weeping )
Anyway, that's why your dumb
Comb-over-embulator won't work.
Can we please just--
What if we block out their sun?
Warmth-generating group hug!
Melt their ice caps?
Pool party planet!
Destroy all their crops and
starve them into submission?
( zapping )
LORD HATER: Wander'll just
come along and hand out,
you know, uh...
BOB: Sandwiches?
ALL: Yay!
Yeah! What Bob said.
Sandwiches!
I, uh, actually
just wanted lunch.
Ooh! Good idea!
Who's got menus?
Sir, we don't have time!
( casual chatter )
Sorry, guess
they forgot yours.
HATER:
It's possible I was being
too negative before.
I need to be more
receptive to the ideas
of my subordinates.
So, tell me,
what do  you  ...guys think?
Sharks but less dangerous.
Interesting.
Keep 'em coming, guys.
We take a cooking
class with them?
No bad ideas.
A really big
laser on the moon!
Hmm, sounds familiar.
Socks but for hands!
Gloves?
You mean gloves.
I'm putting down gloves.
I need to go
to the bathroom.
Not a pitch,
still writing it down.
( all shouting
ideas at once )
Sir!
This is getting us nowhere!
I had a plan
for you this morning.
A good plan.
A solid plan.
A brilliant, fool-proof plan!
Can I pitch you
that plan one more time?
Okay, we'll approach
the fortress from the south
with four platoons.
LORD HATER:
But what if Wander
distracts them
with a silly dance?
And then Sylvia pulls
their pants down?
PEEPERS: We'll just
give them tighter belts!
LORD HATER: What if she ties
their shoelaces together?
PEEPERS:
We don't have shoelaces.
LORD HATER: But what if Wander
disguises himself as me
and orders the Watchdogs
to stop the attack?
PEEPERS: We'll give them
an X-ray scanner.
LORD HATER: What if
Wander throws a picnic
and invites the Watchdogs
and because his pie
is so good they all go?
PEEPERS:
We'll bring giant ants.
LORD HATER: What if he knows
a giant anteater?
PEEPERS: We'll bring
a giant anteater-eater!
LORD HATER:
What if he brings a--
PEEPERS: And so on!
LORD HATER: What if
Wander challenges me
to some carnival games?
Then you don't
play the games.
LORD HATER: What if Wander
flies in at the last moment
and shoots a shrink ray
from his eyes
that makes us all teeny tiny?
He can't do that!
Are you sure?
We'll bring a radioactive
power-absorbing crystal!
Just in case!
Hate's great, best villain!
You know,
this just might work.
Really?
Yes.
Yes. Yes!
With this plan,
Flendar's defenses
will crumble before us!
Their puny pathetic planet
will soon belong to Lord...
Lord...
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh?
Banjo.
Banjo?
♪ Banjo, Banjo
Banjo.
How did that happen?!
It doesn't matter.
What's the point?
Whatever I do,
Wander's gonna find
a way to stop me.
Invasion off.
Everybody out.
Sir, you're forgetting
one thing.
Yeah? what's that?
You're Lord Hater!
The most powerful,
most evil villain
in the entire universe!
And while Wander may have
beaten you a few times
the Lord Hater
I know would never
let some little furry weirdo
get in his head.
He'd just keep conquering
planets and doing evil!
And if Wander did show up...
the Lord Hater I know
would just use his powers
to blast him
into the next dimension!
( evil laugh )
Yes!
Peepers, you're right!
I am awesome!
I can't let some do-gooder
in a dumb hat psych me out!
Oh, that's great, sir!
So, which plan
do you want to use?
What?
Oh, that one you had
in the beginning was fine
or whatever.
Let's do this!
(chanting)
Hate's great, best villain!
TOGETHER: Banjo.
♪ Who is the universe's
♪ Loneliest evil-doer
♪ Oh, oh
♪ Lord Hater, Lord Hater
♪ Whoa-ho-ho-ho,
ho-ho-ho-ho-ho ♪
LORD HATER: Rosa!