♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER WANDER OVER OVER
YONDER YONDER WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT!
♪ READY!
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER WANDER OVER OVER
YONDER YONDER WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT,
WANDER OVER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
( screaming )
( grunting )
( sighs )
SO, UH, HEY...
I COULDN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE,
BUT YOU LEFT ME
ALONE TO DEAL
WITH ALL THOSE
WATCHDOGS.
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
STILL WAITING
ON AN ANSWER.
SILVIA...
THIS IS SOMEBODY'S SOCK.
THAT MEANS THAT THERE'S
A SAD, SOCK-LESS SOUL
OUT THERE
WITH A VERY COLD,
NAKED FOOT
PINING AWAY FOR THEIR
ONE LONELY SOCK'S TWIN!
WE CAN'T JUST TURN
OUR BACKS
ON WHAT COULD BE
SOMEONE'S GREATEST
HOUR OF NEED.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER
LOST SOMETHING
YOU WISHED YOU COULD
GET BACK?
BESIDES THE LAST
TEN SECONDS OF
THIS CONVERSATION?
HA HA! COME ON,
IT'LL BE FUN!
BESIDES, HOW HARD CAN IT BE
TO RETURN A SOCK?
FINE.
PARDON ME, MISS,
BUT IS THIS YOUR SOCK?
YOU GOT FEET? I GOT A SOCK!
WHAT A COINCIDENCE!
( rattling )
ATTENTION, SHOPPERS!
IS ANYBODY MISSING
A SOCK?
IT'S WHITE...
WITH TWO STRIPES.
IT'S A SOCK.
ANYBODY?!
OH, THIS IS GONNA
TAKE FOREVER.
IF WE'RE GONNA DO
A STUPID THING,
LET'S AT LEAST
BE SMART ABOUT IT.
WE'LL LEAVE
THE SOCK HERE.
WHOEVER LOST IT
WILL COME FIND IT.
IT'S RIGHT THERE
IN THE TITLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT KIND OF BACKGROUND
CHECKS DO THEY RUN
ON PEOPLE CLAIMING
LOST ITEMS?
WANDER, THIS MAN
IS A PROFESSIONAL.
HE WILL MAKE SURE
THIS PRECIOUS CARGO
FINDS ITS WAY HOME.
RIGHT?
IT'LL DEFINITELY
END UP SOMEWHERE.
SEE? "SOMEWHERE"!
HAND OVER THE SOCK.
GODSPEED,
LITTLE FRIEND!
ALTHOUGH, IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO FIND THE OWNER...
WE DO! WE REALLY DO!
LEGEND TELLS OF
THE INTERGALACTIC GURU,
A BEING OF
INFINITE WISDOM
WHO HAS ANSWERS
TO EVERY QUESTION
IN THE UNIVERSE.
OOH!
BUT BE WARNED!
THE JOURNEY TO THE GURU
IS FRAUGHT WITH PERIL!
FEW HAVE SURVIVED.
THOSE WHO HAVE
WERE DRIVEN TO THE DEPTHS
OF MADNESS.
THAT...SOUNDS...
AWESOME!
GIVE ME A PEN! I GOTTA
WRITE ALL THIS DOWN!
COULDN'T JUST
TAKE THE SOCK,
COULD YOU?
FIRST, YOU MUST BRAVE
THE GRIZZLY FOREST,
SO NAMED FOR ITS FIERCE
GRIZZLY POPULATION.
( snarling )
BUT BEWARE THE LESS FAMOUS
BUT EQUALLY DEADLY
GIANT HOARDER SCORPION!
THERE YOU WILL FIND THE KEY
TO THE TOMB
OF THE UNKNOWN EMPEROR,
WHERE YOU WILL HAVE TO TAME
THE FIERCE TIGREX OF NIL!
( roars )
( purring )
THERE YOU SHALL FIND A MAP
LEADING TO
THE FARBRIX LAVADROME.
RESCUE THE FAIR PRINCESS
GALACTIA.
( screams )
OH! MY HEROES!
AAH!
SHE WILL LEAD YOU
TO THE INFINITY CRYSTALS,
WHICH YOU MUST PRY
FROM THE THRONE
OF THE EASILY AMUSED
DRAGOR THE DESTRUCTIBLE.
RASSAFRASSIN' CRYSTAL!
AFTER THAT,
HEAD TO THE ICE-ATORIUM
TO RESCUE THE UNFAIR PRINCESS
VERONICRON.
UGH. YOU CALL THIS
A RESCUE?
RESIST THE SOLAR SIREN'S
SWEET SONG.
( wailing )
YEAH, NOT THAT
HARD TO RESIST.
SURVIVE THE QUICKSAND
OF FORGETFULNESS.
WAIT, WHAT WERE
WE DOING?
OH, YEAH. AAAH!
AAAH!
HUMBLE YOURSELVES BEFORE
THE LEGENDARY NEON KNIGHT
OF NALPRAXIS.
CALL ME JIM.
THE NEON KNIGHT
SHALL JOIN YOUR PARTY
BUT BORE YOU
WITH ENDLESS STORIES
ABOUT OLD FISHING TRIPS.
WE NEVER THOUGHT
WE'D CATCH A SNOOK
WITH   THAT   LURE.
NOW, THE THING YOU GOTTA
KNOW ABOUT YOUR SNOOK--
NOT THE TIME, JIM!
DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL FIND TRUE LOVE,
AND YOU'LL
REMEMBER HIM FONDLY.
I'LL MISS HIM
SO MUCH.
HOW WILL WE
EVER GO ON?
WE MUST!
FOR THE SOCK.
JIM WOULD WANT IT
THAT WAY.
ANSWER THE RIDDLES THREE
OF THE BLARNIAN BRIDGE TROLL.
A TRIANGLE,
A CHILD'S LAUGHTER,
AND TO SEE TIME FLY.
CROSS THE MOUNTAIN PASS
WITHOUT LOOKING
AT THE HIPPOGRIFF.
STOP AT BLOYD'S DINER.
( chomping )
AHH. BEST BLEGG-SALAD SANDWICH
YOU'LL EVER EAT.
( burps )
DISCOVER THE TRUE SECRET
WAS INSIDE YOU ALL ALONG.
AND BOOM! YOU'RE AT THE
INTERGALACTIC GURU'S TEMPLE...
AFTER YOU CLIMB
THE MILLION...
QUINQUOG-INTER-QUADRA-
TENTILLION STEPS!
( sobbing )
BUT REMEMBER, YOU MAY ASK
THE GURU ONLY ONE QUESTION,
SO CHOOSE WISELY.
O GREAT AND MIGHTY
INTERGALACTIC GURU,
KEEPER OF THE WISDOM
OF THE COSMOS,
GRAND OBSERVER OF ALL
THAT IS AND WILL BE...
IS THIS YOUR SOCK?
NOPE.
OKAY, THANKS.
"WHOSE   SOCK IS THIS?"
NOT "IS THIS YOURS?"
"WHOSE"!
I'LL ADMIT
THAT LAST PLAN
WAS A LITTLE...TRICKY.
BUT THIS SOCK IS
IMPORTANT TO SOMEBODY.
WE'VE JUST GOT
TO RETURN IT, SYLVIA,
NO MATTER
HOW LONG IT TAKES,
HOW GRUELING THE JOURNEY,
HOW DANGEROUS THE--
OH! SILLY ME!
THIS IS   MY   SOCK.
IT IS?
UH-HUH.
HA HA! WHERE HAS
MY HEAD BEEN?
THANKS FOR
RETURNING IT.
HMM. I DON'T RECALL YOU
EVER WEARING SHOES,
LET ALONE SOCKS.
UHH! GET IN THERE!
STOP, YOU'RE
STRETCHING IT!
( grunting )
( ding )
OH, YOU'VE GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
( gasps )
LOOK AT THAT!
THE RETURN ADDRESS
WAS INSIDE THE SOCK
ALL ALONG!
HA HA HA!
ISN'T THAT HI-LARIOUS?
( groans )
HELLO?
OLLY OLLY OXEN FREE!
( brakes screech )
THIS PLACE GIVES ME
THE HEEBIES
WITH A SIDE ORDER
OF JEEBIES.
CAN ANYONE TELL US
HOW TO GET TO
1313 LOOMING TERROR DRIVE?
( ominous music playing )
I BET THEY HAVE
A BEAUTIFUL VIEW!
NO. UH-UH.
WANDER...
WE'VE DONE A LOT
OF STUPID THINGS
TO RETURN THIS SOCK,
BUT IF WE
GO UP THERE,
WE'RE GONNA DIE.
I CAN LIVE WITH
STUPID, BUT I CAN'T
LIVE WITH DEATH.
BUT WE'RE SO CLOSE.
I DON'T CARE.
WE'RE DONE.
WE STILL HAVE
A CHANCE TO MAKE IT
OUT ALIVE, AND--
YOU'RE ALREADY
UP THERE, AREN'T YOU?
( snarls )
UM...IS THIS--
SEIZE THEM!
( sobbing )
THERE WAS SO MUCH
I DIDN'T GET TO DO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS THE END!
AND ALL OVER A SOCK!
EXCUSE ME,
MR. EXECUTIONER, SIR.
DOES DESTRUCTOR
HAVE TOO FEW SOCKS?
NO.
( groans )
TOO MANY LIKE--
NO.
HAS HE EVER,
EVER LOST A SOCK?
NO. OH, WAIT.
ACTUALLY,
HIS HORRIBLENESS
DID LOSE ONE SOCK.
SO HE BOUGHT A NEW PAIR.
I MEAN, THEY'RE JUST SOCKS.
WELL, TIME TO MEET
YOUR DOOM. SEE YA.
SYLVIA, I AM SORRY.
I THOUGHT THAT GOING
OUT OF YOUR WAY TO BE
KIND TO SOMEONE
WOULD ALWAYS BE WORTH
THE TROUBLE.
BUT I WAS WRONG.
AND YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS   IS   JUST
A DUMB SOCK,
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER
A LICK TO ANYONE.
NO, WANDER. THIS SOCK
DOES   MATTER TO
SOMEONE--TO YOU.
AND I WILL NOT LET
THIS ENTIRE STUPID
QUEST BE IN VAIN.
YO! HEAD-CASE!
( slowed-down )
IS...THIS...
YOUR...SOCK?!
( roars )
( high-pitched )
STOP!
WHO DARES?!
I DARE!
WHO?
SURELY YOU REMEMBER!
LA-LA-LA-LA-LA!
HA HA HA!
IF YOU'RE TO RULE
THIS KINGDOM,
YOU MUST PUT AWAY
CHILDISH THINGS.
( screaming )
MY FRIEND!
I'VE MISSED YOU
SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR RETURNING
LITERALLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE.
RELEASE THEM!
IN FACT, RELEASE
ALL THE PRISONERS!
AND MAKE THEM JUICE!
( all cheering )
EXCEPT THAT GUY!
AWW.
DESTRUCTOR!
MAKE HIM AN ARCHDUKE!
FATHER, ALL IS FORGIVEN.
( cheering )
FARE THEE WELL,
BRAVE HEROES.
I JUST THOUGHT
SOMEONE'S FOOT
MIGHT GET COLD.
WE'RE DEFINITELY
OPENING THIS WEIRD
SPACE DOOR, AREN'T WE?
NO CHANCE OF US
JUST MOVING ON,
HAVING A NORMAL,
RELAXING,
NON-CRAZY DAY?
DIDN'T THINK SO.
AFTER YOU, PAL.
Both: WHOA.
WHERE ARE WE?
SYLVIA, THIS PLACE
IS AMAZING!
A LITTLE EMPTY,
IF YOU ASK ME.
WANDER?
OVER HERE!
AAH!
THAT'S CRAZY.
HOW DID YOU...
DO THAT?
HUH. SO THAT'S WHAT
THE OLD CABOOSE
LOOKS LIKE.
HMM, NOT BAD.
♪ DA-DA
DA-DA-DA-HEY! ♪
DA-DA-DA-- ♪
OOF!
HA HA HA HA!
DO IT AGAIN!
( horn honks,
cow moos )
HA!
WHOA!
( both sigh )
( laughing )
MAN, OH, MAN,
IS THIS PLACE GREAT!
WHOA!
( mumbling )
SYLVIA, YOU GOTTA TRY THIS!
( grunting )
WHOA, I GOTTA
TRY   THAT!
RED! GREEN!
YELLOW! BLUE!
I BET I CAN BE
TARTAN, TOO!
FORM A RED RECTANGLE!
TEAL TETRAHEDRON.
PAISLEY PARALLELOGRAM.
AN ORANGE SPOON!
OH! WHOO!
ALL RIGHT! BRAVA!
UH, WHAT THE--
THIS PLACE IS BANANAS!
TOTALLY NUTS.
IT'S CRACKERS.
COMPLETELY BATTY.
( squeaks )
ABSOLUTELY LOONY!
( squawks )
HA! UTTERLY
JELLYFISH PIE!
HUH?
( laughing )
OH! OW, OW!
OH, YEAH? WELL,
BYE-BYE, JELLYFISH PIE.
TIME FOR WATER BALLOONS!
AWW, COME ON, NOW.
HA HA!
( screaming )
( both laughing )
( laughter echoing )
HEY, YOU SEE THAT DOOR
WE CAME THROUGH ANYWHERE?
NUH-UH.
WE SHOULD
PROBABLY LOOK
FOR A WAY OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
OH, DO WE HAVE TO?
SURE WOULD BE NICE
TO KNOW
WE'RE STUCK IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOTHIN'.
YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
( balloons deflate )
SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
UH, YOU GO THAT WAY.
I'LL GO THIS WAY.
NOTHING OVER HERE.
WHOA! HA HA!
YOU'RE TINY!
AWW! YOU'RE SO ADORABLE,
I COULD EAT YOU RIGHT UP...
LITERALLY!
( chomping )
WANDER! STOP!
PUT ME DOWN!
OR NO--WAIT, WAIT.
LIFT ME UP.
MAYBE THIS PLACE
HAS A CEILING.
SLOWLY-Y-Y-Y!
( echoing )
WHOOPS! SORRY!
QUIETLY!
( softly )
WHOOPS. SORRY.
NOPE, NOTHING
UP HERE!
( struggling )
WHOA! WHOA!
HOLD ON THERE!
STEADY! STEADY!
WHOA-OH-OH-OH!
( sighs )
HUH. HA HA HA HA!
SORRY. IT GOT
REAL LONG.
STILL COMING.
ANYTIME NOW, ANYTIME.
HELLO.
OKAY. NO NEED TO PANIC.
NO NEED TO PANIC.
I'M NOT.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE WE'RE
STUCK IN AN ENDLESS VOID
WITHOUT ANY CEILINGS
OR WALLS.
UHH! OKAY.
SOME   WALLS.
UHH! GRRR!
HEY!
HELP, WANDER!
I'M TRAPPED!
HEY, THAT'S
PRETTY GOOD.
LOOK,
I'M TRAPPED, TOO.
NO! WANDER,
I'M REALLY STUCK.
( accordion playing )
( gasping )
YOU OKAY, BUDDY?
OKAY?! I WAS JUST
ALMOST CRUSHED
INTO A CUBE!
( exhales )
NO EXIT? FINE.
WE'LL JUST BLAST
OUR WAY OUT OF HERE!
OH, LET ME HELP!
( groans )
( chattering )
HOW WAS ANY OF THAT
SUPPOSED TO HELP?
I DON'T KNOW.
SURE WAS FUN,
THOUGH, HUH?
( squawks )
( door slams )
WAIT, WHAT? A DOOR?
OF COURSE. A DOOR!
( groaning )
COME ON, DOOR!
GET US OUT OF HERE!
AWW, SYLVIA, YOU'RE
NOT DOING IT RIGHT.
YOU WANT DOORS?
I'LL GIVE YOU DOORS!
I SAID "DOOR".
"DOOR"!
WHOOPS. HEH HEH!
WELL, GOTTA BE
ONE OF THESE, RIGHT?
( growls )
♪
OHH!
AAH!
OH. OKAY, OKAY.
YOU'RE THE RIGHT DOOR.
RIGHT?
I HAVE A GOOD FEELING
ABOUT THIS ONE.
I DIDN'T TRUST THOSE
OTHER DOORS. PFFT!
OKAY, THINKING
SPACEY THOUGHTS.
AND...
( elephants trumpeting )
♪ ALL RIGHT!
( shrieking )
AAH!
I JUST WANT
TO SELL YOU
SOME INSURANCE!
NO, THANK YOU!
WANDER!
SORRY, BUT COME ON.
GIANT SQUID INSURANCE?
KIND OF FUNNY, RIGHT?
WANDER, THIS PLACE
WILL GIVE US
WHATEVER WE WANT.
I KNOW!
ISN'T IT
AWESO-O-O-OME?!
Y-YEAH, BUT...
I DON'T THINK WE'RE
GONNA GET TO LEAVE
UNTIL WE BOTH
WANT   TO LEAVE.
SO DO YOU THINK--
FOR ME--YOU CAN FOCUS,
SO WE CAN GET BACK
TO   OUR   WORLD?
A-ZOOMA-WIMMY-ZIMMY
ZOOB-ZOOB!
YES!
I KNEW YOU COULD
DO IT, BUDDY.
NO CRAZY FANTASY VOID
IS GONNA KEEP   US
LOCKED UP.
WATCH OUT, UNIVERSE,
'CAUSE WANDER
AND SYLVIA ARE BACK...
IN...ACTION?
HMM, THAT'S WEIRD.
WAND--
SORRY!
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
"...DER!"
BUT COME ON!
WHY WOULD YOU EVER WANT
TO LEAVE THIS PLACE?
IT'S THE BEST!
( muttering )
HERE YOU CAN DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT!
( grunting )
UH...
WAIT.
( boom )
♪
♪ OH, THERE'S A PLACE
YOU CAN DO ♪
♪ DO WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
♪ JUST TAKE A STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
♪ OPEN UP THE DOOR,
WALK ON THROUGH ♪
♪ YOU'LL BE SINGING
WHOOP-DE-DO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU TAKE A STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
♪ OH, MAKE UP STUFF
THAT YOU WANT TO SEE ♪
♪ LIKE A PSYCHEDELIC
BUMBLEBEE ♪
♪ DO SOME THINGS
YOU WANT TO TRY ♪
♪ LIKE FLYING UP
IN THE SKY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU TAKE STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
WANDER! WANDER!
WHICHEVER OF
THESE YOUS IS YOU,
I THINK YOU SHOULD MAYBE
TAKE FIVE, PAL.
AWW,   YOU   SHOULD
JOIN   US.
UH, NO, THANKS.
I'M FINE.
COME ON,
IT'LL BE FUN.
♪
♪ OOH, THERE'S A SPOT
WHERE ALL IS FINE ♪
♪ YOU'LL BE HAPPY
ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ JUST TAKE A STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
♪ DON'T BE SAD,
DON'T BE BLUE ♪
♪ YOU'LL FIND ENDLESS
THINGS TO DO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU TAKE A STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
♪ IT'S A PLACE
FOR YOU TO GROW ♪
♪ BY KNOWING THINGS
YOU'VE NEVER KNOWN ♪
♪ GOT A PROBLEM
YOU NEED SOLVED? ♪
♪ USE YOUR NOODLE AND EVOLVE
TAKE IT, SYL!
NO, THANKS,
I REALLY WANT TO--
♪ JUST TAKE A STEP INSIDE
♪ TAKE A STEP INSIDE YOUR
♪ YEP-A-DEP-A-DEP
BA-BA-DA-BOW ♪
( cheering )
WANDER!
YOU'RE SPENDING
SO MUCH TIME
THINKING ABOUT THE THINGS
THAT   YOU   WANT TO DO
THAT YOU FORGOT
ALL ABOUT ME
AND WHAT I WANT TO--
♪ DO-DO-DOODLY-DO
YEAH.
AND I'M REAL.
( distorted )
♪ TAKE A STEP
INSIDE YOUR MIND ♪
( sighs )
YOU KNOW,
I CAN IMAGINE
A WHOLE BUNCH
OF THINGS.
A NINE-NECKED BANJO,
A PEPPERMINT PUPPY,
A RADICAL RADISH,
A SWEEPING LEMUR,
A SUN THAT COMPLIMENTS YOU
ON YOUR HAT.
NICE HAT!
BUT I CAN'T IMAGINE
A BETTER FRIEND THAN YOU.
COME ON,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
Both: YEE-HAW!
PROUD OF YOU, BUDDY.
( brakes screech )
YES?
NOPE.
♪ ZIP-A-DIB-A-DIB-A-DIB
A-DIB-DIB-DIB ♪
WHOA!