♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander wander
over, over ♪
♪ Yonder yonder
wander wander ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
MAN:
Ancient prophecy foretold
that the beloved
Princess Demura
would be kidnapped
by King Draykor
the evil Dragon King,
who, hungry for power,
stole her away to his
Labyrinth of Delusion!
And now only one hero
can rescue her,
her one true love.
And once he saves her,
they will live
happily ever after
and use their
compatible features
to produce
many attractive offspring,
who will also live
happily ever after!
And I,
Sir Brad Starlight, am...
Now, Draykor plans
to wed Demura at sundown.
I beseech you,
kind travelers,
will you help me save her,
so we may live
happily ever after?
Are you kidding?
Save a princess?
I've always wanted
to save a princess!
Let's go save a princess!
Whoa there,
my furry fellow!
I like your enthusiasm,
but remember...
I'm the hero here.
You're my goofy sidekick,
who trapes, japes, gapes,
and, of course,
sings my theme song.
And my noble steed.
Who trudges,
drudges, begrudges
and generally does
all the heavy lifting.
Whoa!
Nuh-uh.
I don't just let anybody
hop in this saddle.
Grrrr...!
Sylvia, come on!
A princess is in danger.
Uhh! Okay, fine.
But only 'cause
we're helping a sister out.
Hyah!
Onward, noble steed!
Princess rescue!
Wooooo!
♪ I sing the tale
of Brad Starlight ♪
♪ A worthy, brave,
and daring knight ♪
♪ He helped a crone
to cross the street ♪
More dangerous!
♪ Though it was lava
beneath his feet ♪
Put in that I fought a bear
they know how strong I am.
♪ He wrestled a large
and scary bear ♪
And come on,
old crone?
Yuck.
Make it a pretty lady.
♪ All to help a maiden fair
Hey, yes.
She totally wants
to smooch me.
♪ Then his sidekick,
brave and true ♪
Whoa!
Silence, silly sidekick.
We're here.
The Labyrinth of Delusion!
Don't worry, princess,
we'll save you!
Uh,
the prophecy says
that the hero
always leads the way.
Oh, gosh,
I am so sorry. Of course.
After you, Sir Starlight.
Oh, you poor,
silly, stupid sidekick.
That way is clearly a trap.
This is the correct path.
Are you flarping serious?
Easy girl.
I know the danger spooks
dumb beasts like you.
You have no idea
what you're doing, do you?
Ooh, tasty carrot.
Wander, keep an eye
on this fool.
( laughs )
That a girl.
Onward, sidekick!
Oh, and try and throw
in some pratfalls
and silly catchphrases
if you can, okay?
Copy that!
Whoop-a-deedy-doo.
Splat.
Careful, sidekick!
A gauntlet of traps
most fearsome awaits us.
A weakling like you cannot
hope to withstand it.
Truly, it will take one
with big, hero-ey muscles,
such as myself,
to make it through this alive.
We're coming, princess!
Ah, clearly this is just
a warm-up challenge.
Okay.
Here we go.
Excelsior--
( groans )
That's it, Sir Starlight!
You're almost through.
Whoop-a-deedy-doo!
What?
I don't-- How?
Oh, Sylvia?
She took the other path!
Turns out it was
quite pleasant.
There was even
a lemonade stand.
Let's see you get out
of this one, champ.
But don't worry!
It's a pattern,
so all you got to do is--
No! No!
The hero does not need
the sidekick's help!
Now, clearly,
it's some sort of pattern.
( Starlight screaming )
Nice griffin. Ow!
Gah! the griffin
has my cape!
The griffin has my cape!
Get off!
My sword!
Your sidekick tom-foolery
has cost me my sword!
The prophecy specifically
states the hero
has a mighty sword!
Is this mighty enough?
(gasps) The sword of Destiny!
Forged in the fires
of a collapsing star,
the Andromeda Lords
themselves crafted it
so that only the most noble,
the most daring,
the most truly
righteous hero could--
Wha-- But the hero
is supposed to--
Put it back! Put it back!
Put it back!
Oh, sorry. Don't know
my own strength.
Ah, come on,
it's like you haven't
even  read  the prophecy.
Ain't happening,
pretty boy.
Don't!
It's better this way!
Now come on.
Stop dilly-dallying.
We're gonna be late.
Helping a sister out.
( animal howling )
The day's end
may be nigh,
Princess Demura...
but fear not.
No barrier can keep
my love from you.
I shall smash the--
Oh, come on,
are you serious?
It was unlocked.
I don't care!
I need to make
a dramatic entrance.
Close it!
No door is strong enough
to keep me from you, my love.
( all growling )
Ahh!
For the princess!
Wait just a--
Come on, this is my--
I wanted to--
Stop!!!
All I want to do
is save my one true love
and have everyone know
how great a hero I am.
Just like
the prophecy says!
And you're ruining it,
ruining it, ruining it!
Why can't you get it?!
Sidekick!
Steed! Hero!
Prisoner.
So these are the heroes
who've come
to steal my bride.
Well, you're too late
Sir Starlight!
Soon, the sun will set
and Princess Demura will be--
DEMURA: ( gasps )
beloved.
She's beautiful!
And pink. Ugh!
Demura,
it is I, Brad Starlight.
Silence, cur!
( shushing )
It's all right.
There's no need to shout,
beloved, it's fine.
I'm so sorry, honey.
You know I--
I just want this day to be
perfect for you, you know.
Oh, and it will be, Drake,
as long as we're together.
Oh... You're pooky.
Seriously, Bradley?
This again?
I'm sorry, did he
drag you two along
on some crazy
rescue mission?
It's not a crazy mission!
The prophecy foretold!
Prophecy?
You mean your diary from
when we were what, 15?
(sighs)
Look, Brad.
I know this is hard,
but things don't always
work out the way you want.
Life isn't a fairy-tale.
Come on, we can
just be friends, right?
No!
The princess will be mine!
The prophecy
will be fulfilled!
( laughing )
Demura, my love.
We've got to save her.
You!
What should we do?
Yes, you.
Only one brave enough
to conquer the insane labyrinth
we set up to stop Bradley
is heroic enough
to help save
Demura, right?
I've always wanted
to save a princess.
Okay, guys!
New bad guy, new plan.
We're going to need
everybody's
individual talents
to pull this off!
ALL: Yeah!
We're all gonna have to work
together, as a team.
Yeah!
Today,
we're all gonna be heroes!
Yeah!
We're all collectively
coming to save you, princess!
Guys, it's fine.
I handled it myself.
Like I said,
this isn't a fairy tale.
Yeah!
That's why I love her.
And they lived
happily ever after.
Well, that's the plan,
but real relationships
take a lot of work.
However,
if we listen, communicate,
and are sensitive
to each other's needs--
Happily ever after!
We kind of sort of
saved a princess!
Wooooo!
Happy Birthday, Lord Hater!
So me and the guys
all chipped in
and got you
a little something.
Can you guess what it is?
Is it a Doom Arena?
It's a Doom Arena!
♪ Doom Arena
I thought you might say that.
But don't worry,
because our next gift
is sure to put
a smile on your face.
May I present to you...
your most despised enemies
Wander and Sylvia!
Boo! I hate those guys!
See, Sylvia?
I told you
it was a real party.
Oh, look,
it's Mr. Peepers!
Mr. Peepers!
Thank you for the invitation
to the birthday party!
And you thought
it was a trap.
Yes! Best!
Birthday! Ever!
Not only do I get to watch
the destruction of my
most despised enemy,
I get to see him
cower before me!
To see that goofy grin
replaced with pure fear.
Yes!
Peepers!
There is a distinct lack
of cowering in my Doom Arena!
That is contrary
to the purpose
of the Doom arena!
Wander, we've got to
get out of here.
Oh, come on, Sylvia,
the party's not that bad.
Although it is poorly
decorated.
And not very well attended.
And, worst of all,
the birthday boy
does not appear
to be enjoying
the festivities.
Sylvia, we have to stay
in order to see that
Hater has fun on his most
special of special days.
It's up to us
to see that sad old scowl
replaced with a big old smile!
Pakow! Pakow!
Thunder noise!
Don't worry, sir.
One groveling do-gooder
coming right up.
Yeah!
Get 'em!!
( cheering )
Finally!
Some more party guests.
But what are they
gonna do for fun?
Crush us into a fine paste?
Oh, Sylvia.
I have a sure-fire plan to put
a smile on Hater's face.
All you need
to do is make sure
those gladiators
can't see anything.
With pleasure.
Ladies? Shall we?
Yah!
Ah! My eye!
My only eye!
I really wish
I had a second eye!
Put some glue,
more glue.
Oh, glitter,
definitely some glitter,
Hater loves glitter.
Finished!
Now, who wants
to show Hater a good time
by bashing his face in?
Hey! The party's over here,
you optic nerds!
( whooping ) Candy!
( cheering )
Peepers,
Wander still appears
to be enjoying himself...
now at the Expense
of my face!
Don't worry, sir.
We have plenty
of terrifying traps left.
Well, let's see,
meat tenderizer,
flame throwers,
flying tigers...
( groans ) Hurry up already.
Sylvia, Hater is still
not enjoying himself.
The corners of his mouth
are still pointing south.
We got to spin that gram
into a grin.
Spin the bottle?
Hater, you sassy man,
you do want to get
this party started.
Little help?
Hi-yah!
Who's it going to be.
I'm so excited.
Hater,
I was hoping you'd win.
Now Pucker up,
and let's see that smile!
( Watchdogs gasp )
( laughing )
Oh, man, did you see
the look on Hater's face?
I know.
Isn't that awful?
At this rate, we're never gonna
get a smile out of that guy.
Sir, I know this party
isn't going as, uh,
perfectly as you'd like.
So may I recommend
the big red button
in the upper right corner?
( Watchdogs cheering )
( roaring )
Stand back, Wander!
This fella
ain't no party game.
( Sylvia screaming )
( laughing )
Hey, Wander.
Your precious protector
Sylvia is gone.
How you feeling?
Scared?
( monster roaring )
Yes,
here comes the fear.
Any...moment...now.
( purring )
Who's a hungry boy,
who's a hungry boy?
That's right,
it's you.
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
Happiness is a happy
puppy, right, Hater?
( laughing )
I disapprove of this
turn of events!
Sir, come on,
don't let Wander
ruin this party for you.
What if we have him quietly
vaporized out back,
then do cake?
Would that make you happy?
No!
I want it to be perfect.
All I wanted
for my birthday
was to see
my most hated enemy
cower in fear
before his untimely doom!
Is that so much to ask?
Oh.
Party's over.
( alarms blaring )
But apparently
this pathetic "doom arena"
couldn't even terrify
a trembling toddler.
I guess I'm just
going to have to do it
my--self.
( whimpers )
( screaming )
Here we go.
Hater,
look at all this stuff.
We're going to have
so much fun
and you are going
to be so happy!
♪ Doom Arena
Limbo!
( laughing )
Hot potato!
♪ Doom Arena
Yeah. Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Musical chairs!
( Hater screaming )
Race you to the finish!
Aw, the birthday boy
should win at least one.
Let me get that for you.
What--
How are you--
Did you see my doom arena?
You should be
totally afraid.
Oh, Hater.
I am afraid.
I'm afraid you aren't enjoying
your birthday party.
I got it!
I know what will
save this party
and finally put a smile
on your face.
♪ It's your happy birthday
♪ Here's your happy
birthday song ♪
♪ And on your happy birthday
♪ Nothing can go wrong
♪ I can tell
that you're all grumpy ♪
♪ 'Cause you've been
around awhile ♪
♪ Just because
you're old and frumpy ♪
♪ Doesn't mean
you shouldn't smile ♪
♪ Because
it's your happy birthday ♪
♪ Here's your
happy birthday song ♪
♪ And your birthday
best be happy ♪
♪ 'Cause you won't be
around for long ♪
♪ So try not to be so sad
about your impending doom ♪
♪ Some day we'll light
birthday candles ♪
♪ On your frigid tomb
♪ Oh, it's your
happy birthday ♪
♪ Here's your
happy birthday song ♪
♪ And your birthday
won't be happy ♪
♪ Till you all sing along
Everybody!
♪ Oh, it's your
happy birthday ♪
♪ Here's your
happy birthday song ♪
Just the pit monster!
( singing
indistinctly )
♪ I can tell that
you're all grumpy 'cause
you've been around awhile ♪
♪ Just because you're old
and frumpy doesn't mean
you shouldn't... ♪
What's that I see?
♪ Smile
( cheering )
WANDER: Happy birthday, Hater!
( whistling )
( roaring )
( sniffing )
( purrs )
Aww!
( groaning )