♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
I, King Bingleborp
of the Binglebops,
declare this Bingleberry
Festival,
assuming that no horrible
galactic dictators
show up to destroy it again,
to be the best in
the history of Binglebopopolis!
( cheering )
Seriously?
All right, everyone,
you know the drill.
( screaming )
Ah! A giant dom bot?
Oh, the poor Binglebops.
They just refurbished
their Ferris wheel.
What are we gonna do?
( engine revving loudly )
For all your troubles.
Have you met
my daughter,
the princess?
What did he say,
my dear?
It never hurts
to help.
What a show-off!
What an inspiration!
BOTH: Wait, what?
Inspiration?
Wander, the only thing
that guy was inspired
by was us.
I mean, green hat,
orange fuzz.
But where's
the flap-drassin'
heart and sincerity?
But he actually
took out a giant dom bot.
And  nobody's
been able to do that.
Even you.
Well, maybe this guy
is too good to be true.
We need to track
this wandering do-gooder.
WANDER: Huh.
I thought I saw him
take off towards Flendar.
There's the Flendarians.
There's another
giant dom bot
coming to destroy them
and all they hold dear.
But no hotshot.
( gasps ) No hotshot!
Oh, no. Who will save them?!
( shrieking )
You know what?
Tromp that guy.
If he can take down a dom bot,
I can take down a dom bot.
Come on, Wander.
We got this.
Um, Sylvia...
Hey, dumb bot, here come
the real hero-ooooes.
Have you met
the princess?
It never hurts to help.
Oh, yeah!
Did you see
what he just did?
He saved us from
that dangerous dom bot.
No, he shoved us
out of the way
of that dangerous dom bot
so he could get the glory.
Huh. Methinks I spy
a green-eyed monster.
Where? I'll take him down
before that hotshot does.
Sylvia, are you...
jealous?
Of him? Please.
There's something phony
in his bologna,
and I'm gonna prove it.
♪ He rides
a hover speeder ♪
♪ Across the galaxy ♪
♪ When dom bots
come a-callin' ♪
♪ He triumphs handily ♪
♪ He'll rescue towns ♪
♪ And fight for truth ♪
♪ Though he's a mystery ♪
♪ And all the damsels,
they concur ♪
♪ He's the best
you'll ever see ♪
♪ Yes, the best
Hee-yah!
Ahem!
And also Sylvia
is also the best.
There can be two bests.
Okay, I've triangulated
the bot attacks,
and if my calculations
are correct,
this planet is
most likely the next target.
Finally, we'll be able
to stop the hotshot...
I mean bots... Stop the bots
once and for all.
Okay, Wander?
Wander?
Sylvia, I'm
the strong, silent type.
Pretend I'm not
talking right now.
I don't know what
you see in that guy.
Sure, he may be
a little "grrr" for my taste,
but he's stoppin' bots,
helpin' folks,
and makin' people happy.
Maybe we can learn
a thing or two from him.
Now... sh.
Oh, no, you don't.
That bot is mine!
Hello, Mr. Hotshot.
Long-time follower.
Literally. I've been following
you around all over the place.
I've been trying to ask
if you might like to team up
and help us out.
Your hover speeder's
really loud,
and I don't think
you can hear me.
Ha! Not so hot now,
are ya?
( screeching )
Okay, bot, prepare to...
( Sylvia gulps )
( meekly )
Meet your doom.
( angry snort )
( Sylvia yells )
Ah... stop.
Get off.
You're gonna damage
the hardware.
What?
( sheepish laugh )
You should see
your face right now.
It's all, like,
"Waaah, I'm so confused!"
Enlighten me.
Uh, well, so,
like, my cousin and I,
we found this
busted dom bot,
and he sorta thought,
why don't we fix it up?
And I pretend
to attack towns,
and then he can
rush in and save the day,
and get the reward and smooch
all the pretty ladies.
Smooch all
the pretty ladies?
Oh, no.
WANDER: What's your
favorite way to help?
Mine is every way.
Where you from?
Hey, who are you
under this hat?
Get off me, Wander.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Gasp. Brad Starlight.
You?!
But why?
Because I am strong.
I am a man.
I have a big chin.
I am the hero.
Me, me, me!
This should be
my thunder,
and you and your
dumb steed aren't
gonna take it from me.
Brad, there's
plenty of thunder.
Maybe there's a way you can
still help us stop Dominator.
Stop Dominator?
( laughs )
Simple jester.
I can't very well help planets
and smooch princesses
if I'm dead, can I?
But you're not
actually helping.
Aha, quiet, girl.
It never hurts
to help... yourself.
Chad! Okay, take two.
I'll go back to Point A,
you dispose of them,
attack the town,
I'll ride in,
do the thing with the thing,
and the money and the smooching,
and the fame and the glory.
Good? Go!
Who's the wandering hero now?
Ow! Oh, my knee.
My knee!
Shut up!
Yeah, so,
sorry about this, but,
prepare to meet
your doom, I guess.
SYLVIA: Oh, no.
That's a real dom bot.
Wait, what?
Oh, I forgot.
I have, like, a thing
somewhere where there's
not a real killer robot. Later.
Oh, poor Bradley.
He's so misguided
and bad at things.
That bot's gonna kill him!
- Yep.
- Sylvia!
But they're so crush-y
and laser-y and hurt-y.
And Brad is so... Bradley.
NH2H.
Besides, we're
his only hope.
Fine, fine.
We'll go be real heroes.
You, bot.
Prepare to meet your...
Chad! You know the face
is off limits.
Jawlines like these are not
something to take lightly.
Chad! I'm telling
your... mother.
BOT: No mother.
Only Dominator.
- Oh, no.
- ( crashing )
Oh, help!
Somebody help me!
( loud revving )
Sylvia! Whoo hoo!
Wander, sh!
We're trying to do
the strong, silent type thing.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
BRAD: Help!
Not the chin.
Thank you.
This was a hard-won victory,
but under my guidance,
even dumb animals
and silly sidekicks
can be taught to fight
the forces of fright.
Yeah, thanks for the help.
Well, to the victor
go the spoils, huh, hotshot?
Have you met
the princess?
BRAD: Why, no, but
who am I to deny
a comely lass the honor
of repaying my bravery
with copious amounts
of smoooo...
Oh, no!
Aw! I think
she likes him.
( Brad screaming )
System updating.
Integrating frostonium
capabilities.
Twenty-eight percent
completed.
( bored groan )
Ball updating.
( frustrated grunt )
How much longer is
this flarfin' update gonna take?
I wanna destroy something!
Calculating remaining
update time.
Six minutes
and 30 seconds.
Oh, that's not so bad.
Recalculating
remaining update time.
Twenty years
and five days.
What?! Ugh, never mind.
Hey, Bot 76,
you wanna hear a joke?
Okay, okay, so
a Flendarian,
a Kremlon,
and a ballet dancer
walk into a petting zoo.
And then, the ballet
dancer says,
"Annihilation? I thought
her name was Susan."
( laughing )
And then, you know,
she got annihilated.
Oh, come on.
That was funny.
Oh. Run humor protocol.
Humor protocol
updating.
Whatever.
I'm hilarious.
I bet everyone on
that planet is having
so much fun right now.
Ugh. I wish I could
just destroy them.
Hmm.
But since I can't...
Bots, I'm going out.
I know, I know.
"But Dominator,
it's too dangerous
to go out there without
your armor, yada, yada, yada."
Well, no one will even
know it's me. Don't wait up.
There you go.
Take your time.
You're doin' great.
- ( horns honking )
- Thank you for your
patience, everyone.
( dance music plays )
Next up on the mic is
Sylvia the Zbornak.
♪ Party time
and you're on the move ♪
Hey!
It's that Zbornak that's
always getting up in my grill.
( giggling )
This night is shaping up
even better than I thought.
♪ Nobody's gonna
keep you down, girl ♪
♪ Gettin' into
the music sound, girl ♪
♪ You know what you are ♪
♪ You're a groovin' gal ♪
♪ On the prowl ♪
♪ Rulin' the party now ♪
♪ Groovin' gal,
I hear your cats meow ♪
♪ When you get that song
in your ear canal ♪
♪ You can dance,
you can rock ♪
♪ Dance your way
to the top ♪
Oh, no, she didn't.
Ooh, fight.
♪ Groovin' gal ♪
Everybody fight!
Wow, thanks for
saving my hide back there.
- Wait, do I know you?
- No.
♪ Who's that
groovin' gal? ♪
( laughter )
What the...
My totally legitimate
establishment.
Uh-oh.
What a rush!
I haven't had a decent
rumble in ages.
Pretty slick moves
you had in there.
I'm Sylvia.
Oh, and I'm...
uh... Dee.
Nice to meet you, Dee.
I guess I better go find
another karaoke joint.
I've got some time
to kill.
- DRIVER 1: Aw, come on!
- DRIVER 2: Move! Just
pick them up!
You wanna come along?
Oh... ( stammering )
That's them, the broads
that whaled on me.
Get 'em!
- Oh, Grop.
- Quick, hop on.
♪ This is a girls' night ♪
♪ I wanna live ♪
♪ I want a night
on the town ♪
♪ Run wild
in the streets ♪
♪ When everybody
is around ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
( laughter )
♪ This is a girls' night ♪
♪ This is
a girls' night ♪
♪ Inconsiderate goons ♪
♪ Yes, I'm talkin'
'bout you ♪
♪ It's time to let
the ladies be ♪
♪ Let us do what we do ♪
♪ This is a girls' night ♪
And then the ballet
dancer says,
"Annihilation? I thought
her name was Susan."
( raucous laughter )
That is hilarious!
I know, right?
I gotta say, it is so nice
to run wild for once,
instead of always having
to bail someone else
- out of trouble.
- ( horns honking )
I know exactly
what you mean.
Sometimes you just gotta
let loose, have some fun
blow up a sun,
leave a solar system in
an endless state of darkness
and eternal winter
as everyone freezes
in their last
poses of anguish,
like, Noooooo!
( raucous laughter )
Oh, you have such
a strange sense of humor.
Oh, why are all
my friends so weird?
Uh...
friend?
Take a look at that.
What a view, huh?
Yeah. I guess so.
End of the line, girlies.
So youse the ones who
trashed my classy karaoke joint
and roughed up
my nephew.
Now you two's gonna pay.
Unless you offer me
a sincere apology.
I'm sorry, what?
Oh. Oh, yeah,
things did get
a little out of control.
We are sorry about the mess.
Apologize?
You really expect me
to beg for mercy?
Fat chance, you sad,
pathetic excuse for
a crime lord.
Excuse me?
There is nothing I hate more
than rudeness.
Oh, yeah?
And what are you gonna
do about it, bub?
Drip slime on me?
How dare you?!
You want scary,
I'll give you scary.
Maybe my pit monster
should teach you some manners.
Tone it down,
will ya, Dee?
- You're gonna
get us eaten.
- I don't think so.
These losers need to learn
what happens
when they try
to threaten me!
That was so rude!
All right,
listen up, chumps.
I'm the new boss
around here.
You'd all better do
as I tell you
or you'll end up just like
your little frightened friend.
( monster shrieking )
What are you doing?!
Uh, taking over
the seedy underworld
so that we can run
this planet from the shadows
with an iron fist. Duh!
Come on, it'll be fun.
No. No way.
This has all gone
way-ay-ay too far.
I did not sign up for this.
What? Hey, stop it.
I command you to stop.
Command me?
Who do you think you are?
I thought we were friends.
Friends are supposed to do
what you tell them to do.
What, like robots?
That's not what friends do.
Friends help each other out,
but they're still
their own people.
Speaking of which,
how about helping me
fight off this thing?
No one gets to tell me
what to do.
Fight it off yourself.
All right, minions,
who's with me?
Our boss is in trouble.
We gotta help him.
Seriously? Fine!
I don't even need
you lame-o's.
( Sylvia screams )
I can't hold him off
much longer.
Run! Get outta here!
I'm trying!
Sylvia! What are you
doing down there?
Granddad!
Kids!
( roaring )
You have no idea how glad
I am to see you, buddy.
Lady, I do not care much
for that friend of yours.
Who was she anyway?
I have no idea.
And trust me,
she's not my friend.
Oh, that reminds me.
Guess who I just saw leaving
as I was coming in?
Dominator!
Crazy, huh?
Just threw this jacket
into a bus driver's face
causing a three-car
pile-up and took off.
Wonder what she
was doing here?
Wait. What?
I'm back!
Did you miss me?
So today I learned
that friends are dumb,
and way overrated.
They don't do
what you tell them to do,
and sometimes, they even
try and tell you what to do.
Can you believe that?
I don't even know
why everyone makes such
a big deal about them.
How's that update
coming along?
Ugh!
( chair creaking )
( horns honking )
( honking continues )