♪♪
♪  Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪  Wander over yonder ♪
♪  Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪  Wander over yonder ♪
♪  Wander! Wander!
Over! Over! ♪
♪   Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪  Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪   Wander Over Yonder! ♪
( instrumental )
( Lord Hater laughs )
♪  Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
Wander! Wander! Over! Over!
♪  Yonder! Yonder!
Wander! Yonder! ♪
♪  Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪   Do-do-do-do-do ♪
( music over )
( screaming )
This... is...
nuts!
WANDER:
Oooo, good idea!
Squills love nuts!
Excuse me, ma'am,
but would you happen
to have any peanuts
that my companion and I
might use to entice
your frightened
little one home
and back into
the warm embrace
of his lovin' family?
( grunting )
Oh, there he goes!
( lightning )
( eerie music )
I'll save you!
Wander, no!
I don't like the looks
of that cave!
I know.
But if something horrible
happens
to that little guy,
( whispers )
I'd never forgive myself.
But what if something
horrible happens to you?
SYLVIA:
Wander. No. No.
No!
Sorry. I love you.
( laughing )
( sighing )
Love you too, buddy,
but why is there
this part of you
that always has
to do the wrong things
for the right reasons?!
(  Wander screaming )
SYLVIA: Wander!
WANDER:  This is amazing!
( sighs ) Oh,
thank Grop he's okay!
I'm gonna throttle him!
( squirrel chattering )
Whoaa.
It's bee-yoo-tiful.
Well, I'll be.
It's multiple me's!
Howdy do to you!
I mean, me!
That... is...
awesome!
I know, right?
What have
I asked you about?
Runnin' off like that.
Promise you
will never do that--
( Wander cackling )
Hey, what did I just say?
( multiple Wanders cheering )
( various Wanders )
This is amazing!
Let's go!
Yeah!
This is great!
What is going on?!
( yawning ) Hey,
keep it down out here,
I'm trying to slee--
( snores )
Wander!
SYLVIA : Wander?
What is going on?
The indigenous crystals
have fractured the varying
facets of my persona
and liberated them,
sending them traipsing over
the countryside,
hither and yon'...
time is of the essence;
if the personality fragments
are not reunited expeditiously,
the original specimen
will disappear...
Forever!
( grimacing )
( cash register clink )
Okay, wait,
so if he's him,
and he is him,
and you're him,
then that means
that they're also him,
but if I don't get them
and you and him back into him,
then he won't
be him anymore?
In an inarticulate garbled
manner of speaking...
yes.
Thanks.
It's all I needed.
Not so smart now,
are ya?
( sobbing ) No!
Is this the end
of overly dramatic
Wander?!
And... scene.
Yes!
You're gonna be okay, pal.
Just gotta the rest
of yous back into you.
Hey, pal!
Come here!
No. No. No!
( Wander laughing )
Oh, I get it.
You're the one that always
runs off and does stuff
even though
I tell you not to!
Well, fine! Go!
It's your fault
we're in this mess
in the first place.
Wander's better off
without you. ( snorting )
( Wanders cheering )
( sighing )
That's a lot of Wanders.
Four hundred twenty,
to be precise.
There's Angry Wander.
Flabdrassit!
Burping Wander.
( belches )
Curious Wander.
Hey! What's that?
Distracted Wander.
Easily-Impressed Wander.
That's amazing!
Zen Wander.
They who act in haste,
effort will they waste.
The Dancing Wanders.
♪ Oh, plunkin', plunkin' ♪
♪ That's what I do ♪
♪ I pluck my banjo
And I sing you a tune ♪
♪ I sing so sweetly
And it goes like this ♪
♪ Bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
Tree Hugger Wander.
Man, scope out that view.
That's amazing!
Hero Wander.
I'll save you!
Blonde Wig Wander.
( screaming )
I'll save you.
That's amazing!
( laughing )
Woohoo!
( Wanders yelling
in excitement )
SYLVIA: I can't do this!
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
Don't be all down
in the dumps.
It's always sunny somewhere,
Sylvie, ol' girl.
Sylvia, Sylvia, she's our man,
if she can't do it, no one can!
Yeah? Maybe you're right.
That's ama--
( grunting )
( disgruntled )
Okay. Let's catch
some Wanders using
their traits as bait!
That rhymed!
I love you.
Oh, no!
You're a mess!
Mess. Mess.
Did someone say mess?
Clean up.
Clean it up now!
Obsessy via Messy?
Check and check.
That also rhymed!
I love you.
Five down, 415 to go!
SYLVIA: Tea time!
Time for girls
to try on shoes
and talk
about lady things.
Two helpless females
all alone.
I hope no bad guys
are nearby.
( screaming )
Help! Help!
Save me!
I'll save yo--
Save it.
I'm the hero now.
( sniffing )
Smell that righteous grub.
You're doing great.
I love you.
Gosh, oh golly,
those Wanders over there
sure look sad.
I love you all!
And heeere's Wander!
Wander?
Come on, buddy.
Please?
What's wrong?
I put them all back in.
Who did I forget?
( Wander laughing )
No. No. Not him.
He's the one that always
gets us into trouble.
And he won't listen
to me anyway.
If you don't accept
all of us,
you accept none of us.
Whoooaa.
That's deep, dude.
He's just
gonna cause trouble
and then
I don't wanna...
( sighing )
( grumbling )
Flabdrassin' Wanders,
make me do the wrong things
for the right reasons.
( Wander laughing )
Hm. This one always does
whatever I tell him not to.
Ding!
Gotcha!
( struggling )
Are we sure about this?
'Cause my life is pretty crazy
with this one in it.
( sighs ) But it'll be
so much worse without you.
Yeeee-haw!
Wander?
Are-are you okay?
I'm more than okay.
I'm perfect!
Now come, trusty steed,
it's time to stop
that heartless evil-doer,
Lord Hater,
once and for all!
Hyah!
Wait, what? Stop?
Yes. I am a good guy.
And he is a bad guy.
And I stop him.
No, no, no, no.
The Wander I know wants
to befriend Hater,
not stop him.
Wait. Why are all these
other Wanders still up there?
Something's not right.
Wander. That crystal
has no reflection.
We're still missing
some part of you.
That's okay.
I'm a lot better without it.
Let's go go go.
No.
I've learned my lesson.
Every part
of you is important.
The helper seeks to help
because he knows
what it is to be helpless.
Hey, little guy,
it's okay. I won't hurt you.
Come on.
Home.
Thanks, Syl.
That was
the most important part.
Whoo.
I wouldn't want
someone else
to go through
what I went through.
Love that part of you,
buddy.
Over? What do
you mean it's over?
But I conquered you!
Your planet belongs to me.
Belonged to you.
Look, you really haven't
been around a lot lately,
so we weren't even sure
if you were still
underruling us anymore,
so we, like, uh, well,
we met someone else.
Someone else? Who?
Is it Emperor Awesome?
The black cube
of darkness?
Dominator!
It's a...
it's the, uh...
Evil sandwich!
That's right!
It is I, Sourdough.
The evil sandwich.
And I have seized control
of yet another one
of your planets,
Lord Hater.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I didn't even want
that stupid planet anyway.
I got pleeenty of other
planets that are waay better.
No, you don't!
Have you checked the villain
leaderboard lately?
Uh, yeah. I don't know
the exact number,
but I'm like waaay
up there.
Right, Peepers?
Oh, the sandwich is right, sir.
That was the last planet
we had control of
in this system,
which knocks us completely off
the villain board.
You're more
of a "ne'er-do-well"
than a villain.
How bad are you at this?
Wow, you can't even
do that right.
How'd that work out
for ya?
Sir. This is exactly
what I warned you about
in my report
entitled "Oblique Strategies
for Successful Masters of Evil."
I clearly stated
that the only to truly rule
the galaxy
is through careful planning,
precise focus, and hard work.
But, noooo.
You--
Me?!
Don't tell me what
being evil is all about.
It's about being all...
( roaring )
Scary bad guy stuff,
not, uh...
blah blah meeting, staff,
business guy stuff...
Wow. I can't believe
I never figured
this out before.
The reason we've been
failing all this time
is because--
You waste all our resources
trying to destroy
a happy-go-lucky do-gooder
who just wants
to be your friend?
Because you
and your boring plans
have been keeping me down,
Civilian Peepers!
Uh, sir, with due respect,
it's Commander.
Not anymore.
You're fired.
( electric guitar )
Oh, this isn't happening.
This isn't happening. This--
( incredulous )
This isn't happening.
He'll realize
he made a mistake.
He needs me.
Peepers, I need you.
Of course, sir,
what can I do for you?
Before you GO,
how do I, like,
find planets to conquer?
Are they just sort
of around, or...
Check the intergalactic matrix
in the command console.
The red button
on the black thing.
Thanks! Man,
I'm so stoked
to be running things
without you getting
in my way all the time.
Anyway,
you're still fired! Adios.
( sad electric guitar )
( music ends )
Peepers, wait.
Yes?
You know those eyeball
guys I have?
How often do I need
to change their batteries?
They're not robots,
they're watch dogs.
Oh, they're dogs.
Huh. So I gotta walk
them then...
They're not dogs either,
they're--
Gotcha. Robot dogs...
feed them batteries.
Thanks, buddy. I owe ya.
Not enough to save
your job though.
Peepers, wait.
What?
Look, I realize now
I may have been
a bit hasty before.
( gasps ) You do?
Yeah, I almost forgot
to ask you,
what's your
log-in password?
I need to erase you
from the system.
Hater-and-Peepers-Forever.
That's H-8-R-N-P33P3RS
with "3" for the "e's", 4-E-V-R.
Delete that.
Delete...
Actually, no.
These memories...
We've been through
a lot together,
haven't we?
Yes, sir,
we sure have.
I'm having second thoughts.
Instead of deleting these,
could you just crop yourself
out of 'em? Cool.
Well, goodbye forever.
He'll see.
Wait'll he tries conquering
something without me.
( screaming )
♪  Meet the universe's
ultimate evil-doer
♪  Hater! Hooray! ♪
Yeah!
♪  Who set the record
for galactic explosions ♪
♪  Hater! ♪
You got hated!
( song continues )
♪  You better run! ♪
Booyah!
( explosion )
♪  Hater ♪
( evil laugh )
( nineties hip hop )
( Peepers sighing )
( sad music )
♪  It all went by so fast ♪
( Hater laughing )
♪  The conquests
and the glory ♪
♪  But now my time
here's passed ♪
♪ And I've been shown
the door-y ♪
♪ I'm a commander
who's made his last command ♪
♪ I used to be
his right-hand man ♪
♪ But a sandwich took our
planets and I got canned ♪
♪ A commander who's
made his last command ♪
TAXI DRIVER:
Where to, my friend?
PEEPERS: Just drive.
Who wants batteries?
Hater!
Well, well, well.
Sourdough.
I must admit,
it was a pleasure
to beat you.
Oh, I should've said,
"eat you ." Do over.
Wow. You're even bad
at sandwich puns.
Sad. ( screaming )
Why are you messing
with my planets?
Oh, do you
mean  my  planets?
The planets
that used to be yours
but are now totally mine
'cause I conquered 'em
because I'm awesome
and you're a dumb sandwich.
Those planets?
You're conquered.
Deal with it, pimento brain.
What?
You didn't conquer squat.
You just knocked off crowns,
planted flags,
and did stupid dances.
Uh, yeah.
I conquered them.
No. That's wrong.
You've got to leave
a battalion behind.
Establish infrastructure.
Don't you know anything
about being an evil ruler?
Uhhh...
Where's the angry
little smart guy?
The one who actually knows
what evil is all about.
I know what evil
is all about!
Prepare to become
a patty melt.
Uh, finger slipped.
Fire!
Which one's
the shieldy thing?
( fire alarm going off )
How are you so bad
at this? I conquered
this entire quadrant.
And I'm a sandwich.
You're a powerful
electrical skeleton man!
Shut your buns!
( explosions )
Saline tester?
I could do that.
Hey, Peepers.
'Sup?
Sir?
Just one last question.
Not that I need your help.
But if someone got in a major
dog fight with a sandwich,
what would one do?
Oh. I thought
I was in your way.
Oh, you were.
Big time.
And I can handle this.
But I'm just going around,
getting second opinions.
I don't know.
Is there maybe something
you want to tell me first?
Maybe you wanna say you're--
Sorry? Nope.
Uh, can't think of anything.
( getting blasted )
Hurry, Lord Hater,
apologize!
I don't wanna!
I'm waiting.
You want advice?
In old galaxy,
I work as villain.
Shut your face!
Peepers, come on!
What did
I ever do to you?
( security alarm )
( all screaming )
I'm sorry...
You felt
I did something wrong.
I'm sorry...
that you're such
a whiny over-sensitive baby!
No, no, no, no,
wait, please,
I can get this.
This was my bad
and I'm sooooor...
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I'm having
such a hard time with this.
Close enough.
( alarm )
( all screaming )
Watch dogs!
We're pulling a reverse
Galaxon Phalanx maneuver
into an aggressive
Cropdust Wedge!
Eye Fighters, deploy!
( shooting )
( explosion )
PEEPERS: Shields, activate!
And with Sandwich's
whole armada focused on US...
he's left his planets
totally vulnerable!
( Peepers laughing )
Ooo, ooo. I wanna help.
What can I do?
What you do best, sir.
♪  Who is the universe's
ultimate evil-doer? ♪
( roaring )
♪   Hater! ♪
Evil Sandwich!
You're toast!
Ahhh!
♪  Yeah!
Evil's getting revenge... ♪
( song continues )
Now for the finishing touch.
EVIL SANDWICH:
Evil Sandwich....
( nineties hip hop )
ALIEN QUEEN: Hey, Hater.
So glad we're back together.
It was so embarrassing
being ruled by a sandwich.
Well, I couldn't have
done it without...
me! If I hadn't fired Peepers,
this never would have happened.
Oh.
(  Peepers gasps )
PEEPERS:  Sir.
Don't make me fire
you again.
♪  Commander Peepers ♪
Bleep bloop;
rules and planning;
strategy; no emotion;
does not compute;
servo shutting down;
nee nor--
( sighs )
( Peepers oils Hater )
System's operating
at peak efficiency.
HATER: I am a giant nerd.