♪♪
( raucous laughter )
At last,
after all this time,
I, Lord Hater,
have my most hated foe
in my clutches!
The moment of reckoning
is at hand.
I have but one
question for you.
What do you think
this means?
"The vile Lord Dominator
demands the presence
of Lord Hater..."
( reading quickly )
"...aboard her ship..."
"...at once...
Don't be late."
That sounds like a date!
That's what I said,
but Peepers said I was stupid.
Okay, look, I'm
the greatest in the galaxy.
Dominator's probably
already in love with me,
but this has to go
even more perfect than usual.
So I thought,
Wander knows all about
this lovey-dovey junk.
So maybe you could,
you know,
help me out
or whatever.
Excuse me.
I have something
in my eye.
They're tears of joy.
Oh, you gotta be
all Wander-y about it.
No, no, no!
I've got it under control.
So what do you
know about her?
Well, I know she's
already seen my sweet car,
my awesome band,
and of course, my rockin' bod.
Uh-huh.
But what does she like?
Um, me.
I don't understand
the question.
♪ The heart of a lady ♪
♪ Is a mysterious thing ♪
♪ That scientists have
wrestled with for years ♪
Wait.
What's happening?
♪ Your approach thus far
has lacked ♪
♪ A certain
gentlemanly tact ♪
♪ It's time to reassess
your presentation ♪
♪ Redirect
your conversations with ♪
♪ Her ♪
I have no idea
what you're singing about.
What I mean is...
- ♪ Ask her a question ♪
- A question?
- ♪ Something about herself,
a question ♪
- A question?
♪ You gotta focus on
someone else, a question ♪
- A question?
- ♪ Something to show her ♪
♪ That you'd really like
to get to know her ♪
- ♪ Then listen ♪
- Listen?!
♪ Hear what she has to say ♪
♪ And follow up with
some appropriate repartee ♪
- ♪ Then listen ♪
- More listening?!
♪ Always remember there's a
heart inside that scary armor ♪
♪ There's no shortage
of fellas ♪
♪ Who prattle on and on
about themselves ♪
♪ On and on
♪ Flex their muscles
or pump up their chests ♪
♪ Well, that's a perfect way
to bore a lady to death ♪
- ♪ A question ♪
- Again?
♪ Something about herself,
a question ♪
- I did!
- ♪ Gotta focus on
someone else ♪
♪ If you wanna win her,
show some interest in her ♪
♪ If you wanna date her
try to formulate a question ♪
All right, Hater,
give it a shot.
- Okay, have you ever noticed
how incredibly impressive I am?
- No!
Who wants to date the galaxy's
most charismatic dictator?
- You do.
- Try again.
- What's your favorite...
- Mm-mmm.
One of my many, many
outstanding traits
- is my humility.
- No! From the top.
♪ There's no shortage
of fellas ♪
♪ Who prattle on
about themselves ♪
♪ On and on
♪ Flex their muscles
and pump up their chests ♪
♪ That's a perfect way to bore
a lady to death ♪
Wander, can you
hold the singing
for just
five more minutes?
What the...
Hater's prison!
How did... oh, it's
gonna be one of those days.
( panting )
Don't worry, buddy.
I'll have us out of here
faster than you can say...
- What now?!
- I don't get it.
Dominator keeps
destroying planets
she could be conquering.
But why?
What am I not seeing?
Me. Now where's Wander?
♪ If you wanna win her,
show some interest in her ♪
♪ If you wanna date her,
try to formulate a question ♪
Oh! Always
with the singing.
But I'm going to use that
to my advantage.
Your idiot
and my idiot
are teaming up
to ask Dominator out,
leaving her wide open
to attack by
my indomitable
Watchdog army!
You mean
that Watchdog army?
No matter.
I don't need them.
My plan is foolproof.
I've done extensive
research
on our good friend
Dominator.
♪ You see, her whole fleet's
powered by volcanic excavator ♪
♪ So I'll apply frostonium
to this pyroregulator ♪
♪ And completely discombobulate
her army's power center ♪
♪ Divide by nine,
halve the sine ♪
♪ Adjust for Y,
easy as pie ♪
♪ Watch her forces crumble
before my strategic eye ♪
♪ That's how I'll get her,
how I'll get her ♪
♪ That's how I'll get her ♪
♪ I'll sneak into her engine
room and freeze her core, ♪
♪ That's how I'll get her,
how I'll get her ♪
Once I get her ♪
♪ Dominator will
bother us no more ♪
- Did you just sing that?
- What? No.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's a cute plan.
It's just, uh...
"Just uh..."
just uh what?
♪ It's nothing, no,
it all sounds great ♪
♪ And really is quite charming,
you're just forgetting ♪
♪ Her massive flarpin' army! ♪
♪ You clearly put
some thought into ♪
♪ Your big old plan
to get her ♪
♪ But how you gonna
pull it off ♪
♪ With bots
up in your retina? ♪
♪ Listen, Peeps,
her bot army ♪
♪ Will punt you
across the galaxy ♪
♪ With such a massive
peeper, Peepers ♪
♪ How can't you see
you'll never get her ♪
- ♪ Yes, I'll get her ♪
- ♪ You'll never get her ♪
♪ Your wits alone won't
win this interplanetary war ♪
- ♪ You'll never get her ♪
- ♪ Sure, I'll get her ♪
♪ You'll never get her
'cause she's better ♪
♪ You go in there
and you will be no more ♪
Okay, you definitely
sang that last part.
Well, so did you.
I was only
following your lead.
Wait. Follow my lead.
That's it!
I may not stand a chance
against Dominator's bots,
But you could fight them
to a standstill...
While you install
the frostonium
and freeze her army.
No, this is crazy.
Desperate times
call for desperate measures.
Are you a man,
or are you a Zbornak?
All right, I'm in.
♪ That's how we'll get her,
that's how we'll get her ♪
♪ Dominator will bother us
no more ♪
BOTH: Great,
but no singing.
Again.
Uh, look at this muscle.
Pretty cool, right?
Date me.
Again.
Who's your favorite
electrical skeleton man?
Again.
( screams )
This is so hard!
I mean, what does
she even like?
What is she into? What are
her favorite things to do?
- Hater.
- ( frustrated yell )
If I only knew that,
then I could think of
a stupid question
to ask her.
Hater, that was
a question
about someone
other than yourself.
You actually care
about somebody else.
I do?
I do!
♪ I think you've got it ♪
♪ Just can't wait to tell her
I think she's tops ♪
- ♪ You got it ♪
- ♪ She's a lunatic
and needs to be stopped ♪
♪ I got it,
hope she likes me ♪
♪ I believe in you, Hater ♪
♪ Let's all go meet
Dominator ♪
♪ Dominator thinks she's got us
trapped in her clutches ♪
♪ Till she meets
the Lady Haymaker
and the Duchess ♪
- ♪ I'll cut the lights ♪
- ♪ A left, a right ♪
- ♪ Hack the PC ♪
- ♪ And one of these ♪
♪ And so long, Dominator,
get out of our galaxy ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ Don't forget
to speak from the heart ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ We'll tear her robot
army apart ♪
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ I can't believe they think
he's gonna date her ♪
♪ Let's all go meet
Dominator ♪
♪ Let's all go
meet Dominator ♪
♪ Let's all go meet
Dominator now! ♪
♪ Now, now! ♪
WANDER: Here we go.
This is a bad idea.
I'll send flowers instead.
Or maybe a series
of awkward text messages.
( clears throat )
Dominator, it is I,
the Duke of Destruction,
the Monarch of Mayhem,
Lord Hater!
Uh... ahem.
I received your summons,
and in response,
I have
but one thing to say.
♪ I've given all I can ♪
( slow tempo music plays )
♪ Tried to show you
the best of me ♪
♪ But I can't break through ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ So I try again ♪
♪ And I offer
the rest of me ♪
♪ There's a heart
inside these bones ♪
♪ It beats alone ♪
♪ So alone ♪
♪ So I'll do
what I've not done ♪
♪ Ask the questions
that I've asked ♪
♪ Of no one ♪
♪ How are you ♪
( up-tempo music plays )
♪ And how's your day
goin' so far? ♪
♪ What'd you have
for breakfast? ♪
♪ Was it satisfying? ♪
♪ Do you like leisurely
strolls in the park? ♪
♪ 'Cause I do ♪
♪ Cat person
or dog person? ♪
♪ I know it's tough
deciding ♪
♪ Think of the pair
we could be ♪
♪ If you just dared
to open up your evil heart ♪
♪ Tell me about yourself,
don't leave anything out ♪
♪ I can't bear
to be apart ♪
♪ How are you ♪
♪ Seems like
a pretty good start ♪
Yeah!
I think she's
diggin' it.
This is going
super well.
A little too
There's not
a bot in sight.
The ship's core
is just inside.
Easy as
one, two, three.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine?
( both screaming )
♪ Your favorite color,
what you did for the summer ♪
♪ Do you have an opinion
on snow, pro or con? ♪
♪ Mustard or mayo,
tell me what do you say, oh ♪
♪ I'd seriously
like to know ♪
♪ Yes, he'd seriously
♪ How are you ♪
Fantasy sequence,
boys!
♪ Oh, I had a dream ♪
♪ A dream we were running ♪
♪ Running the galaxy
side by side ♪
♪ It was a beautiful dream ♪
♪ It was a beautiful night,
I had a dream ♪
♪ A dream that you loved me ♪
♪ And I held your hand
in mine ♪
♪ Then concluded
at that moment ♪
♪ After much deliberation ♪
♪ I say it
without hesitation ♪
♪ I shout it out loud ♪
♪ You're the greatest! ♪
♪ Baby, you're
the greatest ♪
♪ Oh, you're the greatest ♪
♪ In the galaxy ♪
Saxophone!
♪ Can't you see
I've changed ♪
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ Just wanna
get to know ya ♪
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ So here I am at last ♪
♪ Here he is at last ♪
♪ Just one question
left to ask ♪
Uh, yeah, so,
I was wondering if maybe
Tuesday, if you
aren't busy or anything
you might wanna
hang out,
get a cup of coffee
or espresso or something,
or whatever
works for you.
Yeahhhh!!
What the grop
is going on here?
- ( footsteps )
- You.
But there...
and also throne.
I was in the shower.
That's just my suit.
I received your summons
to appear, and that's...
Oh, dang.
Was that today?
One sec.
Okay, go ahead.
Surrender.
Wait, what?
I think you mean
surrender your heart
to my studly skull muffin.
What? Ew! No.
Hater's the only villain
who hasn't bowed down before me.
I called you here to admit
that I am
the greatest in the galaxy.
Oh, there's a whole part
of the song about that.
Two, three...
♪ You're the greatest... ♪
So you don't
want to date me?
( raucous laughter )
( laughing )
Oh... that is...
You think I...
( laughing )
That is too good.
I mean, it's sad for you,
but... ( laughs )
( sighs )
Let me put this
in a way
you idiots will understand.
( sultry music plays )
♪ I'm not
the damsel in distress ♪
♪ I'm not your girlfriend
or the frightened princess ♪
♪ I'm not a little bird
who needs your help to fly ♪
♪ Nope,
I'm a bad guy ♪
♪ All these former villains
that you see ♪
♪ Each of them
with shaking knees ♪
♪ Have knelt before me ♪
♪ So I'm not your teammate
or your partner in crime ♪
What am I, boys?
She's the bad guy.
♪ Oh, it's magic ♪
♪ To watch a planet ♪
♪ Shrivel up and die ♪
♪ Oh, it's thrillin' ♪
♪ To be a villain ♪
♪ I destroy their homes ♪
♪ And then I watch
them cry ♪
( laughing )
( distorted voice )
♪ 'Cause I'm the bad guy ♪
Oh, my grop.
She's not trying
to conquer the galaxy
so she can rule it.
She wants to destroy it.
Man, that's evil.
( shrieking )
♪ Oh, ain't it fantastic ♪
♪ I see something,
I blast it ♪
♪ And let me tell you why ♪
♪ I've always had a weakness ♪
♪ For barrenness
and bleakness ♪
♪ I crush all your hopes ♪
♪ And then I
watch you cry ♪
♪ See, I find
this business rather fun ♪
♪ I don't want your assistance
or your adulation ♪
♪ I'll vaporize your galaxy ♪
♪ And bid you bye-bye ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ Come on, guess ♪
'Cause you're
the bad guy?
Or, well, girl.
( evil laughter )
Hey, Dominator, freeze.
Oh, yeah!
♪ That's how I'll get her
once I get her ♪
- ♪ Dominator will-- ♪
- No time for a reprise.
This whole place
is gonna freeze over.
We've gotta save Wander,
and to a lesser extent, Hater.
( alarm blaring )
DOMINATOR:
Oh, seriously?
Be right back.
Ooh, why don't you
take this time
to work on
your death rattles?
I like a...
"No, no, no, no, no, no!"
But a... "Why??!"
is not without its charms.
( yelling )
Come on, Hater.
We gotta get outta here.
When I say "evac,"
you say "uate."
Evac, evac.
What's the point?
She thinks
I'm a joke.
Might as well
destroy me.
( playing gentle tune )
♪ My fair Hatey,
pick your chin up ♪
♪ Things are bound
to get better ♪
♪ Yeah, the gal
of your dreams ♪
♪ Turned out deadly,
it seems ♪
♪ And it's probably best
you didn't wind up ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ My fair Hatey,
don't you give up ♪
♪ It ain't
a total disaster ♪
♪ Hey, we gave it a go ♪
♪ Put on a heck of a show ♪
♪ And did a lot of fun stuff ♪
♪ We'll get to
laugh about after ♪
♪ Seems like you're
becoming ♪
♪ Becoming someone ♪
♪ A little less
full of hate ♪
♪ Sure, Dominator's got
an unstoppable army ♪
♪ And a maniacal
determination ♪
♪ To destroy
our whole galaxy ♪
♪ But you know what
I think is great ♪
Please be quiet.
♪ I'm talkin' about
buddies ♪
♪ Sure seems like
we're becoming friends ♪
- ♪ Buddies ♪
- We are not buddies ♪
♪ And buddies stay buddies
till the very end ♪
Stop it!
♪ I know you'll
try to deny it ♪
I do deny it
'cause we're not.
♪ Chase me 'round
the galaxy and try to hide ♪
I swear, if you say
buddy one more time.
♪ We're buddies ♪
♪ Looks like
we're becoming friends ♪
- ♪ We're buddies ♪
- ( shrieking )
♪ And buddies stay
buddies until the very end ♪
Get back here!
DOMINATOR:
Oh, grop.
- Buddy!
♪ Oh, I thought
I'd never see you again ♪
- Uh, buddies?
- Buddy!
This ship is gonna
blow any second now.
But he keeps
saying we're friends!
♪ And he keeps
trying to deny it ♪
Listen, buddies
or no buddies,
I'm not ready to die yet,
so let's go!
( alarm blaring )
No, no, no, no, no, no!
( cheering )
Take that, Dominator.
We did it, buddies.
BOTH: We're not
your buddies!
Oh, man,
this is so cool!
Thanks, losers.
( laughing )
Now she's got lava
and ice powers?!
That's it.
Game over.
We lose,
Dominator rules.
No she doesn't, sir.
If she destroys
the entire galaxy,
there'll be nothing left
to rule.
And you're forgetting
the most important thing.
What's that?
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ Lord Hater,
you're the greatest ♪
That's right.
I am the greatest.
♪ In the galaxy ♪
♪ I'm back, whoo ♪
♪ Lord Hater,
number one superstar ♪
Yeah! Nailed it!
And you know what
I'm gonna do?
♪ I'm gonna save
this galaxy ♪
So we can
conquer it later.
( sighs ) Syl,
I really made a mess of things.
- Good.
- How is that good?
Realizing that is
the first step
to making things right.
Aw, Syl.
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ No, buddy,
you're the greatest ♪
♪ And together, we're gonna
save this galaxy ♪
♪ I'm the greatest ♪
- ♪ He's the greatest ♪
- ♪ They're the greatest ♪
♪ He's the greatest ♪
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ I'm the greatest
in the galaxy... ♪
Enough with
the singing already.
Obviously,
I'm the greatest!
It's ice.
Show's over.
♪ You're the greatest ♪
♪ Yeah, you're the greatest ♪
♪ You're the greatest
in the galaxy ♪
Argh, stupid
catchy tune!