♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laugh )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( creaking )
SHOULD...WE GO IN?
( creaking continues )
I'M-I'M NOT SCARED,
IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE IMPLYING.
GOOD! 'CAUSE I'M JUST WORRIED
MAYBE SOMEBODY'S IN THERE
AND NEEDS...HELP.
OH, YEAH. I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT LOOKS
PRETTY EMPTY TO ME,
AND, UH, ALSO LOOKS
TOTALLY STRUCTURALLY UNSOUND,
SO YEAH, I DON'T THINK
WE SHOULD...
(sighs) I GOT A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
( hissing )
HELLOOOO!
ANYBODY READY FOR
A RESCUE PAR-TAY?
WHOO-HOO!
SHH!
HUH. IF YOU ASK ME,
THESE FOLKS ALREADY
HAD A PAR-TAY.
THIS PLACE IS A MESS!
JUST STAY CLOSE.
GOT IT?
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
YEESH. IF THESE WALLS
COULD TALK.
( electronic crackling )
CAPTAIN'S LOG,
DAY 445.
THIS IS CAPTAIN TIM.
DESPITE MY EXCEEDINGLY
HEROIC EFFORTS
TO CONTROL THE SITCH,
THINGS ARE RAPIDLY
DETERIORATING.
I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH LONGER
MY IMPRESSIVE STRENGTH
CAN KEEP THE MONSTER AT BAY.
( loud stomping,
monster growling )
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS NOW,
IGNORE MY DASHING GOOD LOOKS
AND HEED THIS WARNING--
( screaming,
crunching )
( silence )
( creaking )
WANDER, WE GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE!
THERE'S NO ONE HERE TO HELP!
WANDER! CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
( clatter )
WANDER? IS THAT YOU, BUDDY?
( loud growling )
( clatter continues )
( distant screeching )
( pipes clanking )
WHOA!
AAAAH! OHH!
AAH! I KNEW WE SHOULDA
NEVER COME IN HERE!
AAAH! AAH!
YAAAH!!!
( blaster empty )
YEAH, YOU  BETTER  RUN,
YOU....SPIDER...
ALIEN THING!
WANDER!
DON'T WORRY, WANDER!
I'M COMIN' FOR YA, BUDDY!
BUT FIRST...
I'M GONNA NEED
A BIGGER BLASTER.
( Wander whistling
a happy tune )
( electronic crackling )
( low growling )
HELLO? ANYBODY IN HERE?
( growling )
RESCUE PAR-TAY'S HERE.
( distant clank )
WOOP WOOP?
(distorted ) HELLO?
I'M HERE TO RESCUE YOU!
HELLO?
SYLVIA?
IS THAT YOU?
YOU KNOW, I'M BEGINNING
TO THINK YOU WERE RIGHT.
NOBODY'S ON THIS--
( growling )
--SHIP.
( roaring )
WHAAAA!!!!
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMEONE
ON THIS SHIP WHO NEEDED HELP,
THOUGH I DIDN'T KNOW
THEY'D BE SO CUTE!
(baby talk )
OH, WIDDLE GUY.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
SO SCARED
ALL ALONE IN THIS
BIG OL' SCARY, SCARY SHIP.
( roaring )
HO HO! I'M HAPPY
I FOUND YOU TOO, BUDDY!
OH, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE FULL OF BEANS!
WHO'S RIDING A BIKE?
YOU ARE, YOU ARE, YOU ARE!
OOH! YOU WANNA PLAY, HUH?
BETCHA CAN'T CATCH ME!
HA! HA! HA! WHAAAAA!!!!
( creature hissing )
Wander: I'M HIDING NOW!
BETCHA CAN'T FIND ME!
( growling )
( roaring )
AAH!
OH, FROPP!
AAAAHHH!
OKAY, THIS IS GROSS.
Wander:
YOU STILL HAVEN'T FOUND ME!
OH, NO. WANDER.
STOP! COME BACK!
MY FACE IS WAY TASTIER
THAN HIS! I PROMISE!
( Wander giggling )
NOPE! NOT THERE!
NOPE! NOT THERE, EITHER!
♪ YOU CAN'T FIND ME,
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA ♪
( giggling )
( screaming )
YOU CAUGHT ME,
YOU SNEAKY BOY!
NO! BAD!
"CAPTAIN TIM"?
SO THAT'S YOUR NAME!
WHO'S A GOOD BOY?
YOU ARE, CAPTAIN TIM!
COME ON, GIVE US A HUG!
BAD CAPTAIN TIM!
BAD!
OH, I FORGIVE YOU,
CAPTAIN TIM.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
YOU WEREN'T PROPERTY TRAINED.
BUT WE'LL START TAKING CARE
OF THAT RIGHT NOW!
( growling )
SIT. SIT. SIT.
THERE WE GO!
GOOD BOY!
( screeching )
OH, YUCK YUCK YUCK YUCK YUCK!
YUCK! OH, I NEED A SHOWER!
NO. NO, I NEED
TO SAVE WANDER.
BUT FIRST, I'M GONNA NEED
AN EVEN  BIGGER  BLASTER.
YAAHHHH!!!
YAH HA HA!
OHH! OHH!
HEEL, CAPTAIN TIM,
HEEL!
WHOA!!!
( loud clank )
THE KITCHEN?
OH, IS THE WIDDLE CAPTAIN
HUNGWY?
I BET YOU ARE.
YES, YOU ARE.
YES, YOU ARE,
YOU WIDDLE HUNGWY MUNGWY.
NOW, WHERE DO THEY HIDE
THE GRUB AROUND HERE?
PERFECT!
OOOH. BEANS!
NOW YOU REALLY  WILL
BE FULL OF 'EM.
HMM. NEED A CAN OPENER.
WHY, AREN'T YOU JUST
A HELPY-HELP PERSON TODAY?
DINNER IS SERVED,
O CAPTAIN, MY CAPTAIN.
COME ON, BUDDY, EAT UP!
THEY'RE GOOD FOR YOU!
HERE COMES THE GALACTIC
STAR CRUISER
FILLED WITH A PAYLOAD
OF DESTRUCTIVE LASER BEAMS!
PYOO! PYOO! PYOO!
OOH, HE MADE THE MANEUVER....
KADOOSH!
( gulps, coughs )
( whimpers )
OH HO HO HO HO!
POOR GUY.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY'S
READY FOR A NAP.
♪ LOOK WHO CAME
TO VISIT YOU ♪
IT'S SLEEPY-WEEPY
BEDDY BEAR!
(high voice)
I LOVE YOU,
CAPTAIN TIM.
I  LOVE  YOU.
( smoochy sounds )
WHAT A NEAT TRICK,
CAPTAIN TIM!
CAN YOU DO ANY OTHERS?
I BET YOU CAN'T,
I BET YOU CAN'T!
AWW. A LOVE BITE.
COME BACK HERE.
I HAVE ONE FOR YOU!
NYAH NYAH NYAH NYAH!
WANDER, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
( creaking )
( gasps )
NO. NO!
WANDER...
NOOOO!!!!
IT'S SHOULD HAVE BEEN ME!
WHYYYYYYY!!!!!
( sobbing )
WANDER.
I MAY HAVE FAILED YOU,
BUT AS LONG AS
I LIVE AND BREATHE,
I WILL AVENGE YOU.
( beeping )
COMPUTER, THIS IS CAPTAIN TIM.
Computer:
GREETINGS, CAPTAIN TIM.
WILL YOU BE REQUIRING
MORE COMPLIMENTS ON
YOUR HANDSOMENESS TODAY?
I'M NOT HERE FOR COMPLIMENTS.
I'M HERE TO RID THE UNIVERSE
OF MURDERING MONSTER SCUM!
ACTIVATE SELF-DESTRUCT
SEQUENCE!
ARE YOU SURE?
THIS IS TOTALLY FOR REALS.
NO TAKESIES-BACKSIES.
YES, I'M SURE!
TOTALLY SURE.
OKAY, COOL.
SELF-DESTRUCT...
(evil voice )
CONFIRMED!
( alarm blaring )
GOODBYE, WANDER.
Wander: HA HA!
HEEL, CAPTAIN TIM!
HEEL! HEEL!
Wander: GOTCHA!
( creature growling )
GOOD HEEL!
NOW, LUNCH KISSIES.
WHO WANTS KISSIES?
( chomp )
OOH! YOU DO!
( chomping continues )
OW! YOU DO! OW!!!
OW! OW!
Computer:  THIS SHIP WILL
SELF-DESTRUCT IN THREE MINUTES.
TWO-FIFTY-NINE, FIFTY-EIGHT,
FIFTY-SEVEN...
SIX, FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE.
OH, COME ON, CAPTAIN TIM!
I KNOW YOU CAN HIDE
BETTER THAN THAT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING NOW,
YOU SILLY GOOSE?
♪ MY BEST BUDDY'S NAME
IS CAPTAIN TIM ♪
♪ THERE'S NO ONE
IN THE UNIVERSE ♪
♪ QUITE LIKE HIM
♪ HE'S A QUICK AND SNAPPY
HAPPY LITTLE GUY ♪
♪ I LOVE HIM JUST SO MUCH
I THINK I MIGHT JUST DIE ♪
♪ YEAH, HE'S MY BEST BUD
♪ ALL COVERED IN BLOOD,
DA-DOO-DAH-DOO-DOO ♪
♪ ALL COVERED IN BLOOD
MY--
MY BE-E-E-E-E-EST BUDDY!
( sobbing )
WHAT AM I GONNA--
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITHOUT...
HI-I-I-I-M?
( sniffling )
I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO MOVE ON!
WANDER WOULD HAVE
WANTED IT THAT WAY.
HE'D SAY, "IT'S ALWAYS SUNNY
SOMEWHERE, SYLVIA OLD GIRL,
"SO KEEP YOUR EYE
ON THE HORIZON
AND DON'T LOOK BACK.
NEVER LOOK BACK!"
WANDER?
Sylvia: WANDER!
( growling )
WANDER!!!!
OH! I CAN'T--
HOW DO I GET OUT OF
THIS FLARPIN' THING?!
Sylvia:
I'M COMING, WANDER!
♪ OH, I'M REALLY CRAZY
'BOUT MY BEST CHUM ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE TOGETHER,
WHATEVER MAY COME ♪
♪ NO RIVER WIDE, OCEAN DEEP
OR MOUNTAIN HIGH ♪
♪ CAN KEEP APART A PAIR OF PALS
LIKE YOU AND I ♪
♪ THROUGH THICK AND THIN,
SIDE BY SIDE ♪
♪ WE'RE UNIFIED AND UNDIVIDED,
TRUE AND TRIED ♪
♪ YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND
♪ TO THE LIVING END,
DAH-DOO-DAH-DOO-DOO ♪
♪ DAH-DOO-DIT-DIT-
DIDDA-DOO ♪
OH! ( panting )
COMPUTER, QUICK!
DEACTIVATE
SELF-DESTRUCT SEQUENCE!
OH, MY DIGITS!
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME SAYING
NO TAKESIES-BACKSIES?
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT--
WHOA!!!
OKAY. NO PROBLEM.
THERE'S STILL TIME
TO SAVE WANDER.
BUT FIRST...
I'M GONNA NEED
AN EVEN  BIGGERER  BLASTER.
WANDER! IT'S GO TIME, BUDDY!
AND BY THAT I MEAN
WE GOTTA GO!
WANDER?
WANDER!
WANDER? WANDER!
WANDER! WANDER!
WANDER! WANDER! WANDER?
TIM, IF YOU'RE GONNA LEARN
THREE BISCUITS,
YOU GOTTA PAY ATTENTION.
( loud pulsations )
( explosion )
GET AWAY FROM HIM, YOU!
SYLVIA!
( blaster shots )
CAPTAIN TIM!
Sylvia: COME ON, PAL,
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE!
THIS SHIP WILL SELF-DESTRUCT
IN TWENTY, NINETEEN, EIGHTEEN--
WOW, THIS IT
TAKING FOREVER.
OKAY IF I SPEED THINGS UP?
NO NO NO NO NO
NO NO NO NO NO!
COOL, THANKS.
THREE, TWO, ONE. BOOM!
( explosions )
HOLD ON, BUDDY!
I'M SO HAPPY WE ALL
GOT OUT OF THERE
IN ONE PIECE!
ME TOO.
ALL THREE OF US.
WHAT'S THAT NOW?
ME, YOU,
AND CAPTAIN TIM!
CAPTAIN TIM?!
( growling, screeching )
AAAH!
WANDER, WHADDYA--
I JUST BLEW UP THAT SHIP
TRYING TO DESTROY
THAT HORRIBLE THING!
HORRIBLE?
THIS CUTE LITTLE BOOGER?
YOU'RE CRAZY.
LOOK, I'VE BEEN TRAINING HIM.
CAPTAIN TIM, SIT.
CAPTAIN TIM,
STAND.
SPEAK.
( screeching )
YOU HAVE  GOT  TO BE
KIDDING ME.
I-I...I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED A PET.
AND THIS LITTLE GUY'S
STOLEN MY HEART, SYLVIA...
( sniffling )
HE'S STOLEN MY HEART.
HE'S STEALING MY HEART!
HE'S STEALING MY HEART!!!
AAHHH!
( creature screeching )
SEE?
THAT WAS PROBABLY
JUST A LOVE BITE.
NO! WAIT.
WANDER.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
CAPTAIN TIM
IS A WILD ANIMAL,
AND I CAN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT HE WANTS TO DEVOUR
MY STILL-BEATING HEART.
BUT EVEN SO,
I CAN'T HELP BUT
LOVE HIM, SYLVIA,
WITH ALL OF
MY STILL-BEATING HEART.
NOW, I CAME HERE TO SAVE
WHOEVER WAS ON THIS SHIP,
AND BY GOLLY, I WILL!
NO MATTER HOW MANY EGGS
THEY WANT TO LAY INSIDE
MY RIB CAGE.
IF I CAN'T KEEP CAPTAIN TIM,
WE HAVE TO FIND HIM
A FOREVER HOME.
BUT WANDER, WHO'D WANT
A VIOLENT, FLESH-EATING ALIEN
FOR A PET?
PING!
( Peepers screaming )
AAAAAH!!!!
( roaring )
SIRRRRR!
( distant whistling )
CAPTAIN TIM!
HERE BOY! HERE BOY!
( roaring )
( metallic scratching noises )
HEE HEE! IT TICKLES!
OH, CAPTAIN TIM!
WHO'S A BAD BOY?
SIR, WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I DON'T THINK THIS IS
THE BEST IDEA.
HOW DARE YOU,
COMMANDER  PEEPERS?
CAPTAIN TIM HERE
OUTRANKS YOU.
DON'T YOU, BOY?
YOU OUTRANK HIM.
HE'S INSUBORDINATE!
YOU OUTRANK HIM,
YES YOU DO!
YES, YOU DO!!!
BUT-- AAAAHHH!
♪ CAPTAIN TIM
( sobbing )
WELL, SYLVIA,
IT'S LIKE THEY SAY--
IF YOU LOVE SOMETHING,
SET IT FREE.
IF IT COMES BACK,
IT'S YOURS.
BUT IF IT COMES BACK,
TRIES TO RIP YOUR FACE OFF,
STABS YOU A BUNCH
AND THEN LAYS ITS EGGS
INSIDE YOUR CHEST,
IT WASN'T MEANT TO BE.
( distant screaming )
Wander:
MAYBE WE COULD
VISIT HIM SOMETIME?
Sylvia:
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
♪ ZEE-DOO-DOO-DOO-
DIDDY-DOO ♪
( music box playing
Rock-A-Bye Baby,
creature snoring )
( roaring )