♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Oof!      Oof!
These the ones?
[ Laughter ]
Amethyst: Steven! Greg!
[ Grunting ]
They found me out!
Amethyst!
You won't believe
what I've been through.
These Amethysts,
they're really, really...
great!
What?!
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughing ]
Your faces!
You were right!
That was priceless!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I had to!
[ Chuckles ]
What are you wearing?
Greg! This is
a good look for you.
What is going on?
These Amethysts,
they're all from Earth!
They're from
the Prime Kindergarten!
Wait! Hey, 8XL!
Yeah?
You guys, I'm an 8!
Tell them. Tell them!
The amethyst under me
never popped out.
We were all waiting,
and -- pfft -- nothing.
I'm 8XM!
Facet 5, cut 8XM -- that's me!
This is 8XG,
this is 8XH.
I'm J.
Ah, geez! Sorry!
I'm worse than Holly Blue!
Aren't we all?
[ Laughter ]
Prime, prime, prime.
You Amethysts are
so cliquey.
Skinny's a Jasper!
There are Gems here
from the Beta Kindergarten, too!
Hey, where's Carnelian?
Celebrating.
I'm not the shortest
anymore!
[ Amethyst and Carnelian Laugh ]
This is unreal.
Hey!
Please, if you don't
mind me asking,
we really need
your help.
We came in
with Sapphire, Ruby, and Pearl,
we've got to find them
and get out of --
I'll only be a moment.
What are you all
doing in here?!
Get to your stations!
Even you hideous
off-color betas!
Get out of your cubbies
and into your places!
It's the least you can do
for the Diamond
that kept your worthless,
sorry Gems in service!
That's right --
Blue is back already!
Now go pretend
your filthy vein of Quartz
is capable of gratitude!
Go, go, go!
[ All panting ]
Disperse!
My Diamond is waiting!
Run! Just run!
I'll find you! Go!
[ Both panting ]
Who bubbled
all these Gems?
Greg: Wow!
It's kind of like
a birthday party in here.
[ Gasps ] Oh, no!
We got to hide!
Huh?
Pearl,
close the door.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door opens ]
Please tell me
you're joking.
You only just left,
and you're already back?
Yellow!
W-What are you doing here?
I'm here to bring you
back to reality, Blue.
I'm fine.
Just leave me alone.
It's been
thousands of years, Blue,
and you still can't bring
yourself to destroy these Gems?
She was shattered
by a Rose Quartz!
The entire cut of Gem
deserves the same fate!
But they were hers.
They should be
wiped out of existence,
not kept safe in bubbles!
Yellow,
she made them.
This is all
we have left of her --
these Gems, this place,
and the Earth.
I thought we agreed
we need to put that planet
and this whole debacle
behind us.
Why can't you just
let me grieve?
You can't keep
coming here forever!
Why not?
[ Sighs ]
Pearl, do something.
Sing for her.
Make her feel better.
Yes, my Diamond!
Ahem.
Ahem!
Uh...oh.
♪ Aah haa haa,
aah haa haa ♪
♪ Aah haa haa
haa haa haa haa ♪
♪ Aah haa haa,
aah haa haa ♪
♪ Aah haa haa
haa haa haa haa haa haaaaaa ♪
♪ Why would you want
to be here? ♪
♪ What do you ever see here? ♪
♪ That doesn't make you
feel worse than you do? ♪
♪ And tell me, what's the use
of feeling, Blue? ♪
♪ Why would you want
to employ her subjects ♪
♪ That destroyed her? ♪
♪ Why keep up her silly zoo? ♪
♪ Oh, tell me ♪
♪ What's the use
of feeling, Blue? ♪
♪ An army has a use,
they can go and fight a war ♪
♪ A Sapphire has a use,
she can tell you what it's for ♪
♪ An Agate terrifies,
a Lapis terraforms ♪
♪ Where's their Diamond
when they need her, Blue? ♪
♪ You've got to be
a leader, Blue ♪
♪ Yes, of course,
we still love her ♪
♪ And we're always
thinking of her ♪
♪ But now
there's nothing we can do ♪
♪ So tell me ♪
♪ What's the use
of feeling? ♪
of feeling, Blue? ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ How can you stand
to be here with it all? ♪
♪ Here with it all ♪
♪ Drowning in all this regret? ♪
♪ Wouldn't you rather
forget her? ♪
♪ Ohhh ♪
♪ Won't it be grand
to get rid of it all? ♪
♪ Rid of it all ♪
♪ Let's make a plan of attack ♪
♪ Start looking forward
and stop looking back ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ Of course, we still love her ♪
♪ And we're always
thinking of her ♪
♪ Don't you know
I miss her, too? ♪
♪ But tell me ♪
♪ What's the use
of feeling? ♪
♪ Hmm hmm hmm, hmm hmm hmm ♪
♪ Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmmmmm ♪
[ Door opens ]
And we have arrived.
That will be all, Pearl.
[ Door closes ]
My Diamond.
My gracious, wondrous,
luminous, lustrous Diamond.
Sss?
[ Gasps ] Oh, my!
It's truly an honor
to bask in your radiance...ses.
Get to the point,
Agate.
[ Clears throat ]
Yes, of course.
My deepest apologies.
You'll be pleased to know
that your Sapphire
has completed
your special delivery.
What special delivery?
Um, the special delivery
you requested from Earth,
of course.
I never asked any Sapphire
to go to Earth.
I...
Um...
[ Whispering ] Oh, no!
She's freezing up!
My...future vision foresaw you,
my Diamond,
desiring more...humans
for the zoo.
So I...acted accordingly.
It's true.
The window for preserving
Earth specimens is closing.
Phew!
Is that what you want?
Sapphire, has the cluster
emerged yet?
No, it has not.
Then there's still time.
That will be all.
My Diamonds.
Two Diamonds?!
I can't believe it!
Can you believe it?
Oh, well,
of course you can.
You probably foresaw
the whole thing.
Sapphire: Of course!
No surprises here.
I never expected to see
Yellow Diamond in person.
What a commanding presence.
You can just feel
strength and confidence
radiating from her.
Don't misunderstand me,
of course.
I'll always be
in Blue's confidence,
but if I had been made
for Yellow,
you wouldn't
see me complaining.
I do hope they appreciate
all my hard work
to preserve
the Pink Diamond legacy.
It would really make it
worth being stationed here
with these sorry excuses
for Gems.
Ohhh!
It's a shame, though.
This outpost
is so remote.
I was beginning to think
we'd been forgotten.
But we haven't!
Two Diamonds -- one day!
What an honor.
I don't think anything
could spoil this for me.
[ Nervous laughter ]
What...is...
the meaning of this?!
Why are these two
outside the containment area?!
Holly Blue,
I can explain.
No need,
your Clarity.
Not even you
could have foreseen
how incompetent
these Amethysts are.
Well, if you want something
done right,
you just do it
yourself.
You two are coming
with me!
[ Gasps ]
[ All gasp ]
Both: Garnet!
Steven,
get Greg on board!
Greg: Yes, please!
We'll handle
this noise.
[ Grunts ]
Ooh!
Together:
Ooooooh!
I've been waiting to do this
all day.
Unh!
[ Groans ]
[ Laughter ]
What are you doing?!
They're traitors!
Destroy them!
Bye!    Bye!
Bye!            Bye!
[ Smooches ]
Famethyst for life!
I'll report you
to the Diamonds!
All of you!
You'll all be shattered!
You're really gonna tell
the Diamonds
that you allowed
a band of traitorous rebels
to infiltrate
a highly secure facility
and escape from right under
your careful watch?
[ Inhales sharply ]
Doesn't sound like
a wise thing to do, Holly Blue.
[ Whirring ]
So do yourself a favor
and keep your mouth shut.
That will be all.
[ Groans ]
[ Guards cheering ]
[ Laughter ]
Thanks so much
for coming to get me.
That has to be like
the third-craziest weekend
I've ever had.
Dad, I'm really sorry
I got you into all this.
This whole thing started
'cause I wanted answers.
You don't have to be sorry
about a thing.
I hope you found
what you were looking for.
I did.
I found you.
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Oh!
Good, old natural sand!
That fancy zoo sand
was too fine for me.
Hey! Steven!
Connie!
[ Laughing ] You're back,
and you're okay!
Did you get
your ears pierced?
Oh, man, you're not gonna
believe what happened!
We went to a far-off
space station,
we made some new friends, we
warped the space-time continuum!
I'm sorry we
left you behind.
It's okay. You were really
worried about your dad.
I'm just glad
you're all back safe.
Yep -- all thanks
to this guy.
Did anything happen
while we were gone?
Uh...
Lion behaved himself,
I restocked all the cereal
and washed all the towels.
Sounds like everything
went well.
Well, there was
a little trouble...
When I got that
call from you,
I could tell you had
a lot going on.
Dad's in trouble and we need
to go into space
to get him back!
I can get there in 15.
Or actually maybe 20, 25 'cause
I might have to take the bus --
There's no time!
We're going right now.
Just protect Beach City for me
while we're gone!
You can count on me!
It was a big job
for one person,
but I felt
up to the challenge.
I made my way over
to your house,
and that's when I realized...
I wasn't alone.
[ Gasps ]
Hyah!
Uh, don't you knock?
Weirdo.
Lapis?
Peridot?
What are you doing here?
Just showing off
my old room to --
Oh, wait.
Actually, that's none
of your business!
Who is this, and what is she
doing in Steven's house?
That's Steven's third-best
friend after me and you.
Um, Lapis,
you don't remember me?
Mmm...
You almost drowned me
when you tried to steal
the world's water.
I almost drowned
a lot of people.
I'm Connie.
I'm Peridot!
And this is our pumpkin.
-[ Barks ]
-Oh! Hello!
[ Barks ]
So Steven told me you guys
retired to the country.
What brings you here?
Garnet trusted us
with a mission!
Oh, Steven
gave me one, too.
I just hope
I don't let him down.
You probably will.
That's why they put us in charge
of protecting Beach City.
But Steven
asked me to do that!
You really think
we need your help?
Wait a minute!
Maybe we do need your help.
The crystal gems have been
protecting this world
with a specialized team.
Three gems, each with their
own role, and a human!
Well, Steven's only half human,
but, hmm, close enough.
Meaning?
To do the job of
the crystal gems,
we need to do the jobs
of the crystal gems!
We four --
Four?
I'm counting Pumpkin.
[ Barks ]
We each need to pick someone
from the original team
and perform their role
in the group!
We can be exactly like them --
but better!
That sort of makes sense.
I call Garnet!
I'm obviously best suited
to being the boss.
You are very bossy.
Thank you.
Then I'll do
what Steven does.
Lapis,
you can be Amethyst.
Which one is she?
I'm joking.
Great!
You're already in character!
What about your pumpkin?
Whatever.
She can be Pearl.
[ Barks ]
New crystal gems, congregate!
That means come over here
and do a cool pose.
[ Gulls squawking ]
Hmm!
Let's see...
Nothing there.
Judging from what Steven
tells me, everything's normal!
There!
Am I doing it?
Am I as aloof and distant
as the Garnet?
You were, until you started
to ask so many questions!
[ Snickers ]
[ Barking ]
[ Horn honking ]
Man: Help!
That sounds like it's coming
from the car wash!
Go!
New crystal gems!
What seems to be the trouble
here, Beach City citizen?
It's my dad!
Some jerks have been
messing with his head!
[ Fly buzzing ]
It was funny...
till he made me
bring it here.
Can you guys
wash it off?
Oh, right!
If Mr. Universe and Steven
are in outer space then...
we should run the car wash!
Ahem.
Uh, "water" we waiting for?
Ha ha!
Good one, Steven.
Whatever you say, dudes.
Burp!
[ Barking ]
Well said, Pearl!
[ Grunting ]
What? Whoa!
Here's your vehicle --
washed and buffed!
Courtesy of
the new crystal gems!
That was cool.
Thanks!
After such a rocky start,
it finally seemed like
the new crystal gems
were coming together!
Or were we?
[ Horns honking ]
Whoa!
Looks like word got around.
Encore! Encore!
I know what everyone
is really here to see!
Beach City citizens,
witness the Garnet!
[ Grunting ]
[ Crowd oohing ]
[ Crowd ahhing ]
Amethyst,
your performance is lacking!
Mess around!
Crack some jokes!
Oh, is that what
I'm supposed to be doing?
[ All gasp ]
Lapis! Uh, the Steven
doesn't think that's funny!
[ Gurgles ]
Ha.
I can't believe this!
The only one taking
anything seriously
around here is Pumpkin!
[ Barking ]
That's right.
Pearl does like soap.
Uh, hey, you gonna bring
our car down?
Do not interrupt the Garnet!
Everyone will have a turn!
[ Murmurs ]
Oops!
Peridot, put that guy down!
No one bosses
the Garnet!
Well, Garnet wouldn't
yell at people!
I agree.
Maybe you should let someone
else play the Garnet.
Eh?
[ Crowd gasping ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Murmuring ]
No!
Amethyst,
I have the glasses!
There is no Amethyst!
Only Garnet!
What are
you guys doing?!
[ Grunting ]
Hmm!
[ Groans ]
[ Whimpers ]
Oh, no.
Gotta Steven this somehow.
Look at us!
We're all fighting
with each other!
But we all love each other.
And you all love me.
So we all have
to do this together --
for love!
Steven would have had
a better speech.
I know.
She didn't even cry.
[ Sighs ]
Connie: The wash was a wash.
And so were
the new crystal gems.
I've done a lot of thinking
about what's been going wrong
with this team-up,
and I think it's obvious now
that the problem is all of you!
Connie, you completely lack
Steven's sentimentality.
He would have had a much more
inspiring speech yesterday.
Lapis, your lack of humor has
been hurting our morale.
Maybe you should switch
with Pumpkin.
Let's make Pumpkin the Garnet.
You should be the Pearl.
I'm nothing like Pearl.
She's so uptight
and sensitive!
How dare you?!
I'm leaving!
That's so funny!
You should be Amethyst!
That's so dumb!
You should be a clod!
Oh, so now I'm a clod?
I think you're the clod.
Wow! Your Peridot impression
is lousy, too!
Will you two can it?!
That's not a very
Steven thing to say.
I don't care!
So I'm not Steven!
Maybe he's really great
at helping people
work out these arguments!
Maybe he's really patient
and caring,
even though it must be
hard for him having to be
the adult for a bunch of
super-powered children!
We're both thousands of years
older than you.
Then act like it!
Be the gems you've been
for thousands of years,
instead of playing
this silly game.
It's impossible trying
to solve problems
if we're just trying
to copy other people.
Oh, what's the point
of this?
We'll never be the crystal gems,
we're just...
the crystal temps.
But we have our own way
of doing things.
So let's go back to that,
to fix this mess we made.
You do make a good Steven.
Watch it.
Well...
if there's one thing
Peridots are good at,
it's fixing things!
I guess I could help
wash away the rubble.
And I'll help us
organize.
So here's how I think
we should start...
You sure
you wrecked anything?
The car wash
looks good as new.
Well, except, we couldn't
repair the sign.
Well, about time
I got a new one.
Guess I'll give
my neon guy a call.
Well, don't get out
your checkbook yet.
Bring it on out!
Introducing...
a new sign!
For your business!
We made it ourselves!
Look at it, it's great!
I think I love it!
Really?
That old sign was okay,
but this one's got personality!
Well, it wasn't much
of a mission,
but I guess we handled
that all right.
I knew you would.
Does that mean we can do
a victory pose?
Okay.
Together: Go, crystal temps!
[ Eerie music plays ]