♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Agh! Ohh, Pink!
I can't believe it!
You've been here all along.
Ohh. [ Sobs ]
-[ Groaning ]
-Ohh!
We can't just hand Steven
over to Blue Diamond.
She's a shatterer!
[ Sniffles ] She's not
gonna hurt him. Look at her.
[ Sobs, laughs ]
She really thinks
he's one of them.
[ Sobs loudly ]
Somebody make
Blue Diamond stop!
Are you guys okay?
It's just -- [ Sniffles ]
Blue Diamond's power.
She's obviously relieved
that Pink Diamond wasn't
shattered after all.
[ Straining ]
Hm!
How could you
do this to us, Pink?
Why did you let us think
you were shattered?
Why the strange disguise?
Why are you doing a voice?
Why didn't you say
something at the trial?!
And, Blue, can you
please stop crying?
I can't see.
[ Splash! ]
Sorry.
My mom kept it secret
from everyone.
A-hem!
Almost everyone.
What are you
talking about?
Well, apparently, Mom --
Oh, geez. You don't know
what a mom is.
Okay. Pink Diamond took the form
of Rose Quartz permanently
after faking her shatter.
Then Rose Quartz
gave up that form
to create a new life
with my dad -- me.
Rose passed her gemstone
and some of her powers on to me,
but that's all.
I -- I don't have any of
Pink or Rose's memories.
I'm sorry.
[ Whoosh! ]
Hmm. I'm sure your memories
are in there somewhere, Pink.
Actually
I go by "Steven."
Oh, stars!
How did you even survive?
We blasted the planet
and obliterated every gem
on its surface.
They weren't exactly...
obliterated.
[ Gargling ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Chomping ]
What am I looking at?
[ Screeches ]
No one should have
survived our attack.
Centipeedle's mind is broken.
I've tried to heal her,
but it didn't stick.
Heal her?
But maybe you two
can help her!
You're so much stronger than me.
And I got close.
Well, that's not something
we normally do.
This is completely
unprecedented!
But you did this to her.
You have to help her.
All of them.
Hmm. Very well. I can try.
But I make no promises.
[ Electricity buzzing ]
[ Screeches ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Electricity pulsating ]
There. Good as new.
Aaagg! Crhhhrrr!
She may be
too far gone.
Gently, Yellow.
[ Whooshing ]
[ Screeches ]
There we are.
No! Please, no! No, no.
We're all gonna be --
-Centi?
-No! Please, no!
No, no.
We're all gonna be --
No! Please.
Centi. It's okay.
It's okay.
Nephrite.
Facet 413 Cavishon 12.
-Wh-a-a-at?!
-Unbelievable.
I'm sorry for my failure
to heed my Hessonite's
evacuation orders.
My team and I tried our best to
make it out before the attack.
But -- But you're here.
It must have worked!
You finally avenged
Pink Diamond!
You destroyed Rose Quartz!
[ Screeching ]
Oh, Pink.
How many perfectly adequate
gems did you have us ruin?
Shhh. Yellow.
Pink's been punished enough.
She's been trapped here
on this awful planet
with these...
creatures.
Do it again!
It was working!
How long do you expect us
to hold her together?
I-I don't know.
Forever!
You did this,
so you have to do something!
We can only do so much.
If it was the four of us...
Oh, no.
We can't let her see this.
Who?!
Who do we need?!
What do you mean, who?
White!
-White Diamond?
-What?!
Steven, White Diamond
isn't like us.
She isn't even like them.
You have no idea
what she's capable of.
I just want to talk.
Blue: I don't think you'll
have much luck with that.
White hasn't left
Homeworld in eons.
Then we're going
to Homeworld!
In what? You and your "friends"
destroyed both our ships!
Unless -- You don't
still have yours, do you?
Steven: This place is
filled with Mom's junk,
so there's a good chance
it's buried around here.
We can split up the area like
a grid and divide the search.
It's just past
these pink pyramids!
We've got a lot
of desert to cover.
It may take a while
and be really super-hot,
but if we don't give up,
I know we can find it!
[ Electricity hums ]
Uh, Steven?
[ Gasps ]
[ Rumbling ]
Steven: Ohh.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
♪♪
You're going to do great.
Are you sure
you have everything?
Food, water.
Where's your sword?
I can't believe
I'm saying that.
It's okay, Mom. This is going
to be a diplomatic mission.
And I'll be with her
the whole time.
I know the planet.
There's an atmosphere.
She'll be able
to breathe.
[ Tinkle! ]
All right. Be careful.
Just come home safe.
Aww. Thanks, Mom!
Thanks, Dad!
I can't believe I'm finally
going to Homeworld!
There might be
more Famethysts!
Love you, Shtu-ball.
Be careful out there.
I love you, too.
I'll be back before you know it.
Lion.
Bring it in, buddy.
Garnet,
should I be worried?
Steven will be fine.
If you could water this
for me while I'm gone,
it'd be a big help.
Oh, uh, sure thing.
Don't miss me too much.
[ Chuckles ]
Hmm?
Bismuth, are you ready?
I --
[ Whirring ]
I'm not gonna join
a diamond entourage!
I know what you're doing.
I get why you gotta do it.
But I'm not gonna lay my gem
on their anvil.
Anvil?
Okay. Let me put this
in Earth terms for you.
You're about to enter
the lion's den.
Luckily,
you're a lion, too!
You gotta roar at them
in their language!
You're the one
that has to do it.
Right.
Besides, you're gonna
need me at the home base.
Someone's gotta keep an eye
on these two while you're gone.
We'll be waiting for you
when you get back.
Hm. Okay!
Let's go to Homeworld!
-Yeah!
[ Sarcastically ]
Fantastic.
[ Whirring ]
It's a good look
for you, Steven.
Thank you.
Oh, it's been so long
since we've been together
in Pink's ship.
[ Sobs ]
Please, Blue.
If we could continue?
[ Sniffles ]
Yes. Of course.
For launching,
just get a running start.
Hm!
♪♪
You got this, Steven!
Hold on!
I'm taking off!
♪♪
I'll bet when Mom took off,
it was pretty graceful, huh?
No. Not really.
S-Should I have brought
a gift for White Diamond?
We are dropping in
unexpectedly,
and I-I want to make
a good first impression.
Her help will mean everything
for the corrupted gems.
-Steven.
-Hmf!
Good impression?
We'll be lucky if she ever
speaks to us again after this.
-But --
-The thing is...
White can be difficult.
When we show up
in this ship,
it will be irrefutable
that the last 6,000 years
are now the biggest
galactic embarrassment
that's ever happened.
And we're the ones
to blame.
If you don't want to
be in a bubble for the
next few millennia,
I suggest you let me
do the talking.
[ Clears throat ]
We're here.
[ Whirring ]
[ Yawns ] Really?
Ugh! What...gives?
[ Whirring ]
Steven: Homeworld.
♪♪
Everyone, wait here.
Blue and I will return for you
once White's temper has cooled.
Which might take a while.
-But --
-Wait. That sound.
[ Indistinct cheering ]
[ Cheering continues ]
Whoa!
Maybe things won't be so bad.
[ Cheering stops abruptly ]
[ Whirring ]
-[ Gasps ]
-It's White's Pearl.
Pink Diamond,
your presence is required.
Come on, Blue.
Only Pink Diamond's
presence is necessary.
Uh, maybe we could --
[ Gasps ]
-Wait! Steven!
-Steven!
[ Gasps ]
White: Pink!
There you are.
Hello, Starlight. You certainly
gave everyone a scare.
They're all just thrilled
to see you safe and sound.
Um, hi? I --
As for this latest
little game of yours,
thank the stars it's over.
Did you have fun?
Did you get everything
out of your system?
-I --
-Good, good.
Everyone is so relieved.
Welcome home, Pink.
♪♪
Wh-- Wait! Hold on!
♪ I always thought
I might be bad ♪
♪ Now I'm sure that it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause I think
you're so good ♪
♪ And I'm nothing like you ♪