Hi, guys!
Welcome to "Steven Song Time."
Things have been
pretty crazy lately,
and I've got a lot of feelings
that are hard to talk about,
so I put them in a song.
Oh, and I'll put up guitar tabs
so you can learn to play along
if you like.
These are the strings
in standard tuning,
and the dots
are for your fingers.
Uh, okay, here goes.
The song is
"Still Not Giving Up."
[ Rock music plays ]
♪ Hey, there, have you heard
about the infamous gem war? ♪
♪ Well, it all started
long before I was born ♪
♪ Thousands of years of fighting
to protect the human race ♪
♪ It's been pretty tough
keeping up the pace ♪
♪ I sure have made my fair share
of mistakes ♪
♪ I didn't know that Rose Quartz
was such a big deal ♪
♪ There are some wounds that
even healing powers can't heal ♪
♪ Oh, I feel like I messed up ♪
♪ This magical destiny really
kicked me in the butt ♪
♪ We've had some good times
and some pretty bad luck ♪
♪ But we're still
in this together ♪
♪ And we're still not
giving up ♪
♪ We're still not giving up ♪
♪ I'm still not giving up ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da ♪
Thanks for listening.
If you've been having some
difficult feelings lately,
try writing a song about them.
I'd love to hear it.
Okay. I love you. Bye.