♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Ruby.
Oh boy.
So she's all the way out here.
After everything sapphire said,
she must be heartbroken.
H-hey guys!
Steven?!
How'd you find me?
We sensed you.
We heard you ordered pizza.
Ruby was just telling me about
your mom.
Oh.
Are you okay?
Well, I fell in love with
Rose Quartz
and she fell in love with
Mr. Universe.
Sure she never told me she used
to be pink diamond, but...
[ Chuckles ] I never told her I
used to be Gregory Demayo.
So, how're you holding up, Ruby?
I'm okay.
Want a slice?
Uh...Thank you...
Wait, really?
You seemed so sad before!
Yeah, but me and Greg
talked it out.
I'm fine now.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Sapphire was kinda right
about everything.
We really did stay Garnet
because Rose told us we were...
The...answer.
It's my first time really
thinking about it.
thinking about...Me!
What do you mean?
Back when I emerged,
the first thing I did was get
crammed together
with a bunch of other Rubies,
then...
I was with Sapphire
all the time.
I was always checking in
with someone,
but now I can go wherever
the wind takes me!
I'm up here, eating pizza,
reading comics!
I dunno if Sapphire wants to
read comics!
I don't have to know!
The rest of my life
could be like this!
I don't have to be Garnet --
I could be on my own!
Sure!
I guess...
Wha-a-a-a-at?!
B-b-b-but but you guys
love each other!
You're my favorite couple!
Y-you're like sugar and flour!
I love eating them separately
but I still want cake!
I'm sure Sapphire would want--
I'm not fussed about what
Sapphire wants.
I'm seeing my own future now,
and it's
nothin' but Ruby!
[ Whimpering ]
Relax, kiddo.
This could be what she needs.
But Dad! What if they never
form Garnet again?!
We gotta get 'em back together!
Whoa!
Th-that's not our call to make!
Ruby's gotta want that
for herself.
If it's not what Ruby wants,
then it's not what Garnet
wants, right?
Mmm...I guess so...
So...where you going after this,
dude?
You just gonna stay out here?
I wanna live free!
One with the wilderness!
Facing danger at every turn!
Not needin' nothin' or nobody
to get me by!
Just like...this guy!
[ Dolphin squeaks ]
Hmm, do you mean...something
like this?
[ Whiplash ]
♪♪
[ Gasp ]
That's even better!
The open plain!
That's where I wanna go!
I think I know just the place.
I'll get you there!
Thank you!
Hup!
All right, all right...
I-if this is how it's gotta
be...
I'll support Ruby in her quest
for emotional growth.
Yeehaw! Pa pow!
Pa pow!
Hup!
Bang bang bang!!
Woo-hoo!
[ Engine sputtering ]
[ Brakes screeching ]
Y'all ready to Wild West it up?
[ Western Music ]
[ Whiplash crack ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Western guitar music ]
Here I am.
On the open range.
At least you understand me,
Horsey.
Oh!
Ruby, you need a steed!
I'm always down for a little...
horsin' around...
[ Grunting ]
[ Whinnying ]
Giddyup.
[ Eagle call ]
[ Horse clops ]
How's it goin, Ruby?
Feel like a real cowboy now?
Yep.
I sure reckon I do.
Sorry I gotta be a yellow belly
about this,
but we don't even have a map.
I think we're just gonna
get ourselves lost.
[ Snorts ]
I already am lost.
That's why I came out here...
to find myself.
It's a dead end.
This is what I mean.
What's behind this brush?
I don't know! Sapphire ain't
here to predict for me.
This is my chance to find out
for myself!
Hup!
Aaahhh!
Oh jiminy!
Ruby?!
[ Panting ]
Wh--
Whoa!
I had no idea this ravine
was here!
Huh!
I almost fell down there...
and it was all my choice!
Yee haw!
Independence!
[ Laughing & cheering ]
♪♪
♪ This ol' Ruby rider ♪
♪ Is Ruby ridin' alone ♪
♪ She's a sturdy ♪
♪ Solitary stone ♪
♪ This ol' Ruby rider ♪
♪ Not a fusion no more ♪
♪ Now the dirt and the dust ♪
♪ And the danger
is my new home ♪
♪♪
♪ I used to think I ♪
♪ Would always be
by your side ♪
♪ But lately you've been
rather cold ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ One look in your eye ♪
♪ Could make an honest gem cry ♪
♪ But Ruby Rider don't need
no one to hold ♪
[ Whistling ]
Wow, Ruby's really
getting into this.
Seriously! I just taught her how
to play guitar
like ten minutes ago!
No, Dad, I-I mean the whole
"cowboy being alone" thing.
I've never seen her
like this before.
She seems really...happy.
♪♪
♪ This ol' Ruby rider ♪
♪ Is Ruby ridin' alone ♪
♪ She's a sturdy ♪
♪ Solitary stone ♪
♪♪
Yeehaw.
[ snoring ]
[ Snoring whinny ]
Hey... Ruby!
Hm?
Y'know...
I got-really scared when you
said you didn't wanna fuse with
Sapphire anymore.
I felt like...
I was losing someone
I cared about,
but I saw how much fun you were
having today.
All this buckerooing
really suits you.
I'm sorry I tried to push you
back into being Garnet.
It's...not true.
Huh?
That stuff I sang about...
It's not true!
W-w-what?!
I mean...I did have a lot
of fun today.
I loved it!
But...the whole time I...
[ Sighs ]
I kept thinking about
how much more fun I'd have if
I were with her.
Sapphire was always
there with me.
I'd feel her smile...
just like...it was mine...
It's so lonely now.
[ Groans ]
That's lame, right?!
I came here to be my own gem,
but I'm still thinking about
what she'd like,
what she'd want,
all the time!
Turns out...
I'm no good at
not needin' nobody.
C'mon, that's not lame!
You led us on a frontier
adventure!
You're still the same Ruby who
did all that stuff,
even if you're thinking
of someone.
Look at our friend
Lonesome Lasso.
They call him that
'cause he's lonesome!
"I miss Sally May!"
He's still a rootin' tootin'
cowboy blazin' his own trails.
But...he loves someone too.
Well, if I'm makin
my own decisions,
then I'll decide
I wanna be with Sapphire.
[ Sighs ]
I mean, I gotta ask her first.
I just don't want it to feel
like we're going back to
how things used to be --
back when...
someone else
told us to be together.
I want it to feel different.
Wait a sec!
What do you think of this?!
[ Gasp ]
[ Gulls crying ]
[ Door creaks ]
[ Gasp ]
Steven!
Did you find Ruby?!
She's outside.
She's got something
to say to you.
♪♪
Ruby!
Ruby, I'm so sorry!!
I should've never said those
awful things to you,
that we didn't
matter anymore.
I shouldn't've pushed you away
like that.
I was wrong!
♪♪
Pa-tooey.
Nah..you were right.
Hup!
[ Whinnies ]
Someone else told us
we were the answer.
But...I don't believe
that anymore.
At least...
not till I hear it from you.
♪♪
Sapphire...
Will you marry me?!
What?!
(Laughing) Marry you?!
Yeah! This way we can be
together even when we're apart!
This time, being Garnet
will be our decision!
Whaddaya say?!
Of course!
Yeehaw!!
Mmnngg.
I've been waiting to kiss
your cute face!
Woo!
Hahahaha!
Aaaaaah!!
Psst.
It's me.
I'm a horse.
♪♪
[ Laughing ]
Steven: This is just to
give you some ideas.
Ruby said she wanted your
reunion as Garnet to be special.
[Sighs] And there's nothing
more special and romantic
than a beautiful wedding.
It's like they say,
if you wanna drink the cow,
you gotta put a ring on it.
But, Sweetums,
who says that?
Let's take a look at printing
styles for your invitations.
Would it be cool
if we got flames on it?
Oh! And...
some dolphins.
Yeah! Dolphins and flames!
I think I've got exactly what
you're looking for on page 135.
How long did it take you
to put this together?
My entire life.
This is gonna be
the best wedding ever!
This folding bone
is so nice!
Who knew that planning
a wedding could be so fun?
I did!
Time to sign.
Here you go, Peri.
Ugh!
We've been stuffing
these envelopes all day!
How many does that make?
Liiii!
That makes... 10!
Oh...just...10. Hmm.
[ Birds squawking ]
[ Humming ]
Hyuh! [ Chuckles ]
So, my dad will finish
playing the music,
and then, next,
you'll do the "I do"s
and then I'll say,
"I now pronounce you Garnet"!
And then you fuse!
Everyone'll cheer!
Everyone...who survived.
-Huh?
-Oh, it's just...
there are so many old friends
who won't be able to come.
All the Crystal Gems
who are corrupted
and bubbled
in the basement.
Maybe we could bring
the bubbles up here?
No, no.
It's not safe.
We can't risk them
getting out.
Hmm.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
Ugh.
Uhh.
Hmm? I'm back?
[ Nervously ] Hey, Bismuth.
Long time no see.
Rose. I mean, Steven!
Ohh, there's
a third option now.
Well,
why would you let me out?
I just tried to shatter you.
You know how you fought Mom
because her whole war strategy
didn't make any sense?
Well, you were right!
[ Gasps ]
W-What's going on?
Did Rose do this?
Did she bubble everyone
who disagreed with her?!
Huh? Oh, no! No!
It's not like that.
Tigers Eye!
[ Gasps ]
Little Larimar!
Beryl, Serpentine,
and, ohh, Biggs!
Biggs was beloved
by everyone!
Bismuth, wait!
I got ya, buddy.
Bismuth!
You don't understand!
Come on, Biggs,
help me free the othe--
Biggs?
[ Roaring ]
Bismuth!
[ Grunting ]
I'm sorry, Bismuth!
This is not the Biggs
you knew before.
Steven --
I know
we had our differences,
but so much has changed,
and I just wanted to tell you --
[ Grunting ]
Aah!
Ah! Bismuth!
Biggs. [ Grunting ]
[ Grunting ]
Only a Diamond could
do damage like this.
It was Pink, wasn't it?
And why didn't Rose
stop her?!
Because they were
the same person.
What?
And that's
the whole story.
Hmm.
Uh, are you okay?
Mm. Yeah.
Hang on a sec.
Uh, Bismuth?
[ Muffled screaming ]
Oh, my gosh!
It all makes sense now!
Pretty wild, right?
[ Sighs ]
Oh, that's nice.
Steven, come here and join me.
The lava's great.
I would,
but I'm not lava proof.
[ Chuckles ]
Eesh.
I was so excited to show
Rose the Breaking Point.
Can you imagine?
"Hey, Rose! Check out
this cool weapon I made!
I'm gonna shatter you
with it!"
[ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
I really thought all of
our problems would disappear
if we could just
shatter a Diamond.
Guess she ended up
taking my advice.
Um, sorry
about all this.
[ Sighs ]
Thanks...for talking to me.
Wow, you took that
pretty well.
Way better than
Garnet did.
-How so?
-She unfused over it.
What?! Noooo!
They're my favorite couple!
Don't worry,
they're back together,
but they haven't
fused yet.
Huh?
That's actually why
I came down here to begin with.
I wanted to invite you
to Garnet's wedding!
Garnet's wedding, huh?
Yeah. It would be great
if you could attend.
Yeah...okay.
I don't have any plans,
so I guess I can come.
Yay! This is gonna be
so much fun!
Pfft! Oh, yeah.
No question this is gonna be
the best wedding ever!
Pfft! [ Chuckles ]
So, what's a wedding?
Okay, so we're getting
everything ready for tomorrow.
We'll have a hot dog grill
going on out front,
and the chairs and canopy
are all set up.
Probably should head
out there and say hi.
Uh, Steven?
I don't wanna
ruin the surprise.
What surprise?
You!
They don't know I'm coming?
Wait. I can't do this.
You're right,
you gotta have a gift.
We have a wedding registry.
Do you wanna pick
something from...here?
What? No.
I mean...
[ Sighs ]
What am I gonna say to 'em?
You could do one of your
signature catch phrases.
Like...
"Let's get down to Bismuth!"
[business]
Or, "Anybody wanna start
a small Bismuth?"
[business]
Oh, oh! How about...
"Did you Bis-muth me?"
[miss]
[ Twinkle! ]
Anyway, it's not gonna
matter what you say.
They'll be so glad
you're here.
Just be ready
for my signal.
Ahh, this is gonna
be great!
They're gonna want you
to be maid of honor.
[ Door creaks open ]
A-Attention, everyone.
Please gather 'round.
[ Clears throat ]
I'd like to propose a toast
to Ruby and Sapphire!
Now, we all know you guys
have been runnin' a little
[Chuckles]
hot and cold lately.
[ Laughter ]
We are all excited to see
you two fuse back together
and achieve lifelong,
room-temperature happiness.
All of us, includiiiing...
Pearl!   Pearl!
Pearl!          Pearl!
Mm-hmm.
Yes. And Pearl.
All of us, including...
Uh, Steven, can I drink
this or what?
I'll be right back. And make
sure those cans don't drop.
Bismuth.
Didn't you see my...
signal?
♪♪
Bismuth?
Oh, there you are.
What happened out there?
I-I'm sure if we hurry back,
we can still surprise them.
They're gonna be
so happy to see you.
If they wanted
to see me so much,
they coulda let me out
themselves, but they didn't.
Of course they didn't.
I attacked their leader.
They're not gonna side
with Rose anymore. Not after --
I'm not talking about Rose.
I'm talking about you!
But I'm not the leader.
Garnet's the leader.
And where's Garnet?
She'll be back.
That's the whole point.
It's a big
Crystal Gem wedding.
We should all be there
together.
Why?!
Why are the Crystal Gems
still together
after finding out that
everything was a sham?!
Somebody's making them
believe in the future,
and it's you!
You seriously think
they're gonna want me around
when the last thing I did
was try to shatter you?!
You told them everything,
and they made their choice.
They want me in a bubble,
and you out there.
But, Bismuth...
You say they want me
to be made of honor?
Well, I am.
I'm made of the most
solid, flexible,
diamagnetic stuff there is,
and I'm not as dense
as you might think.
I've got enough self-respect
in this Gem to accept
that they don't want me
on their team anymore.
[ Scoffs ] I blew it.
Everything was different,
and I didn't believe it.
Everything is different!
We had a fight,
so we can make up, right?
If they didn't let you out
because they care about me,
then they're gonna care that
I want you back on the team!
Huh?
I want you back on the team.
Forget the surprise.
If we show up together,
they're all gonna know
that everything's okay.
[ Chuckles ]
Spoken like a leader.
No. Spoken like a friend.
[ Zap! ]
Hey, everyone!
Did you guys...
Bis-muth me?
[miss]
Ha! I win!
Also, less importantly,
who are you?
I invited Bismuth!
I hope that's cool.
Bismuth!
[ Chuckling ]
Whoa! Sapphire!
-Bismuth!
-Bismuth! [ Laughs ]
You wouldn't believe what
we've all been through.
I'm so sorry.
We should've...
Look, I'm right there with you.
Steven filled me in.
[ Chuckles ]
So, is anyone
gonna introduce me?
Let's give 'em some space.
Oh, Ruby! Sapphire!
I heard you're supposed to
bring gifts to these things...
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
And these aren't weapons,
but Steven seemed to think
they'd come in handy.
We love them!   We love them!
♪♪