♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Steven:
Good old beach city,
but so much
has changed lately.
I guess after
all those abductions,
everything couldn't
just return to normal.
With Sadie rocking out
and Lars in space,
I can't even enjoy
my regular snack at
the Big Donut.
What am I gonna do
for breakfast now?!
[ Groans ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
Wait a minute.
Big Donut is still open?
[ Gasps ]
Hello.
Welcome to the Big Donut.
Garnet?
I have so many questions.
Just one moment.
You'll have to wait
your turn.
[ Soft music plays ]
[ Ka-ching! ]
♪♪
[ Doorbell rings ]
Welcome to the Big Donut.
Tell me
how I may serve you.
I never thought
I'd see you working here.
Have we fallen
on hard times?
Oh, Steven.
This isn't about
making ends meet.
This is about being random.
Are you serious?
Oh, yes.
I...don't understand.
♪♪
My future vision allows me
to see down the rivers
of possibility,
granting me insight
into the possible realities
our actions move us towards.
But that doesn't mean
I can predict everything.
What I'm interested in
are these extremely
unlikely realities,
so disconnected from
the natural course of events
that I can't detect them.
When we act
in unnatural ways,
we create
new, unforeseen paths,
and arrive at these pools
of improbability.
Oh, so you want to do stuff
you usually don't
just to see what happens?
I didn't foresee
you understanding that.
So, are we gonna
clean up that coffee?
That's what
we'd normally do.
Let's see what happens
to the world
when we don't.
♪♪
[ Coffee drips ]
We are now dwelling
in a totally new pool
of improbability.
My future vision
is useless here.
I'm scared...
but intrigued.
That's the spirit!
Let's get
even more intriguing!
I quit!
Come, Steven!
[ Soft music plays ]
So, what now?
Hmm...
Instead of selling food,
let's order some.
Like what?
Let's do...pizza.
Now you're talking
my language!
Ordering now.
[ Phone ringing ]
Fish Stew Pizza.
Uh, I want to order
a pizza.
10 pizzas!
No, 20 pizzas!
Toppings?
Um...
Surprise me.
Now you're getting it!
I guess deliver it
to the Temple.
No...
That's just what
they'll be expecting.
Go weirder!
Deliver it to the ocean.
No, no, no!
To Kansas!
No, to the moon!
I don't think that's
within our delivery radius.
Remember.
Improbable, not impossible.
Where's the last place
they'd expect
to deliver a pizza?
Oh! Deliver it to...
Fish Stew Pizza.
So, like,
this is for pick-up?
Now think, Steven,
about what you typically do
when you obtain pizza.
Hmm...
Eat it?
In this timeline,
we do the opposite of that.
Hey, you!
Have a pizza!
[ Grunts ]
Hey, thanks!
♪♪
[ Seagulls squawking ]
One more pizza
to deliver.
Hey, Vidalia's house
is around here.
Let's bring her
the last pie.
Now, that would be nice.
She must be upset
that her son
was taken into space
by those Homeworld gems.
You mean Onion?
He isn't in space.
He's right over there.
Sorry, I -- I must be thinking
of a different timeline.
Okay...
Well, I'm sure Vidalia
would still like some pizza
even if her kid
is still on Earth.
Let's go swing by.
[ Knock on door ]
Mother Onion! Open up!
Vidalia: In the garage!
♪♪
Get excited for pizza!
We got pepper flakes,
and we're not afraid
to use 'em!
Ahh! Wait a minute.
Steven?
What are you guys
doing here?
Trying to scare me
to death?
Oh, sorry.
We were just trying
to bring you a pizza
in the most unlikely way
possible.
Want a slice?
Sure,
I could use a break.
I've been working on
this still life
of a stepstool,
but I just don't feel
inspired.
♪♪
Paint me
like one of your Amethysts.
Paint me, too!
So you wanna be my muse,
eh?
If it's not
too much trouble.
I promise to be
very inspiring.
Hmm...
Yeah, I think this is just
what I needed.
Strike a pose!
It's struck.
Okay, don't move.
I need to capture
your essence.
♪♪
[ Groaning ]
Garnet?
How long do you see me
holding still?
Who knows?
The odds of us being here
are so slim,
I can't even --
[ Clanging in distance ]
Uh, Garnet?
♪♪
Steven, look.
Ba-ba-b-b--
baby kitten?
Is it possible
that we chase that sweet cat?
It -- it's up to you,
Steven.
Yes?
Don't ask me.
Tell me.
Yes!
Whoa!
Huh?
♪♪
Sorry, Vidalia!
Maybe next time!
But wait!
Your essence!
♪♪
That's one fast kitten.
You think
we can catch it?
If we don't
lose sight of it.
♪♪
[ Kittens meowing ]
Steven: Aww...
There's more of them.
[ Meowing continues ]
Aww,
and they have no food.
Aww, and they have no one
to take care of them!
Garnet, we got to help
these kittens.
Look at you!
You're just babies.
Who knows what would've
happened to them
if we didn't find them?
Everything's gonna be
just fine.
We've got you.
[ Meowing continues ]
Here's the last one.
Or -- wait.
All right.
I think we got to stop
being random
and figure out what we can do
for these kittens.
Garnet, can you use
your future vision?
What should we do next?
Garnet?
There's so many...cats.
So many possibilities.
It's too much?
Okay,
can you focus on one?
What's this one's future?
I...
I don't know!
I don't know anything
anymore!
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Are you okay?
Steven, lately,
I've felt so lost.
Don't worry.
I remember the way
back to town.
Oh, it's not just that.
It's you.
You've made so many decisions
I didn't expect --
giving yourself
up to Homeworld,
coming back
through Lion's mane.
The future that you created
was so improbable
that I didn't see it
coming at all,
and now I can't understand
where this timeline is going.
We're on the outskirts
of the possible,
following trickles
to who knows where.
Everyone's looking to me
for answers.
I can't stand it!
It's so hard for me
to just exist
in the first place,
Steven.
I want to love
being alive.
I want to love that there are
so many possibilities,
but I'm the one
with this ability,
so I've got to be our guide.
I thought, if I could use
my future vision
to jump
into improbable futures,
I could get out ahead of
the next big, unexpected change,
but I don't know
what I'm doing here!
I can't tell
what's probable anymore!
Anything could happen!
Anything could happen
to these cats!
[ Kittens meowing ]
That's true,
but maybe instead of
thinking of all the things
that could happen,
let's just pick the thing
we want to happen
and do that.
So, what do you want
to happen next?
I want to get these cats
out of the rain.
♪♪
And then what?
Okay, sounds good.
Thank you so much.
Great news.
The shelter
has a foster program.
They said they can pick up
the cats tomorrow.
Thank goodness.
Whew. Glad to hear it!
How are you little guys
holding up?
Anyone need to use
the bathroom?
Make a phone call?
[ Laughs ]
You guys are gonna be
just fine.
I think I get it.
Hm?
Why my future vision
has been so off.
I have to change the way
I think about you.
What?
I've been looking
into probable futures
where you act
like a child.
I keep expecting you
to run from responsibility
and to turn to me for help,
but you don't do that
anymore.
Those futures
aren't probable at all.
There's nothing wrong
with this timeline or
my future vision.
I just need to factor in
that you've grown up.
[ Laughs ]
I guess I have,
but it's only because I'm trying
to be more like you.
You always know
what to do.
Not always.
Okay, most of the time.
I want to adopt this one.
There's something about her.
Really?
Is that
a probable future?
It is now.
Besides, I've missed having
someone cute and vulnerable
to take care of.
I think I'll call her
"Steven."
Isn't that gonna
get confusing?
All right, then.
Cat Steven.
Oh, my gosh! Wow!
Oh, okay.
This is the best!
What,
you're adopting one?
Too bad I couldn't get her
in your portrait,
which I managed to finish,
by the way.
[ Gasps ] Really?
What about our essence?
Well, I fudged it,
but I think I got it.
[ Both gasp ]
[ Waves crashing ]
[ Kitten purring ]
♪♪
Lars: Captain's log --
I think it's Friday.
I've ordered Rhodonite to do
a spectral scan of the system.
Hopefully, one of
these asteroids
has the Flotanium deposits
we need to get our
warp engines back online.
Hmm.
[ Grunts ]
What now, Steven?
A letter?
Steven: "Dear Lars, how's space?
Is it still big?
You don't have to
answer that right now.
This is a letter.
Since you're away from home,
I thought I'd fill you in
on what's been going
on at Beach City.
Everyone misses you so much.
Since Sadie is busy
with the band,
no one is around
to open up the Big Donut."
[ Sighs ]
Oh, come on.
Are they still not open?
Ugh.
I know Sadie quit a while ago,
but why the heck isn't Lars
here to pick up the slack?
Uh, Ronaldo,
Lars is in space.
[ Laughs ]
Good one, Steven.
I needed that.
You're serious?
Don't you remember when everyone
in town was abducted by Gems?
Mayor Dewey had to give
all those speeches about it.
Do you believe everything
the government tells you?
I'm the one who
told the government.
Wait, what?
So that means...
Mm-hmm.
So Lars
is really in space?
Mm-hmm.
Is he in danger?
Surrounded by aliens?
All of the above.
This is a nightmare.
I'm the one who should
be in space!
Why does Lars get to be whisked
away into the infinite cosmos
on an adventure
of a lifetime?
It's so ironic
it hurts my soul.
[ Sobbing ]
There, there.
Morning, Universe.
Oh, good morning.
Still not open, huh?
I guess me and the Big Donut
have a lot in common now.
We're both empty inside.
Steven: "As far
as local politics,
Mayor Dewey
isn't mayor anymore.
There was an election
and Nanefua
won with her platform
of working together."
Nanefua: So we are all
in agreement, yes?
In the event of a Gem-related
emergency,
everyone should go to
the newly-designated shelters.
Me and Garnet can take
care of food rations.
Anyone know a good,
non-perishable brand of chaps?
You can also put some pizza
ingredients on ice just in case.
That's a great idea, Garnet.
We can ask all the local
restaurants to pitch in food
in case we have
to hide for awhile.
These all seem like
great plans,
but how are you going
to get in contact
with everyone when
there is an emergency?
This may be a small town,
but it's a big small town.
Oh, Mayor Gunga, I could
drive you around
while you use the loudspeaker
to spread the word through town.
Cheese on bread!
That's a good idea.
While Jenny does that, I can
take to the boardwalk on foot
and let all the businesses
know what's up.
And as soon as we know
of any impending danger,
I'll give everyone a call
on my cellular phone.
It might be easier if you
just sent out a mass text.
What number do I call
for mass text?
Pearl, is this your
first cell phone?
Maybe.
Is there anything else we can do
to beef up the town's security?
It would be nice if we could
have some kind of lookout.
Maybe I'll pick up one of
the high-powered telescopes
for the lighthouse
or something.
I volunteer!
I love looking out.
If I can't be in space,
then I can at least look at it.
Nanefua:
This is beautiful.
Ronaldo, Greg,
you're on lookout duty.
Kiki, Pearl, you are
in charge of communication.
Steven, Garnet,
you call for rations.
And Jenny and I will spread
the word about the plan.
Now everyone is helping
to make our town safe.
Everyone except me.
Aww.
Oh, you made
things awkward.
Steven: "Sadie Killer and the
Suspects are still going strong.
They're gearing up for a huge
show right here in Beach City.
I hope you can make it back
in time to see them play."
And just as the chorus
is finishing up,
I'll grab this fake
but very realistic chainsaw,
and then Steven will hit me
with the lights,
and we'll all scream.
Aah.            Aah.
And then I'll come out.
Oogity boogity.
I don't think
you get it, Dad.
We're going for scary scary,
not ha-ha scary.
Oh. All right.
I just wanted to help.
Did you cut holes
in my bedsheets?
Steven: "Jamie the mailman has
been making a lot of progress
establishing
a local theater scene.
He's done a bunch
of one-man shows
and even started
teaching improv."
People of Beach City, are you
ready to laugh your butts off?
I am!
We got a killer lineup
for you tonight,
so please welcome
the Beach City Laugh Guards.
Whoo!
Yeah!
Now all we need to get started
is a single word
from the audience.
Pearl: Steven!
We do a scene
about Steven every week.
Well, I think
those scenes are good.
Uh, spaghetti!
No. No. Uh, car.
No. That's not good.
Oh, how about plumber?
I heard "plumber."
And now the Beach City Laugh
Guards will perform a completely
improvised scene based
on the word plumber.
No.
Do Steven!
Wait, cats!
And no more suggestions
for the rest of the show.
Thanks for coming out
on such short notice.
My sink is clogged.
Well, looks like we're going
to need one of these.
[ Steven laughs ]
No, no, no. Cut. Stop.
Notes -- Barb, love how you
set up the scene.
Amethyst, you don't have
to "become" a plunger.
Just pretend to have one.
Observe and learn.
Ah...
Ooh.
Uh...
What?
Wow.
That's way too confusing.
You could be holding anything.
I'm holding a plunger.
Pearl: Oh.
I thought you were holding a
long, skinny submarine sandwich.
Steven: Pearl!
Be nice.
It's obviously
much more clear
if you can see
the actual plunger.
She's got a point,
there, dude.
[ Laughs ] Looks like
I improved improv.
Dewey: Did I miss my cue?
Oh.
Whatever.
Hello, ladies.
It's me, the waiter
in this restaurant.
Can I offer you some more worms?
Blackout.
It was better
than last week.
Steven: "Anyways,
my dad is still rich
even after buying
that telescope,
so he's been trying out
rich people sports.
He an Garnet have been playing
tennis on the weekends."
[ Panting ]
Garnet, this is a little
intense for a warm-up.
Maybe we could try
a light volley?
This is light.
Being rich
has made you week.
Oh, hey, tennis.
Room for one m-- Ow!
Steven: "In other
sports-related news,
Beach City Underground Wrestling
has been intense lately.
The Marmalade Boys
fought each other in,
you guessed it, marmalade.
The crowd was eating it up,
but not literally because
that would be gross.
Concrete Heat faced off
against the Wolf of Wall Street
inside a steel cage,
and the Good-Looking Gang
finally lost the Tag-Team Title
to the Sea Wasp
and Shark-o-mania.
I know you don't
need to eat anymore,
but I thought you'd
still be interested
in the local french fry scene
in Beach City.
Peedee started his
very own food truck.
He's not old enough
to drive yet, though,
so it's kind of just
another fry stand."
Hey, Steven.
What will it be?
What have you got?
Well, I deal exclusively
in tater tots now.
That's great, Peedee.
Can I get the bits?
Uh, why don't you
try the tots?
They're the fry
of the future.
Do the tots have bits?
[ Sighs ]
I'll get you the bits.
I like your super-cool truck,
Peedee.
I love the giant potato
on the top.
Oh, thanks. It actually used
to be the Mayor Mobile.
I just painted over
Mayor Dewey's head.
It's a good thing that his head
was so big and lumpy.
Yeah.
The new city board practically
just gave it to me, too.
It's like they wanted nothing
to do with it anymore.
Everything has been
pretty great for me
since Nanefua became mayor.
Oh, no.
All right.
I got the bits.
Steven?
[ Sighs ]
Mayor Dewey, wait!
You know, Universe,
seeing my old Mayor Mobile
turned into a giant potato
made me realize that nothing
is like it used to be.
My old life, my old town,
my old citizens,
they've all changed.
They've all outgrown me,
I suppose.
Well, of course
everyone is changing.
Nothing can stay
the same forever.
You know what I miss the most
about being the mayor?
The little things, getting
dressed and ready for work,
walking down the boardwalk
seeing everyone's
smiling faces, yes.
Knowing I had a place
in this town.
I used to look forward
to it every day,
just like the people
of this town
used to look forward
to their morning donut.
I guess these days no one
gets what they want.
Wait a second.
I have an idea.
"And so Mayor Dewey started
working at the Big Donut.
It seemed as if
the entire town showed up
for the grand reopening.
The whole thing filled Mr. Dewey
with a new sense of purpose.
He's really changing
things up, too.
Well, not really,
but he is naming
all the donuts after himself."
Next in line, please.
I'll have a regular glazed.
One Classic Dewey
coming up.
And how about a freshly fried
Dewey Roll on the house?
Take it easy, Billy.
You're going to go
out of business.
Ha ha!
You're cute.
Steven: "But there is one donut
that's not named after Dewey.
He let me name
a donut after you.
It's a pink donut
with pink sprinkles.
I call it the Pink Lars.
Even though you're in space,
there's still a part of you here
in sweet, delicious donut form.
You got to try one
when you get back.
Anyway, hope this letter
finds you in good spirits.
Love, Steven."
I appreciate the letter,
but why did you write this
if you were just going to tell
me everything in person anyway?
Sometimes
it's nice to be read to.
You realize I don't know who
half of these people are, right?
Like, who the heck is Peridot?
Someone who misses you
every day, I think.
You know what?
You haven't met before.
I'll have to introduce you
when you get back to Earth.
Huh.
Thanks for the letter, Steven.
♪♪