Come on, Twilight. You can do it.
Okay. Here goes...
HA-HA! You did it!
Growing magic. That's number 25.
Twenty five different types of tricks and counting.
And I think this is the best trick so far.
Hello, Rarity.
What's that? Oh, it's the nothing.
Just my awesome mustache.
Sorry, Romeo. As attractive and enticing as you
look, it's just for practice and it's gotta go.
Wait!
Rats.
Twenty five, Twilight! Twenty five
different kinds of tricks and counting.
I though unicorns are only supposed to have
a little magic that matches their special talents.
True. For ponies whose talents are
for things like cooking or singing or math.
But what if the unicorn's
special talent *is* magic?
Like you, Twilight. And you know a ton of magic.
Oh, Spike, stop. I'm sure there are
lots of ponies right here in Ponyville...
...that know just as much magic as me.
Are you kidding?
I don't think there's another unicorn in all
of Equestria with your kind of ability, Twilight.
Gangway! Coming through!
Snips... Snails... Wh-What's going on?
Why, haven't you heard?
There is a new unicorn in town!
Yeah! They say that she's got more magical
powers than any other unicorn ever.
Really?
Oh, no way. That honor goes to Twilight here.
Where is this unicorn?
Oh, she's in the town square. Come on!
Yeah! Come on!
Come on, come all!
Come and witness the amazing magic...
★☆★ ...of the Great and Powerful Trixie! ★☆★
Watch in awe as the Great and Powerful Trixie...
...performs the most
spectacular feats of magic...
★☆★ ...ever witnessed by pony eyes! ★☆★
My, my, my. What boasting.
Come on! Nopony's as magical as Twi...
Twi... Twi...
Oh... H-Hey, Rarity, I...
Mustache!
There's nothing wrong with
being talented, is there?
Nothin' at all.
'cept when someone goes around showin' it off
like a schoolfilly with fancy new ribbons.
Just because one has the ability
to perform lots of magic...
...does not make one better than the rest of us.
Especially when you got me around
being better than the rest of us.
I mean... Yeah! Uh, Magic Shmagic! Boo!
Well, well, well.
It seems we have some
NEIGH-sayers in the audience.
Who is so ignorant as
to challenge the magical ability...
★☆★ ...of the Great and Powerful Trixie?! ★☆★
Do they not know that they're in the presence
of the most magical unicorn in all of Equestria?!
Just who does she think she is?
Yeah! Since we all know that Twilight here is...
Spike! Shhh...
What? What's wrong?
You see the way they reacted to Trixie?
I don't want anyone thinking I'm the showoff.
So, "Great and Powerful Trixie".
What makes you think
you're so awesome anyway?
Why, only the Great and Powerful Trixie
have magic strong enough to vanquish...
★☆★ ...the dreaded Ursa Major. ★☆★
-What?
-No way...
When all hope was lost, the ponies
of Hooffington had no one to turn to.
But the Great and Powerful Trixie
stepped in and, with her awesome magic...
...vanquished the Ursa Major and
sent it back to its cave...
★☆★ ...deep within the Everfree Forest. ★☆★
Sooo sweet!
That settles it.
Trixie truly is the most talented, most
magical, most awesome unicorn in Ponyville.
No! In all of Equestria!
How do you know? You didn't see it!
And besides, Twi...
It's true, my enthusiastic little admirers.
Trixie is most certainly the best in Ponyville.
Don't believe the Great and Powerful Trixie?
Well then, I hereby challenge you, Ponyvillians.
Anything you can do, I can do better.
Any takers? Anyone?
Or is Trixie destined...
★☆★ ...to be the greatest ★☆★
equine who has ever lived?
Please! She's unbearable!
You gotta show her. You just gotta!
There's no way I'm gonna use my magic
now, Spike. Especially since...
How about...
YOU!
Well, how about it? Hm?
Is there anything you can do...
...that the Great and Powerful Trixie can't?
I... I...
Well, little hayseed?
That's it! I can't stand for no more of this.
You show her, AJ!
Can your magical powers do this?
Top that, missy.
Oh, ye of little talent.
Watch and be amazed of the magic of Trixie.
Once again the Great and Powerful Trixie prevails.
There is no need to go strutting
around and showing off like that.
Oh?
That's my job!
The don't call me "Rainbow" and "Dash" for nothing.
When Trixie is through, the only
thing they'll call you is "loser".
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Seems like anypony with
a dash of good sense...
...would think twice before
tussling with the Great Trixie.
What we need is another
unicorn to challenge her.
Someone with some magic of her own.
Yeah! A unicorn to show
this unicorn who's boss.
A real unicorn to unicorn tussle.
Enough! Enough all of you.
I take your hint, but Rarity
is above such nonsense.
Rainbow Dash and Applejack
may behave like ruffians...
...but Rarity conducts herself
with beauty and grace.
Ooo, what's the matter?
Afraid you'll get a hair out of place
in that rats nest you call a mane?
Oh, it is ON!
You may think you're tough with
all your so-called power...
...but there is more to magic
than your brutish ways.
A unicorn need to be more than just muscle.
A unicorn needs to have style.
A unicorn is not a unicorn
without grace and beauty.
Rarity won't let Trixie get the best of her.
She's strong, she's beautiful, she's...
QUICK! I NEED A MIRROR!
GET ME A MIRROR!
What did she to my hair?!
I know she did something terrible to my hair!
-Nothing!
-It's fine.
-It's gorgeous.
It's green.
What?
No! Green hair?! Not green hair!
Such an awful, awful color...!
Well, I never...!
Well, Twilight. I guess it's up to you.
Come on. Show her what you're made of.
What do you mean? I'm nothing special.
Yes, you are! You're better that her.
I'm not better than anyone.
You think you're better than
the Great and Powerful Trixie?
You think you have more magical talent?
Well, come on. Show Trixie what you've got.
Show us all.
Who, me? I'm just run of the mill citizen of Ponyville.
No powerful magic here.
I... I think I can hear my laundry calling.
Sorry, gotta go.
Twilight?
Once again the Great and Powerful
Trixie has proven herself...
...to be the most amazing
unicorn in all of Equestria.
Was there ever any doubt?
Here's your smoothie you asked for.
With extra hay, just how you like it.
Hmmm... Hay.
Yes?
Oh, tell us another story,
Great and Powerful Trixie.
Yeah, tell us about how you
vanquished the Ursa Major.
Trixie is far too exhausted from
performing feats beyond imagination.
Begone with you until morning.
Of course, Great and Powerful Trixie.
Anything you say. We are at your beck and call.
What are you two doing?
-Just bringing the G&PT a...
-The what?
The Great And Powerful Trixie.
Sheesh...
Just bringing her a smoothie.
How can you fall for her lameness?
She's just a showoff.
Unlike Twilight...
The Great and Powerful Trixie vanquished
an Ursa Major. Can your Twilight claim that?
Oh really?
Were you guys actually there?
Well, uh... no. But...
But nothing! The proof is in the pudding!
I like pudding.
Look. Unless an Ursa Major comes waltzing up
the street for Trixie to vanquish...
...I am not gonna believe a word she says.
And neither should you!
And Ursa walking up the street, ay?
Snails! You thinking what I'm thinking?
Why is it they call it a flea market
when they don't really sell fleas?
Yeah, uh...
Oh, come on!
Twilight, would you put down
that book and just listen to me?
Didn't you see how they hated
Trixie's bragging, Spike?
If I go out there and show off my magic,
I run the risk of losing them as friends.
It's not the same thing, Twilight. You'd be
using your magic to stand up for your friends.
No, Spike. It's exactly the same.
Come on, Twilight. Any one of these tricks, even
the tiniest, would be enough to show off Trixie.
I don't wanna be seen as a bragger like Trixie.
But you're the best!
Please, Spike, I said no!
If that's what you wanna be, then fine.
Oooh... How we gonna find an Ursa Major when
I can't even see my own hoof in front of my face?
Hold on.
Oh. That's better.
Hey, guys. Where are you going?
-Can't talk now...!
-Got a major problem.
Yeah... Ursa Major, to be exact.
TRIXIE!!!
Twilight!
Trixie! Come out! You gotta help!
Trixie thought she said the Great and
Powerful Trixie did not wanna be disturbed.
We... We have a... a tiny problem.
Actually, it's a big one.
What is so important that you cannot
wait until morning to disturb Trixie?
Twilight! You've gotta come! Quick!
I've already told you, Spike.
I don't wanna show off Trixie.
No, you don't understand. It's...
Uh, is that what I think it is?
Majorly.
Great and Powerful Trixie,
you've got to vanquish the Ursa!
Yeah! Vanquish so we can watch.
It took a lotta trouble to get that thing here.
Wait! You brought this here?!
Are you out of your little pony minds?
But you're the Great and Powerful Trixie.
Yeah, remember? You defeated an Ursa Major.
Uh, okay.
Stand back.
Piece a cake.
Oh, come on, Trixie.
Stop goofing around and vanquish it, eh?
Well, that was a dud.
Yeah, pfft... Come on!
Where's all the cool explosions and smoking?
Stuff like earlier, you know.
What's going on?
We brought an Ursa to town.
You WHAT?!
Don't worry, the Great and
Powerful Trixie will vanquish it.
I can't.
WHAT?!
Oh, I can't, I never have...
No one can vanquish an Ursa Major. I just
made the whole story up to make me look better.
MADE IT UP?!
Nice use of number 16.
Call me, dontcha know?
That's new.
Unbelievable!
That was amazing!
Heavens to Betsy! We knew
you had ability but not that much.
I'm sorry. Please, please, don't hate me.
Hate you?!
Why, what ever do you mean, darling?
Well, I know how much you all hated Trixie's
showing off with her magic tricks and I just thought...
Whoah, whoah, whoah.
Magic's got nothing to do with it.
-Trixie's just a loud mouth.
-Most unpleasant.
All hat, no cattle.
So... you don't mind my magic tricks?
Your magic is a part of who you are, sugar cube.
And we like who you are.
We're proud to have such a powerful,
talented unicorn as our friend.
And after whupping that Ursa's
hind quarters we're even prouder.
You are?
Wow, Twilight! How'd you know
what to do with that Ursa Major?
That's what I was doing when
you came looking for me.
I was so intrigued by Trixie's bragging that
I was compelled to do a little reading up on them.
So it is possible to vanquish
an Ursa Major all by yourself?
That wasn't an Ursa Major.
It was a baby. An Ursa Minor.
THAT was just a BABY?!
And it wasn't rampaging. It was just
cranky because *someone* woke it up.
If that was an Ursa Minor...
...then what's an Ursa Major like?
You don't wanna know.
Huh! You may have vanquished an Ursa Minor...
...but you will never have the
amazing showstopping ability...
★☆★ ...of the Great and Powerful Trixie! ★☆★
Why, that little...
Just let her go.
Maybe some day she'll learn her lesson.
Now, about you two.
Oh, we're sorry that we woke up the Ursa Minor.
We just wanted to see some AWESOME magic.
Yeah! And the way you vanquished
that Ursa Minor was AWESOME!
We deserve whatever punishment you give us.
For starters, you can clean up this mess.
And... What do you think, Spike?
Should I give them number 25?
Oh, twenty five, yes.
And I think I deserve it too.
I think you're right.
Sweet!
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"I have learned a very valuable
lesson about friendship."
"I was so afraid of being thought of as
a showoff that I was hiding a part of who I am."
"My friends helped he realize that
it's okay to be proud of your talents."
"And there are times when it's
appropriate to show them off."
"Especially when you're
standing up for your friends."
So, you finally admit that you're the most
talented unicorn in all of Ponyville?
Well... yeah.
But it's nothing to brag about.
So, uh, how did it go with Rarity?
Eh... She didn't go for the mustache.
You know, Spike, that mustache has
nothing to do with who you really are.
Maybe you should just try being yourself?
Or...
Maybe the mustache wasn't enough?
Maybe if I had a mustache AND a beard...?
Ugh... Not this again.
Okay. Imagine me with a nice,
long Fu Manchu-type beard.
Or maybe a goatee? Oh, no. A soul patch...
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000