Now, what have we learned?
Lots of control...
Good.
Screaming and hollering...
Yes. And most importantly...
Passion!
Right!
So now that you know the elements
of a good cheer, let's hear one!
Yay.
You're gonna cheer for me like that?
-Louder.
-Yay.
-Louder!
LOUDER!!!
Yaaay.
Too loud?
Yay.
And now, phase one of my routine...
Woo...
Phase two...
Way to go.
Here we go. Phase three...
The sonic rainboom!
Come on!
Uh-oh.
Last one.
Thank you so much for helping me
clean up all these books, guys.
It was a crazy weekend of studying.
Rainbow Dash, you rock.
Woohoo.
Did my cheering do that?
Sorry about that, ladies.
That was a truly feeble performance.
Actually, it wasn't all bad. I particularly
liked it when you made the clouds spin.
I'm not talking about my performance.
I'm talking about yours.
That feeble cheering.
What are you two arguing about?
Were we arguing? I'm sorry.
I wish you guys could come to Cloudsdale to see
me competing in the Best Young Flyer Competition.
What's that?
It's where all the greatest
pegasus flyers get together...
...and show off their different flying styles!
Some are fast!
And some are graceful.
Golly! I'd love to see you strut
your stuff in that competition.
Yeah. I wish you guys could be there.
Fluttershy is a great support,
but her cheering isn't exactly inspirational.
Ooh! I'd love to see you make a sonic rainboom!
It's, like, the most coolest thing ever!
Even though I've never actually seen it,
but, I mean, come on, it's a sonic rainboom!
How not cool could it possibly not be?
What's a "sonic rainboom"?
You really need to get out more.
The sonic rainboom is legendary!
When a pegasus like Rainbow Dash
gets going so fast...
Boom!
...a sonic boom and a rainbow
can happen all at once!
And Rainbow Dash here's
the only pony to ever pull it off.
It was a long time ago. I was just a filly.
Yeah, but you're gonna do it again, right?
A-are you kidding?
I'm the greatest flyer
to ever come out of Cloudsdale.
I could do sonic rainbooms in my sleep.
Wow. If you pull that off,
you'll win the crown for sure.
The grand prize is an entire
day with the Wonderbolts.
A whole day of flying with my lifelong heroes.
It'll be a dream come true!
Yay.
I'm gonna go rest up.
Don't wanna overprepare myself, you know.
You, on the other hand, better keep practicing.
I need a cheering section to match
my spectacular performance.
She's practiced that move a hundred times
and she's never even come close to doing it.
I don't know if I can
cheer loud enough to help her.
Well, guess we better get this cleaned up.
Again.
Go on, go on.
Go on what?
Find a spell that will get us
wingless ponies into Cloudsdale.
Didn't you see how nervous she was?
Nervous?! Have you spit your bit or someth'n?
She was tootin' her own horn louder
than the brass section of a marchin' band.
Oh, please.
I've put on enough fashion shows
to recognize stage fright when I see it.
You've got to find a way to be there for her.
Now go on!
How am I supposed to find
a flight spell in this mess?
A flight spell? One sec.
Page 27.
How'd you do that?
It landed on my face when Rainbow Dash
knocked me into the bookcase.
Here it is!
A spell that will allow earth ponies
to fly for three days.
Ooh... It looks really difficult.
I'm not sure I can do it.
You've got to try.
Okay. But who's gonna volunteer
to be the test subject?
I will!
For Rainbow Dash, I will go first.
Here goes...
I think it worked.
You've got to learn to be assertive, Fluttershy.
Don't be afraid to speak up.
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
It's our old friend, Rainbow Crash!
Get kicked out of any flight schools lately?
I didn't get kicked out.
Face it, Rainbow Crash. Flight school had
too many rules and not enough naptimes for you.
Huh. Ask her about the sonic rainboom!
That's nothing but an old mares' tale.
You don't have the skills
to try something like that.
Now wait just a minute!
Oh. I'm sorry. I'm trying to be more assertive.
Anyhow, she *is* going to do a sonic rainboom.
No, she's not, cause there's no such thing.
The show up at the Cloudiseum
and see for yourself.
...if you're free.
Yeah, I'll be free.
Oh, don't worry. We'll be there.
See you then, Rainbow Crash!
Did you see that? I was so assertive.
Those guys are right. I'll never be able to do it.
But Rainbow Dash...
...just because you failed the sonic rainboom
a hundred thousand times in practice...
...doesn't mean you won't be able
to do it in front of an entire stadium...
...full of impatient,
super-critical sports fan ponies.
What do I do?! Everypony's gonna see me fail!
The Wonderbolts will never
let a loser like me join.
Princess Celestia will probably
banish me to the Everfree Forest!
MY LIFE IS RUINED!!!
Rar...
Rare? The sonic rainboom is way more than rare!
Rarity?
Rarity! Are you...
...flying?
I most certainly am!
Aren't my wings smashing?
Twilight made them for me. I just adore them!
Why so shocked?
We couldn't leave our favorite flyer
without a big cheering section.
"We"?
I... I can't believe it!
It's incredible.
This is so cool! You guys made it!
Sure did!
WAIT!
How'd you do that? Only
pegasus ponies can walk on clouds.
Pretty cool, huh?
I found a spell that makes temporary wings...
...but it was too difficult to do more than once.
So I found an easier spell that
lets the rest of us walk on clouds.
And we came to cheer you to victory.
To be honest, I *was* starting to get
just a teeniest, tiniest bit nervous.
But I feel a lot better now
that you guys are here.
Hey! We've got some time before the competition.
Why don't Fluttershy and I
show you around Cloudsdale?
Here it is. The greatest city in the sky!
Some of the greatest pegasi
in history came from Cloudsdale.
Oh! Wait for me!
Those wings are gorgeous!
Oh, why thank you.
Be careful with those wings, Rarity.
They're made from gossamer and morning dew.
And they're incredibly delicate.
Don't worry, Twilight. I'm sure they can't get
worn out from too much attention.
Since we're up here, I'd sure like to get
a look at where the weather's made.
Great idea! Come on, girls!
To the weather factory!
This is where they make the snowflakes.
Each one is hoofmade, as you could see.
It's a delicate operation.
Ooh! The snowflakes look even better from up here.
We better move on before Rarity
ruins winter and causes a drought.
And here's where they make the rainbows.
Spicy...!
Yeah. Rainbows aren't really
known for their flavor.
Where'd you get those
amazing wings? I want a pair.
Yeah, I guess I could see that.
Oh hey, look! It's Rainbow Crash again.
Yeah! Rainbow...
...Crash!
Rarity! What are you doing
talking to *these* guys?
Oh, they were just admiring
my wings, Rainbow Dash.
Yeah. You should forget the sonic rainboom
and just get yourself some wings like these.
Oh. Come on, girls.
Why don't we go see how clouds are made?
Don't listen to them. You're gonna
win that competition for sure.
Are you kidding? I can't do the sonic rainboom.
And just look at these boring
plain old feathered wings.
I'm doomed.
Why, these old things?
Go ahead, everypony. Photos are encouraged.
Rarity! We're supposed to be helping
Rainbow Dash relax, remember?
Put your wings away and stop showing off.
Oh. How can you ask me to put away perfection?
Rainbow Dash, are you okay?
You don't look so good.
Of course! Why wouldn't I be okay?
Everyone's so in love of Rarity's wings
that they won't even notice...
...when I totally BLOW IT
in the Best Young Flyer's Competition.
Hey! There's an idea!
*You* should enter the competition.
Yeah. I could watch you fly all day long.
There really isn't anypony
who uses their wings quite like me.
Perhaps I should compete.
What?!
What am I gonna do?!
I'll never win the competition now.
I'm going to be a while.
Fillies and gentlecolts!
Please rise and join me...
...in welcoming our beloved Princess Celestia!
Please welcome our celebrity judges
for the Best Young Flyer Competition...
...the Wonderbolts!
And now let's find out who will take the prize...
...as this year's Best Young Flyer.
Okay, contestant number one. You're up.
Okay, number two. Let's go.
Um...
Come on, come on. We ain't got all day.
She's talking to you.
Oh! Uh...
Oh, I guess that's me.
Okay, number four. Time to go.
I'm number four and I need
just one more itsy bitsy minute.
Be a dear and have somepony go ahead of me, hm?
Look. I don't care who it is,
but somepony's gotta go on.
LET'S DO THIS!
What am I gonna do?!
I loved number seven. Doing fifteen
barrel rolls in a row can't be easy.
My favorite is number ten.
She just looks like such a nice pony.
Hm. Wonder how come we haven't
seen Rainbow Dash or Rarity yet.
The competition's almost over.
Number fifteen, let's go.
Rarity...
...is ready!
Look, ladies, I don't know what to tell you.
There's only time for one more performance.
If you both wanna compete, you'll
just have to go out there together.
Well, Rainbow Dash? Shall we?
And now, for our final competitor of the day...
...contestant number fifteen!
Uh... and apparently contestant number four.
Good luck, Rainbow Dash. Just do your best.
I hope you don't mind, but I took
the liberty of changing our music.
That rock and roll doesn't really match my wings.
Come on, Rainbow Dash. You can do this.
Just remember the routine.
Phase one...
Nice work, Rainbow Crash!
Time for phase two.
Look. Phase two is working.
And now, for my grand finale, I
will fly right up to the sun...
...and beam my beautiful wings
over the whole city of Cloudsdale.
Oh, they'll be talking about it for years!
Looks like this is my last chance
to turn things around.
Phase three: the sonic...
...rainboom.
Wings, don't fail me now.
Look upon me, Equestria!
For I am Rarity!
Uh-oh.
Oh no! Her wings evaporated into thin air!
Hold on, Rarity!
I'm coming!
I can't look.
A SONIC RAINBOOM!!!
SHE DID IT! SHE DID IT! WAAAH!
Whoa...
A SONIC RAINBOOM!!!
YEAH!!! YES!!!
I did it. I did it!
You sure did.
Oh, thank you, Rainbow Dash. You saved my life.
Oh yeah. I did that too.
Best day ever!
I want to apologize to all of you
for getting so carried away with my...
...beautiful wings.
I guess I just lost my head.
-It's okay.
-Oh, don't worry about it, kiddo.
-We still love you.
And then especially sorry
that I was so thoughtless...
...as to jump into the contest at the last minute
after you would work so hard to win it.
Can you ever ever forgive me?
Oh, it's okay. Everything
turned our all right, right?
I just wish I could have met
the Wonderbolts when they were awake.
Ohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygosh...!
So you're the little pony who saved our lives?
We really wanted to meet you and say thanks.
...ohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygosh...
Princess!
Hello, Twilight Sparkle. And hello to your friends too.
Princess Celestia. I am sorry I ruined the competition.
Rainbow Dash here really is the best flyer in Equestria.
I know she is, my dear.
That's why, for her incredible act of bravery
and a spectacular sonic rainboom...
...I'm presenting the grand prize
for Best Young Flyer to this year's winner...
...Miss Rainbow Dash!
...ohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmy
goshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygoshohmygosh!
So, Twilight Sparkle. Did you learn anything
about friendship from this experience?
I did, Princess. But I think Rarity
learned even more than me.
I certainly did.
I learned how important it is to
keep your hooves on the ground...
...and be there for your friends.
Excellent. Well done, Rarity.
This really is the best day ever!
-Uh... Hey, Rainbow Crash...
-Dash!
Oh! Uh... Sorry. Rainbow Dash.
Uh, we just wanted to congratulate you
on winning the competition.
That sonic rainboom was awesome!
Thanks, guys.
Uh, we're really sorry we gave you
such a hard time before.
Aw, that's okay. Don't worry about it.
Hey, do you wanna hang out with us?
Maybe you could show us
how you did that incredible trick?
Sorry, boys...
...but I've got plans.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000