May I help you, traveler?
Something drew you to my shop...
something powerful.
Ah, you have a keen eye.
The Alicorn Amulet
is one of the most mysterious
and powerful
of all the known magical charms.
I'm afraid this is...
far too dangerous.
Would you like that gift-wrapped?
Season 3 | Episode 5
Magic Duel
Subbed by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
Don't be scared, little friends.
Twilight is wonderful with magic.
Anything happens to them, Twilight,
so help me.
Aww, don't worry, Fluttershy,
Twilight's magic has gotten a lot better
since she accidentally
crushed me and Applejack
with a giant snowball.
Of course she's good with magic.
Twilight's great with magic.
I guess I just don't want
my little friends to be scared...
Oh, oh, look how scared they are!
I promise, Fluttershy,
nothing bad will happen to them.
I know!
Stop, stop!
They can't take it!
Twilight, that looks amazing!
That's all for now, little ones.
Maybe we can practice again later,
if Fluttershy says it's alright.
Your magic has really improved
since we came to Ponyville, Twilight.
- Princess Celestia's gonna love it!
- Thanks, Spike.
I have to be at my best when she arrives
with the delegates from Saddle Arabia.
I can't believe she's trusting me
with the entertainment.
Twilight! Come quick!
It's an emergency!
You beast! This shade of brown
should only be used for accents!
Come on, Applejack. We've got
to get her into a nice, soothing pink.
STAT!
- What's going on here?
- Well, well, well.
If it isn't...
Twilight Sparkle.
- Trixie!
- What's she doing here?
You call that great and powerful?
- Oh! She's Rainbow Wobble, now!
- Yeah!
Good spell,
oh Great and Powerful Trixie!
You two! Quiet!
- What happened?
- Get off of me!
Stop picking on my friends, Trixie!
You and I
have some unfinished business.
My magic's gotten better
since I was here last.
And I'm going to prove it!
Me and you.
A magic duel.
Winner stays,
loser leaves Ponyville forever!
Forget it!
I'd never make a deal like that!
Your choice.
Trixie, put him down.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Because you humiliated me!
After you showed me up
with that Ursa Minor,
I became a laughingstock!
Everywhere I went
I was laughed at and ostracized.
I even had to take a job on a rock farm
just to earn a living!
A rock farm!
Hey! You're lucky a rock farm
would take the likes of you!
Now I want revenge!
And I'll just keep casting spells
'til you agree.
Well?
What do you say?
Alright, Trixie.
Let's duel!
Excellent!
If I lose,
I won't set hoof in Ponyville again.
But if you lose, you're the one
banished from this one-horse town!
Draw!
Snips, Snails, step forward!
What is it,
oh Great and P-P-Powerful Trixie ?
An age spell?
But, how could you do an age spell?
That's only for
the highest level unicorns!
Well, Twilight?
Give up?
Come on, Twilight.
You can do it!
Trixie is the highest level unicorn!
And now it's time for you
to leave Ponyville!
FOREVER!
That's enough, Trixie!
You proved your point,
but you can't possibly
expect Twilight to leave Ponyville!
You fools.
She's already gone.
It's okay guys.
I'll figure something out.
Just take care of each other.
And keep an eye on Trixie.
There's something strange about her...
Twilight?
It's impossible!
How could Trixie know
such advanced magic?
Without Spike, I can't get a message
to the Princess in Saddle Arabia,
so who else do I know who understands
strange and powerful magic?
Your tale of woe upsets me so.
No wonder you're dour,
it's an abuse of power!
I don't know what to do, Zecora.
I feel like I've abandoned my friends.
But I can't take her on horn-to-horn.
If you train with me,
so good you'll be,
I'll show you the way
to make sure she won't stay.
You'll train me in magic?
But she was doing age spells,
weather spells, you name it!
When it comes to magic,
it would be tragic
if somepony licked me,
especially Trixie.
You really think I can beat her?
Okay, when do we start?
You two!
Hurry up with my throne.
And you, how long do I have to wait
for my apple sauce facial?
Forget it, Trixie.
I ain't doing nothin'
'til you let Twilight come home.
Okay, I'll do it, just make it stop!
I thought I told you to dance!
Trixie's cruel magic
is ruining Ponyville.
Somepony has to help us!
No noise, no sound,
no din, no fuss,
must interfere with your focus.
Unlearn what you have learned,
only then can victory be earned.
Trixie is the highest level unicorn!
There is much,
much that I can teach,
but the answer you need
may still be out of reach.
I'm sorry, Zecora.
I'm trying my best, but...
I can't stop thinking about Trixie.
There was something different
about her.
It's like she's gone
from high and mighty to mean and nasty.
Your thinking needs a readjust.
Total concentration is a must.
This really doesn't seem
to be getting us anywhere.
I hear you, Pinkie.
I can't find anything that describes
the kind of magic Trixie's doin'.
There must be something!
Twilight has every magic book there is!
Um, I think I may have found something?
Yes, it's time for us
to consider our futures
in this new Trixie-led Ponyville.
Um, this sounds an awful lot like
Trixie's magic--
She wants me to grow apples
with no peels!
How the hay am
I supposed to do that?
Um, there's a picture here
of that necklace--
It's called the Alicorn Amulet,
and whoever wears it
is blessed with untold--
Hey, everypony, look!
This book has a picture
of Trixie's necklace!
It's called the Alicorn Amulet,
and whoever wears it
is blessed with untold powers!
If you read a little further,
you'll see--
Even though it provides great power,
it also corrupts the user!
Yes, but, um, you can't--
You can't just
take the Alicorn Amulet off her neck.
It has a magical lock!
Trixie's the only pony who can take it off!
Maybe--
We need to get
this information to Twilight.
- She'll know what to do.
- But, how--
If any of us try to leave,
Trixie's magical forcefield will tell her!
- Maybe we should--
- I've got it!
Trying to sneak past the forcefield
would be impossible without help.
But I know who's got the goods
to get into those woods!
- Fluttershy!
-What?!
What do you say, Fluttershy?
Can you handle the mission?
No! I'll crack under the pressure,
I'll snap like a twig!
Perfect! Fluttershy'll sneak out
of Ponyville and find Twilight.
But I-- I--
Okay.
I know just the design
for a dangerous mission outfit!
Pull, you fools!
Somepony set off the magic forcefield,
and Trixie intends to punish them!
But, wouldn't it be faster
if we had some... wheels?!
The Great and Powerful Trixie
doesn't trust wheels.
Now pull faster!
I'm telling ya, Snips,
she's getting weirder and weirder!
Stop!
You there!
What are you doing?!
Why is she so mean to us?
Yeah! I miss the days
when she was just a fraud!
Oh oh dear!
Rarity's dangerous
mission outfit is ruined!
Guess we'd better go back!
Okay, okay, you're right,
I need to be brave and find Twilight.
Oh! You found her?
She's in the Everfree Forest?!
Oh, this is me being brave!
I wanna be brave at home,
locked in my closet,
with my teddy bear!
I can't believe
I didn't recognize the Alicorn Amulet!
The more she uses it,
the more it will corrupt her!
But how am I supposed
to beat that amulet?
My magic's not good enough!
Twilight Sparkle,
much work have you done.
You learned all of my lessons,
all but one.
If Trixie's tricks have you in a fix,
you must mix your magic
and use the six.
Mix your magic, use the six...
mix your magic, use the six!
Use the six, that's it!
Zecora, you're a genius!
Now I need to get you back
inside Ponyville, Fluttershy.
This better not be another false alarm,
or the Great and Powerful Trixie will--
You!
What's the matter, Twilight Sparkle?
Not enjoying your exile?
I know about the Alicorn Amulet.
I know you cheated.
Cheated? Moi?
Yeah. And I thought
you might wanna see
what a real magical amulet looks like.
Zecora gave it to me.
It's from beyond the Everfree Forest,
and it's way more powerful
than your measly Alicorn Amulet!
Ha! Nothing's more powerful
than the Alicorn Amulet!
And nopony's more powerful
than the Great and Powerful Trixie!
Care to put your amulet
where your mouth is?
How about another duel?
Why should I?
I already beat you.
That's up to you!
But I guess you'll never see
the totally awesome magic
from beyond the Everfree Forest...
Come on, Zecora.
Wait!
Okay, okay, you're on!
A second duel.
Let's start with a simple age spell,
shall we?
Let's.
Snips, Snails.
An oldie, but a goodie.
Now let's see
what your little charm can do.
No problem.
Um, Applejack, Rarity?
Could you help me, please?
So you can do an age spell,
big deal.
That's... that's impossible!
That's nothing!
How did you--
Duplication spell.
Ever seen one pony
play ten instruments?
This-- just can't be!
Ooh, one more.
I can turn a mare into a stallion.
Eeyup.
Well, Trixie, looks like my amulet
is more powerful than yours.
Hey! Give it back!
With this amulet,
I shall now rule
all of Equestria!
Witness, my subjects,
gaze upon an ever
greater and powerfuler Trixie!
I don't need
that old Alicorn Amulet.
I have this!
Stop it!
Tha-that tickles!
Tickles?
That was supposed
to make you writhe in agony!
This amulet is defective!
Give mine back!
Sorry. This is going back
into hiding where it belongs.
By the way, Trixie,
the amulet around your neck?
It's one of Zecora's doorstops.
But...
how did you do those spells?
Nopony can do those spells!
You're right.
Not even me.
Zecora taught me so much about
magic while I was in exile.
She even taught me
when not to use it.
My magic alone wasn't powerful enough
to take on the Alicorn Amulet head to head,
so I needed to use
a different kind of magic...
the magic of friendship.
I also knew that the only pony
who could get the amulet off
your neck was you.
But what about
the pony with the ten instruments?
That's not magic,
that was just Pinkie Pie.
Trixie?
It's the least I could do.
I treated you and your friends so horribly
when I was wearing that Alicorn Amulet...
I just couldn't control myself.
You can forgive me, can't you?
- Sure.
- Oh, great.
Don't you think
the Great and Apologetic Trixie
is the most magnificent humble pony
you have ever seen?