TWILIGHT: You wanted to see me?
To give me a test?
CELESTIA:
The Crystal Empire has returned.
You want me to help protect
an entire empire?
It must be you, and you alone.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
But, what if I fail?
Let's just say the empire...
isn't the only thing that's returned.
Go, go!
PINKIE:
Sparklriffic!
With Cadance putting all her strength
into keeping her spell going,
and me trying to keep an eye
on signs of trouble in the arctic,
we haven't been able to gather
much information from the Crystal Ponies.
There are Crystal Ponies?!
I wish I could help you.
But I can't seem to remember anything
before King Sombra came to power.
TWILIGHT SPARKLE:
History of the Crystal Empire.
The last page of the book mentioned
a crystal heart as the fair's centerpiece,
so I used my magic to cut one
out of a crystal block.
The whole purpose of the Crystal Fair
is to lift the spirits of the Crystal Ponies,
so the light within them
can power the Crystal Heart,
so that the empire can be protected!
I think we may have
a problem...
I didn't know it was an actual relic!
It's alright, Twilight.
( creature howling distantly )
Twilie...
( opening theme song playing )
Season 3 | Episode 2
The Crystal Empire, Part 2
Subbed and Synced by GrayJeager
(Hard-of-Hearing version)
Fr.Jeager@Gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
( ominous theme playing )
( croaks )
The empire is under attack.
( roars )
I have to find the Crystal Heart!
TWILIGHT:
No, you stay here with Cadance.
She needs you, Shining Armor.
I'll retrieve the Heart.
Let's do this.
I've been trying to figure out
how I'm meant to pass Celestia's test.
Retrieving the Crystal Heart must be it.
But there is something else you can do.
Name it.
You and the rest of our friends
have to keep the fair going.
What? With that thing
moving into the empire?!
The whole purpose of the Crystal Fair
is to lift the spirits of the Crystal Ponies,
so they can activate the Crystal Heart.
Yeah, and?
If the Crystal Ponies find out King Sombra
is trying to take over the empire again,
their spirits are gonna be
anything but lifted.
It won't matter if I find the Crystal Heart.
They won't be able to make it work.
You have to keep them happy
here at the fair.
Keep the fair going and
the Crystal Ponies' spirits high.
Done and done.
SHINING ARMOR:
Twilie, be careful.
I will.
( croaking )
( calliope music playing )
Okay, here's...
( whispering inaudibly )
Huh?
I just found out they're offering
face painting for the little ones.
( whispers )
Uh-huh, we can do that.
Twilight's doing what?!
He... really... loves
getting his face painted.
( laughs nervously )
Who wants a flugelhorn?
I want a flugelhorn!
Who else wants a flugelhorn?
I want a flugelhorn!!
SPIKE:
Twilight, wait!
I'm coming with you!
You can't. I have to retrieve
the Crystal Heart by myself.
I know. I promise
I won't lift a claw to help you.
Not a claw, Spike.
SPIKE:
Where are we going, exactly?
TWILIGHT: I think I might know where
King Sombra hid the Crystal Heart.
SPIKE:
The castle?
The king would've been
counting on the fact
that nopony would dare
come looking for it here.
They'd've been too afraid to even try.
SPIKE:
I hope you're right.
You and me both.
What are you lookin' at?!
That's what I thought!
Uh, Rainbow Dash?
We're supposed to be actin'
like nothing's wrong.
Exactly!
APPLEJACK: What I mean is,
maybe you should let me
keep the Crystal Ponies away
from the fake heart,
while you show off
your joustin' skills.
Seeing my awesomeness does have a way
of putting ponies into a pretty good mood.
( sheep bleating )
- Come on, Knight Fluttershy.
- Huh?!
It's showtime.
How are y'all feelin'?
Havin' a good time?
The best I've had
in over a thousand years!
That's good! Gotta renew
that spirit of love and unity
if you're gonna power up
that Crystal Heart, right?
I sure would like to see it
before the ceremony.
It's been such a long time.
Oh, I hear ya, but,
uh... phew!
I'm gettin' a little toasty out here.
Bet you'd like to cool off
with a little Crystal Empire nectar!
Uh, you tried
the Crystal Empire fritters yet?
Made from a traditional
Crystal Empire recipe!
You're gonna love 'em!
I hear there's a joustin' match
about to start!
You don't wanna miss that!
Come on, Twilight... these Crystal Ponies
are more curious than a cat!
( panting )
Huh?
( sighs )
It's gotta be here somewhere.
It's just gotta be!
Not a claw, Spike.
( laughs nervously )
Celestia's orders!
CELESTIA: If the empire is filled
with hope and love,
those things are reflected
across all of Equestria.
If hatred and fear take hold...
Of course!
( grunts )
- What? Did you find it?!
- No!
Because this isn't
King Sombra's castle.
SPIKE: Isn't this where he lived
when he was in power?
It is. But it didn't look like this.
( grunts )
SPIKE:
Whoa.
When did you learn to do that?
That was a little trick
Celestia taught me.
( gulps )
( whimpers )
You stay here.
If you insist.
Can you see what's down there yet?
Not yet. I can't even tell
how far down this goes!
( crystal clinks )
- Spike?
- SPIKE: Yeah?
TWILIGHT:
Can you see outside?
( thunder crashing )
Yes... crystals...
It's not good! Cadance's magic
must be fading faster than before!
( suspenseful theme playing )
( grunts )
SPIKE :
Twilight? Are you okay?
Yes...
What in the...
Stop...
moving!
Spike, I think it's here!
What are you doing here?
I don't know!
I opened the door and--
And now you must go.
Go where?
Doesn't matter to me.
You failed the test, Twilight!
I don't understand! The test--
Not only will you not move on
to the next level of your studies,
you won't continue your studies at all!
You didn't say anything about
no longer being your student if I failed!
Didn't I?
But... what do I do now?!
( evil laugh )
SPIKE:
Twilight!
Twilight?
SPIKE:
Twilight!
Twiliiiight!
I know you told me to stay up there,
but you were down here
for such a long time
and you weren't answering
and I got worried so I came down here,
and you were just
staring at that wall...
I was calling your name, but I couldn't
seem to get your attention, and...
What were you looking at?
I mean... it's just a wall.
Ponyville?!
How did I get...
No! I don't wanna go!
Please, Twilight, don't leave me!
( door slams )
King Sombra's dark magic.
A doorway that leads to your worst fear.
We were home... you told me
you didn't need me any more.
You were sending me away...
A fear that will never come to pass.
I'm never gonna send you away.
And I'm not gonna fail my test!
SPIKE:
What's in there?
( sighs )
Stairs.
Lots and lots of stairs.
Maybe you should come
with me this time.
( uplifting theme playing )
( thunder rumbling )
( King Sombra laughing )
( crowd cheering )
( whimpering )
CROWD: Woo! Rainbow Dash!
( thunder rumbling )
( trumpet blows )
( scream )
CRYSTAL PONY:
Bravo, knight Rainbow Dash!
( whimpers )
Isn't there...
somepony else who could...
take over the jousting demonstration
with you?
The fate of an entire empire rests on us
showing these ponies a good time.
But, y'know,
if that isn't important to you...
( sobs )
Okay, okay,
I'll take it easy on you next time.
But not too easy.
I've got a reputation to maintain!
( panting heavily )
What if this is just more of his magic?
He makes a door that links
to your worst nightmare...
why not a staircase
that goes on forever?
Hold on to me.
Uh...
TWILIGHT:
Whoa! Yah!
( ponies whimpering )
RARITY: ( laughs nervously )
Excuse me. Pardon me.
I am running out of weaving materials
for the traditional crafts booths!
I've just made a hat out of
three pieces of hay and a drinking straw!
I made it work. But still!
We gotta do everything we can
to keep this thing goin'.
The Princess isn't lookin' so good.
I can imagine her magic
is gonna last much longer.
It's gonna be fine.
These ponies are gonna power up
that Crystal Heart when the time comes,
and we won't be needin'
her magic anyway.
PINKIE: I sure hope that time comes soon!
Even I can't keep this party going forever!
This isn't the Crystal Heart.
Oh, of course it isn't.
- The real one is--
- On its way!
I was going to say 'being polished'
to buy us some more time?
Oops.
( King Sombra laughing )
CRYSTAL PONIES: It's him!
KING SOMBRA:
Crystal Heart...
TWILIGHT: Whoa!
( laughs )
I actually studied gravity spells,
thinking it might be on our test!
Turns out I was prepared for this!
TWILIGHT: Wooo-hoo!
( laughs )
( alarm sounds )
( growls )
( evil laugh )
( thunder crashing )
( wind howling )
The Heart...
where's the Crystal--
Here! It rolled over to me
when you dropped it!
Don't move!
You can move, just not toward me!
How could I have been so foolish...?
I was just so eager to get it!
Then when I saw what
was going on outside, I...
SPIKE:
You have to get out of there, Twilight!
You have to be the one who brings
the Crystal Heart to Princess Cadance!
If you don't,
you'll fail Celestia's test!
King Sombra is already attacking
the Empire.
He could reach the Crystal Ponies
at any moment...
reach Princess Cadance,
my brother, my friends...
There may not be enough time for me
to find a way to escape.
You have to be the one
to bring the Crystal Heart to the fair.
Me? But Twilight--
Go.
Go!
( ponies whimpering and screaming )
APPLEJACK: Don't y'all worry
your pretty little crystal heads!
The real Crystal Heart
will be here any second!
I don't know if they believe you...
Don't know if I believe me...
( gasps )
He's back! I can't take it!
( screams )
Uh!
King Sombra...
My crystal slaves...
( whimpering )
( grunts )
- Hey! Up here!
- Spike?
I got the Crystal Heart!
That is mine!
( ominous theme playing )
Spikey-Wikey!
KING SOMBRA:
Huh?
CRYSTAL PONY:
Who is that?
Behold! The Crystal Princess!
The Crystal Heart has returned.
Use the light and love within you
to ensure that King Sombra does not.
What?
No... No! Stop!
( majestic theme playing )
RARITY:
Ooh! ( laughs )
( screams )
( uplifting theme playing )
( all cheering )
( sighs )
Good job, Spike.
RARITY:
I do so wish it was permanent.
Did you see how
my mane just absolutely sparkled?
But... good things are better
when they're a rarity.
Oh!
( giggles )
SHINING ARMOR:
Everything's gonna be okay.
You've gotta stop saving my rump like this,
it's starting to get embarrassing.
Wasn't me who saved you in the end.
It was Spike.
It's just a test.
Maybe she'll let you retake it.
I don't think she's gonna
give me a new test.
Keep it together, buddy...
gotta stay strong... for Twilight...
It's beautiful.
I wish it had been me
who ultimately made it so.
But it wasn't.
Twilight,
as I understand it,
Spike brought Princess Cadance
the Crystal Heart
because you weren't sure how quickly
you could find a way to escape the tower.
You weren't willing to risk the future
of the citizens of the Crystal Empire
in an effort to guarantee your own.
Far better that I have a student who
understands the meaning of self-sacrifice
than one who only looks out
for her own best interests.
Does this mean...?
She's totally gonna lose it!
Keep it together, buddy...
gotta stay strong... for Twilight...!
I passed!
( all cheer )
You were prepared to do your best
Had what it takes to pass the test
All those doubts you can dismiss
Turns out
you were prepared for this!
You clearly have just what it takes
To pass the test with such high stakes
We knew for sure you would prevail
Since when does
Twilight Sparkle ever fail?
All those doubts that you can dismiss
Trust yourself and you cannot miss
Turns out you were
Turns out I was
Turns out you were prepared for this!
( laughs nervously )
Yeah, I knew everything was gonna be fine.