Spike is great
Making a jewel cake
Me, that's who.
Been saving up my gems
So fine
For a cake
That is divine
Who are you "hooing" at?
I know. They're delicious.
Now you see them,
now you don't.
This is how you make
A jewel cake
Stir in some gems
And then you bake
Gonna eat, eat, eat it up
Gonna--
What happened
to all my jewels?!
I had a bowl full of them here
and now I don't!
Which means,
somebody took them!
Who? That's what I'm asking.
Who?
Who took my jewels?!
Oh, I'm who.
This cake was gonna be
so good.
Why?
Whyyyyyyyyy??!
Season 3 | Episode 11
Just for Sidekicks
Subbed by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
I have no jewels
I have no cake
I'm a sad little dragon
With nothing to--
...Is it?
Oh! Oh goodness, I hope
I'm not interrupting anything.
Well, I do have this cake
to not bake.
Oh, sorry. It's a bad time.
Inside joke, talk to me.
It's just that Princess Cadence
needs us to do a great job
welcoming the head
of the Equestria games
when she visits
the Crystal Empire tomorrow.
Oh, I know all about that.
As if I wouldn't be any help
at welcoming.
Oh, I don't know
what I was thinking!
Of course, you might be upset
for not being invited,
and here I am coming to ask you
for a favor.
You were probably
going to say no, anyway.
All I had to offer you in exchange
was one little jewel.
What was that?
All I have is this jewel.
That's a really big one.
A really big, juicy,
perfect for a cake-topper jewel.
Does this mean you'll do it?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, thank you. Thank you!
So while I'm gone,
you'll take care of Angel,
and tomorrow is Tuesday,
which is his tail fluffing day.
And it's really important
for him to look good.
Wait, what? You want me
to take care of him?
Oh, well, yes.
But if it's too much
trouble,
I can always see
if there's somepony else.
We already agreed on the
whole jewel thing, so I'll just--
Thank you, thank you,
thank you!
Angel, aren't you
just so excited?
See you tomorrow.
You know, she's not
the only pony with a pet
that might need
some watching.
All I'm saying is if Fluttershy thought
that her beloved little friend
shouldn't be left alone while
you're busy in the Crystal Empire,
then maybe that's just
something to think about.
Tank's not some fuzzy
little bunny.
He can take care of himself.
He's a strong, fearless
and totally together pet.
All right, you can watch him.
But only because, uh...
Tank's got a strict
flying regimen
and someone needs to make sure
that he doesn't slack off while I'm gone.
You know, the two of us
are very diligent.
Okay, whatever.
Yes, yes. And more importantly,
as for Opal,
she likes to eat every
36 and a half minutes.
You groom her with
her silken brush, head to toe.
And don't forget to pooch
her pillow out in the middle,
that's where she likes it.
And the temperature in the room
should always be exactly 81.4 degrees.
That's the only way
she can get to sleep.
So thanks for your help
and good luck to you.
I think the dragon was expecting
a little something for his efforts.
Almost as beautiful
as the pony who gave it to me.
Shouldn't you be critter-proofing
the library or something?
Tank has a tendency to--
Critter-proofing.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Three down, three to go.
What's that you said, Gummy?
Well, you're just gonna have
to ask Pinkie Pie about that one.
Ask me! Ask me!
Go ahead, ask her.
Of course,
you can have another cupcake!
Yeah. Why didn't you say so?
I'll get you a bigger pond
immediately.
I think what Gummy's
trying to say is--
He's always wanted a pair
of riding pants?
His toenails need
a new coat of shellack?
He wants to floss twice a day
instead of just once?
I think what Gummy is trying to say
is that he'd like a little Spike time.
Who wouldn't?
Spike time is the best.
Alas, it doesn't come cheap.
All I'm saying is that you might
wanna think about a helmet.
You only wanna get hit in the head
by a flying turtle... once.
A thousand plus carats
of pure deliciousness.
Looks like you got a regular
pet day care in here, Spike.
You'll still be able to get
some good playtime
with Winona like you said,
though, won't you?
She tends to get a little wild
if she doesn't get her exercise.
Exercise, sure, of course.
I don't remember seeing
critters on the invite list.
That's because we're leaving
them here with Spike.
He's gonna do a little
critter sitting for us.
Oh, really?
So sorry I'm late.
Silly bunny had hidden his brush.
Be sure you get plenty
on his tail
or it won't get as poofy
as he likes it.
Come on, girls,
or we're gonna miss the train.
One more for the road.
Oh, you little puppy,
come on here.
I love you more.
No, I love you more!
I love you more!!
Oh, I promise
it will be okay.
I'll fluff your tail
twice next week.
Three times?
Oh, I know, it's a chilly
81.2 in here.
Spike, take care of this,
would you please?
You got it!
So, what're you thinking about
that hooting little friend of yours?
Suppose you'll want me
to keep an eye on him too.
That would be nice.
You sure you don't already
have your hands full?
Ah. I'll be fine!
But, just between you and me,
I've gotta give priority
to the paying customers.
You're absolutely sure
you can do this?
Of course! Wouldn't have
agreed to it if I couldn't.
Piece of cake.
Speaking of cake,
I've got a little something
I need to attend to.
Yeah, like, keeping an eye
on a house full of critters.
Uh, yeah. That was totally
what I was talking about.
Relax! Go to your welcoming
thing in the Crystal Empire.
Spike's got it all under control.
All right, sidekicks!
Front and center!
There are six of you,
but there's only one
right here in front of me!
Two. And what I say goes!
Spike, the boss of you,
that's who.
One, two, three!
Come on, number four.
One, two, three, four, five.
Who's missing?
Angel.
All I wanted were some jewels.
Big, juicy delicious jewels.
And now what do I have?
A missing rabbit and--
Oh, little fluffy Angel Bunnykins,
you're so cute!
The natural waves in his fluff
are to die for.
Isn't Angel just the cutest thing
you've ever seen?
Look, you don't wanna
be with me.
I'd rather not chase you around
all over the place
when I could be enjoying
some jewel cake.
Watch me solve
both our problems.
You know, I'm supposed to be
watching him,
but you all have just hit it off
so well, that maybe--
Maybe I could let you
take care of him instead.
We would, but we've got some major
Crusaders business planned for today.
Major. We're getting our
skydiving Cutie Marks today!
Well, I suppose
if you've got other plans...
It's just--
You're so good with him.
Like "get a Cutie Mark
for bunny-sitting" good.
A bunny-sitting Cutie Mark.
That would be adorable!
He does seem to like us.
And we hadn't exactly
figured out
how we're going to pull off
this whole skydiving thing.
You know what?
As hard as it's gonna be for me
to part with these little guys,
I think you should probably
just take all of them.
If you ask me, the more critters
you take care of,
the more chances you have of getting
some kind of critter-sitting Cutie Mark.
Am I right?
Or am I right?
Sure.
- Yes!
- But wait.
How are we gonna take good
care of them
without treats
for when they're good?
And we'll need beds
for when their tired!
And toys.
They need toys!
It's an afternoon.
They don't need all that stuff.
They'll be fine!
We need to be able
to buy them some things.
One jewel might be able
to cover it all.
What would I possibly
be doing with jewels?
I happen to know for a fact
that Applejack gave you a gem
to watch Winona.
Which means...
Obviously no one around here
is getting a Cutie Mark
for kindness towards a poor,
hungry little dragon.
Take it or leave it!
We'll take it.
Gonna put in some flour
And add a little sugar
For my five
Delicious jewels
But pink feathers would look
so good with your eyes!
That bird could use
a little color.
Has anyone seen Tank's head?
Where's his head?!
What've you done
to the turtle?!
Oh, he totally forgot
he could do that.
Yeah. So pretty sure
critter-sitting Cutie Marks are out.
And our critter-grooming
Cutie Marks
probably aren't going to appear
any time soon either.
All right,
load them up.
And you can give me back
that jewel I gave you.
Sorry.
We don't have it anymore.
What? Why not?
How do you think we paid
for the industrial-sized pet hair dryer?
Zecora knows just what to do
about all this bad mojo
that's floating around you.
I'm thinking a cage
and a great big lock might be next.
Zecora can take the bad away
if you do just what I say.
Really?
But before I can do my duty,
I'm going to need
some of your booty.
Where are you going?
You think jewels
are what you need,
but there's no worse mojo
than dragon greed.
Almost there.
Just taking good care
of everyone's animals!
What am I gonna have to do
to get this to go away?
Then this is just
between you and me, right?
No other pony
has to hear a word about it?
A word about what now?
This better be important.
All aboard!
Angel!
I can't have all of these
animals on my train.
Not without tickets
and not without chaperones.
All I need is to get
on for one minute,
grab a bunny and get off!
Promise.
A likely story.
No chaperone, no train!
Skydiving Cutie Marks!
Is three ponies enough?
At least I have you two left,
my delectable little treasures.
All aboard
for the Crystal Empire!
Crystal Empire?!
I've always wanted to see
the Crystal Empire!
I wish I were dressed for it,
but still... the Crystal Empire!
We're not really going.
We just needed to get on the train
so I can get that rabbit!
And when I do, we're off!
- What?
- It's not fair!
There he is!
Next stop, the Crystal Empire.
No, no, no, no, no!
So it seems the Crystal Empire
would be really cold,
but I've heard that it's not.
It's as warm as can be!
Do you think the walls are crystal?
Maybe even see-through?
Can you imagine?
See-through walls!
Take it. Just take it!
It's so beautiful.
Well, enjoy it while you can.
We're not getting out of this car
until we're back in Ponyville.
There is no way, no how,
we're coming all the way
to the Crystal Empire
without looking around!
No pony's gonna get past
this dragon!
Don't make me use this!
You wouldn't dare!
Oh no!
Whoa. Just whoa.
I'm in crystal heaven!
Shh. Quiet there!
There's the bunny!
Please, please. Pretty please,
don't go down there.
I'll fluff your tail!
I'll perm, highlight and blow it out
if you'll just stop!
What do you want?
Name it, and it's yours.
Oh, my goodness.
All aboard!
You're coming with me.
We made it!
Without seeing the palace!
I think this car's empty!
They're coming this way.
Everybody down!
There has got to be
a better solution!
Don't sit down,
don't sit down!
My dogs are barking!
Did y'all hear that?
They really are!
Bummer, Spike got
to miss out on all this.
He would have had fun here.
I'm sure he's havinga great time
watching all the critters back at home.
Think he's still got a handle
on things?
If he is staying calm
and collected,
I bet he is doing
a terrific job as a leader.
Go ahead, bunny.
Do your worst.
I deserve it.
I ignored you,
tried to pawn you off
on someone else...
I didn't take these silly things out
or fluff this like I was supposed to.
I wasn't really thinking
about you at all.
Any of you.
Just wanted the jewels.
I hope you'll all forgive me
someday.
You will?
Oh, great.
I'm gonna be the one
who gives us away.
Where did you--?
You all hear that?
I can't wait to scratch
the belly on Winona!
Oh, I miss her.
I can't wait
to see Owlowicious!
Hello!
Thought we'd meet you
at the station!
So we could hear all about
the Crystal Empire
and find out if you brought us
one of the Crystal snow globes
that they sell
at the train station.
How did you know
about the snow globes?
Lucky guess?
I've gotta hand it to you,
Spike.
You did a really good job
of taking care of the animals.
Oh, Spike,
Angel looks perfect!
You did such a good job
fluffing his tail!
Yeah, well,
we're like this now.
You know who.
So, what are you thinking?
Bake them into a jewel pie?
Six-layer gem cake
sounds pretty good!
Yeah, it does.
It really, really does.
Whyyyyyyyy??!