Spike, you really need
to go to sleep.
Two more minutes, Twilight?
I'm just getting to
the really good part.
The Mane-iac is about to--
The Mane-iac?
The Power Ponies'
most evil nemesis.
She was the power-mad owner
of a hair-care product company.
A tragic accident at her shampoo
factory in Maretropolis
not only gave her mane
strange new powers,
but also caused her to go...
...completely insane!
She and her henchponies
are planning to break into
the Maretropolis Museum
and steal the Electro-Orb
so she can use it to power
up her doomsday device.
Of course, the Mane-iac
wouldn't have even known
if Hum Drum hadn't slipped
up and told her all about it.
Hum Drum?
Guy in the blue boots
and pointless red cape.
The Power Ponies' bumbling
and totally useless side-kick.
The Power Ponies have
to stop the Mane-iac
or Mare-tropolis is doomed!
Believe me, Spike, if anypony
understands what it's like
to get caught up in a
really good book, it's me.
But if we're going to make
any progress fixing up
Luna and Celestia's old
castle tomorrow,
we all have to
do our part.
We don't want to be too
tired to lend a hoof.
Or claw.
OK. OK. I'm going to bed.
Good-night.
Two more minutes.
(click)
Yes!
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
HoH version
♪
Looking good, everypony!
Let's keep this magical
make-over moving.
You got it.
Good ol' Spike is here
ready to do his part.
A little more to the left!
No, the other left!
Awesome! That's perfect
right where it is!
On to the next painting.
You sure you don't
need any help?
Naw. That's OK.
We've got everything
under control!
Dash?
I'm good.
(sigh)
Isn't there anything
I can help you with, Twilight?
Don't worry about it
Spike; it's all good.
I think she's right.
It looks like we've
got it, Spike.
Looking great, everypony!
Why don't you find a quiet spot
and finish reading your comic?
Weren't you right at the part
where Hum Drum was about
to stop the villain?
Hum Drum never
stops the villain.
He's just there
for comic relief.
(clatter)
(grunts)
Rarity, let me give
you a hoof with that.
I could do it.
That's OK, Spike.
Pinkie Pie: Pony
Power! Wheeee!
(sigh)
Mane-iac breaks
into the museum...
OK. Here we go.
(groan)
What a surprise, Hum
Drum is in the way again
while the Power Ponies
do all the work.
I guess I know what
that feels like.
(gasp)
Wait.
What? How can
that be the end?
What's that?
You can retry.
What? You can return.
(groan)
I know I saw a magnifying
glass lying around
last time I was here.
Applejack: Spike!
Where are ya, Spike!
Rarity: We're breaking
for tea and biscuits!
Spike!
You can return to the
place you started
when the Mane-iac
is defeated.
Huh?
Take a closer look...
...to join the
adventure in this book?
What does that even mean?
(zap)
Whoa! Cool!
Spike! What are you--
Help!
Spike!
(grunts)
(gasp)
(screams)
Wheee!
♪ (mysterious)
Is this Maretropolis?
♪
Applejack: Somepony wanna tell
me what the hay is going on?
Holy new
personas, ponies!
You're the Masked Matter-Horn.
Fili-Second.
Zapp.
R... Radiance.
Mistress Mare-velous.
Saddle Rager.
You're the Power Ponies!
(crash)
Power Ponies!
(evil cackle)
How kind of you to join us.
Huh?
(evil laugh)
(evil cackle)
Did she just call
us "Power Ponies"?
You're the...
the superheroes
from my comic book.
It somehow zapped
us all in here.
So somepony zap us
back out.
My comic book...
It said the way to get
back to where we started
was to defeat the Mane-iac.
Your arch-nemesis.
Time for the mane event!
(crash)
Rainbow Dash: Pinkie!
Where'd she go?
Wheeeeeee!
She could be miles
away from here by now.
Pinkie is Filli-Second,
the fastest pony in
all of Maretropolis.
(snap)
(shout)
(struggling grunt)
(cackle)
Twilight, freeze her mane!
Do what?
You're the Masked Matter-horn.
You can shoot all kinds of crazy
power beams from your horn!
(zap)
You know, I'm beginning
to enjoy this.
(laugh)
(gasp)
(crash)
Dash, quick!
You're Zapp and your
super-power is controlling
the mighty forces of nature!
Unholster the lightning bolt!
(zap)
(thunderclap)
Lightning! Not a tornado!
(shriek)
(screams)
Fluttershy, you're Saddle Rager!
Lose your temper
and you'll turn into a huge,
super-strong monster!
Oh. Gosh. That wouldn't
be very polite.
(groan)
Rarity, use your jewelry
to create attack constructs.
What's an attack construct?
Just think of
something... anything...
and your bracelet
makes it appear.
(smash)
Something useful!
The Electro-Orb!
Well, this has been quite the
mane-raising experience,
but I really must be going.
(clang)
Why, thank you, Hum Drum.
(evil cackle)
I'm Hum Drum?
Oh, no!
(screams)
Applejack! You gotta
help stop the tornado
from destroying the city!
But every time I move, this
darn lasso gets tighter.
You're psychically
connected to it.
Will it to where you
want it to go...
and it'll obey you.
♪
Pinkie Pie: Haha, That was spintastic!
Let me get this straight.
We've been sucked
into some kind of...
comic book world?
Technically,
it's called Maretropolis.
And if we want to get
back to Ponyville,
I think we have to
stop the Mane-iac
from using her doomsday
device to destroy it.
No biggie. I was
already awesome.
And now we've all
got super powers.
(sigh)
Almost all of us
have super powers.
But you must have
them too, Spikey-boo,
your character is
wearing a cape.
Yeah. For absolutely
no reason.
He's pretty much useless.
Good thing you're not
really Hum Drum then.
Yeah. Good thing.
So the six of us "Power Ponies"
will take care of Mane-iac
and get us back to Ponyville.
Spike, where is the Mane-iac
building her doomsday device?
Her top secret headquarters.
But you'd better
get there quick.
That glowing orb she just stole
is what she's going to use
to power it up.
Lead the way, Spike.
Then leave the rest to us.
(groan)
Spike: There it is.
Is that a... shampoo factory?
All right, Power Ponies,
here's the plan.
Rarity, you, me and--
Rainbow Dash: Come
on out, Mane-iac!
Or the Power Ponies
are coming in.
(thunderclap)
So much for
element of surprise.
Guess I'll just hang back
here doing nothing.
Fluttershy: I don't
think she's home.
Maybe we should just
come back later.
(maniacal laughter)
She's home.
Time to "Power Pony Up".
Oooh. Nice catchphrase.
♪
Freeze Ray!
(zap)
♪
(splat)
It's an improvement, darling.
♪
Hee hee hee! Ha ha!
(crash)
Oh, I do so love a
functional accessory.
(whimpering)
(zap)
My hair!
Seriously?
You aren't even just a
little angry right now?
Twilight Sparkle: Nice
work, Power Ponies.
Now let's take care of the
Mane-iac and get ourselves home.
I don't think so.
I have a city to destroy.
And I'm not about to let
the Power Ponies stop me.
Not this time.
Just watch us.
The Hair Spray Ray of Doom!
It stops you in your tracks
and renders your powers useless!
(hiss)
(clunk)
We'll just see about that.
(hiss)
(crackling)
(clink)
(evil laugh)
Fluttershy, please!
Just a little anger?
Well, I'm not so much
angry as I'm concerned,
bordering on terrified.
(hiss)
Don't spray!
(evil cackle)
Oh, Hum Drum, why in
all of Mare-tropolis
would I use the Hair
Spray Ray of Doom on you?
Rather pointless,
don't you think?
(cries for help)
(slam)
(clang)
♪
Spike: What am I supposed
to do? I'm useless.
No wonder my friends never need
me to do anything important.
They're the ones with
the super powers.
They've probably already
figured out how to escape.
(crash)
Or not.
(cracking)
(bell rings)
(hiss)
(crackling)
Congratulations, Power Ponies.
You shall live just long
enough to see me fire ...
the instrument of
your destruction!
(cackle)
Once the Electro-Orb
has powered it up completely,
this cannon will amplify
the power of my mane
one million times,
expelling an energy blast
that will cause everypony
in Mare-tropolis' mane
to grow wild!
(laughter)
You will be my weapon's
first victims,
and there is nopony who can
save you from this fate!
(evil laughter)
Fluttershy: Ahem.
I don't mean to interrupt,
but aren't you forgetting
about somepony?
Hum Drum? Little guy?
No superpowers whatsoever?
(laugh)
He's utterly useless.
(bell rings)
(hiss)
Please! Everypony knows you
just keep him around
because you feel
sorry for him.
Wah Wah!
Maybe in your world.
But in our world
Spike- uh, Hum Drum,
always comes through
when we need him.
Always.
(shouts of agreement)
I'm not like Hum Drum.
When my friends really
need me, I do come through.
And they need me now.
I see dementia
must be a side-effect
of prolonged exposure to
the Hair Spray Ray of Doom.
Tonight we stand upon the
brink of immortality,
for we collectively -
though mostly me -
have finally defeated our
most hated nemeses.
We have hurled the
brush of badness
into the now fearful face of...
(cackle)
goodness, and have struck
a blow for freedom,
in the name of oppression!
And nothing will stop us!
(laugh)
(bell rings)
♪
(hiss)
Way to go, Spike!
Get mad!
I'm trying.
Grrrr.
Tag! You're it.
Tag! You're it!
Over there!
There, THERE! IDIOTS!
(thunderclap)
Need a place to put these guys!
Hold it right there, partner.
(panicked screams)
Fluttershy, where are you going?
You seem to have
everything under control.
Fluttershy, we need you!
You have to power up.
I'm sorry.
It's just that nothing
is making me mad.
(smack)
(crash)
Oh, goodness.
Are you OK?
Are you kidding me?
I mean, I know you're evil
and everything.
but you'd hurt a teensy, little
harmless fire fly? Really?
WHY, YOU'RE JUST A
GREAT BIG... MEANIE!
THERE, I SAID IT!
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU'RE SO SPECIAL?
LIKE THE RULES OF COMMON
COURTESY DON'T APPLY TO YOU?
(voice deepening)
WHY DON'T YOU PICK
ON SOMEBODY YOUR OWN SIZE!
(huge roar)
(zap)
(roar)
(scream)
(crash)
(roar)
(smashes and roars)
Huh?
(spit)
Mane-iac: My mane!
(screaming) My mane!
(panicked squealing)
Once again, the
day is saved by--
(zap)
(screams)
(thud)
(cheers and whoops)
(excited chatter)
Did you see how I was raining
down a storm of justice
at the end there?
You catch how I was
wieldin' that lasso?
Cupcakes?
How did you--?
We had a good half-second before
we got sucked back out
of the comic and The
Mare-tropolis bakery
was only 65 blocks away.
I'm just glad to be back.
We wouldn't have made
it without you, Spike.
And I hope you realize
that just because we don't
always need your help,
it doesn't mean that we
don't think you're helpful.
And that you don't have
to have super powers
to be a super friend.
But I do have one question.
Where exactly did you
get that comic book?
This one I got in Canterlot at
The House of Enchanted Comics.
Well, I didn't know it meant
they were literally enchanted.
I thought it just meant like,
the comics they sold there
had really enchanting
story lines.
Hey wait up! I'm an important
part of this team; remember?
(zap)