Four more months.
I bet you're excited, huh?
Oh, my, I uh...
I could be excited.
I don't really know.
I wasn't really thinking...
Come on. You gotta
be excited.
Oh, well, I guess
maybe I'm a little,
kind of sort of excited...
I thought so.
Yeah. So, um...
why am I excited?
Because the next Daring Do
book is coming out
exactly four months from today!
THAT'S how exciting it is!
So what amazing, incredible,
awesome adventure
do you think Daring Do will
have in her next book, huh?
Will she at long last
stalk the Fortress of Talocan?
Only to be forced to
contend with its dreaded
and impenetrable
arrow defense?
And if so, could her skill,
quick wits and courage
possibly carry the day?
Or will her next adventure
bring her face-to-face
with the vast and
horrible Ahuizotl himself?
Would she cower?
Turn tail and run?
Or would she fly at
him full bore,
knowing full well
against all odds
that the greatest challenge
she'd ever faced
was still sure to
be no match for--
Look out!
Oh, I'm not so sure she's going
to last another four months.
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Three months and
twenty-six days.
twenty-six days!
Three months and
Hey Twilight, aren't
you excited that--
So glad you finally made it!
What's everypony doing here?
We're having a holiday party.
So what holiday would today be?
National Random
Holiday Party Day.
Whoo hoo!
I'd never heard of it either.
But the punch is quite tasty.
You might say the
secret ingredient is...
A secret.
How come nopony
bothered to invite me?
I came to invite you personally.
But it seems you were
a speck too busy
reading the last Daring Do
book for the twelfth time.
Yeah, well, in three months
and twenty-six more days
I'll be able to read
the next one.
Oh, haven't you heard?
The release of the next book
got pushed another two months.
Two more months?!
I've been waiting
so long already,
I don't think I can take
another two months!
I'll never make it!
Yeah, I can vouch
for that.
Did they give a reason?
The publisher just said
author A.K. Yearling
won't be able to finish the
book for another two months.
Cupcakes?
How could you possibly
know that before me?
I'm the series' biggest fan!
I'm just as big a fan as you.
In fact, I'm the one who first
introduced you to the books.
Remember?
Oh. Right.
A.K. Yearling just might
be my favorite author.
I know everything about her.
Where she grew up.
Where she studied literature.
Where she wrote
the first Daring Do book...
Where she lives?
Uh, no...
though I could probably
find out somehow.
Why?
Don't you get it?
The new book is obviously
delayed because she needs help
dealing with whatever everyday
nonsense is distracting her
from spending her every living
breathing second writing!
So I...I mean fans like me,
can get to read the
next book ASAP!
Think about it.
We could help her with her
laundry, buying her groceries,
cooking her meals.
Whatever.
Now who wouldn't
appreciate that?
Hmm, I don't know.
What she probably wants most of
all is respect for her privacy.
She can always just say no.
Mmh... I suppose you're right.
Of course I am.
So how's about
getting that address?
You see what I mean?
Why would she live in this
remote part of Equestria
except to keep folks from
intruding on her privacy?
We should respect--
I think I spotted
the house!
We're super-close.
This way!
Wait!
Oh no!
What happened?
Apparently, somepony has intruded
on her privacy
pretty hard already.
Ooowee. Somepony really
trashed this place.
Hmm. Maybe.
Or...
maybe A.K. Yearling's just
a terrible, horrible,
unbelievable slob.
I hope A.K.
Yearling's all right.
Oh no! What if something
terrible happened to her?
I know! There might
be no more books!
Uh, but of course I'd be
worried about her, too. Heh.
What are you all doing here?
Uh..A...K...Yearling?
We didn't do
this; we swear!
What have you done to my house?
We didn't do this,
Ms. Yearling.
Agh!
We're awfully glad to
see you're all right.
OK, clearly this
isn't the best time,
but I just gotta say how much
we all really love your books.
Heh heh.
Ah. It's safe.
Great!
Maybe now would be a good
time for me to ask her
how we can help move the
new book along a little faster.
Chop chop.
Rainbow Dash, a
minute please.
A.K. Yearling has
made it pretty clear
that she wants to
be left alone.
We need to respect
her wishes.
You should tell that
to those guys.
A.K. Yearling IS Daring Do!
A.K. Yearling and Daring Do
are one-and-the-same.
My mind is officially blown.
Aw, come on. I knew
it all along.
Amazing.
Incredible.
Wow! So much action!
Wheeeeeee!
Daring Do!
Many thanks, Daring Do.
As you probably surmised, our
earlier search for this treasure
was unsuccessful.
So kind of you to
find it for us.
Give it back, Caballeron!
That's Dr. Caballeron to you!
He's from Book 4: Daring
Do and the Razor of Dreams.
He wanted to partner with
Daring Do on her adventures.
I know. But she
refused.
I can't believe it.
The real Daring Do and
the real Caballeron!
So let me guess:
Ahuizotl has put you up to this.
You're stealing the
ring to give to him
so his hold on the
Fortress of Talocan
will be good
for Eight Centuries
as foretold by prophesy.
Close...
but no.
I'm going to sell this
to him, make a bundle
and retire from
archeology in splendor.
Caballeron, you fool!
You're dooming the valley
to eight centuries
of unrelenting heat!
To market, henchponies.
Uh... should we go in
and help her maybe?
Oh. Right!
Are you OK?
I've got this.
Um... She was just
trying to help, Ms. Do.
Daring Do doesn't need help.
She handles her
business herself.
We've got to go help!
You heard her. She
says she works alone.
How can we just stand
by and do nothing?
You know what's at stake here?
Ahuizotl has sought control
of the Tenochtitlan Basin
since Book 3.
True, but in Book 4,
she defeated Ahuizotl
and secured control of the
Amulet of Atonement,
dispelling the dark magic
of the Ketztwctl Empress
and thus protecting the basin
with the Radiant
Shield of Razdon.
But the Radiant
Shield of Razdon
is vulnerable to the
dark enchantment
of the Rings of Scorchero.
But are you forgetting that
the rings were scattered
to the four corners of
Tenochtitlan,
thus rendering the dark
enchantment powerless?
Only if you assume that the
rings have yet to be retrieved
and the ring
Caballeron just stole
isn't the last to completely
restore the dark tower
and its cruel hold
on Tenochtitlan.
Did you ever think of that?
You gotta admit, Rainbow
Dash makes a pretty good point.
We've gotta help Daring
Do retrieve the ring
for safekeeping
before it's too late.
OK. But sounds to me
like we're in way way way
over our heads.
We're going to need a
carefully thought out plan.
I'm coming,
Daring Do!
That's not a plan!
Come on, come on, come on!
Bingo!
Here I come, Daring Do.
To join in adventure with
the greatest, bravest, coolest,
most incredible hero
I could ever...
OK, maybe I just need a sec.
Just another adventure.
No big deal.
Get a grip!
I got this.
Though doing it
alongside Daring Do?
Wow, maybe I could get my
picture taken with her.
Or an autograph.
There you go again.
She's just a pony like
any other pony.
A pony who stops entire
armies of bad guys
with nothing more than
her bare hooves
and an attitude and
Ow.
Ow... That's starting to hurt.
Aargh!
Ow!
Stop!
Oh. It's just you.
Wait, don't go!
Think fast. This is your
big chance to impress her
with your quick wit and courage.
I am suuuuch a huge fan.
Heh heh heh heh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me help you.
I promise I can be
a huge, huge help
if you just give
me a chance.
I...
Work...
Alone.
But why won't you let me
team up with you just this once?
My work always
involves secrets,
and since you never know
who you can trust,
it's best never to
trust anypony.
But just because you
can't trust some
doesn't mean nopony
can be trusted.
Look, I don't have
time to argue.
Neither do I. Let's go!
I can't believe I'm
even talking to her.
Looks like they decided
to have an early dinner
before making their way
back down the hill
to the marketplace in town.
Oh, I see! You're
going to ambush them
like you did in Book 4
at the Horavian Caves.
Or maybe that neat
trick you did in Book 3
where you swoop in and
knock three guys down
with one swing. Or maybe...
OK. I'll be quiet now.
Just watching very
quietly. Shh.
So what kind of ambush
are you gonna use then?
Wow!
I have been led to believe
you have in
your possession
an item of significant
importance
that might be for sale.
Oh, um, well, I did have
another buyer lined up.
But he's not here, so...
sounds like we have a deal.
Caballeron!
Ahuizotl!
The ring!
Be cool, Rainbow Dash, be cool.
She's got this.
The ring, Daring Do.
Give it to me.
Now Ahuizotl, you know
I love you,
but I can't give you the ring
till I've properly proposed.
Interesting.
Because my friends here
have a proposal of their own.
Meow!
Bring it!
Come on, Daring Do, come on!
Daring Do. I've got your hat!
Want me to toss it?
Daring Do! DARING DO!
Aaaaahh!
Don't worry, Daring Do.
I'll come help you!
Whoa!
Don't bother.
I'd say you've already
"helped" plenty.
What have I done?
Oh, thank goodness
you're all right.
Quick. Where does it hurt?
In here.
Daring Do and the ring have been
captured by the dreaded Ahuizotl
and it's all my fault.
Dash, I'm sure whatever
you did was an honest mistake.
Whatever.
Let's just go home.
We can't go back now!
Looks a might like she
needs our help more than ever.
Trying to help is how I got
in this mess in the first place.
You were right, Twilight.
We should've stayed out of this.
Look, there's more going
on here than meets the eye.
In every Daring Do book
there always is.
We can't turn our backs on her.
She doesn't want
my help, Twilight.
Perhaps.
But she might
need it anyway.
No. My hero's way
better off without me.
This don't
sound like you.
Where's the Rainbow Dash
who would help anypony
at the drop of a hat?
Or pith helmet, as
the case may be.
She's here, where she's
got no business being.
She should be at home.
It's fine to look up
to Daring Do,
but you've put her
so high up on a pedestal
you can't even see your
own worth anymore.
She's in the fortress
and we're here.
And we wouldn't be who we are
if we didn't go in after her.
And neither would you.
So are you with us or not?
Surrender now, Ahuizotl, or
I'll be forced to take you down.
Oh, Daring Do, I will so miss
your amusing laughter-jokes.
Now I must leave to commence
the ring-placing ceremony
to unleash 800 years of
unrelenting sweltering heat.
Gotcha!
You can flap too, you know.
I was just about to save
myself, you know.
Of course.
I just thought you
might need this.
Have I mentioned yet
that I work alone?
Have I mentioned yet that
you're lucky I don't?
Drop the ring,
Huiz-whatever-your-name-is.
Place the ring, quickly!
Get it!
Come with me.
Help me get all these rings off.
If we can remove the giant
ring at the bottom,
the whole fortress
will collapse.
Was this your
plan all along?
I had to find a way to
get into the fortress.
You did it on purpose?
But I thought--
Didn't count on how heavy
this ring would be, though.
Guess having a little
help can be handy sometimes.
Stop her!
You can flap too, you know.
Ponies! Run! This place
is going down!
Daring Do!
I will have my revenge!
Could never have done this
without you, Rainbow Dash.
I've got a book to finish!
Just had the coolest adventure
with the coolest pony ever.
Came this close to blowing it
because I got so wrapped up
in how awesome she was, I
almost forgot how awesome I was.
Good thing I didn't, 'cause it
gave me a chance to show her
how important it is to put
your trust in somepony else.
Package from A.K. Yearling.
Sweet!
The new book a week
before anypony else gets it.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, oh my GOSH!