♪
Twilight: Sweetie Belle,
maybe we should run
through the steps
another few times before
you try it on your own.
Nope. Ready to give
it a shot!
OK then.
(grunt)
Can't seem to...
(grunts)
(thud)
Agh! I think I threw
my neck out.
Aw, you're OK.
A little more magic practice and
lifting brooms'll be a cinch.
I doubt it.
That thing weighs a ton.
Hey, has anypony
here seen my--?
Oh. There it is.
♪ (whistling)
Hmph. I'll never get my
cutie mark for this.
Maybe not.
But I'm happy to keep
helping you learn
just for the fun of
it as long you like.
♪ (whistling)
Hey, who's gonna
clean up this mess?
This is no mess!
These are the carefully
arranged pieces of a unicycle
I took apart and will be
putting back together
as soon as Twilight
shows me how.
Scootaloo, I already told
you I won't show you how.
But I'll help you
find the instructions
so you can figure
it out yourself.
Blech, I hate research.
To your left, third
shelf from the bottom.
You'll find it in no time.
Thanks so much for
helping us all learn
these new skills, Twilight.
Always glad to pass on my love
of learning for learning's sake.
Only I'm afraid I'll never get
the hang of this potion-making.
Did you follow the magic
plant-growing formula
I gave you?
Well, uh more or less.
Well, let's try it out
on this apple seedling
and see how we do.
Ooh, I hope this works!
(poof)
(coughing)
(gasping)
(giggles)
Laying it on a little
thick there, aren't we, pal?
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
HoH version
♪
Diamond Tiara: Yoo
hoo! Gather round!
It's time!
(excited curious chatter)
As you all know, I had
promised to put on an amazing
first-time-ever acrobatic
display for you all today.
(cheers)
I know. It's so exciting.
But I'm tired.
(disappointed sighs)
But I did not wish
to disappoint you all,
so I brought my butler
Randolph to do them for me.
♪
(thud)
(cheers)
That was amazing,
Diamond Tiara.
I know. I don't
know how I do it.
I can't believe she
gets so much attention
without even really
doing anything.
She's using somepony
else to build herself up.
And without even putting in the
effort to learn her own skills
like we do.
Hey, come to think of it,
if we get really
good at the stuff
Twilight's teaching us, we could
be the big shots around here
for a change. Hmm...
Check this out.
And check this out.
(pop)
(impressed chatter)
And check this out.
Whoa!
Hey! Put me down!
(giggling)
Hey, can't you
hear me?
Huh? Wha?
I was asking if your sister
Rarity will be taking you
to Manehattan anytime soon.
Because if she is, maybe
you can meet up with us
while we hang out with a
bunch of famous celebrities.
Cool!
Wow, that's pretty
nice of you guys.
Actually, my sister
hasn't offered to take me
to Manehattan anytime soon.
Yeah, we figured.
Bump. Bump. Sugarlump. Rump.
(mean giggles)
Oh yeah? Well, I don't have to
go all the way to Manehattan
to hang out with the famous
and super-cool ponies.
Me and my friends hang out with
Princess Twilight all the time!
Did you say
"Princess Twilight?"
You hang out with
her all the time?
For real?
More like just once a week.
She helps us learn
cool new stuff to do.
That we actually do.
Ourselves!
♪
You must bring me
along next time you go!
Bring us along!
Tiara: I mean we used to see
her around town all the time.
And I thought whatever.
Me too. I thought that.
But now she's a Princess, which
makes her totally awesome.
Plus she has wings.
And she's an Alicorn.
So can I?
We?
Go?
I don't think
we should.
Won't you two excuse
us for a moment?
We should totally say yes.
This is a golden opportunity!
Are you kidding?
I don't want them laughing at
us while I'm mixin' potions
and accidentally sendin'
plants into choking fits!
But don't you get it?
They'll have to
learn something, too.
And they won't be able to laugh
at us when they're so busy
trying to learn
stuff of their own.
I must admit it's kinda fun
to see them working hard
to get on our good
side for a change
Diamond Tiara: Oh my gosh, a
princess lives in there.
And I'm about to go
inside and see her!
I can't even tell
you how excited I am!
I can't either!
(knock knock)
Now remember, Twilight takes
this time out with us
so we can learn stuff.
Hey there, guys!
Come on in.
(swooning screams)
Princess Twilight!
Oh! It's really her!
Oh my gosh! I don't believe it!
Oh, and uh, you
brought guests.
Great.
Princess Twilight, it is such
a thrill and honor to be here,
you have no idea.
Oh my gosh, who dyes your tail?
I so have to
get that done.
Actually, it's not dyed.
I've always--
Diamond Tiara: (gasp) Are
those books in there?
What a bold design choice.
You should so do that, Di.
I know, right?
Listen. I'm all for helping
as many ponies as I can,
but maybe we should keep
these weekly visits
just between us, hm?
OK, which one of you
wants to practice first?
Shouldn't they go first?
No silly, I set up Twilight
Time especially for you.
Applebloom, go ahead.
Let's see how your plant
potions are coming.
I can't believe I
let you talk us
into bringing
guests yesterday.
I didn't hear them laugh
at us once, Applebloom.
Because they laughed
on the inside.
Don't worry.
We won't make that
same mistake again.
Oh great.
Look who showed up
to make fun of us.
So much for learning
skills to be big shots.
Hey, guess what!
I told everyone about your
special Twilight time!
Oh no, here it comes.
And they all want in!
Twilight Time! Twilight Time!
(continues)
Thanks to me, you three are
now the hottest thing around.
You're welcome.
Twilight Time! Twilight Time!
Twilight Time!
Uh oh.
Twilight time! Twilight time!
Wow! All these ponies really
want to meet Twilight
that badly?
We love you, Cutie
Mark Crusaders!
(cheers)
Diamond Tiara: Now
now, everypony.
Demanding time with a
Princess as an unruly mob
simply won't do.
Might I suggest you get
organized through us,
the Cutie Mark Crusaders'
nearest and dearest friends?
Everypony get in line.
No pushing. No pushing!
(excited shouts)
What a mess.
Of awesome!
Don't you see? We're really
and truly and certifiably
the biggest of the bigshots
in school right now!
Huh?
They all think
we're the greatest
because we're their
ticket to get time with
Ponyville's newest and biggest
celebrity: Princess Twilight.
We just said like two seconds
ago that inviting two ponies
to Twilight Time
was a big mistake!
and now we're supposed to
bring the whole class?
Relax.
I got this.
I don't like this,
Sweetie Belle.
You said not to invite them
to Twilight Time and I didn't,
so what's the problem?
This feels like a trick.
What's tricky about inviting
Twilight out for a meal
thanking her for all the nice
things she's done for us?
Seems like the least
we can do for the Princess.
Did someone say Princess?
When I told you when you could
come eyeball the Princess
at one of her favorite hangouts,
I said only two or
three of you, tops.
All: Oops.
She's coming!
OK, but stay out of sight.
As you wish, Sweetie Belle.
Yes. As I wish.
(chewing)
Mmmm. Mmm.
I didn't realize
how hungry I was.
I'm so glad you asked
me to join you here today.
(swallows)
I'm so honored.
(chomp)
You are?
When you first asked me to
help you develop new skills,
I thought: working with young
students so devoted to the joy
of learning purely
for its own sake?
What could be better?
You all remind me of
myself when I was your age.
(chewing)
Yes, well, we feel
the same way.
That's why we invited you here.
Because of our love
of learning.
(slurp)
Pinkie Pie: Twilight!
Haven't seen you here in,
like, forever-and-a-half!
I know.
I've been so busy I forgot how
delicious everything is here.
Totally!
Hey, what's going on
out there?
Oh, never mind. They're gone.
They're back!
Never mind. They're gone.
♪ La la la la la.
(camera shutters clicking)
Knock it off!
What in the world is
going on out--?
(gasp)
What was all this?
And this?
I couldn't help it.
When I don't smile in
a picture, I look sad.
Oh, we're gonna
look sad all right.
(door closes)
(gasp)
(birds chirping)
Uh, can I help you?
(excited screams)
Get my picture
with her!
Me first!
Hey, get out of the shot!
This is bad.
Twilight's gonna be
so ticked at us.
I told you this was
a terrible idea.
You seriously all
want my autograph?
OK, I'll sign just a
couple more for you,
but then I really must get
back to my little friends.
Oh, there you are.
Wow, to think I've been to the
Hay Burger so many times
never knowing it was the
regular hangout for a Princess!
This isn't my regular hang out.
I'm only here to be with them.
You mean, Princess
Twilight decides
where it's cool to go
based on where they go?
Wha - ?
Thanks guys. This was fun.
See you around.
(excited chatter)
I'm opening a new
lemonade stand.
Won't you come to the
grand opening?
I'll give you free
lemonade for a week.
Relax. I know exactly
how to handle this.
(snip)
(cheers)
Yippee! Lemonade!
♪
More lemonade?
Don't mind if I do.
♪
Done shining your hooves.
It's an honor to do
you the favor.
Wow, so bright I can see myself.
And so can I.
Nice job
bedazzling my bow.
What do I owe you?
Your gratitude is
thanks enough.
You three must come
to my pool party.
It'll be much
cooler than this.
Look who's inviting
who to her fancy house.
I believe we have arrived,
Cutie Mark Crusaders.
Yeah!
(splash)
(laughter)
Wow, this is nice, but
there's no one else here.
Why is this party
cooler exactly?
Because of all the
ponies we're keeping out.
This has been great,
but we have to go.
It's Twilight Time.
So we're coming
too, right?
Um...
Actually no.
We didn't have a chance
to ask Twilight, so...
Really? After all the
favors we did for you?
After all the favors
they did for you?
Twilight Time! Twilight Time!
(chanting continues)
OK. I know exactly
how to handle this.
Run!
Twilight time! Twilight time!
(struggling grunts)
We've got to beat them to
Twilight's so we can explain.
This way. I know a short cut.
Twilight time! Twilight time!
Then we run...like the wind!
(gasping as she speaks)
We made it! Quick, knock on--
(tire screech)
♪ (scary)
(knock knock)
(door opens)
Twilight, we can explain.
We know you said we should
just keep Twilight Time to us.
We didn't mean for so many
other ponies to be here.
Honest!
Oh, don't be silly.
I only meant that
for your benefit,
so you could get the most
out of our time together.
But if you want to share your
time with others, that's fine.
So you're not mad?
Of course not.
Come on in, everypony.
Spike made nachos.
(happy chatter)
Turns out we'll need
some more than that.
(sigh)
(chatter)
Before we start, we should
maybe get a bit more organized.
Ponies interested in
magic in this corner.
Ponies who want to learn
potions over here.
Bookworm
ponies over there.
Incredible.
Looks like everything's
working out just fine.
And I was so afraid Twilight
would be disappointed in us.
Told you I knew exactly
how to handle all this.
Thanks to all of you
for taking time out
to come learn new things.
Thank you, Princess!
We love you, Princess!
(cheers)
OK, OK, let's settle down.
If you want to thank anypony,
thank the Cutie Mark Crusaders
for so generously
sharing this time.
It was nothing, really.
We just felt it was
the right thing to do.
Hmph.
What a laugh.
Let's begin over here.
And what would you like
to learn, little one?
I want to learn how to
become a Cutie Mark Crusader.
And why do you want to become
a Cutie Mark Crusader so badly?
Because then I could get all my
classmates to do me favors
and stuff because I'm friends
with a famous Princess.
Hoo boy.
Is this true?
We wanted our time together
just as a way to be with you
and learn new things.
Really and truly.
Prove it.
Huh?
If it's true, then I'm sure
you've all been practicing
your skills over the past week.
Show me how much better you got.
Uh well, uh, we can't.
We kind of rushed over and
forgot to bring our stuff.
Hmm. I see.
No wait!
Hey everypony, you're in luck.
You came to learn,
but instead you're getting
dinner and a show!
Get ready, 'cause we,
the Cutie Mark Crusaders,
are about to lay on
you the amazing skills
we learned in Twilight Time!
(curious chatter)
Unfortunately, since we don't
have Scootaloo's unicycle parts,
she'll take apart and
put back together
one of the scooters
from outside.
Hey, that's my scooter!
You got us into this mess, kid.
Might wanna roll with us.
Huh?
Sweetie Belle: Applebloom
doesn't have her apple seedling,
so she'll just grab an
apple from the kitchen.
And I will begin by using
my magic to lift this broom.
♪
(clink clink)
(poof)
♪
♪ Ta da!
Become a tree!
Rise!
(thud)
(clatter)
(explosion)
That didn't turn out
quite how I had hoped.
Looks like Twilight
Time is over.
And look who's not the
Princess' entourage anymore.
All: Oooooh!
Guess they didn't come
here to learn after all.
Well, neither did any of you.
Awwwww.
We're really sorry, Twilight.
We made a huge mistake.
And we really and truly
did enjoy learning
new skills with you.
Guess we'll just have to keep
on doing it without you now.
Thanks, Twilight.
(poof)
Thanks.
♪
Sweetie Belle?
Remember a moment ago when you
asked me to "give you a chance?"
(grunts)
Awww, come on!
I guess Twilight must not
be so super upset anymore
'cause she's letting us do a
diary entry like our sisters do.
Boy, did we get our
priorities mixed up.
We started acting special
because we were friends
with someone special.
We almost forgot the real
reason she's special:
because she's our friend.
But she forgave us and, like
magic, things are good as new.
That's the kind of magic I
really want to get good at...
now that I'm getting so
good at the other kind.
Wow, all three of you have
made so much progress.
I'm really proud of you!
See you next time.
We're just glad Twilight
Time is back to normal.
Well? Almost back to normal.
I just hope no one sees us.
Because we're trying to keep
Twilight Time a secret now?
Or because we
look ridiculous?
A little of both,
actually.
(laughter)