Wow! I can't believe how
many ponies showed up.
I can.
I mean, finding out who
the Ponyville Days
Pony of Ceremonies is,
is a pretty big deal.
I didn't know Granny Smith was
on the Selection Committee.
Of course she is.
Ponyville Days celebrates
the founding of Ponyville
and she was right there.
I'm glad the Committee didn't
automatically pick me
so everypony gets
a chance to see
how great being
me actually is,
even though the Festival
is basically a party
and the Pony of Ceremonies
organizes the whole thing
so it would make
sense if they picked me.
Shhhhhh!
Citizens of Ponyville,
this year's applicants
were all exceptional,
but there can only be
one Ponyville Days
Pony of Ceremonies.
And that pony is...
Rarity!
Whoo whee!
All right, Rarity!
Congratulations, Rarity.
Do you know what
you're going to do?
Oh, I might have a few ideas.
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
I'm so excited for the Festival
I can hardly stand up straight.
Me, too. I'm glad
Rarity was picked.
I know she'll add a touch of
elegance to the whole thing.
Probably more than a touch.
Ahem.
This year's Ponyville Days
Festival designed by Rarity,
will feature various high
class events, such as...
A silent cider
auction and tasting...
Ooooh!
A Ponyville gala
in Town Square...
Aaaaah!
And, of course, a
Ponyville fashion show.
Ooooooh!
This year's Ponyville Days
Festival pony of ceremonies,
creates shimmering
couture of her own design.
And the theme is,
Small Town Chic!
Wow, Rarity! You really have
put a lot of effort into this.
I'll say.
I think it's going
to be magical.
Do you really think so?
Are you kidding?
I can't wait!
Oh, that's such a relief.
But, of course, I couldn't
possibly do it all on my own.
The festival is in three days!
Pinkie Pie and I can hang
lights and decorations
in the Town Square.
And I can get Sweet Apple Acres
all ready for the cider tasting.
That's just perfect.
And now Twilight, if you and
Fluttershy wouldn't mind helping
with the fashion show...
Of course.
I'd be honored.
I can focus on the one thing
I'm worried about most of all.
What?
Creating a Ponyville
Days Festival
fantastic enough to impress...
TRENDERHOOF!
Uh, who's Trenderhoof?
WHAT?
How can you not know
who Trenderhoof is?
Trenderhoof is only
the most amazing,
handsomest travel writer to
have ever traveled or written.
Before Las Pegasus became an
Equestria travel destination,
he wrote about it.
Before the culinary
revolution in Trottingham,
he discovered it.
He knows what's going to be hot
even before it's tepid.
Sounds like somepony has
a little bit of a crush.
Oh, Twilight.
"Crush" doesn't even
begin to describe it!
He's practically divine.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S COMING!
Thank you ever so much
for joining me, Twilight.
I don't think I could have
met Trenderhoof on my own.
It's no problem, but you
shouldn't be nervous
about meeting him.
Is that him? Do you see him?
Twilight, is he there?
Uh...I'm not sure.
You don't suppose he
decided not to come?
Twilight, I don't see him!
What if he doesn't arrive?
The whole festival
will be a disaster!
TWILIGHT, WHERE IS HE?
Ahem. Sorry.
Rarity, you have to
get a hold of yourself.
I mean, you haven't
even met him yet...
What's wrong?
Shhhhhhh.
It's him, it's him, it's
him, he's here, it's him.
Well, go up and talk to him.
I can't.
Um... Hi. Ahem.
Hello. Mr. Trenderhoof.
I am Rarity and I have been
chosen as Pony of Ceremonies
for the Ponyville Days Festival.
Please.
Call me Trend.
And over here will be the
climax of the Festival,
The Ponyville Days Gala.
Music. Dancing.
And of course a locally sourced
menu of delicious treats.
Reminds me of the Spring Fling
meets Manehattan Wedding
I wrote about in
Gallop & Prance.
Exactly! I can't
even describe
how much your work
has influenced me.
And finally, Sweet Apple Acres.
Ponyville's core, heh
heh, so to speak,
where our quaint
little hamlet began.
Oh! Breathtaking!
I've heard about it, of course,
but to see it in verite,
to stand on the soil
of a working farm.
You can really feel
the authenticity.
Oh yes! Uh, they really
do grow apples here.
Thank you, Rarity.
Thank you for
bringing me here.
This farm is truly
something special.
I had planned to transform it
into an elegant country inn
for the Festival,
but now I see just how
special it is au natural.
Au natural, indeed.
Who.
Is.
That?
Who? Applejack?
Ahem.
Why are you staring
at her like that?
I've seen a lot in
my travels, but...
I've never beheld such beauty.
Applejack.
The pony of my dreams.
Rarity?
Hello?
I brought my cider
tasting cup.
Are you ready to
go try the samples?
What's the point?
Rarity, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Is it something I said?
He doesn't like me.
What?
Rarity, I can't hear--
HE DOESN'T LIKE ME BECAUSE
HE HAS A CRUSH ON APPLEJACK
EVEN THOUGH I'VE HAD
A CRUSH ON HIM EVER SINCE
THE BEGINNING OF TIME
AND IT'S NOT FAIR!
Trenderhoof doesn't like you?
That's ridiculous.
Oh, Spike, how could you
ever know what it's like
to be totally
obsessed with a pony
only to find out
they're obsessed
with somepony else?
I mean, what could Applejack
possibly have that I don't?
Hmmm.
You know, I have such
respect for the work ethic
of Earth Ponies.
Uh, gee, thanks.
Granny Smith always said,
"Pick an apple a day
and keep trouble away."
How many varieties of
apples do you think there are?
On the farm or in all
of Equestria because--
I once had
an apple so rare,
they thought it
was extinct.
I ate four of them.
Is that a fact?
That's my thing.
I take the mundane,
the simple, the...
unappreciated, and
I make it relatable.
Well, I hope you can
relate to Ponyville.
Me too.
But enough about me.
I want to know about you.
What do apples
mean to Applejack?
Look, I'm glad you're
interested in Ponyville and all,
but I'm kinda busy
with my chores
and if I can't get 'em done,
there won't be a
Ponyville Days Festival
for you to write about.
Well, that
will never do!
Rarity, what are you wearing?
What, this old thing?
Aren't you too busy
planning the Festival
to keep making new
outfits for it?
I am, but the thought of
hauling apples inspired me
and I just couldn't
stop myself.
Really?
If there's one thing I
love, it's hauling apples.
I'm growing fond
of it, myself.
Maybe you two should
try it sometime.
I'm feeling a tad inspired.
♪ Without farm life there'd
be such disparity. ♪
♪ These thoughts I think
with great clarity. ♪
♪ Apples high to the sky,
She's the one of my eye. ♪
That fruit hauling
pony named..♪.
♪ ...Applejack.
Rarity, why do you
want to plow a field?
Is it me or could this
use a splash of color,
and maybe a wash?
Don't we need to check
on the gala decorations?
Yes, yes. Of course.
But Trend obviously has
a thing for farm life.
If I can't convince him that
I'm just as much of a farm hoof
as Applejack, I'll never get him
interested in the Festival.
The Festival.
Right.
And I do appreciate
your help ever so much.
I couldn't do a thing
without you Spikey pooo.
Well... that's what
friends are for.
Right! So!
Come... On... farm thing!
How does Applejack do it?
Well, it would help
if the harness was on right.
What are you doing?
I'm simply lending a
hoof with the chores...
...which I love
doing ever so much.
Well, if you're still
interested after the Festival,
I can teach you all about it.
But right now, I need to get the
plowing done if you don't mind.
Not at all.
She makes it look so easy.
I know.
Isn't she fantastic?
I really don't see what
the fuss is all about.
Now, Rarity, you be careful.
If you don't get the
bucking just right,
you could sprain a hoof.
I am perfectly familiar with
the applebucking process,
thank you very much, but while
you seem to rely on raw power,
I believe a certain amount
of style is required.
It's really more of a
dance, if you ask me.
Et voilà.
Well, your way is
definitely long on style.
Thank you.
Now if you'll all excuse me,
I have some more chores to do.
Inside!
Rarity, can I ask
you something?
Why, Trend, you can
ask me anything.
I've been meaning to ask
for a while and, frankly,
I'm sort of embarrassed.
Rarity...
Do you think Applejack would
be my date for the Festival?
Why don't you go ask
her yourself?
Phew!
That was close.
If you've come to apologize,
there's really no need.
What are you talking about?
Let's dispense with
the charade, shall we?
Listen, I know you really
want Trend to like you.
And he does.
Despite somepony's
best efforts.
I swear, I don't know why he's
paying so much attention to me.
And I don't know anypony who's
that interested in farming.
Not even me.
Well, maybe it's time Trend
met a real country pony.
Shouldn't you be
working on the Festival
instead of coming up with
new ways to impress Trend?
Oh, I'm sure you'd love that.
Well, I have a new
vision for the Festival.
And it's gonna be more country
than the whole Apple
Family put together!
Um, Isn't it a little late
to be changing the theme?
Applejack, what's going on?
I'm too scared to guess.
Firstly, I just wanna
thank you'all for comin'
and second I know
y'all will all adore
my new Festival theme...
Simple Ways!
Well, what's so funny?
Rarity, that is the silliest
getup I have ever seen.
It is a little funny.
Funny?
Rarity, you aren't
serious, are you?
Well, of course I'm serious!
Ahem...
Why wouldn't I be?
Because you would
never dress like that.
You like fashion and high
society and fancy things.
And I can like plowing fields
and hauling apples just as much.
But you don't!
How do you know
what I like?
Because I know you.
Well, maybe you don't know
me as well as you think.
And I suppose it's just a
coincidence that Trenderhoof
seems so interested
in country life too?
I don't know what
you're gettin' at.
Well, then I guess I'll
just have to show you.
Be my guest.
Now, if y'all will excuse
me, I have a hootenanny
of a Festival to put on.
Now, to be a model in the
Simple Ways fashion show,
you might think simple
means less is more.
Well, that just ain't so.
If you want to be real
simple, more is more.
Now y'all go off and make
yourselves look just like that.
Who's our next model
for the fashion show?
Um...
Apple Jewel?
Who the hay is that?
Is this some kinda joke?
Why, Rarity, what ever would
make you think I was joking?
Because you would never
wear an ensemble like that!
You like plowing fields
and hauling apples...
And I can like
fashion just as much.
But you don't!
Well, maybe you do not know
me as well as you think.
Fine.
But I got a whole
Festival to plan,
so if you're gonna start
modelin', just get on with it.
Life is a festival, and you
should celebrate it
by looking just like me, because
I'm a trend-setting Fashionista!
You're a trend-setting
Fashionista?
Why that's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever--
I mean, good for you.
I, on the other hoof, couldn't
care less how I look
long as I get the chores done.
Oh? Is that so?
Yes indeedy doodle.
Not me.
My mane needs to be perfectly
coiffed at all times.
Well, my mane is full
of dust and split ends.
My hooves are so polished you
can see your reflection in them.
My hooves are cracked and dry
from working in the fields!
I'm so fashion forward.
I wear droopy drawers.
I smell like rosebuds.
I LOVE BEING COVERED IN MUD!
Goodness! Your couture!
Oh, it's bad.
Will somepony
bring me a towel
to wipe this repulsive
filth from my hooves!
There's the Rarity I know!
Oh, Applejack, I'm sorry
I said all those things.
You're a true friend who
probably knows me better
than I know myself.
I don't know what I was thinking
wearing this ridiculous outfit.
I kinda know how you feel.
But you were just trying to help
me see how silly I was being.
And you were right.
Besides, that gown
looks just gorgeous on you.
I wish I hadn't ruined it.
Thanks. It's
nice ain't it?
It's magnificent!
Wherever did
you get it?
Oh. It's uh... one of yours.
I'll need 3 gallons of boiling
water and one ounce of detergent
START!
I'm moving to Ponyville!
Being the most interesting Pony
in Equestria is exhausting.
I want to leave my exotic,
exciting life behind
and live on a farm.
What?
Well, that's real nice, but I
sure hope you weren't thinking
of Sweet Apple Acres.
Oh.
Look, you're a fine
pony, but uh, well, I'm...
I think what Applejack
is trying to say,
is that there's something
unappealing about a pony
who'd change themselves so much
just to impress somepony else.
If somepony doesn't like you for
who you are, it's their loss.
Well, this is awkward.
Not at all.
In fact...
I think I know
just how you feel.
What do you think, Rarity?
Is it too late to go
back to Small Town Chic?
Not if I can help it!
Organizing the
Ponyville Days Celebration
was one of the hardest
things I've ever done...
But I learned an
important lesson.
Real friends will like
you for who you are
and changing yourself to impress
them is no way to make new ones.
And when you're as
fabulous as I am...
it's practically a crime.