Well, Boneless, looks like
our work here is done.
Yeah, those ponies
never partied so hard.
Thanks to me...
Cheese.
Cheese Sandwich.
Whoo hoo hoo!
That was a doozy!
Well, Boneless, looks
like our next party's
gonna be in...
Ponyville!
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
♪ Every single day there's
something new you can plan for ♪
something wonderful to do ♪
♪ But nothing makes me happy
like a day that I can say ♪
"Today I planned a party
and it's just for you!"
How's it going
today, Pinkie?
Great, thanks!
Got any streamers today?
You betcha! Big
party planned?
Don't ya know it!
♪ Don't have much time to
gather all the things I need ♪
♪ If I'm really going
to make this party fly ♪
♪ For today's another day that
all of Ponyville will say... ♪
♪ There goes the Super
Party Pony Pinkie Pie! ♪
♪ She planned our
first foal shower ♪
♪ Where we played
all sorts of games ♪
♪ Having so much fun as we chose
Pound and Pumpkin's names! ♪
♪ She planned my Cute-ceanera,
My Dad made me, I won't lie ♪
♪ I demanded all the best
I suppose she passed the test ♪
♪ Sure it was pretty good
all thanks to Pinkie Pie ♪
Thanks. I guess.
What color paints
do you need?
I'm gonna need the
full rainbow!
A paint brush too?
Yes, if you please!
And what from me?
Your biggest banner!
This party's going
to be the best!
I don't doubt it!
♪ Every single day there's
something new we can plan for ♪
something wonderful to try ♪
♪ But nothing makes us happy
like a day that we can say ♪
♪ Today there'll be a party
planned by Pinkie Pie! ♪
I don't know how
she does it!
Wow, look at her go!
Oh boy, this is
going to be good!
Go Pinkie go!
♪ There's no other pony
like her ♪
♪ No pony that could be
♪ As great (As great!)
♪ As fun (As fun!)
♪ As our Super Party
Pony Pinkie! ♪
Oh! I am so, so, so excited
because today I'm planning
the birthday bash of...
RAINBOW DASH!
Yeah!
Rainbow Dash.
Yes, Pinkie?
You realize that by enlisting
me as your party planner,
I guarantee that this is
going to be the funnest,
most fantabulous, superbial
party in Ponyville?
Uh, yeah? I guess.
No guesses.
Parties are no picnic.
Oh, I like a nice
picnic party.
Oh!
Parties are serious.
And you have my certified
"Pinkie Party Promise"
that you will have the
best birthday party ever!
OK!
Great!
Now, who's ready to join this
Super Duper Party Pony
to plan this super
duper par-tay?
I am.
Who are you, stranger?
Name's Cheese Sandwich.
I plan parties.
What an amazing coincidence!
I'm Pinkie Pie and
I'm planning a party!
Oh, it's no coincidence,
my little pony.
My Cheesy Sense was a-tingling,
tellin' me a party
was in the works.
A Cheesy Sense? Ah!
Double Amazing!
I have a Pinkie Sense!
Yes. I sensed you did.
And I happen to be the
premiere party planner
in all of Equestria.
If there's a party in
need, there I'll be.
Be it wing-ding, hoe-down,
hootenanny, or shindig,
I'm your pony!
A pair of Party Pony
Planners in Ponyville?
What could be more perfect?
I'll tell you what!
Making this party epic!
Cause this isn't
just ANY birthday.
It's also the anniversary of
when I moved to Ponyville!
Good heavens, Rainbow Dash!
It's your birth-aversary!
Exactly!
So what do you say,
party planners?
Oh, I think we
can do it!
Oh, I don't think so.
I know so.
After all...
♪ The Super-duper-party-pony.
♪ That pony is me!
♪ I always knew that was the
kind of pony I would be. ♪
Me too!
C'mon ponies!
Who here likes
to party?
Ha ha! You do! I can tell!
♪ When I was but a little
colt, I just wanted to play. ♪
Like me!
♪ But everypony told me
♪ "Cheese! That fun
just wastes the day!" ♪
As if!
♪ But when I threw a party
and I busted out some moves. ♪
♪ The ponies finally saw the
light and got into the groove! ♪
You know it!
♪ The super-duper-party-pony.
♪ That pony is me!
And me!
♪ You'll never meet another
party pony quite like Cheese! ♪
Uh, Pinkie?
Hey good lookin'!
Want some mayonnaise?
♪ My parties are all
off the hook,
I never plan them by
the book! ♪
♪ They start out fun
then whoops-a-daisy, ♪
♪ Everypony just gets crazy!
♪ Bored of snacks
made by your mom? ♪
♪ How 'bout a giant
party bomb! ♪
♪ Huge pinatas
filled with cake, ♪
♪ or dive into my
fruit punch lake! ♪
Geronimo!
♪ The Super-duper-party-pony.
♪ That pony is me!
♪ You'll never meet another
party pony quite like Cheese! ♪
Come on, kid! Take
it for a spin!
Golly! Thanks, Mister!
♪ Oh, when I throw a
Cheese party ♪
♪ be sure to not be lame
♪ and miss my
pie fights, wacky kites, ♪
♪ and streamers in your mane.
♪ Fizzy drinks, Hawaiian shirts
and brie fondue delight ♪
♪ You know that with
Cheese Sandwich ♪
♪ you'll be partying
all night! ♪
Come on everypony, let's
party down with Cheese!
You're really a
certified party Pony?
That's right!
That's my guarantee!
♪ The super-duper-party-pony
♪ That pony is me!
♪ But what about the super
party pony named Pinkie? ♪
Yeah! Now that's what
I'm talking about!
I am so stoked you're
here, Cheese Sandwich.
Yeah, you sure did
come on the right day.
Your parties sound
simply divine.
We're so lucky to
have you here.
Just doin' my job,
little fillies.
I mean, Pinkie Pie's parties
are fun and sweet and all,
but now this
party's gonna be...
...epic?
You said it!
No offense, Pinkie.
None taken.
My birth-aversary's
already lookin' way cooler!
You are my kind of party
pony, Cheese Sandwich!
You got that right,
Rainbow Dash!
All right, party ponies!
I've got some planning to do!
Pinkie!
Aren't you going to help
Cheese Sandwich plan the party?
That's OK. Heh heh.
He obviously has what it
takes to do it all by himself.
Really?
Yes, indeedy!
After all, if Cheese really
is the super-duperest
partyingest pony of them all,
maybe that means...
I'm not.
♪ For all my life all
I've wanted to do ♪
♪ Was make my friends
want to smile true ♪
♪ But maybe I was wrong
♪ and Pinkie Pie shouldn't
plan parties at all. ♪
♪ I'll try to get
up on my hooves ♪
♪ And try a different task
♪ I'll find something
new to do ♪
♪ There's gotta be more to me
Than planning a party or two. ♪
♪ I put away my party cannon,
I deflated all my balloons ♪
♪ The bubbles all burst
Now what is next for you? ♪
♪ For you..
Oh I remember this one:
my first party ever!
My whole family was there!
And that's Twilight's
Welcome to Ponyville party!
She didn't even expect
that one.
Oh, look at Gummy. He
just looks so excited
for his birthday party.
Mmmm...Shining Armour
and Cadence's wedding
sure was special...
Especially once
I got hold of the music!
♪ Oh look at those
happy faces! ♪
♪ All the parties
that I have thrown ♪
♪ I made them laugh
Have such a blast ♪
♪ A smile that's
all their own ♪
♪ They loved seeing me
The real Pinkie ♪
♪ Show them the time
of their life ♪
♪ like they've never known!
♪ Like they've never known!
♪ I've got to get back out there
Have to show them that I tried ♪
♪ For there's only one great
Party Pony that is Pinkie Pie ♪
♪ Won't let Cheese
Sandwich beat me, ♪
♪ Won't let him get me down
♪ For I am Pinkie,
♪ the bestest Party
Pony around! ♪
Rarity: I must say I
marvel at your superior
party-planning expertise,
Cheese Sandwich.
Well, they don't call
him the super-duper
Party Planner for nothin'!
That's it! This pony has got
to get her title back!
And I know just what to do!
Totally Awesome!
Best I've ever seen.
I can't believe it.
Freeze, Cheese!
I challenge you...
to a GOOF-OFF!
Oh no!
Not a Goof-Off!
What's a Goof-Off?
I have no idea.
This Cheese has stood alone
a long time, Pinkie Pie.
You think you
can out-goof me?
Oh, I don't think so.
I KNOW SO!
And the stakes are
high, Cheese Sandwich.
Whoever wins will be dubbed the
ultimate Super Duper Party Pony
and headline the Rainbow
Dash Birth-Aversary Bash!
And the loser?
DOESN'T!
So, are you in, Cheese?
Or are you boneless?
Nopony calls me boneless!
Right Boneless?
Then the Goof-Off
is on for High Noon!
Um, Pinkie? It's already 3:00.
Oh, well then. Make
it 3:10 to Goof-Off!
All right, everypony!
According to my official
Goof-Off Rule Book...
She actually has a
Goof-Off Rule Book?
Are you kidding?
Twilight can find a rule
book for everything.
Shhh.
The two competitors have
free range to Goof About,
be it by singing, dancing,
playing, prancing, joking,
or performing to make the
Judge chortle, chuckle, giggle,
guffaw, hoot and holler,
whoop it up, and party down!
The funnier, sillier, wilder,
and goofier, the better.
Rainbow Dash, since the winner
will be headlining your party,
you are the Judge.
Henh. Big, tense competition
on my birth-aversary.
What could be better?
Cheese Sandwich? Pinkie
Pie? Are you ready?
I was born ready!
I was ready before I was born!
Then...let the goofing begin!
♪ It's your birthday party
A very special day ♪
♪ I've got a song
won't take long ♪
♪ I just wanted to say
♪ Happy, happy, happy, happy,
happy, happy, happy, happy, ♪
♪ happy, happy, happy,
happy birthday to you! ♪
♪ If you wanna be the
life of the party ♪
♪ but you're feeling just
a little uptight ♪
♪ Call the doctor, beg and plead
"Doctor tell me what I need!" ♪
♪ Try to put a little
cheese in yer knees! ♪
♪ Bubbles and balloons
Bubbles and balloons ♪
♪ What's a birthday party
without bubbles and balloons ♪
♪ Star-shaped or trapezoid
Look what I can do ♪
♪ Only Pinkie Pie can make
a bubble shaped like you! ♪
♪ Just let yourself go floppy
For now this is your chance, ♪
♪ Pretend you have no bones and
do the Rubber Chicken dance! ♪
Hit it, Boneless!
Cooler than a rubber chicken
And tastier than cake
Come on you let's party
down and do the Gummy shake
Hit it, Gummy!
Uh huh, you know it!
Shake it!
'Cause I like to make you
smile, smile, smile, yes I do
♪ It fills my heart
with sunshine ♪
♪ all the while, yes it does
'Cause all I really
need's a smile, smile, smile
From these happy
friends of mine!
That's my song!
What do you mean?
I have no idea what
you're talking about!
That's it!
♪ Roll out the party cannon
♪ When you hear the
party canon song Kaboom! ♪
♪ Why should you compromise
Try this one on for size ♪
♪ 'Cause nothing
quite says cheer ♪
♪ Like the ringing in your ear
♪ Of the cheese supreme
cannon bomb surprise! ♪
♪ Dale, dale, dale
No pierdas el tino ♪
♪ Porque si lo pierdes
Pierdes el camino! ♪
Rainbow's not having
the best party ever.
I...I broke the "Pinkie
Party Promise."
STOP! The Goof-Off is off!
But I haven't named a winner.
You don't have to.
I forfeit.
Which means, Cheese
Sandwich wins!
Ha ha ha! ... I do?
Yes, you get to headline
Rainbow Dash's party.
But what about
you, Pinkie?
I...I don't!
Pinkie, wait!
I'm sorry I got all swept
away by Cheese Sandwich.
We all are.
Don't know what
got into me.
Sorry, Pinkie.
No, I'm sorry I let my
pride get in the way
of you having the best
birth-aversary ever.
Cheese Sandwich really is a
Super Duper Party Planner
and he'll be a
terrific headliner.
I should have been a big
enough pony to admit that
and let you have your day.
But don't you get it?
You're both Super
Duper Party Ponies!
Sure, Cheese Sandwich is
a great guest party pony.
But you're Ponyville's
permanent party pony!
Nopony could ever
take your place
and we could never have
a party without you!
Rainbow Dash is right.
I never meant to take
your place in Ponyville.
I just wanted to show you what
a great party pony I am, Pinkie.
Why me?
Well...
♪ I fear I told a little fib
♪ About my pony past
♪ I hope that when
you hear the truth ♪
♪ You will not be aghast.
♪ I wasn't quite the super
party pony like I claimed ♪
♪ The fact is that
I was so shy, ♪
♪ Nopony knew my name.
♪ I stumbled into Ponyville
One afternoon by chance ♪
♪ And found the biggest ever
celebration party dance ♪
♪ Everything was perfect
♪ Cheer was filling
up the place. ♪
♪ And I saw that every pony
had a smile upon their face ♪
♪ I vowed that day
to change my life ♪
♪ The past I did set free.
♪ For now Cheese Sandwich was
a party pony full of glee ♪
♪ A super-duper-party-pony
that's what I became ♪
♪ I traveled all Equestria
and all did know my name ♪
♪ But that never would have
happened on my own ♪
♪ I'll tell you why...
♪ For the one who threw that
party, it was you, Pinkie Pie ♪
Me?
Yes!
Really?
Ha! Really!
So I was the pony that threw the
awesomely spectacular party
that inspired you to become
an awesome spectacular
party thrower?
Swear on cammonbare!
Enough with the warm
fuzzy stuff, you two.
It's my birth-aversary and
you've gotta throw me a bash!
Yeah!
Let's go!
♪ Super-duper-party-ponies,
that is me and you ♪
♪ A party thrown by one is
good, but not as great as two! ♪
♪ Come on and let's
join forces ♪
♪ Have twice the expertise
♪ Now let's all go
to the party ♪
♪ planned by Pinkie Pie
and Cheese! ♪
All right, everypony!
We are here to celebrate
the birthday...
And anniversary...
of Rainbow Dash!
Hey, everypony!
Who's ready to get
their party on?
Hit it!
♪ Get your hooves up the party's
starting now right now ♪
♪ Everypony, everypony
get down ♪
♪ Time to make a wish,
better make it right now ♪
♪ It's been a year and today
is your birthday party ♪
♪ Make a wish
It's your birthday ♪
It's your birthday party ♪
♪ Make a wish
It's your birthday ♪
It's your birthday party ♪
Cheese Sandwich!
I gotta tell ya! You and Pinkie
have totally made this
the best birthday-anniversary
super combo ever!
It's totally...
...epic?
Yeah, it is!
That's all I needed
to hear, little filly.
Just a little memento
of my visit.
You're giving me your special
rubber chicken friend?
Oh, he's not the only one.
Well, Boneless Two,
another job well done.
But it's time we mosey along.
Another town, another party.
I never did get
that pony's name.
CHEESE SANDWICH!
Oh yeah!