♪
Fluttershy: OK,
everypony, as you know,
the adorable fairy
creatures known as Breezies
are about to come
through Ponyville.
Yes! It's so exciting!
I can't wait for Rainbow Dash
to make the breeze for them
so I can see how cute
they are up close!
I've never done it before.
Not that I won't be
totally awesome at it.
Because I totally will.
And that breeze
is very important.
But so is cheering on those
teeny, tiny little things
so they have the confidence
to ride that breeze
to their native land.
Did I mention how tiny they are?
So tiny.
I was thinking we could do
a special Breezy cheer.
I LOVE CHEERS!
But these cheers
should be quiet cheers.
We don't want to
startle them.
They need to be
able to concentrate.
Why don't we try it?
You can do it, Breezies.
YOU CAN DO IT, BREEZIES!
Oh my.
Sorry, Fluttershy, I had
no idea how hard it was
to do a cheer quietly.
It's OK. Quiet doesn't come
naturally for everypony.
Let's try it again.
YOU CAN DO IT, BREEZIES!
Perhaps just a
little bit quieter.
You can do it, Breezies!
Just a little quieter.
(whispered)
You can do it, Breezies!
PERFECT!
Oh, um, I mean...yay.
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
HoH version
♪
♪ (mariachi band)
(whistling wind)
That's too strong!
We've gotta slow
this breeze down
or we're going to blow
those Breezies apart!
What I don't understand is
why they need the Pegasi
to make a breeze for them.
Well, you see,
it's the breeze
that activates the
Breezie's magic.
And that magic protects the
pollen they're carrying
from being destroyed.
So no breeze means no magic
means the pollen goes bad?
That's right.
And they only have two days
to get that pollen back
before the portal to
their home closes.
That's why it's
ever so important
that we help them make their
way through Ponyville safely.
We certainly wouldn't
want to scare them
and divert them from their path!
Now you understand.
You certainly know
a lot about them.
Oh, thank you.
I went to see them
gathering their pollen
in Western Equestria.
♪ (majestic)
Um, Rarity, I hate
to weigh in with you
when it comes to fashion, but--
There's too much
purple on this, isn't there?
I KNEW it!
But Twilight
refused to admit it.
What? I--
Fluttershy: No, no. It's the
perfect amount of purple.
It's just that there's an awful
lot of sequins on your jacket.
Oh, darling, please! One can
never have too many sequins.
You can if they
reflect the sun
and the light catches a group of
Breezies right in their eyes
and blinds them long enough to
get them off their course
so they never get home!
I stand corrected.
I suppose there is
the rare instance
where one can have
too many sequins.
I'll just take
off my jacket.
♪ (angelic chorus)
I suppose this won't do either.
(quietly) Everypony, it's time!
Please welcome the Breezies!
♪
They're as cute as Apple
Bloom on the day she was born!
And would you look at those
adorable little packs
they carry their pollen in.
(high-pitched gibberish
giving an order)
So! Cute!
Can't! Take! It!
(growl)
Pinkie Pie! Can I hop on you
so I can see the Breezies?
May! Explode!
(thud)
(boing boing boing)
(wind whistles)
OH NO!
(high-pitched panicked squeals)
(horrified gasp from all)
Slow down the breeze for
the other group to catch up!
They're too far back!
We can't connect the breeze
to both sets of Breezies!
What if we speed it up?
Then the first group
will be going too fast
and will get separated
from each other!
(screams)
(frightened screams)
(shouting orders)
(frightened squeals)
(gasp)
Manglemarsh mooth!
He's right!
You must all gather as
close as you possibly can!
(cheers)
(squeaky cheers)
Muggledy Sarken dose?
Oh. I understand the language
of all kinds of creatures.
You must be so proud.
And you speak my language, too?
I can. This lot can
only understand you.
Clearly, they're not the
brightest bunch around.
(protesting squeals)
THAT...WAS...AMAZING!
I'm sorry we couldn't
get a breeze going
that would get them
back to the others.
Oh, it's not your fault.
I for one am very proud
of you, Fluttershy.
Leaping into action
like that.
I feel like I should design
you a special hero's gown.
Or a sash. At least a sash.
Spike: OK, OK, OK!
I know what you're all thinking.
Why don't you just say it?
I'm sorry! (sobbing)
This is all my fault!
I'm so, so sorry!
Oh, Spike, it's OK.
It could have happened
to any one of us.
OK. Thank you!
(angry squeaks)
Uh, I'm just going to
stay over here.
So Fluttershy, you want us to
get the breeze going again
so these little guys
can get a move on?
(clamouring)
Maybe we should wait
just a moment or so.
They've been through so much.
Just give me the word when
you think they're ready.
♪
Oh my, Twirly, you look
like you need a blanket.
Sampkin.
No problem.
Melanky?
Oh. Did you need
some more water?
(slurp)
Now who else needed a
hoof-knitted sweater?
(clamouring)
Hey there!
Can we come in?
Oh, of course.
But watch your step.
Oops. Sorry about
that little one.
We just wanted to see if you
thought the Breezies were ready
to give it another try.
Has it been an hour already?
My goodness.
Time flies when you're making
sure little creatures
don't feel that you're
abandoning them
to the cruel world.
But they're not going
to a cruel world, right?
They're going home.
Oh yes! That's right.
(clamouring)
On second thought.
I don't think
they're quite ready.
Marshkin pupskin larfer!
Farclop pannywafer!
Uh, what did he say?
I'd rather not say.
OK, well, I'm sure you
know what you're doing.
No one knows rare magical
creatures like you do.
We'll just wait for your word.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch very soon.
(door closes)
We need to go NOW or
we will never get home!
I wish we did not need
that stupid breeze
to activate our magic
or I would just force you
all to fly home right now!
Why do we have to need magic
to keep our pollen safe?
Now Seabreeze--
Why are you giving
in to these wimps?
If they had not been so
scared in the first place,
this never would have happened!
Well, that is just
not true, Seabreeze.
It was because of a
leaf and you know that.
Oh, please!
They have no idea what
they're doing out there!
Like you said, we need as
much time as we can get,
because they are so incompetent!
Well, I didn't say that
exactly, now did I?
(angry) Huh!
Oh, well, maybe a snack
will lighten the mood.
(excited chatter)
♪
(little burp)
Munfarzen.
You're excused.
Well, my Breezies? I
think we can all agree
that now that you've eaten and
you have a little energy
going in your Breezy bodies,
you're strong enough
to face the breeze!
I've loved having you here and
I hope I've made you all feel
loved and special.
But you have to go; no
pony here will deny that.
Seabreeze: There is nothing
special about these losers!
They cannot handle a
simple breeze home!
If they could just stick with
the program and listen to me,
we would be safe! AT HOME!
Home! Where everybreezie
is like us!
(sigh)
OK. Well.
A confusing pep talk,
but nonetheless,
I do know that if you
don't leave soon,
you may never make it back
and that would be terrible.
Achoo!
Multy marshkin follow.
(cough cough)
MULTY marskin toomba too.
I had no idea you
all have colds!
Really? All of you?
(coughing)
Oh dear. I can't let you
go out there sick!
What kind of a friend would
I be if I made you go now?
(excited chatter)
(angry gibberish)
(knock knock knock)
Hey, Fluttershy.
Just wondering if the
Breezies are ready to go yet.
Clock's kind of ticking
for them to make it back
before the door
closes on their home.
Oh yes. I mean, not quite.
Um, maybe just a
few more minutes?
(door closes)
Uh... all right.
We wait too much longer,
we'll have to create
such a strong breeze it may
be more than they can handle.
We just have to
trust Fluttershy.
She must know what
she's doing.
(happy chatter)
♪
(clatter)
All: Awwww!
Why are you spending
your time on this?
I will never get home!
Breezies, I must say,
Seabreeze has a point.
I think it's time for me to get
Rainbow Dash and her friends
so they can create the breeze
for you to get home.
(protests)
Oh. You're all awfully anxious.
I don't want you
to feel abandoned
or that I wasn't the most kind
host I could possibly be.
Doshin bafin dorm.
Yes, that does make sense.
Seabreeze, do you
think you could wait
just a couple more hours?
Seabreeze? Seabreeze!
Has anypony seen Seabreeze?
(gasp) Where is he going?
There's no way he can handle
being out there on his own!
(whistling wind)
(panicked shouts)
(frightened gibberish)
(crash)
(panicked shouts)
(buzzing)
(pop)
(scared squeals)
(buzzing)
(panicked shouts)
Fluttershy: Excuse me, bees?
Can you please back
off my Breezy friend?
He didn't mean any harm.
It was just an accident.
I'm working on a bee type dance
and was hoping you
could help me.
Does this bring to mind
any images for you?
Perhaps a bee?
(buzzing gets louder)
Excuse me!
I have done NOTHING but be kind,
but I guess that is NOT working!
You bees know better than
to hurt a helpless Breezie!
I demand that you go away NOW
or you'll have to answer to ME!
Mankylin!
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you for coming after me.
Of course!
You could have gotten
seriously hurt out there!
Ponyville is much too
dangerous for you!
One tiny acorn is a threat!
Yeah! I know.
That is one reason why
I have been trying to get us
to go from the beginning!
Oh my goodness.
I was just trying not to
hurt any creature's feelings,
my displays of kindness
may have cost you everything!
Time is running out and
you may never make it home!
That is exactly what I have
been telling all of them,
but they do not listen to me.
No Breezie
ever listens to me.
Seabreeze, I understand
your feelings are hurt,
but it's hard for them to hear
you when you're shouting
and being mean.
The message doesn't get across.
But what about those bees?
You were not nice to them
and that was the only
way they listened.
Yes, but they HAD to go.
And they wouldn't listen
to me any other way.
We need to go. Now!
(whistling wind)
(skid)
My dear Breezies,
I had to rescue Seabreeze
from serious harm.
And now I know more than
ever that you must leave
before it's too late.
You would never
survive in Ponyville.
Mulshy barfin gorfis.
I can't help you anymore!
In fact, I wasn't helping
you at all by being nice.
But the truth of the matter
is that I must be firm!
You must go.
NOW!
(sniff sniff whimper)
(door closes)
It's too strong!
I can't do it any lighter!
Neither can I!
Fly back! I'm going to try and
see if I can slow it down!
Now it's too light!
This will never get them home!
Oh my. Maybe it's because
there are too few of them.
When they started their
journey there was more of them
to face the breeze together.
I've been studying
an old spell book
from the Castle of
the Two Sisters.
There's a spell that
I think could help us.
This is probably going to
feel a little funny at first,
but you're going to
have to trust me.
I love new ideas that make
me feel funny at first!
(zap)
(gasps)
(zaps)
(poof)
(pop)
Whoo!
(poof)
(giggle)
♪
Marful fly bartontook.
Um, I mean, let's go.
♪
(whistling wind)
Marshkin parskin.
Mikar.
You can do this.
I am sorry for how I
treated you before.
It was not right that
I called you names.
I did not even really believe
those things I said.
I was worried we would never
get back to our home,
and I lashed out.
I know you can do this.
I believe in you.
Hold onto me, let us
join the group.
♪
(rushing water)
(gasps)
♪
Holy mini-sized paradise!
This is simply beautiful!
So much inspiration!
Where is my sketch
pad when I need it?
SO! STINKIN'! CUTE!
(excited chatter)
♪
You OK, Fluttershy?
I'm just so very happy they
got to be reunited
with their family.
(happy shouts)
We'd better get going
before the entrance,
well, exit for us, closes.
Goodbye, Breezies.
I must go now.
To remember us by.
Thank you.
I'll miss you.
I'll miss all of you.
Fluttershy: My experiences
with the Breezies
have helped me to see that
kindness can take many forms.
And sometimes being too kind
can actually keep a friend
from doing what they need to do.
Pushing them away
may seem cruel,
but it's sometimes the
kindest thing you can do.
Whoa. That was a close one.
OK, gather around!
(zap)
So, uh, I've always kind of
wondered what it would be like
to be a Gryphon.
Not a chance.
You sure? What about a
dragon? No?
It doesn't have to shoot fire!