♪
(chugging train)
Pinkie: (scream) Yes!
Best day ever!
We're all going to the Rainbow
Falls Traders Exchange.
And not just going.
We're accompanying a princess
on an official royal duty.
Please. It's not that
big of a deal.
There always has to be a
princess at the Exchange.
Last year it was
Princess Cadance.
This year it's me.
It's just a formality.
I'm sure none of
the other ponies
will even notice I'm here.
(cheering)
Look over there!
The Princess!
This is amazing!
(cheering)
Could be wrong, but I think
they might've noticed.
(giggle)
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
HoH version
Oh my goodness!
Rarity: You said it!
The Rainbow Falls Traders
Exchange is simply divine.
You can get anything
you want here.
If'n you got the
goods to trade for it.
(grunt)
Whoa!
No!
Thanks, Twilight. Phew!
One ding, nick or dent and this
Power Ponies comic book
wouldn't be in perfect mint
condition anymore.
And if you want to
trade for a mint comic,
you've gotta have a mint comic.
(excited murmuring)
I guess a pony who's here on
official princess business
has to expect a little fussin'.
But all I'm supposed to do
is settle disagreements
over whether a trade
is fair or not.
And since the rule is
that a trade is fair
as long as both ponies
get what they want,
there's never been a
disagreement.
So there's really no
reason for anypony
to treat me as
anything special.
Hi, can I help you?
(groan)
There's a pony here who's got
a signed, first edition
of Daring Do and the Quest
of the Sapphire Statue.
And I'm gonna get it!
I've been able to get first
editions of all the
Daring Do books except this one.
No pony's ever put
together a whole set.
And I'm gonna be the first!
If it hasn't been traded yet.
It's the only one
in all of Equestria.
Oh no! I'd really hate to
see you disappointed.
I did want to trade this
bear call I brought
for a bird whistle.
But getting that book
seems so important to you.
So if you need me
to help you first...
Normally, I'd say I
don't need any help.
But you're right: This
is really important.
I've gotta get that book!
Well, I'm off to take a gander
at some of the vintage stalls.
Did you say vintage?
Why, old and rare items
are so in style right now.
I'm hoping to get a
vintage item as well.
I just hope I brought
enough to trade.
I know what you mean, Rarity.
Hey, why don't we pool
our trade stashes?
Pool?
That way, if one of us finds
something real valuable
she can't live without...
She'll definitely
be able to get it.
Who could say no to
exchanging a single object
for such a huge
assortment of items?
Oh, yes, that is
absolutely brilliant.
I'm so glad I have a
friend like you, Applejack.
I feel the same way.
Then let's go shopping!
Um, shouldn't Your
Princessness be heading
to the royal box seats?
I may be the princess on duty,
but I don't think that means
I have to sit up there
all alone doing nothing.
Ever since I became a princess,
Celestia has been sending me
more books to read than ever.
The library is overflowing.
So I figured
while we're here.
I might as well trade away some
books I don't need any more.
Mm hm!
(gasp) There it is!
The first edition of Daring
Do and the Sapphire Statue!
It hasn't been traded yet!
Lucky for you.
Because I've brought my
most valuable possession
to trade for it:
(clang)
My lucky horse shoe.
I don't want it.
What?
It's just a rusty
old horse shoe.
That's not worth
anything to me.
But how is Rainbow Dash going to
get the book she really wants?
Well, she's not.
(sigh)
(thud)
Unless ...
she can get me that.
(snarls)
Ooh, an Orthros.
How cute.
The pony running the
Ancient Beast Stall
doesn't want
anything I got.
But if you can get
me the Orthros,
I'll trade you
the book for it.
You got it!
I don't know how, but somehow
we're gonna get that Orthros.
Oh, Applejack!
I am so glad I found you.
Me, too. You're not
gonna believe it.
(both at once)
I found a super valuable vintage
item I just have to have.
And all it's going to
cost is all our stuff!
Uh-oh.
So where is this
valuable vintage item
you want to trade
everything we have for?
There.
Where?
Right there.
But that's a dented
old pie tin.
A dented vintage pie tin.
The metal they used to fashion
this one helps cook the pies
up to five seconds faster.
They don't make 'em
like this anymore.
I am so glad you showed
that to me, darling.
(crash)
Because once you
see what I found,
you won't want to waste
our trade goods on that.
Just look at this
gorgeous vintage brooch.
It's one of a kind.
It looks exactly like the
one you're already wearing.
Well, yes, they
may look the same.
But I know it's older.
That's what makes it
so much more divine.
But that doesn't
make a lick of sense.
Why I wager if I
switched 'em up,
you wouldn't even
know the difference.
Oh, don't be silly;
of course I would.
So which is the vintage one?
That one, of course.
Ha! You're bluffin'.
Am I?
How can you tell?
Well, because...
Agh! I can't.
'Cause the one you want to
waste our whole stash on
is exactly the same as
the one you already got.
There's no way anypony
would notice the difference.
I'd say it's a lot more
likely they'd notice that
than some dented tin
that cooked a pie
a whole two
seconds faster.
It's five
seconds faster!
(growling)
(snap)
(threatening barks)
Yes, such a good
two-headed boy.
Yes you are.
Stop that!
Come on! Don't you
start now, too.
OK, I can see you're busy, so
I'll give it to you straight.
I need to trade this
horse shoe for ...that.
Nope.
(groan)
Down boy!
Watch out for the lamp.
(smash)
Well, I could use
another lamp.
A whole stand filled with
Discord-shaped lamps?
Seriously?
They really do have everything
at the Traders Exchange.
Will you trade a lamp
for my horse shoe,
so I can trade it for an
Orthros and get my book?
No.
But I'd trade it for
an antique chicken.
Great!
What's an antique chicken?
Oh, I got all kinds of
antique chicken statues:
I got your Blue Hens,
Speckled Greys, your...
OK, cool.
So will you trade
one for a horse shoe,
so I can trade it for a lamp and
then trade it for an Orthros
so I can get my book?
Well, let me think.
Uh, no.
(sighs)
But I'd gladly trade one of my
chickens for a crystal chalice.
(panting)
Hang on a sec.
(big inhale)
We need a crystal chalice
to trade for a chicken
to trade for a lamp to
trade for an Orthros.
So what are you
willing to trade for?
I'm guessing it's gotta
be some crazy thing
way across the Exchange.
Actually, I could use a
slightly rusty old horse shoe.
Yeah, but where am
I gonna find...wait!
I've got one of those!
Now that we've got the chalice,
this is gonna be a cinch.
Do you really think so?
All we gotta do is bring this
thing to the chicken stand
and we are--
(smash)
(horrified scream)
You want me to trade all
my books for a broken pen?
All right fine, you got
yourself a dea--
Stop! What are you doing?
I was trying to get rid of all
the books I don't need anymore.
For that?
Do you really want that?
Well, not really.
But I'm running out of
library space, so-
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh!
I can't believe that
almost happened.
But luckily it didn't happen.
Thanks to me.
What are you talking about?
According to the
rules of the Exchange,
a trade is only fair
if both ponies end up
with something they want.
You can't break
the rules.
Did anypony see you do it?
I don't think anypony saw.
But you're not going to
say anything, are you?
Just kidding.
Or am I?
Sometimes I can't
even tell...
You know, if you
want to go check out
the rest of the Exchange and
trade whatever you brought...
Nope. I just came
to pony watch.
I'm not going anywhere.
I won't let you make a
mistake like that again.
Hey, Everypony!
Step right up.
Do not walk.
Gallop over here for your
chance to trade for authentic,
one-of-a-kind, official
princess merchandise!
(groan)
Well, that took forever.
I just hope it looks OK.
This is perfect!
(smash)
(gasp)
Perfect for the broken
chalice mosaic I'm making.
All right, so what kind of
antique chicken do you want?
I got speckled, brown, grey...
Oh, no!
The pony we're supposed to
trade the chicken statue to
didn't tell us what
kind he wanted.
OK, look, I'm fast.
I'll fly over to the
lamp stand and find out
what kind of
chicken he wants.
Just don't let anypony trade for
any chicken while I'm gone, OK?
Um, well, OK.
Um, I can do that.
I think.
Uh, well, maybe you
shouldn't get one of those.
You know, unless
you really want to.
(frustrated snarl)
Beat it!
You go.
I'll stay here.
Well, since we can't
both get what we want,
I will be the
better friend.
You take our trade goods
and get what you want.
I'm an amazin' friend.
So even though it's fer
somethin' that don't seem
valuable at all,
you take our stash.
How dare you let
me get what I want?
What kind of friend
do you think I am?
You're going to
get what you want.
No, you are.
Hello?
(knocking)
We got the kind of
chicken you asked for.
Hello?
Where's the pony
running this joint?
On break?
(growl)
These books made Twilight
the princess she is.
Before that, she was nothing.
Big fat zero.
Hey!
Then she read these
books and voila!
Princess!
So who wants to
start the bidding?
Me!
Me first!
(all shouting)
Just a moment, please.
Pinkie, I appreciate
your help and all.
But I'm not sure I'm
comfortable with this.
No pony should
trade for my books
just because I'm a princess.
I'm not better
than anypony else.
I know you're not
better than everypony.
Just leave this to me.
Did I mention that Princess
Twilight got these books
from Princess Celestia?
Whoa, wait!
You don't mean?
Oh, that's right:
double Princess.
(excited shouts)
There he is!
Look, I know it's
your break and all,
but you've got to
open your stand
so we can trade
you for a lamp.
(rumbling)
Sorry, girls.
Been trading all day.
My belly's telling me it's
time to eat an oat burger.
Oh, come on.
Please?
Pretty, pretty please?
Sorry. Belly
says "no."
But the Exchange
ends at sundown.
No!
I've got an idea.
Next.
Next!
(click)
♪
(grunts)
We're home free!
(crash)
As long as this thing
doesn't drown us in slobber.
Oh, he's just an affectionate
little two-headed fellow,
aren't you, little boy?
No, I insist you go
fetch what you want.
Cause that's the kind of
tried-and-true friend I am.
Well! I am way too generous to
let you out-friend me like that.
We've got to hurry.
(gasp)
♪
We're never going to get
to the Daring Do stand
through this crowd in time.
(loud growling noise)
Come on!
My bear call.
We've got to go.
Of course.
It's just a bear call.
There's nothing I
could've traded it for
that's more valuable
to me than you.
OK, the Exchange is almost
over, but we did it.
We traded a crystal chalice
for an antique chicken.
And the chicken for a lamp.
And the lamp for an Orthros,
just like you asked.
(bark)
So here you go.
Now where's my book?
Yeah, you know, the thing is, I
don't want an Orthros anymore.
But...
What do we do now?
(moan)
(thud)
(splash)
Oh goodness.
Oh goodness!
(splat)
Agh!
(grunt)
Good boys.
Hey! You said you
wanted an Orthros!
I've been watching that thing
over in the Ancient Beast Booth.
It's crazy. I don't
want one in my house.
(snarl)
There, there; that's
a good Orthros.
You just have to know
how to treat them.
With a little patient training
and a big slobber mop,
they can be a wonderful
household pet.
(slurps)
(laughing)
All right, all right.
I'll trade you.
Yes!
If she comes and stays
with us in Manehattan
until it's trained.
Gosh. Training an Orthros
takes a long time.
I'll probably be gone
from Ponyville for...
I don't even know
how many moons.
But if that is what
you really want.
So we got a fair deal?
Of course, it's a deal!
Yeah ha ha!
(whoosh)
I did it! I did it!
Fluttershy, can you
believe it?
Oh, no!
What did I do?
Pinkie: Who's got something
valuable enough to trade
for Princess Twilight's
princess books
that she got from
Princess Celestia?
Did I say princess?
Over here,
over here!
Oh, come on.
These are the books the princess
would sit up with all night,
with nothing to read by but
the light of her own horn.
Ooh, now that looks fun.
But not fun enough.
These are the books that made
Twilight the princess she is.
So who's got what it
takes to trade for them?
When you put it
like that...
(giving up murmurs)
Wait! Stop.
Come back!
These books aren't that great.
Oh, yes they are.
But I thought you wanted
to get rid of them.
None of those ponies had
anything valuable enough
to trade for my books.
Not because these books
belonged to a princess.
But because they helped make me
who I am, just like you said.
This is the one I was
so absorbed in
the day Spike decided he
owed Applejack a life debt.
And this one reminds
me of the day I got it,
which was the day I met you.
I may not ever need
to read these again,
but that doesn't mean
they don't have value.
I realize that now,
thanks to you, Pinkie.
I told you I'd take
care of everything.
Twilight!
I need you to say a
trade wasn't fair.
Fast!
I've heard what you
both have to say.
And I'm sorry, Rainbow Dash.
But my hooves are tied.
You said it was a fair trade.
Yeah, I said it.
But I was wrong.
I did want that book. A lot.
I said I wanted it
more than anything
in all of Equestria.
But there's no thing that's
worth as much to me as a friend.
I might've forgotten that for
a little bit, but it's true.
Which means there's no way
this trade can be fair.
Oh, come on; that's...
(softens) the sweetest
thing I've ever heard.
OK, the trade's off.
(cheers)
(crash)
And with that, I
declare this trial
and this year's Rainbow Falls
Traders Exchange over.
(knock)
Whoo hoo!
Rarity: I know it's not the
pie tin you were after.
But I hope you like it.
It's the rustiest piece
of junk I could get.
Well, I took my half of
our stash and got you this.
Ooooh!
And I know you're
gonna love it
cause you already
have a bunch a ones
that look exactly the same
sittin' in a drawer
doin' nothing.
So that should settle
once and for all
which of us is the
better friend.
Oh, come on!
You both gave up what you wanted
to do something for each other.
That's the coolest
thing a friend can do.
Trust me, I know.
Hey, where's your
double doggie?
I traded it for
something way better.
(chirping)
Well, what do you know?
My copy of Daring Do
and the Sapphire Statue.
It's just a beat
up old paperback,
not a one-of-a-kind
first edition.
(gasp)
Even better!
Because I can read this
one with all my friends.
(giggle)