Aren't you glad
y'all came with me
to see Applejack compete
in the Appleoosa Rodeo?
Totally!
This place is a
Cutie Mark gold mine!
There's barrel racing...
Roping contests...
Rodeo clownin'...
Steeplechase...
If we can get into
some of these events,
we could all three walk off
the train back in Ponyville
with brand spankin'
new Cutie Marks!
Wouldn't a barrel
look good here?
I want a lasso!
I don't know.
All these events look a
little, well, dangerous.
No risk, no reward.
Pony: All right,
everypony listen up!
We need a big presence
at this here rodeo,
so make yourself plenty seen!
I want that low-down varmint
to know we mean business!
I hope nothing
bad is going on.
A Cutie-Mark-a-palooza
and a low-down varmint?
This is shapin' up to be the
most exciting rodeo ever!
Yeah! Come on!
♪♪
HoH subtitles by YayPonies
We have Muffins!
http://main.yayponies.eu
♪♪
Woohoo!
Yeehaw!
That's my cousin!
Go Applejack go!
Phew! It's been a dog's age
since I got to compete.
All the rodeos 'round
Ponyville have closed down
for some reason.
Well, I guess having injured
kinfolk in Appleoosa
sure paid off then, huh cuz?
Just doin' my best to fill
your horseshoes, Braeburn.
Keep tossin' like that
and I'll be out of a job!
Ow-ow.
Ooh. Sorry.
Say, where's my sister
and her friends?
Uh-oh, gee I, uh...
I guess I got so caught up
watching you that I--
You said you'd keep an
eye on those fillies!
How am I supposed to focus on
practicing if you're not gonna--
There they are!
Right where I
left 'em.
Aw, don't be mad.
Ouch.
My foreleg!
Hurts so much.
[giggles]
Y'all can't go running
off like that, y'hear?
Backstage at a rodeo
ain't no kinda playground.
Sorry, Applejack. We
won't wander off again.
But, uh, speakin' of the rodeo,
what would you say about
me and the Crusaders
maybe competin' in one teensy
weensy little event or three?
Look out!
♪♪
[fearful cries]
[crash]
Applejack: What the
hay just happened?
You fillies all right?
Uh-huh.
Sugar and Saltlicks!
Well, I'll be...
What is it, Sheriff?
Is it him?
Ain't no doubt.
It's Trouble Shoes.
♪ [harmonica] ♪
[concerned chatter]
Pony: Is it true? Is
Trouble Shoes here?
Pony: You ain't gonna shut
down the rodeo, are ya?
All right now, I called for
a meetin', not a mob scene.
Now as many of you know, the
Equestria rodeo circuit
has been plagued by the dirty
dealings of a notorious outlaw.
He knocked barrels every which
way at the Hoof City Rodeo!
Nearly crushed my Aunt Bay Mare!
That's nothin'!
He sabotaged the steer
pen at Pinto Creek Rodeo,
settin' off such a stampede
they cancelled the
whole dadgum thing!
Now, Now.
It's true, we had an
incident this mornin'
at our own Appleoosa rodeo.
Hay bale stack came
down pretty near on top
of three little fillies.
I examined them
hoofprints myself, and...
It was Trouble Shoes, all right.
[everyone gasps]
I reckon I oughta
cancel this rodeo
like all the others done...
But daghoofit, this
has gone far enough!
We'll double the patrols!
This rodeo will go on!
Appleoosa ain't
gonna be intimidated!
[cheers]
Glad that's settled.
So, uh, Applejack, about me and
my pals competin' in the rodeo.
Apple Bloom: Don't
send us home! It's not fair!
Now quit your
belly-aching.
I can't have y'all around here
with some outlaw on the loose.
Aw, maybe I oughta call
it quits and go home too.
No, you can't!
This rodeo is important to
Appleoosa and with you in there,
we got a real shot at winnin'.
Come on, now, you head
on back to practice
and don't worry none
about these three.
I won't let 'em
outta my sight.
[door closes]
Ya hear?
Y'all ain't leavin' my sight.
[snoring]
I thought we weren't
going to wander off again.
This ain't wandering.
We know exactly where we're
headed: to find Trouble Shoes.
But isn't he a
dangerous criminal?
We only need to find him; we
don't need to capture him.
The sheriff can handle that.
And once he's in jail, we'll
be competing, and then it's...
...Cutie Mark city!
Worst idea ever.
[hooting]
♪♪
It's another giant hoofprint!
Do either of you have
any idea where we are?
[thunderclap]
Uh, maybe we should head
back and try again later.
Come on, before
we lose the trail!
[thunderclap]
[squeal]
Come on, we've
gone far enough!
It's time to
go back!
The rain is only getting
worse, Apple Bloom.
Let's come
back tomorrow.
Maybe y'all are right.
So how do we get back?
You mean you
don't know?
[crack of thunder]
Good job, y'all.
I know they need lots of
mud for the rodeo tomorrow,
but I wish they woulda warned
us about this rainstorm.
[horse whinny outside]
Braeburn?
Where are the girls?
Heh heh.
Applejack: WHAT?
♪ [honky tonk piano] ♪
Fished. My. Wish.
Gol-dang nab it!
[clunk]
[door opens]
Sheriff Silverstar!
You gotta help!
My sister's gone!
And her friends, too!
I've searched and searched
but no sign of 'em anywhere.
It must've been
Trouble Shoes!
Now hold on there.
Trouble Shoes done a lot
of bad things in his day,
but nothin' like that.
You really want to
take that chance?
Come on, y'all!
Let's ride!
You sure about
this, Scootaloo?
I thought I was,
but now I'm not.
So I pretty much got us
completely and totally lost.
How could this
get any worse?
[rumbling]
[screams]
We gotta get out
of this rain.
There's no tellin' how
long this storm could last.
Look!
Apple Bloom: It looks abandoned.
Let's go see if we can find
some blankets or somethin'.
♪♪
[footsteps]
[scream]
[male scream]
[crashing]
Ow!
Whoa!
[crashing]
[clatter]
Hello?
You all right?
Surely.
We didn't mean no harm.
We just came in to
get out of the rain.
Had some hot cider
cooking in the kitchen.
Doubt it survived.
[clang]
I ain't gonna rise
to greet y'all.
Awfully rude I reckon,
but as you can see
I'm the fresh casualty of an
unusually unfortunate
circumstance.
My lot in life, I s'pose.
Are you...
Trouble Shoes?
That's me.
Wh-what are you doing?
I'm gonna unwrap him.
You can't do that.
That's Trouble Shoes!
Aw, he don't seem so bad.
A'course guests would arrive
while I ain't got
no pie to offer.
Score s'more misfortune
points for ol' Trouble Shoes.
Whoa!
[crash]
[bonk bonk bonk]
Typical.
Bad luck never rests.
Apple Bloom: You sure
that's bad luck?
Seems like maybe you're
just a little, um...
klutzy?
Tell that to the flank!
Upside down horseshoe.
Bad luck.
Follows me wherever I go
like sour on old milk.
Y'all best vamoose a'fore
my bad luck rubs off
and sticks to y'all.
Get along.
Skedaddle.
Amskray!
Um...we don't really know
the way back to Appleoosa.
But a'course I do.
Wouldn't ya know
it, my lucky day.
It's actually kinda sweet of
him to help us out like this.
I know.
What do we do if he takes
us back to Appleoosa
and the Sheriff arrests him?
If I get a Cutie Mark for that,
I'll feel guilty
every time I see it.
Say there, Trouble Shoes, you
might not want to take us
all the way back to Appleoosa.
The Sheriff sorta has
it in his mind that
you're a no good outlaw lookin'
to shut down the rodeo.
My kinda luck he'd think that.
But...
is it true?
Y'all like stories?
Mm hm.
Just my luck.
I was hopin' you'd say no.
When I was a colt,
I wanted to be a rodeo
star somethin' fierce,
but I just didn't seem
to have a knack for it.
[clang]
Whoa!
[laughter)
Oh!
I practiced and practiced and...
Whoa!
...and finally I
wrangled up the guts
to audition for
rodeo school.
Right in middle of that tryout,
I knew I was doin'
what I was meant to.
And wouldn't ya know it?
In a flash comes
this here Cutie Mark.
[crash]
[laughter from judges]
I can still remember
them judges laughin'.
I didn't even finish my
routine 'cause right then
I knew bad luck was my fate.
That fire for rodeo'in
never did leave me, though.
I couldn't keep away from 'em.
So I'd sneak down and have a
look and wouldn't ya know it,
[crash]
bad luck would strike again.
Just my lot in life, I reckon.
Poor Trouble Shoes.
I can't believe
those mean judges
would laugh at
him like that.
Don't ya see?
They weren't
laughing at him;
they were just
enjoyin' the show!
What are you saying?
Think about it.
If we saw a rodeo clown doin'
what he did back in that shack,
we'd think he was the greatest!
You're right!
He could still be in rodeos,
just not the way he thought.
So he's been looking at his
Cutie Mark wrong the whole time!
It's not bad luck, it's--
Gotcha!
Just my luck.
Trouble Shoes, you're under
arrest for vandalizin'
the property and peace of mind
of the good, rodeo-lovin'
ponies of Equestria,
not to mention fillynappin'
and generalized mayhem.
Wait!
Braeburn, get these
fillies someplace safe.
Wait! No!
Listen, Applejack!
All three fillies: No!
Apple Bloom: But Trouble
Shoes isn't the menace
everypony thinks!
Sakes alive,
what's with you?
Why in tarnation would you want
me to help get him out of jail
when he's the one who ran
off with y'all to begin with?
Now if y'all excuse me,
I'm off to win the Appleoosa
Rodeo Hay Bale Monster Stack!
Um... Applejack?
[door closes]
[sigh] Well, at least
I get me a view
of one small corner
of the rodeo.
[thud]
Figures.
Aw, come on now, Trouble Shoes,
I'm runnin' out of mattresses!
♪♪
Come on, Sheriff,
you're about to miss the
Hay Bale Monster Stack!
Jiminy! That startin' already?
Let's go, Trouble Shoes;
this here's a jailbreak!
Ain't no need.
Can hear the rodeo just
fine from this vantage.
But we've got a plan to
help you live your dream!
Listen, y'all, I'm
a known criminal.
How you proposin' on
gettin' me into a rodeo?
[clunk]
[cheering]
Woohoo!
You can do it!
Go Applejack!
Well? How do I look?
[giggles]
Come on, now,
stack them bales!
Woohoo!
♪♪
Crowd: Whoa!
[cheering]
That's my sister!
♪ [circus theme] ♪
[laughter]
OK now Trouble
Shoes. You're on!
Say what?
I may be dressed like one,
but I ain't no rodeo clown.
You got your Cutie Mark
all wrong, Trouble Shoes.
You were born to entertain!
You got a gift for makin'
folks laugh, don't you?
But my Cutie Mark's an
upside down horseshoe.
And that means bad luck!
That all depends on
how you look at it.
You always wanted to be a
part of the rodeo, right?
Well, now's your chance.
♪♪
Go on!
Whoa!
Oof!
[laughter]
[encouraging shouts]
There y'all are.
How 'bout your
big sis, huh?
Yeah, way to go.
Since when are y'all
so into rodeo clowns?
♪♪
[laughter]
Just leave me be, Cutie Mark.
♪♪
I aim to clear that there hoop.
[screaming laughter]
[crash]
[laughter]
Come on now!
[grunts]
[laughter]
[hooting laughter]
That's the best rodeo
clown I ever seen!
Ha ha ha!
[laughter]
[gasp]
Trouble Shoes!
What the hay?
He escaped from
jail!
Ruinin' another
rodeo!
Let's get 'im!
[angry shouts]
Wait, y'all!
He ain't what you think he is!
Stand aside, young 'uns.
This one's goin'
back to jail.
But he never wanted
to ruin any rodeos!
Those were just bad accidents.
Sweetie Belle, what're
you talkin' about?
Trouble Shoes has a gift
for making ponies laugh.
He's maybe the best
rodeo clown I ever seen.
That's true, he
is awful funny.
He thought his Cutie
Mark was tellin' him
to keep away from rodeos,
but deep inside he knew that's
where he was meant to be.
He just didn't
know how to do it.
[murmurs]
What she says is true.
This here, entertainin'
y'all with my klutzin',
that's what I'm
s'posed to be doin'.
I know it now.
I didn't mean no harm, honest!
I just ain't never loved nothin'
like I love the rodeo.
So I kept on sneakin' back and
makin' a big ol' mess a' things.
Turns out I was just lookin'
at my Cutie Mark all wrong.
That may be so, Trouble Shoes,
but you still gotta face charges
for the problems you caused.
If I done wrong, I'll see to
it that I take my medicine
and square my accounts.
Truth be told, we could
understand all the trouble
with the rodeos.
But why'd ya have to run off
with these here littl'uns
last night?
Uh... yeah, about that...
You really want us to clean
up all this mess
Trouble Shoes made?
Maybe it'll teach you
not to go wanderin' off
after I say not to.
Ain't it bad enough that you
get to go back to Ponyville
with a shiny trophy and
all we're bringin' back
is these same old
blank flanks?
Y'all helped Trouble Shoes
realize what his Cutie Mark
really means.
Ain't that a nice feeling
you can take back with ya?
I guess we did make
things a little better.
Does feel kinda nice.
So, we can stop now?
Nope.