♪♪
I'll never understand
the ponies in this town.
Everywhere I went, they
were all gussied up
and looking at me funny.
Kept asking if I
was nervous.
Did they forget the
wedding is tomorrow?
Ah, maybe they're
just as excited
for us to be
married as I am.
Aw! [giggle]
Well, they're going
to feel awfully silly
when they realize they've
got the wrong date.
THE INVITATIONS ARE WRONG!
THIS SAYS THE WEDDING IS TODAY!
But I got such a
good deal on them.
Everypony in
town got these!
The princesses have even RSVP'd!
I told you we
should have eloped!
Oh dear!
The caterer, the
flowers, the musicians!
We've got to move
it all to today!
What?
Where's my wedding planner?
You told me you could do it for
half what the others charge!
And then you
sent invitations
to everypony in town
with the wrong date!
Muffin?
Hearing impaired subtitles by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
♪♪
I really messed up
on those invitations.
I feel just awful, Doc.
Hmph. Perhaps that explains
why I never got mine.
I told Cranky I could get
'em printed for cheap,
but that meant hiring
somepony with no experience
using a printing press.
[crash]
[splash]
Oh, I wish there was a way
I could go back in time
and fix all this.
Going back in time is
old thinking, my friend.
I was working off a
cutting edge theory
of making time come
forward to you!
My life's work, decades,
hm, centuries really,
of research and experimentation.
And I nearly had it cracked.
Turns out there's a
magic spell for it. Who knew?
[zapping]
But there are so many
things that magic can't explain!
Where science and mathematics
are the real magic!
Derpy: Like these?
They're pretty!
Ah, yes. My flameless fireworks.
I never could quite figure
out how to get them to ignite.
How did you learn to make
all this stuff, anyway?
I've been studying
science my whole life!
Ever since a particularly
traumatic experience as a foal,
I've been looking for
ways to make sense
of the world around me.
Science provides
explanations of things
we never thought possible!
Now. Why did we
come here again?
Yeah, oh!
Because I accidentally
sent out invitations
for Cranky and
Matilda's wedding
with today's date
instead of tomorrow's.
Great whickering stallions,
I completely forgot!
And I still need to
get my suit tailored!
♪♪
Rarity?
[banging on door]
Rarity!
[grunts]
♪ [faint headphone music] ♪
Please, you've got to help me!
I lost track of
time, unbelievably,
and forgot that the
wedding is this afternoon!
♪ [loud headphone music] ♪
Have you seen Rarity?
She's got to alter the
sleeves of my suit
and she's got to do it now!
Oh, ha ha! Thank goodness!
Lead on, my friend!
[crashing pins]
Why have you brought me here?
Rarity would never
set hoof in...
Great whickering stallions,
they've got style!
Gentlecolts!
I'm facing certain calamity
and I couldn't help noticing
your remarkable
fashion sense!
Could I get the name of
your incredible tailor?
Well, yeah man, his
name is me.
Me. What an unfortunate name.
No, man, like, I manufacture
all my own garments.
We all do, man.
Then you've got to help me!
I need this suit tailored!
It's an emergency!
Ha ha ha. Sorry, man, we're
just about to start the finals.
What's this word
you keep using... "man"?
I don't know, man,
but guess what?
Our fourth didn't show.
So if you roll with us,
we'll alter your suit for ya.
I'm sorry, gentlecolts,
but I will not bowl.
The splits! The spares! There
are simply too many variables!
Variables? What are you
talkin' about, man?
Just throw the ball straight.
Hold on. Straight?
Very well. I'll try your
"straight" technique.
It just might be
crazy enough to work.
Do we know what
they're on about?
The way they're
huddled up like that?
I'd say it's either a friendship
problem or a monster attack.
A monster attack? Blast!
I'm performing at the
ceremony this afternoon
and I still haven't
sorted out what to play.
How am I meant to practice with
a monster invading Ponyville?
Maybe it's just a
friendship problem
and it'll all be cleared up
in a half an hour or so.
Ugh. I hope so.
Where's Pinkie Pie? I need
my wedding planner!
[growl]
[loud growl]
[growls]
Oh no! On my wedding day?
SOMEPONY'S GOT TO HELP ME!
You!
Me?
I need to move an entire
wedding from tomorrow to today!
But nopony's asked me
to organize anything
since Twilight came to town!
So you'll do it?
I used to be the best
organizer in all of Ponyville.
You bet I'll--
[growl]
Rainbow Dash: Ahh!
[crash]
Come on, we'd better
get to the salon
before that monster
flattens it!
[roar]
What am I gonna do?
[gasp]
Matilda!
I feel so bad about
the invitations!
Is there anything I can do?
FLOWERS!
You want Matilda's
arrangements today?
This is awful!
The horror! The horror!
So there's no way you can do it?
We don't even have
Matilda's flowers in yet,
much less arranged.
Oh. This is a disaster!
Okay. Thanks anyway.
Look, girls!
A broken stem on
one of the zinnias!
WHAT?
Oh the horror!
The horror!
I have to admit, when Matilda
said we needed this place
ready by today, I was
a little nervous.
With you by my side, I knew
we'd get it done in time.
There is nothing like a
best friend, is there?
Anything's possible
when you know somepony
as well as we know each other.
[distant growl]
What was that?
There's some monster attacking
Ponyville or something.
What is it this time, a creature
from the Ever-Free Forest?
Uh, I think it's
some sort of Bugbear.
[giggle]
Did you say Bugbear?
He found me.
What are you talking
about, Bon Bon?
My name isn't Bon Bon; it's
Special Agent Sweetie Drops.
I work for a super-secret
anti-monster agency in Canterlot.
Or at least I did until the
Bugbear went missing
from Tartarus a few years back.
What are you talking about?
When it escaped, we had to
shutter the whole agency.
Every last shred of evidence
of the organization's
existence was destroyed.
Celestia demanded
complete deniability.
What?
It was me who
captured the Bugbear.
I had to go deep cover
here in Ponyville
and assume the name Bon Bon.
I never thought it'd
be able to track me.
But now it has.
Are you saying our whole
friendship was based on a lie?
I'm sorry, Lyra, I couldn't tell
you for your own protection.
But, but the lunches,
the, the long talks,
the benches we've sat on!
None of that was real?
It was all real.
You're my very best friend.
[distant growl]
I've got to go find a
crowd to blend into
before I put you in danger.
I'll see you at the wedding.
Fine. But we're going to
talk about this later!
I need my ring today,
no matter the cost!
As long as it doesn't
cost any extra.
7-10 split, man.
Harshest of the harsh.
But if you pick this up,
we win the whole shebang.
Doc! I finally figured
out how I can help!
Your flameless fireworks
look just like flowers!
I'll use them for the wedding!
Great whickering
stallions. Wait!
Wait!
The flameless fireworks
are extremely volatile!
Without knowing
what the trigger is,
they could go off at any moment!
My word, is that a Bugbear?
Matilda: There are so many
things I'm forgetting!
I hope Cranky remembers
to tell the musicians.
Oh, oh! I'll never get
my mane done in time!
You must relax, my dear!
We can handle anything.
We once did a pony's
hair during the ceremony.
Oh, it's true!
It's true!
They really are the best!
Matilda, I've just got to say I
already feel like we're family.
You do?
Of course!
I'm Stephen Magnet,
Cranky's best beast!
You're Stephen Magnet?
Well, what'd you
expect, a Bugbear?
I've known Cranky forever!
Surely he must have told
you about the time
he saved me from
Flashfreeze Lake.
You're Stephen Magnet?
Oh, I know, I KNOW!
Typical Cranky to leave
out minor details,
like the fact that I'm, you
know, a sea monster, right?
[laugh]
Oh, I just love that old burro.
I'm sorry, Stephen, I guess
I assumed you were a pony.
And I had no idea you had
such adventures together.
Oh, honey! You don't
know the half of it.
But let me tell you something:
in all that we've been
through together,
the only thing he ever
cared about was finding you.
Really?
Well, that and a
baldness cure. [giggle]
He is the sweetest
thing, isn't he?
All the stress I've
put myself through.
put him through!
The only thing that matters
is that we're together.
The wedding isn't the important
thing; the marriage is.
[laughing]
Oh, my goodness gracious!
If you believe that, I have
got a bridge to sell you!
All these ponies
travelling to Ponyville,
putting on
uncomfortable clothes,
sitting through a
long ceremony...
you think any of them
care about the marriage?
Honey, the wedding
is EVERYTHING!
♪ [wedding theme] ♪
Ugh, all these wedding
songs are so standard.
I want Matilda and Cranky's
wedding to be special.
♪♪
Thanks, but I'm not sure that's
appropriate for a wedding, is it?
♪ [classical music] ♪
♪ [added percussion] ♪
That's more like it!
♪♪
♪ [intensifies] ♪
STOP!
I'm going to be late
for the wedding!
♪♪
What is life?
Is it nothing more than the
endless search for a Cutie Mark?
And what is a Cutie Mark
but a constant reminder
that we're all only one Bugbear
attack away from oblivion?
And what of the poor
gator, flank forever blank,
destined to an existential
swim down the river of life
to an unknowable destiny?
Something like that might work.
What do you mean, you
left it on the counter?
I thought you
were bringing it!
Well, this is
just wonderful.
I handled the gift for
Cadance and Shining Armor.
You were supposed to
do this one, remember?
Well, we can't just come to
this wedding empty-hoofed!
[sobbing]
It's all right. He always
cries at weddings.
[loud sobbing]
Usually it's not until
the wedding starts.
These flameless fireworks
look even better than flowers!
[giggle]
Bon Bon: Attention, everypony!
Our friends have done it!
They've defeated the Bugbear!
[cheers]
Hey.
Hello.
So, uh,you didn't happen to
mention our earlier conversation
about my secret identity
to anypony, did you?
No. I did not.
And you're not the only one
with a secret, you know.
You know those
expensive imported oats
you were saving for
a special occasion?
I cooked them up and
ate them.
All of them.
Whew!
It's sort of thrilling to reveal
your deepest, darkest secrets!
[laugh] That's what
best friends are for!
Next time you can just bring your
own gift and I'll bring mine.
Fine.
Doctor: There you are!
My suit has
vanished and this
was the only thing
left in my closet.
How do I look?
Like a million bits!
Great whickering stallions!
Look at the time!
We'd better get
inside. Allons-y!
I can't believe I lost my hair!
I look ridiculous!
The love of my life
deserves better than this!
Have no fear, Cranky, my dear!
It's Stephen Magnet's
moustache to the rescue!
Aw, thanks, buddy.
No problem.
Now you get in there
and marry that donkey!
Well? Is everypony here?
[slam] [clink]
All set, Mayor!
Dearly beloved, we are
gathered here today
to join these two
in maretrimony.
As I look around this room,
I can only imagine
how uncomfortable
Cranky must be.
[laughs and chattering]
[grumbling]
But I also see so many ponies
from all trots of life
brought together by love.
Cranky searched all across
this great land of ours
to find Matilda.
And no matter what
obstacles kept them apart,
love would finally
bring them together,
just as it has brought
all of us together now.
It's remarkable to
me how a story
like Cranky's search for
Matilda could fill this room
with such a unique
collection of ponies.
It makes you realize
that everypony
is the star of their own story.
And it's not just the main
characters in our stories
that make life so rich.
It's everypony, those
who play big parts
and those who play small.
If it weren't for
everypony in this room
and many more who
couldn't be here today,
Cranky and Matilda's lives
wouldn't be as full
and vibrant as they are.
[loud sobbing]
And so, in front of all
these loved ones...
Cranky, do you take this donkey
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
You bet I do.
And do you, Matilda,
take this donkey
to be your lawfully
wedded husband?
I do.
Then I'm proud to say, I now
pronounce you jack and jenny!
[cheers]
[popping explosions]
Of course! They need
love to ignite!
How could I have missed it?
You know something, girls?
We are so lucky to
live in this town.
I love you all.
Rainbow Dash: Ow! That's
where the Bugbear bit me.
Twilight Sparkle: Sorry.