La-la-la-la-la.
La-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la-la.
This is gonna be
so great, Gummy!
We have absolutely nothing
to do today except bake!
I've been waiting for
just the right time
to finally try Granny
Pie's super special
triple chocolate fifteen-layer
marjolaine recipe!
It's gonna be amazing!
Let's see: nutty meringue,
chocolate ganache,
praline and nuts,
cocoa-flavored buttercream...
An hour per layer; that's 15
hours of pure baking bliss!
OK, Gummy, I think we're ready
to start prepping the second layer.
Oh my gosh!
My Cutie Mark!
You
know what this means?
The map!
Uh, Gummy?
Could you take over for a bit?
Hopefully this'll be quick.
I'll just measure the
baking powder for you.
And when the first
layer cools,
you can drizzle some of
the ganache over it.
And don't forget to beat the
egg whites for the merengue.
I know you can do this, Gummy.
You're the best alligator
baker I've ever met.
Hearing Impaired Subtitles by YayPonies
We have Muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
This is so exciting!
The map is summoning
you to Griffonstone!
The very heart of
the griffon kingdom!
I don't know if
either you have read
"Bygone Griffons of Greatness,"
but griffons were known to be--
Rude, insensitive bullies?
You mean Gilda?
Yeah, I mean Gilda!
When she came to Ponyville,
she was a total jerk
to all my friends!
Especially Pinkie Pie!
She was a bit of a party pooper.
Mm-hm.
So maybe Gilda
was a little rude.
You still get to
go to Griffonstone!
And according to this book, it
has a rich, fascinating history.
In ancient times, griffons
were known to be as greedy
as dragons, always hoarding
their bits and other treasures.
But all that changed
when King Grover
found the mysterious
golden idol of Boreas!
Legend says the idol
of Boreas was made
from the dust of
golden sunsets,
blown across the mountains
by the north winds.
Possessing the idol of Boreas
filled the griffons'
hearts with pride.
It's said that that one great
treasure is responsible
for turning Griffonstone into the most
majestic kingdom of all the land!
And why do you care so much
about griffons, anyway?
It was actually Gilda's
visit that made me curious.
So I picked up "Bygone
Griffons of Greatness"
and I've been hooked ever since.
And now...
Now you two get
to see Griffonstone
with your very own eyes.
Huh?
Just me and Rainbow Dash?
Hey, you can totally take
my place if you want.
I still had half
a nap to finish.
Why don't you just come with us?
I mean, you are the
Princess of Friendship!
No no, if the map wanted me to
go to the coolest kingdom
in all of Equestria
and tour the palace
and see the actual idol that
unites an entire species,
which would be super amazing,
I'm sure it would have said so.
You two can handle whatever
the issue is just fine.
I'll stay here and do important
princessy things... I guess.
Well then, c'mon Dashie!
We're goin' to Griffonstone!
Fine.
That's the spirit!
Whatcha reading, Rainbow?
Twilight literally
wrote a book
on what we need to
do in Griffonstone.
You mean like a guide on how to figure
out what problem we're supposed to fix?
And then some.
It's like Twilight
herself in book form!
"Always carry plenty of bits.
The griffons are
sure to help you
as long as you
share the wealth."
Can I borrow some bits?
Upon
arriving at Griffon Gorge,
be sure to pause and
cast your eyes northerly
up the Hyperborean Mountains,
taking in the breathtaking
beauty of Griffonstone.
Once in Griffonstone proper,
go immediately to the palace
and introduce
yourself to the King.
"Bygone Griffons of Greatness"
was written a long time ago
and it ends with the coronation of
the fourteenth king of the griffons,
King Guto.
I have no idea
who's in charge now.
Tell the King you've been sent
by the Princess of Friendship
and you're there to help
with some sort of problem.
If for some reason
the King can't help,
I'd try the Griffonstone
library next.
It's a little known secret that
if you befriend a librarian,
you can usually
find out anything.
Plus, as a bonus, there's a
statue of King Grover outside!
Photo op!
And don't forget to sample
some famous Griffon Scones!
They're supposed to be the best!
Aw, Twilight should
have come along.
Then she could have seen first
hoof that Griffonstone is...
...a total dump!
Ugh, maybe the map should have
called Rarity instead of us.
Excuse me, sir?
This is Griffonstone, right?
Well, that wasn't
very nice.
See? These griffons are exactly
what I thought they'd be.
Maybe we should just
find the palace
so we can ask the
king what's going on.
We don't have a
king, loosers.
Hello, Gilda.
Dash.
Pinkie!
What're you
doing here?
Uh, I'm a griffon?
What's your excuse, dweebs?
Hey! These dweebs are here
to help Griffonstone!
Help it what?
Well, we're not really sure.
But it involves a map and Cutie
Marks and a problem and--
Bored now.
Well, if you don't have a king,
can you at least tell us
where the idol of Boreas is?
Ha-ha! Don't tell me you really
believe in that thing.
You'd
better believe in it!
The idol was the best thing
to ever happen to us griffons!
Oh, great!
Now you got Grampa
Gruff started.
I'll tell you the whole
tragic tale...heh heh heh.
For a couple of bits.
The first griffon
king, King Grover,
united our kind like we've never
been united before or since.
And he did it all with that
incredible idol of Boreas.
That idol brought pride to the
heart of every griffon that saw it.
From one king to the next,
Griffonstone and our golden idol
were the envy of
all other species.
It held us together,
gave us an identity.
Right up until the
reign of King Guto.
That's when Arimaspi came.
To steal our griffon treasure.
King Guto tried
to fight him off,
but Arimaspi managed to
get away with the idol.
They say when our treasure
fell into the Abysmal Abyss,
our pride went with it.
King Guto was the last
king of Griffonstone
and we all lived
miserably ever after.
The end.
That was the saddest story ever.
Oh, well ... tough
tailfeathers! No refunds!
No wonder Twilight's book ended
with the coronation of King Guto.
Who would want to record
a history that sad?
It's not sad!
Do we look sad to you?
Pinkie, I think I know
why the map sent us here!
We need to find
the idol of Boreas
and bring glory and pride
back to Griffonstone!
Ha ha.
Here we go, typical
pony hero complex.
None of us care about
that dumb old idol.
Don't you get it?
We don't care about anything
and that's the way we like it.
I think Rainbow Dash is right.
The map sent us here to
fix some sort of problem.
The only problem
Griffonstone has is you!
Well, I don't care
what she says.
We're going to
find that treasure,
make Griffonstone cool again,
and get back to Ponyville.
C'mon!
Wait, Rainbow Dash, what
about Twilight's advice?
What, taking a
bunch of pictures?
She mentioned finding
answers at the library.
Knock yourself out.
But when you get bored
with Twilight's tour book,
I'll be at the Abysmal Abyss
finding the idol of Boreas.
I'm here to find your missing
idol and save Griffonstone!
Uh, I'll need some
rope, a grappling hook,
and a guide to take me
down to the Abysmal Abyss.
And I'll need some bits.
Hey, Gilda!
Word on the street is that
Griffonstone has an amazing
library chock-full of answers!
Word on what street?
OK, maybe not this street.
But on other streets, your
library is the talk of the town.
The library's right there
so why don't you go inside
AND LEAVE ME ALONE!
Maybe it's good that
Twilight didn't come.
It's sad what happened
to your town, King.
But Rainbow Dash can't be right.
This can't all be because
of a missing hunk of gold.
"You're right, Pinkie.
And you've got amazing hair."
Aw, King Grover,
you old charmer.
I know what Griffonstone needs!
Fewer ponies?
A song!
I've got a super
song about smiling
that's sure to make even the
most grumpy griffon grin!
You can't sing here.
But how do you break into uplifting
musical numbers with no singing?
Yeah, that's Griffonstone's
biggest problem.
Lack of uplifting
musical numbers.
Well, if I can't sing,
how 'bout a party?
If there's one thing these griffons
need, it's some good cheer.
Where's your party store?
No party store?
Aw. How about cake?
Nothing cheers
folks up like cake!
Where's your bakery?
NO SINGING?
NO PARTY STORE?
NO BAKERY?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
You're welcome to
leave at any time.
Well, that just takes the cake.
Wait, no.
It can't take the cake
cause there is no cake!
Or muffins!
Or Griffon Scones!
Oh, we got Griffon Scones.
That's my specialty.
I'll buy one!
Bits first.
Well?
What, you like it?
That's my Grampa
Gruff's secret recipe.
Ow! I think I broke a tooth.
Well, whatever, no refunds.
I don't even care anyway.
I just want to sell
enough of these
so I can leave this lousy town.
I can help you with that!
Uh, you think you could
tighten the strap on my helmet?
Can you give me more bits?
Never mind.
I got it.
So how deep is this abyss?
How deep are your pockets?
Don't you griffons ever talk
about anything but bits?
Give me some bits
and I'll answer.
No wonder Gilda's
such a delight.
Grampa Gruff's recipe is good,
but it's missing one
important ingredient.
Don't tell me...friendship?
Uh, no.
Baking powder.
Lucky for you I never
leave home without it!
Now just pop those in the oven
and you'll have Griffon Scones
worth their weight in gold!
Oof!
Greta!
AH-HA!
I saw that, Gilda!
You may act like a
gruff, grumbling griffon,
but inside you're
gracious and great!
What are you talking about?
You just helped your friend
up when she got knocked down.
What, her?
Greta's just some
griffon I know.
We don't have friends here.
I did have a friend once,
but you saw how that turned out.
Oh my gosh!
I gotta go find Rainbow Dash!
See ya.
You sure we can't just fly down?
Whoa!
Never mind.
Totally got my answer there.
Just gotta find that Golden
Idol and get out of this place!
Aaaaah!
Oof!
Oh! Oww!
Ooh!
My hoof!
Help!
Throw me another rope!
You got bits?
Wait!
HELP!
AHHHHH!
There you are!
Forget about finding the idol.
I figured out how to solve
Griffonstone's real problem!
SCONES!
PINKIE PIE, YOU GET BACK HERE!
Yeah?
Can you throw down
a rope or something?
Lemme look.
One rope, comin' up!
We need help!
Don't go anywhere!
Where does she
think I'm gonna go?
Unh!
I hope I don't go anywhere!
Rainbow Dash is stuck
on a ledge in the Abysmal Abyss
and I need your
help to save her!
Not my problem.
Of course it's your problem!
She's your friend!
Used to be.
Can't you remember when she was?
Yeah.
Of course.
Doesn't that griffon know that
she's supposed to fly
at the Junior
Speedsters Flight Camp?
Maybe she just doesn't
want to make you look bad.
Hey there!
I'm Rainbow Dash.
And you are...?
Uh, G-Gilda?
You sure about that?
Stick with me, Gilda,
and those guys won't
give you any more guff!
Whoa! You're awesome!
You too, Rainbow Dash!
Well, Gilda, let's show
these guys how it's done.
Junior Speedsters are our lives!
Sky bound soars
and daring dives!
Junior Speedsters
it's our quest,
to someday be the VERY BEST!
Fine.
I'll help her.
But that doesn't
make me her friend.
Duly noted.
Except it does.
Hang on, loser!
I'm coming!
What took you so long, doofus?
RAINBOW DASH!
I'M COMIN' FOR YA!
AAAAAAHHHH!
Gotcha!
Hold on, you two!
Huh?
The idol of Boreas!
I'm slipping!
AAAAAAAAHHHHHHH!
The idol!
You're more important to me
than some dumb chunk of gold!
Hugging later!
Climbing NOW!
I'm really sorry about
how I treated you two.
Thanks, Gilda.
Apology accepted.
And I'm just sorry we
didn't get your idol back.
Now we'll never be able to
solve Griffonstone's problem.
That's what I was
trying to tell you!
The map didn't send us here to
find the lost idol of Boreas.
It sent us here to replace
it with something better!
Nothing's better than
gold to a griffon.
That's because you
don't have friendship.
If you can learn to care
about each other again,
Griffonstone could be a mightier
kingdom than it ever was before!
And you don't need some
golden idol to do that.
You just need each other.
Whoa, Pinkie.
That was...really sappy.
Eh, what can I say?
That's how I roll.
Go on, Gilda.
Go make a friend.
I don't know, Pinkie.
You really think these
griffons are up for this?
We aren't exactly in
Ponyville, you know.
OK.
So she was really weirded out
until I gave her the scone.
Then she tried it and
said it tasted good!
That's the first nice thing
any griffon's ever said to me!
Whoa, Pinkie!
I guess that really was the
problem we needed to solve.
Baking powder makes baked
goods and friendships
fluffy and delicious!
Well, we better
be headin' home.
What? Y-y-you want me to spread
friendship here by myself?
How am I supposed to do that?
I haven't even made
one single friend yet!
No, you haven't.
You've made two.
Hugging!
Hugging now!
But you'll come back
and visit, right?
Just try and stop us!
See you later,
you old charmer.
Uh, Pinkie?
Who are you
talking to?
Nopony! Come on, let's go
home and see how Gummy did
with Granny Pie's
marjolaine recipe...