♪♪
[ticking]
[sigh]
[gasp]
Was that the Pony Post?
Oh, it was just you, Opal.
Every other day he's
here like clockwork.
But not today! What could
possibly be holding him up?
Strawberry Cinnamon
Cilantro Salutations!
What?
What indeed!
I bet you're wondering what
warrants such a welcome.
Well, that welcome is warranted
by a pony that whisked up
a warm batch of Strawberry
Cinnamon Cilantro cupcakes!
That strangely sickening
flavor combination
sounds just as bad as it tastes.
[gulp]
Ugh.
So I came here to
offer you some!
After that visually descriptive
and disturbing endorsement,
I'll pass.
Oh! I almost forgot! I have
this letter for you, Rarity!
The Post Pony was
going to deliver it,
but after his Strawberry
Cinnamon Cilantro cupcake,
he was feeling kind of queasy.
And since I was
heading over anyway,
I figured I could do it
for him. There you go!
Oh!
[muttering]
[excited shriek]
What's it say?
I GOT IT!
WOO HOO!
Got what?
I have been holding out
for the perfect location
and it finally became available.
So now I can fulfill my dream of
OPENING A BOUTIQUE IN CANTERLOT!
I'M SO EXCITED, I THINK I'M
GOING TO LOSE MY CUPCAKES!
♪♪
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
[train chugging]
♪♪
Rarity's such a
savvy business pony!
I'm so impressed she used
the huge bonus she earned
making the costumes for Sapphire
Shores' Equestria-wide tour
to open this
second boutique!
[admiring chatter]
I take it from your reaction
that you like the boutique.
It's lovely.
Gosh, Rarity, I know
hard work when I see it,
and it looks like you worked
your hooves to the nub.
I don't know. Those hooves don't
look nubby. They look scrubbied.
And buffied. And pedied!
Well, despite my nubby,
scrubby, buffy pony pedi,
I actually have been
working very hard.
However, I never could have
gotten the boutique ready
for the Grand Opening
without the help of my new
manager: Sassy Saddles!
Bust my buttons, Rarity!
The Ponies from Ponyville!
[greetings]
I knew I needed a manager
for Canterlot Carousel.
So when Sassy showed
me her resume and I saw
that she'd worked in all the
finest boutiques in Canterlot,
I hired her right
on the spot!
I then laid out this
plan or "pattern"
as we say in the fashion
biz, for Canterlot Carousel,
so that Rarity's boutique
will be a guaranteed success
and those doors will
never, ever, ever close!
Wow, Sassy, your attention to
detail is truly impressive.
I've already put a pin in the
first piece of the pattern,
"Beautify the Boutique."
But next was the very
crucial pattern piece,
"Marketing to the Mares."
Turns out that everypony
here loves royalty!
So I created a collection that
beautifully revolves around
the royal element of Canterlot.
And it just so happens there's a
hot new princess in Equestria.
In every poll
Sassy Saddles took,
you were the most
popular Princess!
Coincidentally, one of my gowns
is inspired by the window
in Canterlot Castle
commemorating your coronation!
[admiring chatter]
While I've always prided myself
on paying attention to detail.
I've taken my latest collection
to a whole new level
with Rarity's Rules of TLC.
Judging by this baby, TLC stands
for Tasty Licorice Candy!
TLC stands for Time,
Love, and Couture.
And while I do agree that
this dress has potential,
I have not had enough Time
to give it enough Love
to become Couture.
But the rest of the
gowns in tonight's line
have met Rarity's Rules and
are ready to be presented!
My marketing research also
confirmed that customers
that viewed somepony
famous wearing a gown
wished to own that
gown for themselves.
I call this piece of the
pattern "Celebrity Status."
So, Twilight, we were
wondering if perhaps
you might possibly
wear this tonight?
If being a Princess
and wearing that dress
can help your boutique
in any way, then I say...
Stick a pin in it! It's done!
All right, everypony!
Let's set the stage!
Ever since I was a little filly,
all I've ever wanted was to own
a boutique here in Canterlot.
Somepony pinch me, I'm
about to open the doors
to that very boutique!
♪♪
Welcome to the Grand Opening
of Canterlot Carousel!
[cheers]
Oh, hello! Nice to see you!
Welcome, welcome! Oh, I'm
so happy you could make it!
That Sassy totally stepped
on your hooves, Rarity!
Oh, no! Did she mess
up that nice pony pedi?
OK. Phew!
Oh, I don't think she meant to.
Rarity. Are you ready to
reveal the collection?
Is she sure she doesn't
want to do it herself?
[snorts] Yeah.
Yes, I am. Fluttershy. Could
you help Twilight get ready?
Oh, certainly.
Fillies and Gentlecolts!
I am designer and
couturier, Rarity!
I would like to
welcome you again
to the Grand Opening
of Canterlot Carousel!
And I am thrilled that
you're here to see
my newest collection
inspired by this regal city.
[Oohs and ahs]
♪ [dance] ♪
[exclamations continue]
♪♪
Rarity, I'm...
Fashion Plate of
Cosmare Magazine!
I'm so honored that Cosmare
was able to do a piece
on the Grand Opening
of my boutique!
Well, when Sassy Saddles
calls saying she's found
the latest and
greatest in fashion,
we high tail without fail!
Now tell me all about
your latest collection.
Ooh, uh. It's called
Rarity's Royal Regalia!
[gasp] Royally radiant!
[camera clicks]
My favorite part
of being a designer
is finding my inspiration.
And that really wasn't difficult
when it came to Canterlot.
Everywhere I looked, the
royal city just spoke to me!
I call it, "In-Spire-ation!"
Genius! Simply genius!
♪♪
I spent hours by the lily
pond on the castle grounds,
which inspired this
gown, "Water Filly."
Oh, the whimsy!
Watching Celestia raise
the sun each morning
literally lit up my day!
This is "Tripping the Light!"
Fantastic!
♪♪
And of course, Luna raising
the moon guided me to sleep.
I call this, "Over the Moon."
Oooh!
Well, I certainly am!
And for our finale, I have
something very special.
I was inspired by the
stained glass window
created in honor of
Princess Twilight.
So I call this, "The
Reign in Stain!"
Because the dress is
inspired by the...
stained glass window
of a reigning Princess!
Yes!
Well, I think "The
Reign in Stain"
is too difficult
to explain!
Especially for the signature
piece of a collection!
But I rather like...
Fillies and Gentlecolts!
I, Sassy Saddles, am
pleased to introduce
the Grand Finale of
the Grand Opening
of Rarity's Royal Regalia!
"The Princess Dress!"
♪♪
[gasp] Success!
[squeals]
[excited chatter]
Everypony! Please follow me
and you can all place your
orders for...The Princess Dress!
[chattering]
Rarity, I want to be the first
pony to congratulate you.
The Princess Dress
has just guaranteed
Canterlot Carousel's success!
[excited chatter]
[squeals]
Yeah! Rarity's Royal
Regalia is amazing.
And everypony seemed to
love the Princess Dress!
You bet your saddle they did!
Rarity now has one hundred
orders for her signature gown!
[stammering] One hundred
orders? All at one time?
According to my pattern,
the next piece is
"The Success of The
Signature Dress!"
So, I do not see the problem!
Uh...
Cupcake?
[ahem]
First of all, Sassy Saddles,
I would have appreciated
getting to name the final gown
from my collection myself.
My research shows that
your "Reign in Stain" name
was a play on words that
was both very confusing
and quite unappealing.
While I see your point, we
should have discussed it
prior to the Grand
Opening, Sassy.
My only goal is for Canterlot
Carousel to succeed!
That's why I changed the name.
And that is why I took all those
orders for the Princess Dress.
But receiving orders for one
hundred dresses in one day
is just too much too soon.
Are you actually saying we
should cancel these orders?
No, Sassy. Promises were made
and I shall sew my very best
to provide each and every pony
a Princess Dress full of TLC!
Oh, thank you,
Rarity! Thank you!
[sigh]
Oh, satin and silk, Rarity!
Are you sure you don't want
your friends to help you
make the dresses?
No, Sassy. These orders
are my responsibility.
All I have to do
is stick to my plan
so I can deliver each
and every Princess Dress
in keeping with my
Rules of Rarity.
♪♪
♪ The Rules of Rarity
Guaranteed Quality! ♪
♪ This I can assure! ♪
♪ For each and every dress
I vow to give finesse ♪
♪ With Time, Love, and Couture ♪
♪♪
♪ My favorite moment's
when a pony sees it. ♪
♪ That special gown
that she just adores ♪
♪ That pony's now in style!
My hard work's all worthwhile ♪
♪ Oh, yes, it makes my
heart, my heart, just soar! ♪
♪♪
♪ [music slows] ♪
♪ The Rules of Rarity
Just a parody ♪
♪ No dress here's unique
♪ The panels all the same
Each colored window pane ♪
♪ My fashion only makes
me want to shriek! ♪
♪ Oh, to create! ♪
♪ Would give me elation! ♪
♪ To feel once again
some inspiration! ♪
♪ Come on now, Rarity!
Give me some clarity ♪
♪ Time for your
couture love to rule! ♪
♪ The Rules of Rarity!
Extra TLC ♪
♪ This feels more sublime! ♪
♪ Soon now they will see
how good these can be ♪
♪ with a little extra shine! ♪
♪ The Rules of Rarity!
Guaranteed Quality! ♪
♪ All can see it's true! ♪
♪ These new gems add such flare
Their beauty can't compare ♪
♪ This old style
suddenly gleams anew! ♪
♪♪
[bell jangles]
Is that the customer who
ordered this Princess Dress?
I'll take care of
her. You keep working.
Uhh, actually, I'd love
to see her reaction
to this particular dress.
Paisley and Poplin, Rarity!
Look at all the orders
you still have to finish!
And you want to
take a break? Now?
Well, it's just...I made
some really lovely changes
to this dress.
You did what?
But every Princess Dress is
supposed to be exactly the same!
Yes, yes, I know. But these
gems just spoke to me.
Fine. Go see her reaction.
Hello, and welcome to
Canterlot Carousel.
I am so pleased to
present to you your...
PRINCESS DRESS! Finally!
I've been simply
desperate to get this
ever since I saw Princess
Twilight wearing it at your...
Wait a minute. There's
something different.
Well, as an artiste,
I did take the liberty
to change a few minor details.
I...I saw these gems
glistening in the light
and they just spoke to me.
Aren't they lovely?
And so unique?
They're fine. But they're not
what I ordered, are they?
No...no, they're not.
I want the dress to be
exactly like the one
Princess Twilight
wore. Understand?
Yes. Yes, of course.
♪♪
♪ The Rules of Rarity
Once stood for something ♪
♪ But now it feels just
like some factory ♪
♪ Now every dress I make
With every flaw and mistake ♪
♪ Oh, how it makes my heart,
my heart, just break! ♪
♪♪
Raving ricrac, Rarity! You made
two hundred Princess Dresses!
Yes. Isn't it spectacular?
And I have a special
surprise for you!
The latest issue of Cosmare
Magazine just hit the stands!
Rarity: Canterlot's
Newest Rising Star!
And in the hour since
the magazine's come out,
we've gotten another hundred new
orders for the Princess Dress!
[slam]
One...hundred...more...
Princess Dresses?
I'm the Cosmare Coverpony.
I have the most successful
shop in Canterlot.
I've gotten everything I ever
wanted, but...I'm...miserable.
How could you
possibly be miserable?
My pattern is perfect.
"COSMARE COVERPONY!" Done!
You have your signature gown!
"THE PRINCESS DRESS: A SUCCESS!"
I don't want to make another
hundred Princess Dresses!
I have a piece for that!
"ASSEMBLE THE ASSEMBLY LINE!"
You'll never have to sew again
What? No!
Yes! Then the "CANTERLOT
CAROUSEL NEVER CLOSES!"
and "SASSY SADDLES'
BOUTIQUE SUCCEEDS!"
Stop! This is not
your boutique!
And if this is what success
in Canterlot looks like,
I want no part of it.
Now, make up flyers for a
Going Out of Business Sale!
I'm closing
Canterlot Carousel!
What? No! Oh, you
can't, Rarity!
I've worked too hard
to make this a success!
I can't be a part of...
ANOTHER FAILED BOUTIQUE!
[slam]
♪♪
Oh, don't you look lovely! Nice
to see you out here again.
♪♪
Seems Sassy Saddles
isn't rushing
to open the door
this time. Hmm.
Welcome to the Going
Out of Business Sale
of Canterlot Carousel.
[clamouring]
♪♪
Hey, is this Princess
Dress on sale?
No, I'm sorry, the Princess
Dress has been discontinued.
But there are plenty of other
lovely dresses on sale today.
Whoa. This dress completely
speaks to my soul.
Can I try it on?
Certainly! The dressing
area is right back there.
This is the most amazing
of amazing dresses!
Just looking at it
brightens my day!
And I'm sure you'll feel even
brighter once you try it on!
Do you still have this
In-Spire-ation dress
that's in the new
issue of Cosmare?
Oh, yes, I do! It's right here!
Bats in the belfry!
I have to try it on!
Whoa, this dress makes
me feel like a Princess.
And this dress makes me
feel like a Princess!
This gown is quite beautiful,
but it totally clashes
with my complexion.
Hmm. Perhaps you'd be even
more taken with this one.
It was inspired by the fountain
in the Canterlot Castle Garden.
I call it, "The
Fountain of Truth."
It's exactly what
I've been dreaming of!
Ooh! Well, then, I'll finish it
and the gown shall be yours!
How could I have forgotten?
This is what I've
been dreaming about!
♪♪
♪ My favorite moment's
when a pony sees it ♪
♪ That special gown
that she just adores ♪
♪ That pony's now in style
My hard work's all worthwhile ♪
♪ Oh, yes, it makes my
heart, my heart, just soar! ♪
♪♪
Attention everypony! Canterlot
Carousel WILL NOT be closing!
[cheers]
But this stuff's
still on sale, right?
Yes, yes, of course.
Oh, Rarity,
I'm so sorry!
I focused on that
one dress
and the rest of Rarity's
Royal Regalia paid the price.
Well, so did the
Princess Dress.
The more I sewed, the
more each dress lost its
Time, Love, and Couture becoming
Terrible, Lackluster and Common.
I think I finally understand
the Rules of Rarity
and will apply them
at my next job.
I beg your pardon?
The Rules of Rarity
are only to be applied
at Canterlot Carousel.
Which is why you must continue
to manage the boutique
while I'm in Ponyville.
Ponyville?
Well, yes, I'll come to
Canterlot with new designs
and to see the
customers, of course,
but Ponyville was always
going to be my home base.
Bobbins and
bodkins, Rarity!
Oh, thank you,
thank you!
And I promise to run everything
following your rules!
I would expect
nothing less!
OH MY GOSH! A SALE?! DO YOU
HAVE THAT PRINCESS DRESS?
NO!
[laughter]