♪♪
[Spike sighs] Didn't we
just shelve all the books
in the library a few
months ago?
Yes, but that was
because we needed to;
this is just
because I want to:
I call it my
booksortcation.
Three uninterrupted days
of re-organizing books!
Can you think of
anything more relaxing?
Well, claw massages, back
rubs, bubble baths...
You weren't really looking
for an answer, were you.
I've even devised a better
system for organizing them.
It decreases the amount of
time it takes to find the book
you're looking for by
nearly 3/4 of a second.
Whoa! That much?
Look at them all.
Why there must be at least
20,000 books to organize.
Whoooo!
Best long weekend ever!
I'm sure we can make some
time for a claw massage
and a back rub, too.
Yes! Best long weekend ever!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
♪♪
[door opens]
[sigh]
Whoa, that strange yellow
orb in the sky! What is that?
All right, all right.
So it's been a little while
since we've seen the sun.
A little while?
We've been in that library
for 3 straight days.
Yes! But they were three
very productive days!
Even if you did take that
two-hour claw massage break.
Hey! You promise a claw massage?
I'm getting a claw massage.
It's not like we
missed anything.
[whoosh]
[crash]
Hello, Twilight.
Hi, Spike.
Hi, Rainbow Dash.
Good to see you, Discord.
Did you rehearse
before you found us?
What makes you
think we practiced?
Come on, Rainbow Dash.
What's going on here?
[laughter]
Sorry, me and Discord are
just messin' around. Ha ha.
Like we do.
Since when?
Oh, Twilight, we've simply
had a momentous time together
these past three days.
You could say it was
hisss-sterical! Ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha! Sneaky Snake.
Hoo hoo hoo! Just
snaking around.
Good one, Discord!
It is?
Kind of an inside joke
from this weekend.
You wouldn't really get
it unless you were there.
Oh. OK.
Cool. Well, uh, catch
you later, Twilight.
Catch you later, Twilight.
That was strange, right?
Since when have Rainbow Dash
and Discord had "inside jokes"?
Since sometime in the
last three days, I guess.
Hey! Nopony made you join
me on my booksortcation.
I'm joking. I'm joking.
[door jingles]
Rarity?
Twilight! You've returned from
your book-sorting sabbatical.
All that organizing has done
wonders for your complexion.
Thanks. It was
very relaxing.
And we were able
to clear a shelf
for those old-fashioned
books you wanted to donate.
They're not old, darling;
they're vintage.
And they're over there. I've
even included my favorites
by former Canterlot Designer
to the stars, Rococo Froufrou.
Ooh, I love her.
Him.
Uh, ha. Both.
Discord: Twilight!
This makes twice I'm seeing you
in one day. Aren't I lucky?
Weren't you just with--
Hi, Twilight! Hi, Spike!
How was your booksortcation?
It was good.
[giggle] Orange you
glad you did it?
[laughter]
"Orange" you glad! Fluttershy,
you're a card! [giggles]
Oh please, you'll make me blush.
You do seem to be turning
a shade of [gasp] orange!
[uncontrolled giggling]
Oh, sorry, darling. You see, we
were at Sweet Apple Acres...
And oh, how to explain...
Well, let me try and paint
her a picture, dearest.
[whisper] "Dearest?"
You see, we were all
at Sweet Apple Acres
and I ended up turning
the trees into the most--
Oh, who am I kidding?
I simply can't do it justice.
You really had to be there.
We would have invited
you to come along too,
but we didn't want to
interrupt your organizing.
We know how important
it is to you.
And I'm sure it was
much more important
than the fun that we had.
I appreciate that.
Speaking of books, I should
get these on the shelves.
[giggling]
♪ [hypnotic music] ♪
Hmm, Rainbow Dash
bonding with Discord;
Rarity finding something
he did genuinely funny?
Must have been some weekend.
Somepony sorry she missed it?
Of course not.
[hysterical laughter]
What's got you two
in hysterics?
Oh, we were just reminiscing
about the best weekend ever!
He's everywhere
today, isn't he?
Oh, now where was I?
Ah, yes, we'd just finished our
soup and then Applejack said,
"Peanut butter hoof? Yuck!
Not even with jelly."
[laughter]
I don't get it.
It was hilarious. I wish we'd
taken a picture for you.
Discord: Oh, well
this should do.
[clattering]
[hysterical laughter]
I guess that's funny?
Well, seems this has become
quite the sticky situation.
HA! Sticky situation!
Aw shucks, Twilight,
we haven't even asked
how your weekend went.
It was fine.
And yet you look so glum.
Does somepony need
a huggy-wuggy?
Whoooo.
I am not glum. I'm glad.
I'm glad you all had such
a good time together.
Having inside jokes can
really create a lasting bond
between friends.
I'm just sorry that all
this bonding happened
while you were holed
up in your castle.
Oh, don't you worry
'bout Twilight.
Bet you were in hog heaven
organizin' all them books.
Again.
I'm sure I had just as much
fun as the rest of you.
I can't believe I missed
out on all that bonding.
I knew it! You are jealous!
Spike, I'm the Princess of
Friendship. I don't get jealous.
I'm sorry I missed out because
sharing that experience
would have helped me with my
Princess of Friendship duties.
Come again?
If our friends could enjoy
three full days with Discord
that much, it must have
something to do with
the specific things
they did together.
If we could find out
what those things were,
it could be a real breakthrough
in the science of friendship.
I guess so.
I know so! You thought our
booksortcation was fun?
This is going to be
even better!
Thank you for coming.
I wouldn't have asked you
here if it wasn't important.
I love important!
I want to know how these "funny"
moments you shared came to pass.
I can use this data to
help advance friendships
all over Equestria.
Well, I like the sound of that.
[agreement]
Perfect. Let's start
with, "The Snake."
[raucous laughter]
I don't know if I can get
it out! It's too funny!
Oh, but we must. It's
for the greater good.
It started when we were helping
Granny Smith with her garden.
Uh, I reckon you mean
my sister, Apple Bloom.
Oh. All you Apples
look the same.
And then Rainbow
Dash saw a snake.
I think it was a garden hose.
It was a "Hose
Snake." Super Deadly.
I recall it being a large stick
that looked like a hose
that in turn did in fact
resemble a snake.
Point is WE galloped away!
And it chased after us!
The hose? A snake? A stick?
A snake!
A hose!
A stick!
We literally trotted for our
lives. Isn't that hilarious?
I guess you had to be there.
I DO need to be there.
But you weren't.
And it's already happened.
Oooh. Are you suggesting--
Time Travel?
Absolutely not! Time travel is
not something to be messed with.
We simply need to
recreate everything
that led to these jokes.
Oh! What a brilliant idea!
Shall we begin with the
lunch date that kicked off
the glorious weekend
you missed out on?
Are you sure it was this table?
Uh, does it really matter?
When it comes to science,
everything matters.
One change to the equation
could ruin the experiment.
Ohhhhh. It was this table here.
♪♪
All right, so you
sat down at the table
and then what happened?
Oh, well first, I
expressed my displeasure
with the design
of the menu and--
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt, but
I've just noticed something.
Yes?
The tablecloth. It
isn't the same color
as the one the restaurant
used on the day in question.
Really?
He's right. The
tablecloth was red.
I remember because it clashed
with the font on the menus.
I don't suppose that
means we're gonna need
to get a new
tablecloth, does it?
Oh, most definitely.
Wow!
One change to the equation
could ruin the experiment.
Twilight said so herself.
Anything stand out as being
different? Anything at all?
Um, I've noticed a
couple of things.
Me, too!
Excellent.
Discord: A little to the left...
no, my left...
a little bit more...
oh no, no, no, a
little more right.
The cloud over our table looked
like an ice cream sundae.
Perfect.
No. No. No. No. No. This is
barely room temperature.
Garcon! Garcon, over here.
[laughter]
No? Nothing?
Are you sure there's not
something you've missed?
Some other detail about
your lunch together
that you're forgetting?
Well, I don't know
about the rest of you,
but I feel we've been pretty
exhaustive in our attempts
to recreate every single detail
of our previous encounter.
[agreeing chatter]
Yeah, Twilight. If you
don't get it by now,
I don't think you're
ever gonna get it.
But it is really important
that I figure this out.
It's for the good
of all Equestria.
Well, perhaps we should
have another look
at the data we've collected.
[gasp] Of course!
There is one last variable
that we haven't accounted for.
What?
You!
Me?
You weren't there observing us.
No matter how hard we try,
we can't possibly recreate
our weekend of fun
exactly as it happened
because you'll always be
watching and you weren't there.
He makes a good point.
It has only served to prove that
moments of levity and bonding
between friends simply
cannot be recreated
so that others might
share in the experience.
He makes another good point.
Oh, don't worry, darling;
I'm sure there'll be plenty of
other chances for you to share
in the kind of frivolity
we had with Discord
while you were away.
Yeah. And I'll bet they'll
be just as...hissssterical.
[laughter]
Absolutely.
I'm not buying it.
Not for a second.
There is definitely something
else going on here, Spike.
Or maybe there isn't
and you should just drop
this whole thing and admit
that you're a little jealous?
Even if I'm not able to
laugh at what happened,
I should be able to figure
out why they find it funny.
Why they think they had
this amazing and hilarious
time together.
But I can't figure it out.
It doesn't make sense.
Some things just
can't be explained.
Our friends think something
great happened to them
while I was away. But no!
It was something awful!
If we don't break the
spell they're under,
who knows what terrible
things could happen?
Spell?
Come on, Spike! There's
no time to lose!
Zecora, what do you think?
Can you undo Discord's magic?
[bubbling]
In what way can you tell that
they are indeed under a spell?
They're having fun with
Discord; that's why.
Ahh, a friendship with
Discord is truly a shock
but who says it is something
that we must block?
Trust me, they would
never laugh like that
unless something magical was
involved. It's not that funny.
I know funny.
All right, this potion
will break the spell
then you will be able to tell.
Wait, if that's the potion, then
what's brewing in your cauldron?
It ties the room together
and emits a warm glow
but if I am to be honest,
it's just for show!
♪♪
[yawn]
I wonder why she asked us
here so bright and early.
Another map adventure perhaps?
Nope. No glowing tushies here.
Maybe it's more of
a non-adventure.
Maybe she just wants to tell us
how last night's slumber went.
Hey, gang!
Ooh, you look excited.
I am excited! We're
gonna have fun today!
Yes!
Just one tiny, miniscule,
microscopic thing
before fun times.
I need everypony
to sip this potion
to break Discord's spell on you.
Uh, what now?
Don't be embarrassed. So what
if Discord cast a spell on you
so you THOUGHT you
had a great time
and now you have all
these inside jokes
that you seem to be
constantly laughing at.
Don't worry, you didn't have
your defenses up; I get it.
You're kidding.
Twilight, darling, we simply
had a nice time with Discord.
As I recall, we spent much
of yesterday afternoon
re-enacting it for you.
Uh-huh. Or you re-enacted
what you thought was fun
but really wasn't because
you were under a spell
that made you think
what happened was fun.
What kind of fertilizer have
you had your nose in, Twilight?
Be honest; the only reason
you won't drink the potion
is because deep down in your
hearts you know there's a chance
that Discord has
you under his power.
Twilight! How could
you say such a thing?
I know Discord still
makes mistakes sometimes,
but you're accusing him
of being downright evil.
Yeah! And to top it
off, you're accusing us
of not being able to tell
he was up to something.
What do you take us for?
Yeah. What do
you... take us for?
Delicious! Got any
more, Twilight?
Hi, Twilight.
The gang mentioned we'd all be
hanging out together today.
The gang?
Yeah, the peanut
butter hoof gang!
[tapping]
[giggling]
It's still funny!
So much for that
whole spell theory.
[laughter continues]
Ugh! It's still not funny!
It's funny if you were there.
[yelling] But I wasn't there!
I wasn't included.
Maybe it's my own
fault for staying in
and having a booksortacation
when I could have been
making jokes and memories
with my friends.
But I didn't do that,
did I? You all did.
You were all there but--
[sigh]
I wasn't there. I missed out.
And seeing you having all
these jokes I wasn't a part of
and couldn't
understand made me...
Jealous?
No. The Princess of
Friendship can't get jealous.
Sure you can, Twilight. And
none of us begrudge you for it.
We're sorry if we made
you feel left out.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You're allowed to share
things that don't include me.
And you're allowed to feel
a little jealous about it.
You just have to be able to
admit that's what you're feeling
so you can let it go.
And, you know, not try to
make us recreate everything
that happened when
you weren't around.
Of course, none of this
would have happened
if I hadn't encouraged everypony
not to invite you this weekend.
They wanted me to be there?
And you convinced
them to not invite me?
Well, I didn't think that
they should interrupt you.
But now I see that we should
have. Oh, I feel just terrible.
You don't look like
you feel terrible.
Better?
Applejack: Wait a minute.
You didn't suggest
not inviting Twilight
cause you wanted to make
her feel left out, did you?
Of course not!
That whole jealousy thing
was just a happy accident.
Certainly we can all agree
that Princess Twilight
learned a valuable lesson here.
That even she can have
feelings of jealousy.
That she should
recognize said feelings
rather than try to pretend
that she doesn't have them?
Did I get the tiniest bit
of glee out of watching her
try to recreate our weekend of
fun in the name of "science"?
Oh, most definitely.
But what's important here is
that it was never my intent
to make Twilight feel jealous.
That's something the old
me would have tried to do.
Orange you glad I've changed?
I said "Orange you
glad I've changed?"
[cough]
Orange! Like the ones
at the Applejack farm.
From this weekend.
No? Nothing? Really?
I thought you'd find
this hisss-sterical.
[rattle]
Yes, no. Discord, I think these
jokes have run their course.
Only way we'd find
them funny now is
if you put us all under
some kind of spell.
Come on! You'd have to
be a complete crazy pony
to think he'd do
something like that.
What are you going
to say next, Pinkie?
That we'd all have to drink some
weird potion to break the spell?
[laughter]
What's so funny?
Come on, Discord, do we really
have to spell it out for you?
[laughter]
I don't get it.
Somepony want to tell me
what's so hilarious? Anypony?
Hello? I'm talking to
you! You and you, you!
Well, what's funny about spells?
I don't get it; I feel left out
and I feel really bad about it.
Sorry, buddy. Guess
you had to be there.
[POOF]
[laughter]