Wow, Applejack!
Are you sure you've never
managed a concert before?
Well, it turns out
doin' up a concert's
the same as settin' up a rodeo.
And thanks to Pinkie's
connections organizing
the Ponypalooza Rock Concert,
we've got quite a line-up
for the Helping
Hooves Music Festival.
Twilight! Applejack! Rainbow
Dash! Rarity! Fluttershy! Spike!
Pinkie Pie! Oh, wait,
that's me! EVERYPONY!
What is it, Pinkie?
I have the most
amazing news ever!
It is totally going
to freak your frizz!
Well, spill it, Pinkie!
It wasn't easy. In fact,
it was terribly difficult.
But I have managed to book
the biggest Pony Pop Star
in all of Equestria
as the main attraction
of the Helping Hooves
Music Festival!
Sapphire Shores?
Sapphire Shores? Please!
Sapphire Shores is merely the
SECOND biggest Pony Pop Star
in Equestria!
I have booked: The One. The
Only. Countess Coloratura!
OOOOOOOOOO! AAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!
Who in the hay is
Countess Coloratura?
My frizz has been freaked.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Pinkie Pie, who is this
Countess Coloratura pony?
I just told you
that she's the biggest Pony
Pop Star in Equestria!
How, how, how, how, how
have you not heard of her?
Don' know. Though I did
know a gal named Coloratura
when I was just a filly.
Wouldn't it just be the funniest
thing if that Coloratura
and this Coloratura were
the same Coloratura?
Do you mean to tell me
that you actually know
Countess Coloratura?
Well, I don't think
it's the same pony
since my friend wasn't any
sort of highfalutin' Countess.
Do you remember her Cutie Mark?
Sure do! It had this super
colorful bunch of musical notes
that just shimmered
in the light.
You mean, like this?
Well, fancy that! That there's
the very same Cutie Mark!
Do you have any idea the number
of hoops I had to jump through
to get her to perform at the
Festival? A whole lot of hoops!
That pony is very demanding!
Naw!
Yaaaaw!
I completely understand.
We artistes require
certain necessities
in order to do our best work.
This was clearly some
sort of misunderstandin',
cause Rara was just
as down home as me!
Rara?
Even that big name
was too fancy for her.
So I shortened
ColoRAtuRA to Rara.
We had the best time
at Camp Friendship.
Rara was just so easy goin'.
We were like two apples
from the same branch.
Rara and I prepared this song
for the Camp Talent Show.
When we performed,
she belted it out,
singin' in the most colorful,
clear voice I'd ever heard.
♪ Equestria, the land I love ♪
♪ A land of harmony ♪
♪ Our flag does wave
from high above ♪
♪ For ponykind to see ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Equestria, a land of friends ♪
♪ Where ponykind do roam ♪
♪ They say true
friendships never ends ♪
♪ Equestria, my home. ♪
After camp, we wrote to
each other for a bit,
but then we lost touch.
But Rara always did
want to go to Manehattan
to try and make it big.
But a demandin' diva?
Just you wait, Pinkie.
Once Rara gets here, you'll see
she's just a plain ol' pony
like you or me.
I don't have to
wait! She's here!
Really?
Rara?
AAAAAAH! COUNTESS COLORATURA!
Clear the way. Step back.
Keep your hooves and
tails to yourselves.
No. That can't be her.
Um...Hi. Remember me? We
met at Camp Friendship?
I gave you the
nickname Rara?
AJ?
Yeah! Howdy, Rara!
Hoovsies!
Ooh! You got Hoovsies from
Countess Coloratura! Look!
Ooh! She clearly thinks
you're very special!
Hoovsies! Hoovsies! Hoovsies!
Yeah, real special.
Now that's how you
make an entrance!
Big! Bold! Absolutely stunning!
Though it was muddied a
bit with your interaction
with that dusty farm pony.
Do you actually know her?
Oh, yeah. That's my
childhood filly friend, AJ!
She was the one that
started calling me Rara.
Oh, yes. How cute and common.
Of course, I was the one that
started calling you Countess!
And just look at how
you've moved up
in Equestria since then!
Why, you've gotten everything
you've ever wanted!
Speaking of which...
Where is the pony Pinkie Pie?
Ooh! I'm the pony Pinkie
Pie, Mr. Manager, sir!
Do you have the water
imported from Rainbow Falls
that I requested for
Countess Coloratura?
I have twenty glass
containers full right here!
Did I not tell you
to provide straws
in all of Countess
Coloratura's beverages?
I don't think so.
But lucky for you,
I have the biggest straw
collection in Equestria!
I call this straw Fernando.
Hmm. Let us confirm that you
acquired the rest of the items
that Countess
Coloratura requested
before she performs her
run-through, shall we?
Oh, we shall!
Floral arrangements from the
Royal Canterlot Gardens.
Chocolate éclairs made
by Gustave le Grande.
A selection of crystals
from the Crystal Empire.
Freshly picked cherries
from Cherry Jubilee's farm
separated red from yellow?
Absotutely!
Well, by some miracle,
your requests have
been reasonably met.
So let us move
on...to rehearsal!
See, Applejack? Demanding!
Pinkie's right, Rarity! The Rara
I knew didn't hide behind a veil
givin' out fake stamp kisses,
sippin' up imported water,
and needin' her
cherries separated.
Oh, I do understand.
Sometimes it's hard to
see our friends change.
She's become a whole other pony!
Trust me, once you see
Countess Coloratura perform,
you simply won't believe it!
♪♪
♪ Time for the Spectacle! ♪
♪ Time for the Show! ♪
♪ The lights are bright ♪
♪ And the colors glow ♪
♪ I'm not just any pony ♪
♪ I think you know ♪
♪ The time is now ♪
♪ It's about to blow! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Razzle Dazzle!
Glitz and Glam ♪
♪ Turn it all up ♪
♪ It's a spectacle ♪
♪ Razzle Dazzle!
Glitz and Glam ♪
♪ Turn it all up ♪
♪ It's a spectacle! ♪
♪ Give me more Razzle Dazzle! ♪
♪ Glitter eyes Big surprise ♪
♪ Lights! Cameras! Ah,
Ah, Ah, Ah, Ahah! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Razzle Dazzle!
Glitz and Glam ♪
♪ Turn it all up It's a
spectacle ♪
♪ Hear the applause ♪
♪ Here to impress ♪
♪ Not just a pony
I am the Countess! ♪
Rarity was right.
I don't believe it.
Oh, my shining star! Thanks
to the sparkling costumes,
dazzling choreography, and
brilliant vocal effects
that I designed,
your performance
was SPECTACULAR,
Countess Coloratura!
Oh, thank you, Svengallop!
Correct me if
I'm wrong here,
but that feller isn't
actually complimentin' Rara.
He's complimentin' all the bells
and whistles he's piled on
to make her Countess Coloratura.
Oh, no, no, no, no! You
don't understand, Applejack.
Creating all those
elements is a lot of work
and Countess
Coloratura's performance
wouldn't exist without them.
If you ask me, that wouldn't
necessarily be a bad thing.
Oh, if we're all done here,
I'd love to go back to my
trailer and rest, Svengallop.
Actually, right now
you're scheduled
for your Meet and Greet
with the school ponies!
I can totally get
you out of meeting
with the school
ponies, Countess.
Absolutely not! My
favorite part of any event
is meeting with
the school ponies!
The school ponies'll be so
happy to hear that, Rara.
Ponyville School Ponies!
As part of the Helping
Hooves Music Festival,
I'm holding a contest where
some of you will get a chance
to sing with me on stage at the
concert tomorrow! Sound fun?
All right! Now who
wants more Hoovsies?
Now, that's more like
the Rara I remember.
But I got everything
you requested.
That was for
Countess Coloratura.
This is for me. And what
I want is premium oats.
Oh, well, we have lots of tasty
oats right here in Ponyville.
I would not feed
those to a chicken!
I want top-of-the-line,
Appaloosan Oats.
Next. It appears that we are
surrounded by apple trees.
Bring me 500 pre-peeled,
pre-cored apples.
And I want those
things in 24 hours!
But that's impossible!
Do you want me to pull
Countess Coloratura
from your little podunk
charity show? Because I will.
Applejack! Svengallop just
made all of these new demands
I heard, Pinkie.
But don't you fret.
I'll talk to Rara and
fix things right up.
Did you see, sis? Did you see?
Is this the little sister
you wrote to me about, AJ?
Hold on, Applejack! You wrote to
Countess Coloratura...about me?
AJ said you were the best little
sister ever, Apple Bloom.
All right now, you best
git along, little ponies.
Hey, Rara, you mind if I talk
to you about your manager?
Sure, what about him?
Well, while you were meetin'
with the school ponies,
he was demandin' all sorts
of stuff from Pinkie Pie.
Svengallop works very
hard as my manager, AJ.
So if he needs some things
when we're on the road,
I don't see anything
wrong with that.
Well, do you see something
wrong with him telling Pinkie
that if she doesn't get
those things by tomorrow,
he'd pull you from
our charity festival?
What? But...he knows how
important charity is to me
and leaving the festival would
completely ruin my image!
I'm afraid Svengallop doesn't
give a pickled Pippin
about your charity work.
That's not true!
Svengallop has always supported
me in all my interests.
You're just saying those
things because you're jealous.
Jealous of what? A pony who
hides behind a veil so thick
she can't see when
somepony's using her?
No, I'm not jealous
of that, Rara.
I am not Rara! I am
Countess Coloratura!
And while we may have been
friends when we were young,
we have clearly gone in
different directions!
It just ain't right!
He's manipulatin' her and
she's just not seein' it.
Enough stewing! More peeling!
Sorry, Pinkie, but
there is no way
I'm lettin' that
lousy Svengallop
use my friend like that!
Ohhhh.
Countess Coloratura!
Wow, AJ! You said my real name.
I said your new name, but I
saw the real you hangin' out
with those school
ponies yesterday.
And I know somepony
that'd prefer
if you stopped doin'
those little events.
Oh, not this again.
C'mon, now. You just
gotta give me a chance
to prove what I'm
sayin' is true!
And just how are you
going to do that?
Do exactly what I say; we'll
see if that Svengallop
truly has your best
interests at heart.
Svengallop? Svengallop?
Where are you, Svengallop?
Here I am. Did you
need something?
Yes, I was...considering...
maybe canceling the contest
with the school ponies?
Countess, this is
wonderful!
I've been waiting
forever for you to cancel
that pointless
school pony contest!
You...have?
You do it at every charity event
and it does absolutely nothing
to promote the Countess
Coloratura image that I built!
Consider it CANCELED!
Pinkie Pie!
Yes, Svengallop, sir?
We're making some adjustments
to the show. Follow me!
Cancel the contest
for the fillies
and schedule
me a spa treatment.
Now that I don't have to oversee
a rehearsal with those brats,
I have time for the works.
You know the drill:
deliver, or the diva
ditches your dippy charity.
OK, Countess Coloratura!
All taken care of!
recording plays through PA:
You know the drill:
deliver, or the diva
ditches your dippy charity.
So that's how you've
been managing things?
Yeah, so? What's the problem?
The problem is that
you've been using my name
to intimidate ponies
to get what you want.
But I work incredibly hard for
you! I deserve everything I get!
But not because you scare ponies
into thinking I won't perform
for their charities otherwise!
I would never do
that to my fans.
Which is why you should have
known that I would never
cancel the School
Ponies Contest!
Hmm. All this charity and
school pony contest nonsense
is just remnants of that
boring little Rara
I met back in Manehattan.
You clearly don't
understand the real me.
That's a joke! I
made you somepony.
What can you even do without me?
Good luck, Countess
Coloratura! Good luck!
Oh, Rara! I'm so sorry.
Are you gonna be OK for
the concert tonight?
Of course. After all,
the show must go on!
Oh, my gosh, Rarity!
Svengallop's right!
This is going to be a disaster!
I'm gonna be terrible!
Can you give us
a minute, Rarity?
Certainly.
Now, why's it gonna
be so terrible?
Because Svengallop was
in charge of everything!
The lights! The
visuals! The sound!
Without Svengallop,
I have nothing!
Now, now. don't go
gettin' yourself
into a tizzy there, Rara.
Svengallop turned you
into Countess Coloratura
and acted like your friend
so he could enjoy the perks
that came with bein' a star.
But the real perk of friendship
is gettin' to see your friend
bein' true to theirself.
And, Rara, when
you're simply yourself,
you're the brightest star
I've ever seen shine!
Good evening, everypony!
Welcome to opening night of The
Helping Hooves Music Festival!
Now it is my great honor
to introduce you to
our headlining act,
Countess Coloratura!
This song may be familiar, but
yet it's totally different.
Kind of like me: Rara.
♪♪
♪ I'm here to show
you who I am ♪
♪ Throw off the veil.
It's fin'ly time ♪
♪ There's more to me
than the Glitz and Glam ♪
♪ And now I feel my stars align!
♪
♪ For I had believed
what I was sold ♪
♪ I did all the things
that I was told ♪
♪ But all that has changed
and now I'm bold 'cus I know ♪
♪ That I am just a pony ♪
♪ I make mistakes
from time to time ♪
♪ But now I know the real me ♪
♪ And put my heart
out on the line! ♪
♪ And let the magic in my
heart stay true oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Just like the
magic inside of you ♪
♪ And now I see those colors
right before my eyes ♪
♪ I hear my voice so clearly
and I know that it is right ♪
♪ I thought I was
weak, but I am strong ♪
♪ They sold me the world
but they were wrong ♪
♪ And now that I'm back I
still belong, cause I know ♪
♪ That I am just a pony ♪
♪ I make mistakes
from time to time ♪
♪ But now I know the real me ♪
♪ And put my heart
out on the line! ♪
♪ And let the magic in my
heart stay true oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Just like the
magic inside of you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Just like the magic
inside of you. ♪
Thank you, everypony!
When I arrived at the Helping
Hooves Music Festival,
I had forgotten
who I really was.
But then an old friend reminded
me what real friendship is about
and she told me that if
I was true to myself,
I couldn't go wrong.
So, I have a very special
surprise for her.
Apple Bloom, Sweetie Belle,
Scootaloo? Come on up!
♪♪
♪ Equestria, the land I love ♪
♪ A land of harmony ♪
♪ Our flag does wave
from high above ♪
♪ For ponykind to see ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Equestria, a land of friends ♪
♪ Where ponykind do roam ♪
♪ They say true
friendships never ends ♪
♪ Equestria, my home ♪