♪♪
Spike: Starlight Glimmer?
I was sure I saw her, Spike.
Welcome home, Twilight!
We travelled back in time to
when Rainbow Dash performed
her first Sonic Rainboom?
Without the Rainboom,
you and your friends
will never form your
special cutie mark bond.
But whatever Starlight did in
the past changed things here.
I don't want to live in
that awful future we saw.
I don't think
you'll have to.
All servants of Queen
Chrysalis found in these woods
must be destroyed!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Wait! We're not changelings!
I'm a pony! And he's a dragon!
A likely story!
Do something dragonish!
[whoosh]
[cough]
That works.
The servants of Chrysalis
will do anything
to save their evil skins!
Zecora: STOP!
If they are
changelings,
we'll soon see.
Though I think they're not
what they appear to be.
Zecora! Please,
you have to listen.
Beneath this salve
no changeling hides,
for it reveals the
truth inside.
♪♪
[gasps]
What does it mean?
The meaning is far worse, I see.
For it is we who should not be.
I think I can explain.
I'm sure you can, but
let's not talk here.
Chrysalis and her army
will soon draw near.
The changelings took
over not long ago,
though I'll wager in
your world that isn't so.
Chrysalis and her army tried
to take over Canterlot,
but my friends
and I stopped her.
Those friends as you know
them are not here, alas.
But tell me how all
this came to pass.
Starlight Glimmer. A pony
who traveled back in time
to stop my friends and me
from ever coming together.
And it is these friends
you have in life,
that keep Equestria
free from strife?
I guess so. But this is the
second time I've come back
and this world is even
worse than the last one.
If Starlight keeps doing
the same thing in the past,
how could the present
be so different?
Ahhh, time is a river where even
the tiniest changes seen...
Can lead to a cascade
of effects downstream.
♪♪
This part of the forest
is dark and damp,
but it's done well
to hide our camp.
This is cozy.
[scream]
Please, you have to help us!
The changelings
attacked Ponyville.
We barely escaped
with our lives!
The only changeling
attack I see
is the one that come
here looking for me.
It's taken quite a while
to find you, Zecora.
[laughs]
[whoosh]
♪ [dramatic] ♪
[evil laugh]
What a lovely
village you've chosen
to stage your little resistance.
It looks absolutely
delicious!
Oh, come now, Zecora,
you're vastly outnumbered.
♪♪
I know you don't want
your charges hurt.
Come quietly to the
dungeons of Canterlot
and I promise to leave
the others alone.
Why would she ever trust you!
Even if there's a chance
Chrysalis will honor her word,
shouldn't you try?
Race to the map while we
hold off their attack.
Stop Starlight and put the
whole world back on track.
Time to make a decision, Zecora.
Even if what you are
saying were true,
we'd never surrender
to a creature like you.
[war cries]
♪♪
[crashing]
[panting]
♪♪
[whoosh]
Not bad. But it's going to
take a lot more than that!
Lucky for you, there's
more where that came from!
You've really got
to work on your aim!
♪♪
[panting]
WHOA!
What are you doing? You
have to finish your race!
No way! This is
way more exciting.
See? You can't stop me
no matter what you do.
[whoosh]
Aw, man!
[grunts]
[groan]
That's strange.
Well, you obviously
don't mean us failing,
because that's becoming
pretty routine.
No. It's just the other
times we've come back,
it's been day, but look.
Why would the map
would bring us back
to a different time of
day than when we left?
Um, maybe we should
figure it out later.
[growls]
[panicked shouts]
[howling]
[panting]
The Castle of the Two Sisters!
[howling]
Well, don't just stand here!
[slam]
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
This place looks a lot
cleaner than I remember.
Rarity?
The castle isn't open
for viewings today.
The tapestries all need
changing... again.
Rarity, it's me.
I don't socialize with dragons.
I don't know anypony who would.
Rarity, you have
to listen to me.
The future of
Equestria is at stake.
I don't know how
you know my name,
but I am far too busy to
entertain some tourist's
ridiculous fantasies.
I have to get back to the
map so I can stop Starlight
from changing the past because
every present I come to
is worse than the last!
Time travel, you say?
Now that's something
I would like to see.
[evil laughter]
Tell me how you came by this
magic to travel through time.
The Princess asked
you a question!
And unless you want to
end up in the dungeon,
you'll tell her what
she wants to know.
No pony in my kingdom but
me should possess a magic
powerful enough to change time.
Your kingdom?
Who else?
Um, Celestia, of course.
[laughter]
My sister has been imprisoned
in the moon for years!
But it is no less a fate
than she sentenced me to.
Now. Reveal to me the
source of this time magic.
All right.
Twilight! No!
We have no choice, Spike.
I can take you to it,
but you'll have to get
past the Timber Wolves.
I am the ruler of
all of Equestria.
Do you think I can't
deal with Timber Wolves?
No. I know you can.
And if you were thinking
of trying to escape...
it would be very
unfortunate for your friend.
[night insect noises]
[bark and whine]
How does it work?
A pony from my time used a spell
to travel back and
change the past.
And now you will give
this spell to me.
With it, I will ensure that
the Elements of Harmony
are never found and
my rein lasts forever!
But it won't.
What?
In my world, my friends
and I found the elements
and used them to defeat you.
And I will do
everything in my power
to bring that world back.
NO!
[whoosh]
NOOOOOOO!
Now more than ever, I know how
important it is to stop you.
Well, good luck!
[whoosh]
Whoa!
[power up]
[rumbling]
[zap]
[squeak]
♪♪
[splattering]
[engine hum]
♪♪
Up for another race-ending
fight, Twilight?
No. You were right.
I can't stop you.
[zap]
But you can't stop
me from trying
and we could be stuck doing
this for all eternity.
If that's what it takes to
keep you and your friends
from getting your cutie mark
connection, then I'm game.
[zap]
What you're doing goes
way beyond cutie marks.
Everything we do
here in the past,
even the smallest change,
can snowball into an avalanche
of trouble for the future.
Oh. Next I suppose
you'll tell me
that the fate of
all of Equestria
hangs in the balance.
IT DOES!
Spare me your over-blown ego.
No group of friends, not
even Princess Twilight's,
is that important.
[zap]
[screams]
[whoosh]
I don't know how important
other ponies' friendships are
to the future,
but I can show you what the
world is like without mine.
[rushing wind]
Where are we?
The future. Or
rather, the present.
But there's nothing here.
I wish I could say
I was surprised.
But every world I come back
to is worse than the last.
I don't know why my friends
and I are so important
to Equestria, but we are.
I don't believe you!
Come on, Starlight. Look around.
Like I said, everything in
the past affects the future,
even the tiniest act, and
what you're doing leads here.
I know I can't stop you,
but I thought showing you
this might change your mind.
Change my mind? You don't
know anything about me.
I was perfectly happy
before you and your friends
ruined what I built.
I don't know what happened
that led you to make
your village
without cutie marks.
And I'm sorry my friends
and I had to take it away.
You want to know what happened
to me? I'll show you!
[whoosh]
Where are we?
That map of yours is connected
to every part of Equestria
and this part is my home.
Sunburst and I did
everything together.
In fact, I don't remember
us ever being apart...
until today.
♪♪
[zap]
[whinny]
[excited chatter]
And just like that,
my friend was gone.
His family recognized
his magical talent
and sent him off to Canterlot.
I never saw him again.
Why not?
Because of his cutie mark!
He got his and I didn't.
He moved on and I didn't.
I stayed here and never
made another friend
because I was too afraid
another cutie mark
would take them away too!
That's ridiculous.
A cutie mark can't
take your friends away.
Not everypony's lucky
enough to get her cutie mark
at the same time as her friends.
You don't know what it's
like to lose a friend
because of a cutie mark.
But once I stop the
Rainboom, you will!
And when I destroy this scroll,
there'll be no way
for you to change it!
♪ [intense orchestral] ♪
Starlight, you're right.
I don't know what
you went through,
but I do know you
can't do this.
I've seen where this
leads and so have you.
I only saw what
you showed me.
Who knows what'll
really happen?
I've seen it a dozen times.
Things don't turn out
well in an Equestria
without my friends.
Agh! What's so special
about your friends?
How can a group of ponies
that are so different
be so important?
The differences between
me and my friends
are the very things that
make our friendship strong.
I thought Sunburst
and I were the same,
but we turned out different
and it tore our
friendship apart.
So try again. Make new friends.
And if something that
you can't control happens
that changes things, work
through it together.
That's what friendship is.
And it's not just my
friendships that are important
to Equestria. Everyponies' are.
When yours ended,
it led us here,
but just imagine all the
others that are out there
waiting for you if you
just give them a chance.
How do I know they won't
all end the same way?
I guess it's up to you
to make sure they don't.
[whoosh]
♪♪
One Castle of
Friendship. Check.
What in Equestria was that?
Is everypony OK?
Can you do it again?
One group of amazing
friends. Check.
Yeah, Spike. It looks
like we're home.
Uh, what's she doing here?
Actually, it's kind
of a long story.
I mean, I knew my
Rainboom was awesome,
but I never thought all of
Equestria depended on it.
Or on us!
I think it's more than that.
Friendship connects
all of Equestria
and undoing one group
of friends
made its magic
less powerful.
I can't believe y'all
were able to travel
through time like that.
That Starlight must
be pretty magical!
She obviously has
more talent for magic
than almost any pony I've seen.
My magic couldn't stop her.
I had to convince her
to stop on her own.
Once I realized that,
everything fell into place.
But if she's as
powerful as all that,
we can't just send her
on her way, can we?
Actually, I kind of have
something else in mind.
[gulp and sigh]
I know there's no
excuse for what I did,
but I want you all to
know that I'm ready
for whatever punishment
you think is fair.
I've been thinking a lot about
how badly Equestria fared
without just one
group of friends.
Because even when
one friendship dies,
the results can
be disastrous.
I know, firsthoof,
how true that can be.
And that's why I've
asked you here.
If you're willing
to learn,
I'm willing to teach
you what I know.
You'll have the power
to make Equestria
an even better place.
How do I start?
Starting is easy. All you
have to do is make a friend.
And you've got seven
of them right here.
♪ [upbeat] ♪
♪ I never thought that I
would find a place, ♪
♪ to step right in
and start again ♪
♪ I never thought that
I could just begin, ♪
♪ Right where I left
off and make a friend. ♪
♪♪
♪ Don't ever think that
it might be too late. ♪
♪ You don't have to wait, ♪
♪ there's no mistakes with
the friends you make. ♪
♪ A friendship's only
made of what you bring, ♪
♪ and if you do it right,
you can do anything. ♪
♪ Just use... your eyes...
this time... no lies ♪
♪ Just don't... disguise...
who you are inside. ♪
♪ Because your friends are
always there for you. ♪
♪ You don't have to
be the same ♪
♪ For friendship to be true. ♪
♪ Because your friends are
always there for you. ♪
♪ Around the world
it's still the same, ♪
♪ together you have
more to gain. ♪
♪ There's nothing that
a friend won't do ♪
♪ Everywhere you go,
friendship there will grow ♪
♪ When you find it,
it's the key! ♪
♪ Friends can change
the world, you see ♪
♪ Everywhere you go,
friendship there will grow. ♪
♪ When you find it,
it's the key. ♪
♪ Friends can change
the world! ♪
the world, you see! ♪