♪♪
♪ Ponies' voices
fill the night! ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Happy hearts so
full and bright ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Oh what a sight! ♪
♪ Look at the light. ♪
♪ All for tonight. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪♪
♪ Clouds arranged so
they're just so. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Gonna make some
awesome snow. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ The chill wind blows ♪
♪ Making a show ♪
♪ Snowflakes aglow ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪♪
♪ A day that's filled
with songs to sing ♪
♪ Ding Dong Ding Dong Ding ♪
♪ Cakes and pastries
we shall bring ♪
♪ Ding Dong Ding Dong Ding ♪
♪ We're so busy
making merry ♪
♪ Windigos should
all be wary ♪
♪ As our mighty
voices carry ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again! ♪
♪♪
♪ Decorations we shall make. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Perfection you
just cannot fake. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Not one mistake ♪
♪ Don't let that break! ♪
♪ [smash] ♪
♪ Oh, Goodness Sake! ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once ... ♪
♪ Happy, Happy,
Hearth's Warming, ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming, Happy,
Happy, Hearth's Warming Eve. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again ♪
Hey, Starlight! Ready
to celebrate your first
Hearth's Warming Eve
here in Ponyville?
I was thinking I
might just skip it.
[gasp]
Derpy is Best Pony!
Hearing impaired subtitles
by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu/
SKIP HEARTH'S WARMING EVE?
I just find it all
a little silly.
It's mostly a day dedicated to
presents and candy, isn't it?
And why would you deny
yourself presents and candy?
That's crazy talk!
I THINK what Spike
means to say is,
Hearth's Warming is about
more than presents and candy.
It's a time to spend
with friends and family
when we celebrate a
very important day
in Equestria's history.
I think to most ponies,
it's just an excuse
for silly songs and fun,
not a day to remember
some old story.
Maybe you just haven't
heard the right
Hearth's Warming
Eve story yet.
Earth ponies, pegasi
and unicorns sing songs
around a hearth to fight
back an eternal winter
caused by the
mythical Windigos?
[laugh] Every foal and
filly knows that story.
Not THAT one. My
favorite holiday story.
A Hearth's Warming Tale.
Oooooo! I love that one!
This is the story of a powerful
unicorn named Snowfall Frost
who hated Hearth's
Warming Eve!
It all began many moons
ago in Canterlot...
Every home in Canterlot was
filled with Holiday spirit.
Every home except one.
It was said of Snowfall that
she was almost as studied
as Starswirl the Bearded.
Almost, since everypony knows
that Starswirl was an expert
at everything from
transfiguration,
Dimensional Calibration,
Teleportation--
Spike: We get it.
Starswirl's awesome.
Right. The point is, Snowfall
was also a powerful unicorn.
She wanted to be perfect.
Anything that got in the way
of that was a waste of time.
Ugh!
[clanging bells]
Well, that batch is
ruined. SNOWDASH!
Snowdash was Snowfall's
loyal assistant.
What do you need?
Get this mess cleaned up.
Those foolish ponies were
ringing those blasted bells
outside the window and
I lost my concentration.
Whoa. Ponies
actually enjoying
Hearth's Warming Eve. Where
did they get that crazy idea?
Today is nothing
to celebrate.
Hearth's Warming
Eve is a menace,
a dangerous day for
all of Equestria.
Dangerous? It's awesome!
It's the day we remember
how unicorns, pegasi,
and earth ponies came
together in friendship
to defeat the Windigos!
That silly legend
is the problem!
Telling everypony that
singing songs and being nice
will solve anything? I've
spent years studying magic
and that's not how it works.
I think you might be
missing the point.
Work hard, learn and use your
skills to better Equestria.
THAT'S a worthy
goal for anypony.
But by all means, if you
want to go home early,
ignore all of the work you
have and spend the rest --
SWEET!
Ugh.
I HATE Hearth's Warming Eve!
All of Equestria
would be better off
if we just skipped
the day all together.
♪ "Happy Hearth's Warming" ♪
♪ They say in the street. ♪
♪ They think they're so sweet. ♪
♪ Words said so often ♪
♪ That they lack any meaning. ♪
♪ Why should I join in? ♪
♪ When I could be
intervening! ♪
♪ Everypony loves
this cursed holiday ♪
♪ but would they be better off ♪
♪ with it out of the way? ♪
♪ Well, OK. ♪
♪ Say goodbye to the holiday ♪
♪ With my magic
I'll erase it ♪
♪ The greatest gift
that I give today ♪
♪ And everypony will
have to face it. ♪
♪ No more little games
for you to play ♪
♪ After you say goodbye
to the holiday. ♪
♪♪
♪ Goodbye Hearth's Warming ♪
♪ You had a good run ♪
♪ It's over, you're done ♪
♪ Finally set free from ♪
♪ your forced celebrations ♪
♪ no need to reply ♪
♪ to your trite invitations ♪
♪ Calendars shorter
by a single day ♪
♪ Is my magic up to the test? ♪
♪ Time to see, I can't delay. ♪
♪ Say goodbye to the holiday ♪
♪ Prepare the spell,
no hesitation ♪
♪ All memories shall fade away ♪
♪ See Equestria's
new transformation ♪
♪ No more shall any ponies say ♪
♪ "Happy Hearth's Warming" ♪
[cackles]
♪ after today! ♪
♪ After today. ♪
Once the spell is cast, all of
Equestria will be better off.
And they'll have
me to thank for it!
Wait a minute.
Snowfall doesn't like
Hearth's Warming Eve
so she decides to cast a spell
to get rid of it all together?
That seems a little extreme.
Says the pony who tried
to make everypony the same
by replacing their cutie
marks with equal signs.
I THINK what Spike is trying
to say is that everypony
has their reasons for doing
things. Even Snowfall.
And if I could
continue the story,
we might just find
out what they are.
Proceed.
Snowfall was all set to cast
her spell that would erase
Hearth's Warming
Eve for all time
when a voice from the hearth
caught her attention.
You SURE you wanna
go through with this?
[gasp] Who's there!
The Spirit of Hearth's
Warmin' Past, that's who.
And you and me have got
to have us a little chat.
A spirit! I didn't cast any
spirit-summoning spell.
What are you doing here?
You don't think a spell
like that would get by
without some powerful
forces noticing?
You've got our attention,
Snowfall Frost
and we've got some
pretty strong opinions
on this spell of yours.
We?
They'll be along in a bit.
For now it's just you and me.
Let's get a move on.
We got a ton to see
and barely any time
to see it.
[laugh] I'm not
going anywhere.
I've got a spell to cast. And
I don't need a history lesson
about Hearth's Warming Eve.
We aren't goin' to the past
to learn about the holiday.
We're goin' to
learn about you.
Whoa!
♪ [strumming banjo] ♪
♪ As a young thing,
life sure is something ♪
♪ You go makin' choices
large and small ♪
♪ Always growing
like a seedling ♪
♪ and playin' is
like dreaming ♪
♪ And before you know
it big and tall. ♪
♪ And every little
bitty choice you make ♪
♪ Sends you down a path
to who you are today ♪
♪ So let's take a little
trip down memory lane ♪
♪ And see just what
the past has to say. ♪
♪♪
Awww, look how
cute you were.
Looks like you're
not too upset it's
Hearth's Warming Eve, either.
♪ The seeds of the past,
they grow pretty fast ♪
♪ Just look at who
you were back then ♪
♪ The seeds as they grow,
look what they can show ♪
♪ Reveal the truth
time and again ♪
Just what do you think
you are doing, Snowfall?
Decorating the classroom
for Hearth's Warming Eve,
Professor Flintheart!
You said you wanted to learn
to be a powerful unicorn,
did you not?
I do!
And what is the way that one
becomes a powerful unicorn?
[ahem] Work hard, learn
and use your skills
to better Equestria.
And how do these help
you to learn magic?
I want to be strong enough to
stop Windigos and help ponies!
That's just a story
we tell little ponies.
Real magic takes
time to learn.
[shatter]
It's your choice.
Spend your time learning to
become a powerful unicorn,
or play with your toys and
make nothing of yourself.
♪ Then some distress,
words so careless ♪
♪ Standing there, you
don't know what to do ♪
Feeling helpless,
can't make it hurt less
♪ So you go and change
your point of view. ♪
♪ And in that moment
though you didn't know it ♪
♪ Your defenses set up
walls you built to last ♪
♪ Leading to the pony
you've become today ♪
♪ And the spell you're
about to cast, ♪
♪ it all comes from your past. ♪
♪ The seeds of the past'
we grow up so fast ♪
♪ Some hurts never go away ♪
♪ The seeds as they grow,
this we can't let go ♪
♪ All tied to this one holiday ♪
[gasp] Spirit? What
am I supposed to--
SNOWFALL FROST! IT IS I,
THE SPIRIT OF HEARTH'S
WARMING PRESENTS!
Um, don't you mean
present, like, the time?
No. Toys, Hearth's Warming
dolls. Here! Want a cupcake?
Fine. Presents. All of
the pointless things
that ponies waste
their time on.
Oh Snowfall. It's not what
the gift is that matters,
it's what the gift MEANS!
It doesn't mean anything.
It's just stuff.
Exactly! Sometimes a
cupcake means I love you!
Or a toy means Hi!
How ya doin?
And sometimes a book means,
"Your mane looks AMAZING!"
And sometimes a scarf means...
well, a scarf usually
means you look cold.
That one's easy.
I don't understand
anything you're saying.
Whoa, whoa! [grunt]
What's happening to you?
My Spirit of Hearth's Warming
Presents-sense is going off!
That means a song
is coming on!
♪ Take a look at everything ♪
♪ around you ♪
♪ All the smells that
surely will astound you ♪
♪ Open up your heart;
it will surround you ♪
♪ In the magic of
Hearth's Warming Eve ♪
♪ The little things
that make it better ♪
♪ Little ponies
spreading cheer! ♪
♪ Give a toy, a hug, a sweater ♪
♪ Memories that last all year! ♪
♪ The present's always
filled with presents ♪
♪ Large, medium and small ♪
♪ Sometimes the most
important things ♪
♪ Aren't very big at all. ♪
♪ [tap shoes clicking] ♪
♪ What a party! There's
so much to see here! ♪
♪ I can't believe you
didn't want to be here ♪
♪ You would've had a
blast I guarantee here ♪
♪ THIS is the spirit of
Hearth's Warming Eve! ♪
♪ The cider's flowing,
this is living! ♪
♪ Come on and feel the beat! ♪
♪ Life is better
when you're givin' ♪
♪ Each time you do
it feels so sweet! ♪
♪ The present's always
filled with presents ♪
♪ So come on open your eyes ♪
♪ Spend time with
ponies just like you ♪
♪ and watch your spirits rise ♪
♪ The present's always
filled with presents ♪
♪ Take a look around ♪
♪ The reason for the holiday ♪
♪ is quite easily found ♪
♪ Yes the reason for the
holiday is quite easily found ♪
♪ And the reason is to
be with your friends! ♪
What?
You know you're doing your
Pinkie Pie voice, right?
I was not...
[laugh]
So [sigh] what happens next?
Well, the party was--
WAIT! Can we take
a quick break?
I need to refill my cocoa!
[growl] Fine.
But hurry up! We're
almost to the best part!
OK. I'm ready.
The party was in full swing.
Snowdash!
Hey, Merry.
Why, whatever is
the matter, darling?
Was it the eggnog?
[sigh] I knew I put
in too much cinnamon.
Oh, no! The eggnog was
awesome, Flutterholly.
I'm just mad at somepony
who was complaining
about how awful
Hearth's Warming Eve is.
I don't suppose that pony's
name starts with "Snow"?
And ends with "frost"?
She said Hearth's Warming Eve
is just an excuse to party
and we'd all be better
off spending time working
to make Equestria
a better place.
Boo!
What does Snowfall think a
better Equestria looks like?
Ponies working hard.
Learning.
And using their abilities for
the benefit of Equestria.
[giggle]
Yeah! [laugh] [cheers]
It looks like we've got
everything on Snowfall's list
right here.
I think a perfect
Equestria looks a lot like
a Hearth's Warming Eve party.
Me too. Too bad it's going
to be the last one EVER!
Ever...ever...ever.
Spirit? What do you mean?
What's going to happen?
[whistling wind]
Who are you?
I am the Spirit of Hearth's
Warming Yet to Come.
Are you here to show me
what future Hearth's
Warming Eves are like?
No. For there are no more
Hearth's Warming Eves
for me to show.
Why not?
You will succeed in erasing
the holiday as you wished.
And what happens?
♪ I see a cold wind
blowing through ♪
♪ I see days neither
fun nor free ♪
♪ I see a future
caused by you ♪
♪ I see a path not
meant to be ♪
♪ The future should
be filled with magic ♪
♪ dreams and wishes
brought to life ♪
♪ But the days ahead
are dark and tragic ♪
♪ no time for hope
when all is strife ♪
♪ Whatever might have been ♪
♪ all the dreams
that ponies share ♪
♪ Because of you,
Snowfall Frost ♪
♪ Now the future is
a cold nightmare ♪
WINDIGOS!? They
aren't real.
It's just a little
filly's story!
They are all too
real, Snowfall.
And your actions will
allow them to return.
The future of Equestria
shall be bathed in a blanket
of eternal snow.
No! I never meant for this to
happen. I didn't understand!
I didn't see how important
Hearth's Warming Eve was!
Please, spirit! I haven't
cast the spell yet!
Is there still time?
I'm sorry!
There's still time!
Oh my.
Snowfall Frost?
I was hoping I wasn't
too late for the party.
I brought gifts.
[spits] Boss?
I was wrong earlier. About
Hearth's Warming Eve.
It's not all about
singing and presents.
The singing and presents
are all about celebrating
the ponies in our lives.
The ponies we should listen
to more often. Our friends.
Wow.
Dragon toenail? Uh...thanks?
I was in a hurry. I'll
do better next time.
[laugh] You kidding?
No one's ever given me
dragon toenail before!
It's awesome! Now
come get some eggnog!
And from then on it
was always said of all
the Hearth's Warming
Eve celebrations,
Snowfall's was the
Hearth's Warmingest.
The end.
Well, that's it. Thanks for
letting me read you the story.
Guess you can call
it a night.
Spike and I are
heading downstairs.
And if you wanted to, you'd
be welcome to join us.
[giggling]
Welcome to the party. Happy
Hearth's Warming Starlight.
Happy Hearth's
Warming, Twilight.
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is filled with presents ♪
♪ some take you by surprise ♪
♪ A story shared by
your good friends ♪
♪ that makes your
spirits rise ♪
♪ Sometimes you just
let go of the past ♪
♪ enjoy the present
while it lasts ♪
♪ And really it's not
that much to ask ♪
♪ with good friends
by your side. ♪
♪♪
♪ Now it's time to celebrate ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again ♪
♪ All together feeling great ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again ♪
♪ Can't hardly wait ♪
♪ We'll party till late ♪
♪ Our favorite date ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪
♪ Happy, Happy, Hearth's
Warming, ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve, Happy,
Happy, Hearth's Warming Eve. ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is here once again. ♪