Ahhhhhh!
Miss Rarity? How much
longer are you planning
to stay in here, darling?
Oh, dear, is somepony
else waiting?
No, no. I just don't
want you to get all,
what is word, pruney.
Oh. Well, I'm just waiting for
Applejack. It's been so long
since we've had a relaxing
day at the spa together.
I'm quite certain she'll be
along any moment.
Hey, there, Rarity. I really
tried to get here earlier.
I just can't believe how
much time my chores
are taking up these days.
At least now we'll
finally get to spend some
quality spa time
together, right?
OK fillies, that's it. We're
closing up for the day.
Aw, shucks, Rarity. I guess
I missed the whole day.
I sure am sorry.
Me too.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Hi, Rarity.
Morning, Twilight. Spike.
Good heavens that's a
lot of empty pie plates.
Uh, yeah. We were just heading
to pick up some fresh pies.
I don't know why we keep
running out at the castle.
What are you
going to get?
Applejack,
actually.
Although I'm quite sure
she'll be too busy once again.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing. It's just
that Applejack and I
haven't had one of our
spa days in ages.
You two really should set
aside some time.
Darling, I have been
trying for moons,
but Applejack is so busy these
days, it's next to impossible.
Wow. I didn't realize Applejack
had so much to do.
Hey, Applejack. Another
order of pies, please.
Sure thing, Spike.
Agh!
I don't suppose those
pies are the last chore
on the schedule for today?
Gah! Land sakes! Is it time
for our spa day already?
Rarity, why don't you go on
ahead and I'll meet you there?
Ugh! Please, Applejack,
let's not kid ourselves.
Well, it ain't 'cause
I don't wanna,
but the work on the farm
has just been taking up
more and more of my time.
I hate seeing you two not
spending time together.
Can't you get somepony
else in your family
to take over for a bit?
Wish I could, but Granny,
Big Mac and Apple Bloom
all have chores of their own
and today they're all busy
taking the harvest
to market.
I know we're not farmers,
but I'm sure Spike and I
could handle things
for a little while.
Maybe.
Is there one chore
we could do?
Well...I suppose if
you two got started
on feeding the pigs,
I could maybe leave
for an hour.
An hour of
spa perfection?
I can work with that!
Perfect. You head
off to the spa
and Spike and I will take
care of things here.
Whoa! Ugh! Whoa!
Uh yeah. We've totally
got everything covered.
OK. This list pretty
much covers everything
you need to know
to feed the pigs,
but uh, maybe I should go
over it with you just to--
Applejack, please, if
there's a list involved,
I am one hundred
percent on top of it.
Uh, right.
And don't worry
about things here.
Spike and I have
totally got this!
I mean, it's just feeding
the pigs. How hard can it be?
Uh... Twilight?
Whoa!
I'm glad we're
doing this, Rarity.
I've been putting work before
our spa time for too long.
I know we've only
got an hour,
but I can't wait
to have a steam.
A steam is just
the start.
I know exactly
what we'll do
and an hour will
be simply perfect.
OK, Spike. Ready
with that list?
Ready!
Let's do this!
Step one, open the gate.
OK. Step two, close the gate.
Huh?
Mmm. That's what it says.
Step three, walk away.
Walk away? Really?
I just hope Twilight and
Spike can handle things
until I get back.
Now, Applejack,
if we are really to enjoy
this time together,
you simply must give
yourself over to the idea
that you are off duty
and try to relax.
I know. You're right. I really
am glad we're doing this.
And as long as
it's only an hour,
I'm sure everything
will be just fine.
Exactly. Now, kindly step
this way. Relaxation awaits.
Rainbow Dash?
What are you doing here?
Yeah. I didn't think
spa treatments
were your thing exactly.
What?
Oh. They're totally not.
At least, not the
"frou-frou" kind.
Ah.
Yeah, I-uh, I think
I tweaked something
at Wonderbolts practice
the other day.
I just came in for a deep
tissue sports massage.
Ah, Miss Dash? I
am so sorry,
but we are running
just a tad behind
and we're not quite
ready to start your
pampered muzzle massage and
indulgent hooficure just yet.
Oh.
I-I'm pretty sure that
wasn't what I signed up for.
But they are your usuals-
And it seems like you're
really busy today anyway.
I'll just come back tomorrow.
Uh, see you two
later. Have fun.
But put me down for
the same thing.
Too bad Rainbow
Dash just "hates" those
"frou-frou" spa treatments.
She could have joined
us for a nice steam.
Whoo wee! I can't wait.
Indeed. Although if
they couldn't fit Dashie in,
I wonder just how far
behind things are running.
Obviously we're on a
very tight schedule.
Well, maybe not everypony is
waiting for the steam room.
Oh, no, no, that's exactly
what we're waiting for.
Oh, I hope you're
not in a hurry.
So every pony here
wants a steam bath?
Well, the solution
is obvious.
We'll simply have to start
our short time at the spa
with something else.
Huh! Nothin' doin'! I
came here to have a steam
and that's just
what I'm gonna get.
But-but it will take
most of our hour
just to get through
this line.
Rarity! My favorite
customer!
And Appleyack!
Well, it certainly has been
a long time since you two
were here together. So
lovely to have you back.
Well, I wish I
could say the same.
Yes, the wait time
for the steam room
certainly has been
getting worse lately.
But I'm sure we'll be
able to accommodate
your usual treatments.
Not without my steam.
Apparently Applejack won't
consider starting her time
at the spa without a steam
and we only have an hour.
That is a problem.
Applejack, where are you going?
Um... Why are y'all
just standing here?
Ugh! Just waiting for
the steam to build up.
Without steam, a steam
room's just a room
and I've got plenty
of those at home...
because I live in a mansion.
It has been taking longer
for the steam to reach that
"Ponyville Day Spa" quality.
We even had to add a
warm towel service.
So sorry for the
delay, everypony,
please help yourselves.
So, if you're not
getting enough steam,
that must mean there's
not enough hot water.
Oh Applejack, honestly,
can't we just start
with a hooficure?
We're going to
run out of time!
Hmmm.
Ha! Now, what do we have here?
The laundry room, of course.
And at this point, I'm
considering soaking my hooves
in one of the machines so my
time here isn't a total loss.
The Ponyville Day Spa prides
itself on sanitary conditions
and fresh linens
are integral part.
Well, sure, but have you
always run every single one
of these here machines
full-bore, all day, every day?
The answer is no...
...but ponies sure do love
their warm towel service.
Hmmm.
You are all wanting towel?
Looks to me like you
don't have any left.
Well, like I said. Warm
towels are big hit.
I think I figured
out the problem.
You've got a small leak
and that means the steam
takes just a little
longer to build up
and while ponies wait,
they get cold.
Cold ponies start wrapping
themselves in towels...
...and all those dirty
towels have to be cleaned...
...because Ponyville Day Spa
prides itself on cleanliness.
Eh. What?
Basically, losing steam
makes you use more towels.
That means you do more laundry
which uses up the hot water
you need to make more
steam so the problem
just keeps getting worse.
Oh.That makes sense. I see.
Ah! I had no idea.
Wonderful!
Now that we've solved
the great steam mystery,
we can finally get
back to our...
significantly less than
an hour of relaxation.
Rarity, are you kiddin'?
I can't just leave
things like this.
I'm gonna need my tools.
Uh!
Whoo! Now that
that leak's fixed,
ponies won't get so cold
they use up all those towels
and without all that laundry,
there'll be plenty of hot
water for all the steam
anypony could want.
And I'll only have to be
doing wash once a day!
Wow, Appleyack. Have you ever
considered a career
in the spa industry? I'm sure
I can find something for you.
No thanks. I'm just
relieved I can finally relax
in the steam. What do
you say, Rarity?
Mmm. It sounds lovely,
Applejack,
but unfortunately...
...you spent so much time
fixing the steam room
we don't have any time
left to use it.
Honestly, how in Equestria
did it never occur to you
to check for leaks?
There's just so many other
things to worry about.
I suppose we get used
to the way things are
and we don't realize
there was problem.
You obviously need an outside
eye to evaluate the situation.
It's lucky for you Applejack
is too stubborn to relax.
Uh, I'm sorry, Rarity.
We'll just have to
do this another day.
Twilight and Spike should be
done feeding the pigs by now.
Twilight is a very capable pony.
I'm sure she can figure
out what to do next.
Look, I know Twilight's a
princess and an alicorn,
but she isn't a farmer.
I've been doing farm work my
whole life and I'm not sure
it's something you
can just figure out.
Of course. Why don't
we pop back so you can explain
to Twilight what to do next
and then we'll come back here
and pick up where we left off?
Well, I suppose I could try,
assuming everything
went well so far.
Oh, Applejack, honestly!
How could it not?
Wouldn't it be
easier to just fly?
I told you, Spike, we're
following Applejack's list
to the letter and Applejack
doesn't fly--
Aaaaah!
Whoa!
I'm sorry, Rarity,
but I think I'm gonna have to
finish these chores myself.
Twilight, darling, how in the
world did you end up there?
Spike and I were just trying
to follow Applejack's list
as closely as possible.
Mmm...maybe not the best plan.
I'm sorry, Applejack.
But we never even got
started feeding the pigs.
That's all right, Twilight.
I know you did your best.
I guess a list can't really
capture all the ways I have
of doin' things.
At least you two got to spend
some time at the spa together.
Yeah, that must have
been super relaxing.
Well, if watching
Applejack fix plumbing
counts as relaxing, then yes.
What about your hour
of spa perfection?
As it turns out, the Ponyville
Day Spa had a few problems
with their steam room and
somepony refused to relax
until she had fixed them.
I'm sorry, but I just
couldn't let those spa ponies
go another minute putting
up with problems
they didn't even know they had.
Somehow they just got used to
a huge bottleneck of ponies
standin' around waitin'.
But I took one good
look at that spa-jam
and I knew I had
to do something.
Sometimes the simplest
things can just derail
a whole operation.
Whether it's a leaky pipe
or doing too much laundry,
you can't just stick to the
same old way of doing things
and expect them to get better.
I mean, thinking you can is
just plum ridiculous, right?
It's funny when
you realize the extra work
they were doing was actually
making things worse.
I mean, I guess it's possible
to get stuck in a routine
where you're doing all
this extra stuff
and not realize it,
but I can't for the life
of me think of how.
Why are y'all starin'
at me like that?
Um, are you certain
everything you just did
is entirely necessary
to feed the pigs?
What? Of course! Why would
I be doin' it if it weren't?
See this gate here used
to squeak so loud,
the pigs would run to the
other side of the pen
and never come out,
so I open and close it to
let them know it's safe.
But it doesn't squeak anymore.
Of course not. I
fixed that ages ago.
Then I realized putting a
little fright into 'em
got them all hustlin'
out of the pen.
They don't look
scared to me.
Well, no, they got
used to it.
Which is why I started doing
the chicken dance to show 'em
that if they didn't get to
eatin' their food,
the chickens would.
Of course, being a chicken,
I couldn't very
well open the gate.
Getting the food bucket to
spill into the trough
was just a happy accident
because one time I left
it there by mistake.
Uh Applejack, it seems like
everything you're doing
is to fix things that aren't
really problems anymore.
Well, I'll be.
Hm. Maybe it isn't so
hard to get stuck
doing extra work after all.
Huh, I wonder if I've been
doing that around here
with anything else?
Well, there's only
one way to find out!
Thanks y'all. I
guess I just got so used
to doing everything
a certain way,
I didn't realize there
were any problems.
Having a friend look
at what you're doing
with an outside eye
can really help.
Um-hm. And I suppose
if it weren't for our
unsuccessful time at the spa,
none of us would
have realized it.
Well, now that your
chores are streamlined,
what are you going to do
with all the extra time?
I think I have a few ideas.
Think you can come
up with enough things
for us to do now that we have
more time to relax?
Oh please, I could plan a
week's worth of treatments.
Huh. Well, let's
just start with the
rest of the day for now.
After all the work we
just did on the farm,
I am ready for some
serious relaxation.
Thanks for letting me
know there was an opening.
I don't know if I could
make it without my
pampered muzzle massage.
Don't worry about it.
Shall I put you down for
another one tomorrow?
Oh, absolutely.
Sometimes a girl just has to
pamper herself, am I right?
You
certainly are.
Oh. Oh! Hey! I
was just, uh, uh...
Getting a "sports"
pamperin'?
Don't
worry, Rainbow Dash.
We were just heading in for
some pampering ourselves.
You could always join us.
That is if you don't mind
suffering through
one or two "frou-frou"
treatments.
Ah, I suppose I could take
it. You know, for you ponies.
Busted!
Yeah.