Thanks for coming, Rarity.
The rescue center needs
all the help it can get.
Oh, but of course, darling.
Helping cute little puppies and kitties
will never go out of style.
Once a year, a lucky volunteer
gets to clean the hamster habitat.
I signed up for it
months ago to be sure I'd get it.
Housecleaning!
Ooh. Uh, Fluttershy, darling,
aren't hamsters, uh, rodents?
They sure are.
But they're cute and cuddly like bunnies.
Okay, everyhamster,
follow Rarity into the next room.
She'll take good care of you
while I give your home a nice scrub.
Rarity, what happened?!
Well, uh, Carl Pettington's coat
just begged to be accessorized,
but Emilia Furhart refused to be left out
and got Curtis Pawpower
to chew right through Carl's little scarf,
and before I knew it,
I had a habitat-wide feud on my hands!
Also, I named them.
Ladies and gentlehamsters, please!
Now, I know you're all upset,
but why don't we head back
into the habitat and talk it over?
I never would have guessed hamsters
could be so touchy about fashion!