Just remember, the most important thing
about sugar butter cocoa cookies
is to fold your batter.
Too much arm turnin'll make your cookies
tougher than a lump of coal.
Come on, Pinkie. You're s'posed to
help me find a drummer for my band.
I guess I could fold a little faster.
Most people don't know
how hard it is to find
someone who could use both hands
the way a drummer does.
I'll bet!
Now, it's important that
our banner look awesome!
So feel free to use
as much glitter as you want.
- A drummer can't just be anybody.
- Oh, of course not.
They need to have
the right instincts, you know?
Totally!
It's gotta be someone with a lot of...
- ...energy.
- Absolutely!
I mean, a lot!
Energy, enthusiasm...
- Pinkie!
- Whaaaaaaat?!
They have to be able to carry
the whole band on their shoulders!
Pinkie!
We've got to find
an outlet for all that energy!
What ever made you think of
Pinkie for the drums?
I dunno.
Guess I just have a sense for these things.