Come on, Rarity! You simply must
get this piano to band practice!
What kind of person
doesn't put a piano on wheels?
Just look at me.
I'm a mess.
What I need is
a bit more muscle.
Oh, boys!
I simply cannot thank you enough.
And while I am a bit repulsed
by your musky smell,
I can appreciate that
you're all diamonds in the rough.
Excuse me!
Pardon me! Excuse me!
Thank you!
Where is Rarity?!
That gal probably just wants
to make some sort of grand entrance.
Tada!
- Told ya.
- Rarity,
couldn't you have chosen
a more portable instrument?
Heavens, no! The grand piano is
the most refined and elegant of instruments.
With it, I will be able
to express my full musicality.
Well, our time's up. I guess
we'll have to move our practice to the gym.
Guess you're gonna express
your "full musicality" clear across campus.
Huh? Awww...
Or you could play this!
It's part guitar, part keyboard!
It's a guitarkey!
You mean a keytar.
Po-tay-to,
to-mah-to.
Oh, my!
Well, look at that!
- Wowee!
- Oh, my goodness!
Well, then,
how about ya take that keytar
and move your tail
to our next rehearsal space?
Fine, fine.
I don't suppose...