♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
- ( bell ringing )
- ( playing "Twinkle
Twinkle Little Star" )
Mr. Candle said
I'm gonna be a musician.
Sweet. I got
champion swimmer.
I was gonna get dressed,
but now I don't need to.
Wow. Everyone's getting
really awesome careers.
I can't wait to find out
what my future holds.
( nervous laughter )
MAN: Star Butterfly.
- Please sit.
- Okay.
Help yourself
to some candy.
No, thank you.
I'm just really excited
to have my fortune told.
How do you do it?
Read palms?
Converse with the dead?
Examine head lumps?
Nope. Just normal
guidance counselor stuff.
Have you given much thought
to your future?
Totally.
When I grow up,
I wanna raise warnicorns.
( whinnying )
Well, that seems like
a fun hobby.
But you might not
have much time for hobbies
as the queen of Mewni.
Queen?
I may not know
your fortune,
but your future
is set in stone.
Stone?
Are you dating anyone?
What? Uh, no.
What about that Marco boy?
Got a secret crush on him?
He's my roommate.
We're just friends.
Yeah, that's weird
to date your roommate.
Maybe someone else then.
It's never too early to start
searching for the future
king of Mewni.
Maybe.
Cheer up, Star.
Or should I say
Your Majesty.
Hmm.
So how'd it go?
Or we can catch up later.
Mr. Diaz.
I've been very anxious
to speak to you.
Seen my test scores,
have you?
Indeed.
Garbage Island?!
What's the use of taking
honors classes
if it gets you sent
to the middle of nowhere?
So don't go.
At least you have a choice.
Apparently, the only
thing in my future
is being queen.
Oh, man, I'd love
to be queen.
You never have to
think about what to wear.
You have somebody
do that for you.
( groans )
People would just love you
because they have to,
no matter how weird
you are.
( groans )
You never have
to bathe alone.
Marco, please stop
talking.
Head janitor,
Garbage Island.
( sighs )
( plopping sound )
I'll come back later.
All right, sir,
phase one is complete.
What's next?
Sir, are you there?
You idiot!
You forgot
the most important part. Me!
I got confirmation.
- Starco is
completely platonic.
- MARCO: Starco?
Make sure there's
no possibility of them
ever being a thing.
Absolutely, sir.
Also, stop offering
everyone candy.
You're gonna blow
my cover.
I want her back.
- I gotta go.
- I'm not done.
No. You don't understand.
- I gotta go.
- Flush me first!
( whistling )
Hey, Mr. Candle.
Oh, hello, Marco.
I appreciate
all your guidance
with Garbage Island
and all,
but I'm gonna pass.
Actually, I was just thinking
I might be...
king of Mewni.
( sputtering )
What?!
The thing is,
Star and I
have recently become
smooch buddies.
On the lips.
Even if that's true, kid,
you shouldn't say that out loud.
Yeah, we've been trying
all styles.
German, Italian...
Polynesian.
My tonsils are so tired,
I can't feel my teeth.
( ferocious growl )
Busted. I knew you weren't
a guidance counselor.
Oh. These women
look so miserable.
( sighs heavily )
MIRROR:  Calling Mom.
What did you do?
What... nothing!
Yet.
I'd like to
ask you something.
Are you happy?
Happy? What difference
does that make?
I mean, I don't know.
Do you have
any warnicorns?
Goffrey, do I have
You have 19,
Your Majesty.
- Oh. Apparently,
I have 19.
- Oh, sweet.
But when you are queen, you
don't have time for warnicorns.
Everything I'm saying
is in your guide book.
Incidentally, you may want
to review the chapter
on hair care.
If you're going to be queen,
you have to look the part.
Don't worry so much
about happiness.
It makes you look pale.
Love you. Bye.
( buzzing )
Stop! I knew
you were listening.
I never made out with Star.
I just said that
to get your goat.
What?
You lied to me.
Well, you lied to Star.
You made her think
all she's good for
is being queen.
Dude, just take me home.
I can't do that.
You know too much.
Now I gotta destroy you.
What?!
That's not fair.
All right, fine.
Battle to the death.
I win, you die.
What do I get
if I win?
It's not gonna happen.
So, yeah, ask for
whatever you want.
If I win, you gotta
take me home.
And you gotta tell Star
the truth.
Fine.
Pick your weapon.
Dueling battle axes?
Rhino fiend joust?
Pear grenades
of anguish?
( shrieking )
What about ping-pong?
That's cool.
Your weapon of choice,
my liege.
I oughta warn you,
I'm not only a karate master.
I'm also good at
ball sports.
Ow!
Point, Master Tom.
Okay, so I'm
a little rusty.
Wait till you...
hi-yah!
Owww!
Game point.
In your face!
Ow! Ugh!
Since when do ping-pong balls
hurt so much?
These balls are
guided by demons.
Okay. Let's play
for real this time.
Double or nothing.
Dude, you're
out of paddles.
Just give up.
No, it's fine.
Here, you can have mine.
I don't need it.
Hey! Isn't this
kind of cheating?
You think this
is cheating?
You should try playing
Star at ping-pong.
Well, Star doesn't
really cheat.
She just makes up
her own rules.
And then she changes the rules
again halfway through the game.
Oh, so that's why
I never win.
She just does
whatever she wants.
Yeah, that's Star.
Yeah.
She is kinda awesome.
You know you're
never gonna win, right?
I know, but
you're not either.
It doesn't matter if
you beat me at ping-pong
or pull out all my organs.
You can't make Star
be your girlfriend
unless she wants to.
Star, I have something
to tell...
Whoa.
Oh, hey, Marco.
Did you know that if you
cut off a mermaid's tail,
you can never be queen?
It's all in the guide book.
Star, you don't
have to do that.
Oh, thank goodness.
I'm so sorry, Tiffany.
I never wanted to hurt you.
Shameful.
Tom! What's going on?
I have something
I need to confess.
I used Mr. Candle
to try to get
back together with you.
It took me destroying
Marco 58 games to zero
to realize I was wrong.
Like, I slaughtered him.
I mean, beating him
was so easy.
Okay, she gets it.
All I wanted
was to get you back.
But I never stopped
to consider what you wanted.
I'm sorry.
Ow!
You tricked me.
But it doesn't even
make a difference.
I'm still gonna
be queen.
Yeah, but that doesn't
sound like a bad thing,
because you're gonna
run Mewni your way.
No matter how destructive.
That's true.
Point, Marco.
Well, I should go.
By the way,
I like your hair.
STAR: So you guys
were hangin' out?
Uh, yeah.
Is he still
dark and broody?
Oh, yeah.
But he's not so bad.
No, Brittany,
I don't believe
your life has peaked
at such a young age.
Dude, abort the mission.
I'm done.
( whistles )
( growling noises )
Star?
I don't know
my combination!
( gasps )
I'm... I'm...
I'm wearing a suit!
What are your plans
for the future, Mr. Diaz?
Mr. Candle?
GIRL: We're moving on
with our lives.
But I haven't made up
my balloon yet.
My red belt.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Wait!
Come back.
Marco. Marco, Marco!
- Marco, Marco, Marco.
- ( screaming )
- Star?
- You okay?
Sounded like you were having
one of those "stuck in life"
dreams again.
Yeah. Wait. What are
you doing in here?
I'm hanging my first
Love Sentence poster.
You can be
my prisoner of love,
Justin Towers.
Uh... that's not
what I meant.
I was sleeping.
Oh! Right.
You have a hammer?
I'm putting this bad boy up
Earth girl style.
No majack!
Yeah, all I'm saying is,
you could've tried
knocking on my door,
Earth girl style.
Why would I do that
when I have dimensional...
Oh!
How can I be so "duh"?
Nothing's easy on Earth!
( laughs )
I'm gonna find a hammer
the hard way.
Scavenger hunt!
Do we even have a hammer?
Sensei, I need to
talk to you about
- graduating to a red--
- Silence!
I'm about to achieve
oneness with the universe.
( inhales loudly )
( unintelligible muttering
and grunting )
Now, bow to your sensei.
Master, I've been
a green belt for five years.
It's time for me
to level up.
( laughter )
Five years, and you
think you're ready?
Go get an ice cream cone
or something,
and quit wasting
my Saturday.
Sensei, I'm serious.
Are you sure?
The training you desire
has broken many a student.
I'm ready to do
whatever it takes.
Fine.
We start...  now!
- Clip the toenail.
- Seriously?
- Clip the toenail!!
- Plunge the toilet.
- Ugh.
Take the deduction.
Is your moment of failure
at hand, Mr. Diaz?
No, sensei.
Hey, guys!
Just ignore me.
Why exactly are we
ignoring you?
I'm scavenging the house
for a hammer.
Just pretend
I'm not here.
Okey-dokey.
- Do we even
have a hammer?
- No.
( groaning )
If I was a hammer...
- I'd be up there!
- ( dogs barking )
We have to do something.
That's right, Mr. Diaz.
Feel the squeegee
deep in your soul.
Preparation is key.
- You never know when
trouble will arrive.
- ( horn honks )
- Hello, dear.
- Mom!
How nice to have you...
visit me at my own house.
It's nice to see you finally
getting to those windows.
And you have
a little friend helping you.
Maybe I'll fix you
a big helper's snack.
Your mom seems nice.
Oh, yes, she often
comes to see me.
But not too often,
on account of her
having her own home.
I'm glad you made
that distinction,
because it almost seemed
like this was her house.
Here you go, boys.
If you need me,
I'll be taking a nap
in my room.
Okay?
Okay.
It's clear that
you live at home,
in a room that is
unsettlingly similar to mine.
Uh... great.
Then you'll have
no problem cleaning it.
Wait a minute.
Are you training me
for a red belt,
or are you making me do
all your chores?
No, no, we're training.
Ha! Cut the toenail.
Ugh! I think I've
more than earned my red belt.
Uh, you can't because...
I, uh...
( sobbing )
- Because I'm also
only a green belt.
- What?!
I didn't know what
I wanted to do with my life
so I rented a dojo
and ordered these
instructional videotapes.
Each tape told me what to learn
to get each color belt.
It was going
pretty well at first,
- but I only watched as far
as the green belt tape.
- Why'd you stop there?
Because the red belt tape
got stuck in the machine.
Now it just holds up
the short leg on
my computer table.
Couldn't you just try
to get the tape out
and untangle it?
I did, but that tape
got stuck in another machine!
What kind of sensei
can't even work a VCR?
( breathes deeply )
Well, we can totally
find it online.
Except we can't.
It seems like this is
one of the rarest sets of
videotapes in existence.
I guess we'll just
have to find it IRL.
No way.
I owe those guys
too much in back taxes.
IRL means
in real life.
We just have to find
a copy somewhere out there.
I see. In that case,
we'll need wheels.
( Marco laughing )
- To adventure!
- Feel the wind
in my tassels!
( dog barking )
Mom, call Rocket.
He's being weird.
( loud clattering noises )
( groaning )
Find... hammer.
What is this place?
It's cool.
You'll love it.
Yuck. Come on.
It's like a yard sale,
but inside.
These are the only
kind of places
you can find
old videotapes anymore.
- Is that it?
- No.
- Nope.
- Is that?
Got it. Never mind.
This is how to karaoke.
This is impossible!
We're never
gonna find it.
Come on,
we just got here.
Why don't you go check
one of those other bookcases?
Sensei?
How about grape and cherry?
Ooh, you know what?
Just squirt every flavor
you got on it zombie style.
- Ooh, yeah.
- Why'd you leave?
Got some cash? I don't
get my allowance till Friday.
Oh, uh... here.
Fifty-one, 52, 53...
Sensei?
What are you doing?
Dude, these chicks
totally dig my bike.
- Are you for real?
- What?
You don't really wanna
earn your red belt, do you?
Look, we tried
and we failed.
And that's okay.
It's not okay.
I actually wanted
to be like you,
but you're just like me,
except I'm not gonna end up
38 years old
and still living
with my parents.
- I'll see ya later.
- Where you going?
I'm going to find that tape
and get my red belt.
Uh, bow to
your sensei.
I don't have
a sensei anymore.
So where am I gonna
look next?
I could check
more thrift stores,
but what are the odds I'll...
oh!
Bump into it?
You are no cinephile.
Next.
I'm looking for a rare set of
karate instructional tapes.
Finally. A customer who
knows what he's talking about.
It's the How To Karate series.
The red belt tape.
Behold, the coveted
volume 8 red belt cassette.
Viewed only once.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Not without
gloves, please.
Okay. How much is it?
I will give you
the aficionado price. 2,400.
Dollars?!
I can't afford that.
Well, there is another way.
Fight me for it.
Really? Yeah, okay.
I'm not leaving
without that tape.
Hey, Marco.
I'm still your sensei, right?
Sensei, he has the tape.
Mr. Diaz,
clip the toenail!
You... defeated me.
The tape is yours.
Can you ask him if he has
the How To Untangle
Multiple VHS Tapes
VHS tape.
No. Do you have
a pair of scissors?
Actually, we--
Not the critically
acclaimed
award-winning
romantic comedy
A Pair of Scissors.
An actual
pair of scissors.
No.
It's okay, guys.
I'm done.
Go on without me.
- ( clattering )
- A hammer!
( both sighing )
Now I just need
to find some nails.
Back to the store.
You know, red is
really your color.
It's yours too, sensei.
I'd say this Earth girl
did a job well done.
Now, let's clean this house
the easy way.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪