♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna
get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time! ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another ♪
♪ Whoo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah! ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-puh
-puh-puh-pu uuhh! ♪
♪ It's gonna
get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension! ♪
STAR: Far, far away
in a magical land called Mewni,
lived a princess--
Star Butterfly.
I'm fine!
Some people
have called me reckless
and irresponsible
just because...
( growls )
I fight monsters
and tame wild unicorns...
Yee-ha!
I like to have fun.
And I'm about to have
a whole lot more
because today
is my 14th birthday!
And according to tradition,
my mom, the Queen,
has to bestow upon me
our greatest family heirloom--
The Royal Magic Wand!
( hoof beats approach )
( all screaming )
( panting )
Now, Star.
This wand
is a big responsibility.
Yeah!
If it falls
into the hands of Evil Forces,
the universe
could be destroyed!
Aha-ha-ha-ha!
Don't worry, Mom,
I can handle it.
( screaming )
BOTH:
She can't handle it.
No! (sobbing )
I can be good!
Please!
Don't send me
to Saint Olga's Reform School
for Wayward Princesses!
Aaaaahhh!!!
Sweetheart, we're not
sending you there.
Oh!
Yet.
We're sending you to train
in a safer dimension,
a place called Earth.
Earth?
Manfred, open the portal.
( sighs )
Goodbye, Mewni.
( evil laughter )
( roars )
So you say you're from
another dimension.
And you said
there was no magic on Earth.
Yeah....
This isn't
gonna work.
( cash register dings )
She is gonna
love it here!
She's going to need a guide.
MAN: (on PA) Marco Diaz
to the principal's office.
Marco Diaz to
the principal's office.
Ooh, looks like
someone's in trouble.
So I guess everyone
who voted me Safest Kid
must be feeling
pretty embarrassed
right about now.
Do I need a hall pass?
Would you
just go already?!
Marco!
I want you to meet our new
foreign exchange student
Star Butterfly!
( gasps, growls )
Huh?
I need a responsible
never-take-chances type
to keep an eye on her,
and who better than you?
The safe kid!
What?! No, no, no,
I'm completely wrong for this.
I'm a misunderstood
bad boy!
You're adorable!
Now I'm off
to the ice cream shop.
Daddy's getting all 52 flavors!
Huh.
( growling )
Thanks for showing
me around, safe kid.
What? No.
Whatever you heard
about me isn't true.
Hi!
I don't know where people
get the idea I'm so safe!
Oh, watch your step.
Loose tile.
It's ridiculous!
Careful.
You wear a helmet
in the gym shower one time
and you're
labeled for life.
Oh, broken glass.
Frankly,
I like taking risks
and would welcome
a little danger in my life...
( screeches )
( screams )
What the heck was that?!
Oops...
I thought you wanted
a little danger.
Who  are  you?
(sing-songy)
I'm a magical princess
from another dimension.
( creatures screaming )
Well, that brings us
to the end of our tour.
I'm going home now.
Bye, new friend!
See you tomorrow.
Bye!
Bye, new friend!
See you later!
( laughter )
Oh, Marco! Come meet the new
foreign exchange student
who's gonna be
living with us!
Wha.. Wha..
What?!
I had no idea
these were your parents!
I just assumed
everyone on Earth
had the last name Diaz!
Won't it be nice
to have Star's upbeat,
lively energy
around the house?
We could have gotten that
from a litter of puppies.
I love puppies!!!
( yipping )
BOTH: Aww...
Oh. Eh...
Well, they are really cute.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ay! My eye!
Marco, why don't you
show Star her new room?
Yay!
( evil laughter )
( croaks )
Ludo, Master.
I've tracked down
Star Butterfly.
They've hidden her
in the Earth dimension,
unguarded.
( evil laughter )
Excellent work,
Buff Frog.
I knew they couldn't hide
that royal brat
from me for long.
So the wand will be mine.
And then the universe.
And then...
Actually, the universe
should do it.
I'm coming for you,
Princess Butterfly.
Here's your new room.
Ow!
O-kay.
I can
work with this.
Sparkle
Glitter Bomb Expand!
Whoa.
Ah, that's better.
I wish I had a room like this.
You do?
Huh?
Mystic Room Suck Transform!
( screaming )
Suck? Suck?!
Why was the word "suck"
in that spell?
I don't know.
It just came out that way.
( groans )
I'm sorry, Marco. Uh...
How about a little sunshine
to brighten your day?
( thunder rumbles )
Ohh...
I can't
take this anymore!
If you're moving in,
I am moving out!
Uhh!
Are you okay?
Luckily the cactuses
broke my fall.
Do you need any help?
Ow!
I'm fine!
Just leave me alone!
Uh. Ohh.
Ahh. Hmm.
Ahh. Uhh.
Huhh.
Here he comes,
here he comes.
Hey, brother, do me a solid.
Refill this for me!
They won't let me back inside
because I'm soggy!
Did you bring me my refill?
Don't make eye contact.
If you come to my house,
you bring toilet paper!
Whoa!
What are you
doing here?
I didn't get a choice
about coming here to Earth,
and you didn't get a choice
about having to deal with me.
I'll...
I'll find another family
to live with.
S-- St-- Star.
( growling )
Star Butterfly!
At last I've found you!
Ludo!
How did you know I was here?
( chuckle )
Wouldn't you like to know?
Yes, that's why I asked.
Well, Buff Frog...
Hey, I don't have to tell you
anything!
Get her!
( roaring )
Hi-ya!
( laughing)
You can fight?
It's called karate.
Karate!
You said
she was unguarded.
I don't know.
Hi-ya!
Huh?
Whoo-hoo!
Rainbow Fist Punch!
( growls )
Haa!
( horse neighing )
You're embarrassing me.
Get up!
( growls )
Jelly Bean
Hallucination Mist!
Whoa.
What is happening?
Hi-ya!
Mega Narwhal Blast!
( groaning )
STAR: You want some of this,
Ludo?
No.
You see, you morons?
This is what happens
when you don't work out.
Your muscles are like pudding.
Come on.
Back in the portal.
Back in
the portal.
You even
retreat like losers.
I'll get you,
Star Butterf--
That was amazing.
I was amazing.
You were amazing.
Yeah, I guess we were.
Well, I should probably go...
pack my bags.
Wait.
I don't want you to go.
I want you to stay with us.
Really?
Hugs!
Are there going to be monsters
attacking us all the time?
Yeah, probably.
All right!
Sounds so dangerous.
Whoa.
Let's cross at the light.
Okay, wild man.
MARCO: All right, Star...
feast your eyes on this!
♪ Marco's Super Awesome Nachos ♪
Ooh! Triangle food.
( knocking on door )
Yo, what up, home fries?
( screaming )
Oh, my gosh!
( groans )
Flying Princess Pony Head!
Oh, hello, B-Fly.
Girl, we're going out tonight.
Are you ready to make
some bad choices?
Let me just wake up Marco.
Oh, that is
not a dead person?
Not dead. Ohh...
Pony Head, meet my
best friend Marco Diaz.
Your  best  friend?
Huh? Oh-- no, no, no.
On Earth.
You're  my best friend
on Mewni.
Marco, this is the Pony
I've been telling you about.
I hate your face.
Plus, you're ugly.
(laughing) Just kidding.
That's a joke.
Tick-tock girl,
let's par-tay.
Yeah, Marco,
With her?
Um, okay, well, I was gonna--
but I mean--I was gonna--
I--uh-- all right.
My two besties
are gonna be besties!
Sweet. Let's go.
STAR: Dimensional scissors!
Ah! Jealous.
Wait, we're going
to another dimension--
Come on!
(bites)
Glitter.
She was here.
Ahh!
Huh?
( party music playing )
Where are we?
STAR: The Bounce Lounge.
My favorite
place to chill.
Just stay away
from the edge.
Huh?
Ahh!
Marco, photo booth.
Photo booth.
Come on!
STAR: Yeah!
Whoo! Now just you two.
A souvenir from the night
my besties became besties.
Yay.
Listen, we are not
gonna be besties.
We're not even
gonna be second-besties.
Second-besties?
That's not even a thing.
Oh, you want to
make this a thing?
Look here, Earth Turd,
this night is really
important to me.
You mess that up,
and you're gonna get the horn.
Got it? Good.
Real good.
Later!
Wow-whoo! Look at this!
Psst. Star, I need to
talk to yooooo...
Star, Pony Head
threatened to--
( screams )
Fall, fall, fall, fall...
Marco, be careful.
Pony Head just tried to
shove me off this cloud!
Oh, no,
she just gets a little wild
when she dances.
Oh, yes!
Oh, you like that.
You know you do.
You love it.
Well, she also
threatened to skewer me
in the photo booth.
Yeah...
she can be possessive.
Pony Head, let's go to
the Amethyst Arcade.
Marco will have
more fun there.
No way, girl.
I'm getting my dance on.
( gasps )
Yes, you are right, Star.
He will like
the arcade better.
Let's go!
(sing-songy)
She's warming up to you.
Holy pixels.
So many videogames!
Yes, I knew
you would like it here.
This place is
full of squares.
( groaning )
Look.
Lance Lance Revolution.
That's perfect.
You guys, go play.
COMPUTER:
Pony Head VS Earth Turd.
Hey.
COMPUTER: Round one.
Joust!
( neighing )
MARCO: Hi-ya.
You're going down,
Downer.
Oh, yeah?
Well, your mother's a horse.
Ah, okay,
and your point would be?
Aw, look at you two
getting along.
Eww.
Oh, I'll go get us
some nice cold icicles
to put on your disgusting,
sweaty back.
Hey, you, Square.
Have you seen this head?
Don't lie to me,
little man.
COMPUTER: You win.
Hah!
Who's the turd now?
Still you.
I think I'm next.
But with less abusive
trash talk, please.
Um, let's see,
do I want the pointy one
or the pointier one?
Oh, it's such a tough choice.
Hey, Star, I'm bored.
Uh, I know this other club.
So let's bounce.
Sounds cool.
I'll go get Marco.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
he went on ahead.
Um, yes, he wanted to save us
a good spot in the mosh pit.
Yes, that is
the course of events.
Classic Marco.
Always putting friends first.
COMPUTER: Finish him!
You win!
Ha! Did you see that, Star?
Try and beat that,
Pointy Head.
Star?
Pointy Head?
( heavy breathing )
( girls laughing )
Is this not a blast
or what, B-Fly?
Yeah-heah! But I don't see
Marco anywhere.
Pfft.
You got me, girl.
And I'm way more fun.
Uh, what are you talking about?
Uh, funny story,
you're gonna love it.
I kind of ditched him and left
him in the other dimension.
Oops.
What?!
( screams )
B-Fly!
How could you do that
to my best friend?
Best friend?
Last time I checked,
the best friend was me.
I can have two best friends.
Unless one of them
is a friend-ditching liar.
That Earth Turd means
that much to you?
He's the best turd
I've ever known.
Okay.
MYSTERIOUS FIGURE:
For the last time,
where is she?!
I'm telling you,
I don't know!
Not talking, eh?
What if I do...this?
Stop!
That's  really  annoying.
There he is.
Crystal Dagger--
Wait, B-Fly!
It's too dangerous,
girl.
Hold out your hand.
Your dimensional scissors?
I won't need them
where I am going.
But, Pony Head--
Oh, hey, creeps,
I heard you're looking
to ride with a pony.
So come and get me.
( growling )
( neighs, laughs )
Wow!
Out of the way, Squares!
( video game music playing )
ALL: Yay!
Stand back, Marco.
No, it's okay.
My hand is free--
Shiny Emerald Snake Strike!
Bleech.
Marco,
stop playing around.
PONY HEAD: Okay!
Whoo-hoo!
I feel so  alive.
Whoa!
ALL: Huh?  Run!
Back off, creeps.
Don't worry, Pony Head,
we've got your back--
of your head.
KING PONY HEAD:
Time to give it up, Cupcake.
Is that King Pony Head?
( whinnying )
Hello, Daddy.
Hello, Princess.
What is he doing here?
Oh, B-Fly,
it's the end
of the line for me.
But at least I got in
one last night of fun
with you, girl.
One last night?
Before what?
Before this:
I'm going to St. O's!
Not St. Olga's Reform School
For Wayward Princesses?!
( screams )
Oh, it's true.
I did it to myself.
I'm headed to the slammer.
It's reform school,
Cupcake, not jail.
Although admittedly
it is a lot like jail.
Oh, Pony Head,
you knew you'd get
sent to St. Olga's,
but you still came back
to save Marco.
Ah, well, you know,
it's hard to say it,
but he is your other bestie.
Okay, I said it.
Aww, come here.
BOTH: Hugs!
All right, Princess,
time to go.
STAR: Bye, Pony,
I'm gonna miss you.
MARCO:
Hey, Pony Head.
Good luck in Princess jail.
Aw. Thanks, Earth T--
I mean, thank you, Marco.
But don't worry about me.
No jail can hold onto
me for long!
( laughter )
Ah, kids, you have 'em
and then you wish
they weren't around.
Yay!
My besties  are  besties.
Yeah,
I wouldn't go that far.
Hey, we're stuck
in another dimension!
(sing-songy)
Oh, no, we're not!
Whoa.
Now we can go
anywhere we want,
anywhere
in the entire universe.
I know just the place.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been through
outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me ♪
♪ It's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪