♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from
another dimension ♪
( clearing throat )
Okay, quiet, everyone.
Quiet!!
Oh.
I assume you all brought
your swords.
Uh... what?
It said on the invitation
you're supposed
to bring a sword.
I was a little confused
by your invitation.
I'm not confused.
This is clearly a drawing
of meat.
I came for the meat.
I think everyone's
just wondering why they're here.
Uh, it's the 37th
of Grovnok.
- Mewnipendence Day.
- ( Ferguson coughs )
( frustrated groan )
Mewnipendence Day.
Along time ago arrived the first
settlers of Mewni.
( boat noises )
A modest people
with noble pursuits--
life, liberty,
and corn.
But the wicked monsters
rose up and attacked
the innocent Mewnans
to re-steal Mewni
for themselves.
So the queen
used her magic
to turn the simple peasants
into a fearsome army.
And then there was fighting.
Fighting, fighting,
fighting, fighting.
And the Mewnans won.
Ta-da!
( imitating fireworks
exploding )
Wait. But you just blew
past all the important parts.
- When do we eat?
- We feast after we re-enact
the great monster
massacre!
Now please split into
two teams--
monsters and Mewnans.
- Can I be a human?
- You are a monster.
That's why you
were invited.
Why do I always
get picked to...
- I wanna be a Mewman.
( all chattering )
You get to be
my general.
Thanks.
Lookin' pretty good.
Now we can begin
making costumes,
and after that,
the blood battle
can commence.
Yes, Marco.
What's that?
Oh, that's just
an all-seeing eye.
It follows you
around all day.
It's staring at me.
Don't worry, it's just
to remind the monsters
that the royal family
is always watching.
It's not actually
watching you, though.
( laughs )
That would be weird.
This is amazing!
She thinks
it's the all-seeing eye,
but it's not.
It is the most
efficient way to spy
on your enemies.
( giggling )
I can see her pores.
What secrets
lie beneath?
Ludo, Master.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
( makes kissing noises )
Look at this.
Now we can watch Star
wherever she goes.
In the kitchen,
bedroom, even in the bathroom.
Uh... sir?
Maybe we don't
keep the bathroom channel.
But Ludo, this eye
only has one eye.
My face has two.
That's twice the number
of the eyes.
Now that you don't have
any spy stuff to do,
you should get us
some popcorn and milkshakes.
I'm pretty sure we're gonna
binge-watch this baby
all night.
You can join us if you want,
as long as you keep quiet
and sit in the back.
She doesn't even know
we're watching her.
Sometimes your biggest threat
is right under your nose.
My nose is in my beak.
Mm-hmm.
( straining )
There.
That'll keep your entrails
from becoming your out-trails.
My pillow.
Hey, Star, I've been
looking through your...
Hold on.
I've been looking
through your book,
and, uh, something
seems off.
What do you mean?
Let me see.
Oh, okay.
Wow, you're right, Marco.
I can't believe
I didn't notice that before.
Sharper, sharper,
stabbier,
and you need to be on
a Warnicorn.
And now, for the monsters.
Hey, what do we get?
Hello. You're monsters.
Use your claws.
( growling )
Star, I know the monsters
are bad and all,
but this seems unfair.
Unfair?
Do something.
He's writhing in pain.
Oh, never mind.
He stopped.
Mom.
Owie.
Comrades, it's beginning.
Toffee replaced me
with electronic eye.
- Uh, we don't care.
- But you should.
Pretty soon,
Toffee will replace you
with electronic
ice cream cone,
and you with another
electronic ice cream cone.
And you with...
What is it you do
exactly?
Um, there's two of us,
so... maybe that's a thing.
Are you finished?
Gentlemen, allow me to direct
your attention
to our new
surveillance device.
Princess Butterfly
is re-enacting
our favorite holiday,
the great monster massacre.
My least favorite
holiday.
Don't worry, we can take
advantage of this opportunity.
Why send an army
after the wand
when it can be
hand delivered?
( gasps )
Oh, isn't that a thing thing?
And it's not like
she's going to notice
a real monster.
Those aren't real?
Okay.
Now, who'd like to bring
Ludo his wand?
( all mumbling )
I will go.
I thought you might,
you fat bag of garbage.
- I'm so sorry,
Ferguson.
- Come on!
Hey, Star,
everything's
set up.
We'll get started
whenever you give
the signal.
Or not, and we can
just go eat.
No, it's okay.
It'll be fun.
Okay.
Here we go.
Knights of Mewni,
Take up your
stabby weapons,
and drive out
the evil monsters!
ALL: Wow!
( battle cries )
I can't do this.
Make me invisible.
- I'm so sorry,
Ferguson.
- Come on!
Careful.
What a massacre.
Please don't hurt me.
( laughs )
( stammering )
( gasping )
What is he doing?
Ferguson?
Ferguson!
I am so sorry.
Marco was right,
this is unfair.
Ferguson, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just invisible.
All right, let's go
eat some corn.
ALFONZO: Yeah,
I need to sit down
for a few days.
What a disgrace.
This is what you get
when you hire people
from the swamp.
Let's watch again.
I'm telling you,
this thing,
it didn't work.
- It works fine for me.
- He sabotaged it.
I rescued you from
a life in the swamp.
I took you in,
I gave you pants,
and this is what
you do to repay...
wait a minute.
Where are your pants?
Uh, well...
Oh, get real!
You've brought shame
on this house.
Now go to your room.
I don't know what to do
about that one.
Should I take away
his milkshake privileges?
Seriously? This was
idiot-proof.
I think you know
what you have to do.
Uh...
No, wait. No!
Well, that was
pretty hardcore.
You did what
had to be done.
( chattering )
Um, are you sure
this is accurate?
You know what?
I think it's time
we just put the book away.
Okay.
No.
Nope.
Reading in the tub
is not...
a sure-fire fun way
to spice up a dull day.
Hmm.
Today might be the day
I face my biggest fear.
Boredom.
Maybe today's the day
I renounce my vow
to never have a dull day.
Today I will look
boredom in its eyes,
those beady little
black eyes,
like tiny little
black fists.
I'll look into those eyes
and I will say...
Oh, wait, never mind.
What's this? Oh!
The banagic wand.
Earth's coolest
magical treat.
( gasps )
Earth magic!
I swear to baby dolphin
giggles,
I will find
the banagic wand
before this day is done...
or die trying.
Or my name's not
Star Butterfly.
As me as my witness,
I'll never go bored again!
And anything else
I'm supposed to say
to make this official.
Whoo-hoo!
I don't know
where I'm going.
Hmmm.
Ah, "as featured on TV."
But I saw it in
this magazine.
Mmm. Aha!
A riddle.
( laughs )
But I'm terrible at riddles.
Need Marco.
( inhaling deeply )
- Marco!
- Ah!
- Earth magic. Look.
- That thing from TV?
( gasps )
You've seen it?
Yeah. It's one of those
late night commercials.
So it does exist.
To the TV!
I can't. I've gotta get
to my karate class.
Your new kidney
came from a werewolf.
Glitter Grenade Rewind.
It's so hot.
And I'm so bored.
What are they gonna do?
It's a little bit
of banana,
and a little lot of magic.
Designed by leading
freeze-ologists,
the banagic wand uses
state-of-the-art
molecular ice-stronomy
to frostulate
your sizzle zones and...
- Mmm.
- I'm totally
chilled out.
There's enough banagic fun
for all my friends to enjoy.
( all exclaiming
happily )
Friendship magic.
Available at better stores
near you.
Better stores?
Supplies are limited.
Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
I can't.
I have karate.
Today we're learning
how to channel
our emotions.
To a better store
near us.
- Did you hear
anything I just said?
- ( humming )
♪ A little bit of banana,
a little lot of magic ♪
Star, I can't go now.
And I'm not sure you have
a firm enough grasp
on Earth culture
to go on your own.
Hey, get out of yard box,
you scoundrel!
Hide your dragon eggs
somewhere else.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's go.
- ( groans )
- Marco, we're not moving.
You push these little thingies
with your feet.
Honestly, Marco,
sometimes I wonder
if you have a firm grasp
on this Earth stuff.
Oh, too slow.
Bunny Rocket Blast!
Karate class?
Marco, we don't
have time for detours.
The commercial said
we have to hurry
while supplies last.
Focus on the quest.
This is where I'm going.
Karate.
I am not going with you.
Dear, sweet Marco.
I commend him for making it
this far on the journey,
and vow to complete
the quest in his honor.
Good-bye, sweet Marco.
The store is guarded
by a werewolf.
I wish you no harm,
werewolf.
All I seek
is the banagic wand.
Is this a better store?
Uh, better than what?
( frustrated groan )
More riddles.
I wish Marco
was still with us.
You must learn to channel
what is deep inside you.
Diaz, name an emotion.
- Uh, hunger.
- Channel your hunger, Diaz.
Channel your emotions
to brave the gauntlet of fire!
Wait, we're gonna walk
on those?
( evil laughter )
- ( door bell rings )
- Uh, that one's okay.
but there's a better store
down on Main and Riverside.
A better store near me.
There's a better store
on Main and Riverside?
- Yeah.
- Whoo-hoo!
Which way is
Main and Riverside?
Aha!
Diaz, approach.
Classic Marco.
Writhing in agony.
( growls )
Okay, I'm on Main Street.
Now, where is
Riverside?
( gasps )
A river and its side.
I found it!
Like I knew I would.
Ahoy, matey.
- Pirates.
- That's what we arrgh.
Now come with me
to Davey Jones' fish locker.
Okay, pirate.
I am at your mercy,
for I am but
your helpless prisoner.
Not true. I'm a powerful
princess from another dimension,
and I'm gonna get us
all out of here.
Freedom is nigh!
Arrgh, ma'am?
Surrender, pirates.
Huh?
Stay back, you
bloodthirsty savages.
- Tiara Tornado!
- Enough!
Do you surrender, pirate?
We aren't pirates.
This is a pirate-themed
restaurant.
( nervous giggle )
Do you know where
I can find a better store?
( screaming )
A better store.
MAN: There she is!
Can I borrow this?
Thanks so much.
Bye.
My baby's in there.
Oh, no, there he is.
( all yelling )
Oh, no!
Starlight Foot Smash!
Miranda, I swear, if you
wear fuzzy boots to my party,
I will break
your feet off.
What the...
Brittany, you've gotta help me.
There's an angry mob
after me.
Could you throw 'em
off my trail?
Tell them I went
that way? Thanks. Bye!
She went in there.
And here we have
Marco Diaz
approaching
the gauntlet of fire.
It's been a tough 14 years
for Diaz.
No girlfriend, can't seem
to get past green belt.
That history of failure must be
suffocating him right now.
Jeremy, get out of here!
I'm trying to channel
my emotions.
( camera clicks )
Fail, fail, fail.
Enough!!
You little twerp.
Diaz, wait!
- Huh?
- You did it!
( laughs )
I did it.
I understand now, sensei.
Diaz.
- This was all a part...
- Diaz.
- You had Jeremy act...
- Diaz!
Foot fire, buddy.
( shivering )
They're magnificent,
aren't they?
You! Time to pay for
what you've done.
Are they talking to you?
Mm-hmm.
Wreck my store?
I'll show you.
Okay, you guys
need to chill out.
( gasps )
The banagic wand.
♪ A little bit of banana,
a little lot of magic ♪
Designed by leading
freeze-ologists,
the banagic wand uses
state-of-the-art
molecular ice-stronomy
to frostulate your sizzle zones
and chill you out!!
Star, I'm back.
You still wanna go... huh?
Hey, Marco.
I conquered my boredom.
( all cheering )
Hey.
Here. I went downtown
by myself.
I know. I was there.
It was way easy.
I guess you could say
I've totally mastered Earth.
Sorry I underestimated you.
You underestimated me?
Uh... yeah.
I did.
Sorry.
This stuff looks
delicious though.
- Why did you...
- There was a fly on it.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪