♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
( straining )
Faster, Marco, faster.
Stairs!!
- That's it.
- Huh?
If you love
bike riding so much,
you should learn to
ride one yourself.
You can do that?
Teach me,
teach me, teach me!
( whimpering )
You're not gonna let me
fall, are you, Marco?
Nope. I got you
by the seat.
You won't let go?
I won't let go.
Promise?
Yes, I promise, Star.
Okay. Vroom!
Okay, hold on.
First, this bike
is not a toy.
It's my baby.
My honey.
Custom-tuned
alloy spokes.
Sweet ergonomic grips.
Custom-forged
titanium fork.
- ( kissing sounds )
- Okay.
But where are the giant
invisible goats?
Invisible goats?
Come on,
you know.
To pull you!
Everything on Mewni
is pulled by invisible goats.
What? Uh, there are
no giant invisible goats.
On Earth, we use pedals.
Oh, cute!
On Mewni,
only flowers have petals.
Okay, the first step
of biking is to coast.
Okay, you've
got the seat.
I've got the seat.
Huh? Wow!
Hey, I got this.
Yes! Okay, Marco, you can
let go of the seat now.
I think I'm ready
to do it on my own.
- Oh, I already
let go of the seat.
- What?
Yep, you've been riding
all by yourself.
Marco! You said you'd
hold onto the seat.
You lied to me!
Ah, come on. I did it
to give you confidence.
And look at you.
You're awesome, and I
taught you everything you know.
- Except how to stop.
- What?! Use the brakes.
You never taught me...
how!!!
( panting )
Call Star.
( shrieking )
Hi, Marco.
You have to use
the brakes.
Just put your feet
on the pedals
- and push back.
- That doesn't even
make sense.
It's spinning
the other way.
This princess says
no, thank you.
Fine. Do you have
your wand?
Oh, dip.
It's in my backpack.
( keytar playing )
Uh... Oskar?
What are you doing
in my driveway?
I thought this was
my studio.
JK. Everywhere's
Whatever. Just drive.
That way.
Seatbelt.
Uh, why is your car
filled with garbage?
Yeah, it's sort of
a live/work space.
Oh, hey, it's Gene.
Oh, double hey, it's my keys.
Go!
Don't walk.
It says don't walk!
Sorry.
( horn honking )
Oskar, Oskar, Oskar, Oskar!
- Cool. Little book dude.
- Glossaryk.
Pop quiz, Mr. Diaz.
Where is Star,
and why do you
have her wand?
I was teaching Star
how to ride a bike.
She doesn't know
how to stop.
- Help.
- Hmm.
Where are the giant
invisible goats?
There are no giant
invisible goats.
Star doesn't have her wand.
You have to help her.
Mmmm.
( chanting )
What?! Are you joking?
Boy, this isn't
a magic problem,
and thusly...
is beyond my control.
Whoa, you put corn
chips on your subs?
That is dope.
I love the crunch!
You must try it.
Whoa!
Cheers.
Uh...
- What is that?
- You play?
( people screaming )
- OSKAR: Okay, now
to the right.
- ( honking )
Back to the left.
You're getting it.
Now put
one finger here.
Can you guys stop
goofing around?!
Star is in trouble!
( synthesized voice )
Trouble, trouble...
Oh, yeah.
MC Oskar on the mic.
Marco make some noise!
Trouble, trouble,
tr-tr-trouble.
Trouble, trouble
tr-tr-tr-tr trouble.
( Oskar rapping )
♪ Now in my car,
I am the boss ♪
♪ Tracking down Star
at any cost ♪
♪ Booker can't help
'cause there is no magic ♪
♪ Star will be fine,
this won't end tragic ♪
♪ Trouble,
tr-tr-trouble ♪
♪ Trouble, trouble...
Yeah! ♪
♪ Got sloppy hot rhymes
like a meatball sub ♪
♪ Little book dude,
he is my bud ♪
♪ Drivin' through signs
'cause we doin' our thing ♪
♪ Marco lookin' chill
like he relaxing ♪
Oskar, could you maybe
be looking at the road?
Oh, you are just
so cute.
( barking )
Okay, Mama doesn't
have time to play. Shoo, shoo.
Uh, I'm out of rhymes.
Wiggly fan man,
take the mic.
( wind rustling )
Great song.
Number one hit.
Now can we just get
focused on Star
getting her wand back?
I'm with you, man,
but I don't think
we can get to her before the...
Sinkhole?
A sinkhole?!
( screaming )
- Good work, wings.
- ( barking )
If only those dogs
had been wearing helmets.
Wish we had some.
Star, pedal in reverse.
It will work.
Trust me.
I don't trust you
anymore, Marco Diaz.
Besides, I'm moving forward.
Pedaling backwards
doesn't make any sense.
I know just how she feels,
'cause I can't stop either.
The brakes are out.
Steering wheel, too.
Everybody lean!
Cuddle puddle.
Star, quick,
the wand.
- Use your magic.
- What?
Oskar!
Star, wait. Your wand.
( gasps )
Total eclipse!
- Marco!!
- Star!
- ( shrieks )
- ( horn honking )
I should've never
let go of her seat.
Okay, no more
kidding around.
This calls for magic.
( chanting )
( stomach rumbling )
Uh... which is what I'd do
if I hadn't eaten that...
ooh... that meatball sub.
( groaning )
Word.
( groans )
Okay, it's up to
you, Marco.
Give her wand to her
and save her life.
How? The car's wrecked.
Ride the invisible
goats, of course.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna be sick.
( vomiting )
( angry stammering )
For the last time, there are
no giant invisible goats.
Sure there are.
You just need to believe.
If you want to save Star,
trust in goats.
( vomiting )
Fine. If it saves Star,
I'll believe.
ALL: Believe,
believe, believe.
Believe!
( goat bleating )
I'm on an invisible goat!
( laughing )
Okay, goat, tally whoa!!
Whoa!
Star, take the wand.
Marco, you're my hero.
Who I'm still upset with
for lying to me
about holding my seat.
Come on, give me one more
chance. Hurry!
( Marco yelling )
Help! Help, help!
( Star screaming,
goat bleating )
You're gonna have to stop
the bike by yourself.
Pedal in reverse!
I told you, that is not
how we do things on Mewni.
You're not on Mewni
anymore, Star.
And if I can believe in
an invisible goat,
then you can stop
that bike.
I got you.
Trust me.
Thanks, Marco.
But you believing in me
is all I need.
- Star!
- ( goat bleats )
I was so worried
about you.
Marco, you were right.
I can ride a bike.
And I am
awesome at it.
How about
Mysterious Sonograms?
That's a good
band name.
But does it match
our sound?
Hey, Oskar, I'm really
sorry about your car.
But if you want, I can
give you a ride home
on my bike.
Cool. Hey, Glossaryk,
Gene, hop on.
Safety first.
Marco, you coming?
No thanks, Star.
I'll take the goat.
Believe.
( laughter )
Oh, Marco, the goat
left long ago.
( groaning )
( horns honking )
Okay, Diaz, you got this.
Aim it at
the little...
( angry muttering )
All right, going again.
Hey, this is
hard enough already.
Star, can you please
get control of these puppies?
I'm trying to focus.
Yeah, no problem.
Totally. Come on.
I believe in
you, Marco.
Star, I'm concentrating.
Right, right,
right, right, right.
Okay, I'll be quiet.
Even if no one
else does...
I believe.
Got it. I'm
trying to focus.
( mirror chiming )
Just answer it, please.
Ugh. Hey, Mom.
Star, your Aunt Felicity
still hasn't received
her thank-you card for
the lovely necklace...
Just give me the juice!
I can't right now, Mom.
Things are happening.
You said that
the last time...
Marco, did you
free the nectar
from the juice cocoon?
Get the puppies
out of the way.
Oh, stop it, puppies.
Here. Go fetch!
Oh no!
Did you just
throw your wand?
I threw my wand.
The poo-poo bin!
No, no, no!
Oh, thank Mewni.
Saved by the bush.
What?
( straining )
Got it.
Oh, you're
just a doggie.
For a second, I thought
you were a gargoyle.
- Thank you for
bringing me my wand.
- ( growls )
Ooh!
- I can just...
- ( growling )
- Let me just get...
All right,
this is annoying.
Is your person
here somewhere?
There's no one else
in the park, Star.
Everyone always leaves
when we get here...
for some reason.
The laser puppies
are hungry.
- Just grab your wand.
Let's go.
- Hmm.
Star, what are
you doing?
That's a dog,
not a coat.
- Fur coat.
- No.
Look, you're basically
a pet owner now.
You're gonna have
to feed him.
He'll put the wand down
if he wants to eat.
- Okay.
- Is that normal?
( toilet flushing )
( water running )
Sorry. This is
your problem.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Come on, puppies.
( barking )
Hi.
So it's
bedtime now,
and I sleep best
with my wand
right under my pillow.
Even though my mom
says not to,
because of...
radiation.
( growling )
( snoring )
Star, you down here?
- What?
- ( screams )
Star, come on.
We gotta get going.
We're gonna be
late for school.
Okay, okay.
- Just give me a sec.
- ( growling )
Magic doggie,
get me ready for school.
All right.
Guess it's a hat day.
( bell rings )
They make this for kids.
Just open!
- Miss Butterfly.
- What?!
Where are you going
with that dog?
He's got my wand.
A dog in a classroom
is a roadblock to learning.
Do not come back until
you get rid of that dog!
( groaning )
- Cool hat,
Star Butterfly.
- Shut up.
Star, you have to send
your aunt a thank-you card.
It's a really nice
necklace.
I can't talk right now, Mom.
I just got kicked out of school.
-   What...
- Uh, no dogs in the store.
Sure. Ignore me.
I'm not, like,
a person with feelings.
Or anything.
That'll be a buck-fifty.
Oh, I can't make
any money right now,
'cause my dog
has my wand.
- ( growling )
- See?
Right.
On your tab then?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's Marco Diaz.
Cool. Thanks, Joe.
Name's not Joe.
And my name's
not Marco.
( gasps )
Lost dog!
( doorbell chimes )
Come back.
Please stop that.
Sorry.
( giggles )
"Lost smallish
medium-to-large dog."
You're a smallish
medium-to-large dog.
"Dog-ish face."
Yep, dog-ish face.
"May or may not bark."
( growls )
You may or may not bark!
I'm pretty sure this flyer
is talking about you, mister.
"Call 555-0199."
Okay, 555-0199.
( phone dialing )
( line ringing )
Hello. Thank you
for calling--
Hi. I got your flyer
and I think I found your dog.
I do not have
any pets.
Is someone calling
about my dog?
- Uh, yeah.
- It's for me.
Hello.
This is Lydia.
Hi. I found your dog.
I am outside
the Stop And Slurp.
Be right there.
Okay. Bye.
Hi. Here for
this little gargoyle?
I found him.
Here you go.
Come to Mommy,
my little, um...
Willow... bee.
Right. Okay. Can you get
Willoughby to drop my wand?
I... I can do that.
Willoughby,
put it down.
Where are you going?
( toilet flushing )
( water running )
It's cool you taught
your dog to use the bathroom.
Yeah.
( nervous giggle )
That's not your dog,
is it?
( nervous giggle )
But I have...
so much love to give.
MARCO: Stand up.
- Bark.
- ( barks )
Now play pirate.
Now laser the hole.
( shrieks )
- Okay, everything
is half red.
- ( door opens )
Star, where
have you been?
- I don't wanna
talk about it.
- Okay.
Today was the worst
day ever, Marco.
I got sent home from school,
I couldn't make any money,
- so I had to put
everything on your tab.
- What?
I was harassed
by a weird lady,
and worst of all,
Willoughby still won't
give me back my wand.
( frustrated groan )
His name's Willoughby?
That's what the weird
lady called him.
I thought I found
his owner, but she
was just a fake.
Yeah, this flyer's
obviously fake,
but let's go back
to the dog park
and see if his real owner
put up a flyer.
( sighs )
Okay.
- You know your eye
is glowing, right?
- I know.
Nope.
Beep, beep, beep.
Where's your owner?
My problem is,
I'm stuck in
a doubt loop.
You so are.
( beeping rapidly )
( buzzing )
Mm-mm.
Come on, Willoughby.
- Why is this so hard?
- I know. Right?
Oh, right.
Your thing is hard, too.
( groaning )
Willoughby senses something.
( Star gasps )
Marco, look.
Beautiful businessman.
Go, Willoughby.
Go to your businessman.
That's it!
What the...
Sorry.
What just happened?
Who are you?
It doesn't matter.
Why did you
take my wand?
( sighs )
Because in my dimension,
dogs are the ones
with all the problems.
There's no escape.
Only sadness.
It's easier if you
poke it from the bottom.
You did it.
White grape.
All I really want
is to be...
like them.
I thought if I
zapped myself with your wand,
I could quiet
my troubled mind.
( slurping )
But you can't just
run away from
all your problems.
( choking ) You run away from
your problems all the time.
No. I just take breaks.
That's what I want.
I want a break.
You don't need
magic for that.
You need
a chew toy.
( squeaking )
And you need
to play fetch.
No, Star!
No fetch.
Oh, yeah.
And you need
a Marco, too.
Hey, Lydia,
I found your dog.
Again.
I've been here
all along.
Come here,
my sweet little boy.
Actually, he's a girl.
It doesn't matter.
My little cake pop.
It's time to come home.
Go on.
I guess it couldn't hurt.
Wait.
There's one more thing.
Your necklace?
I couldn't.
Eh, it's a win-win.
This way, I don't have
to send my Aunt Felicity
a thank-you card.
( baby talk )
Now go get your Lydia.
Uh, why are you
talking to me like that?
'Cause that's how
we talk to wittle doggies.
This is what happiness
feels like.
( panting )
Thank you for
finding my dog.
Bye.
See, Marco?
I do face my problems.
( compact ringing )
Is that your mom
calling again?
Break!
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪