♪♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ Gonna get a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from
'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another, woo-hoo ♪
♪ Yeh-heah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Pa, pa, pa, pa,
pa, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from 'round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Guess who!
It's me, Star.
I have some exciting news
for you.
Well, first, Marco
got kidnapped,
and then I blew up
a bunch of stuff,
including my wand.
And I was super bummed
because I thought
I was never gonna get
to do magic again,
but then, I got
my new wa...
My new wand!
Oh, yeah,
and Marco's okay.
Say hi, Marco.
Hey!
I don't want the computer
to watch me shower.
( gasps )
- What's up with
your wand?
- I don't know.
Oh, no, it's going
downstairs.
( yells )
I almost died.
My towel!
Hang on.
I'll get you out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second.
- I'm not decent.
- Oh, okay.
Don't open that.
Wasn't gonna.
Uh, it's locked.
What?!
Try the knob.
What do you think
I am doing?
No, no, not now,
sweetie.
I usually open
this door with my wand.
Well, your book ate it.
Better not be
pokin' around in there.
That's my secrets closet.
It's private.
Just get me outta here.
( straining )
What are you doing?
Uh, hey, Glossaryck.
My wand's locked
in the closet.
Hey, what about me?
Oh, yeah. Marco's
in there, too.
And my spell book.
Basically all my stuff.
I want my stuff.
Did you try the knob?
I tried
the knob.
Anything?
Nope. Still locked.
Aha! What's going on?
Is this some kind
of training thing
or something?
Are you some kind
of training thing?
Are you mad?
Is this wolf-kabob rock bandage
ba-ba-bandage --
Stop, stop. Stop it!
Just tell me how
to get out of here.
Okay, I'll tell you
what to do.
- Are you listening?
- Yes, I'm listening.
To reach the chunks
in the hobo stew,
find her secret.
That's the clue.
So if I find her secret,
the door's just gonna
magically open?
Good-bye!
Secret?
Which one?
Here we go.
Why don't you try
the easy way
and open the door
with magic?
I can't do magic.
My wand's in the closet.
( gasps )
Do you wanna try
the hard way?
Yeah!
What's the hard way?
You've never heard
of the hard way?
Nope. Sounds hard though.
Oh, it is.
But I can teach you.
Teach me.
The lesson begins
inside my eyeball.
Imagine the universe
as this big old cauldron,
and magic is
the bubbly stew inside,
and your wand is the spoon.
And now...
My wand isn't a spoon.
It's a wand.
It's a metaphor, Star.
No, it's a wand.
Fine. It's a wand.
Now you're getting it.
Now the wand can only
skim the surface
of the hobo gravy,
watery and brown.
But if you want
to get to the chunks,
you've got to dip down.
Get it?
Uh-uh.
Okay, look.
You can do magic
without your wand.
You just have to
dip down, ya know?
Dip down.
Dip down!
Without my wand?
Your mom did it.
Psh! If she can do it,
I can do it.
Okay, I've just gotta
dip down.
Hot laser!
I am so sorry.
Star, try dipping down...
for the chunks.
( whistling )
Ow!
Ah, Marco my boy.
How's it going over there?
Oh, you know, just trying
to find her "secrets"
in a closet full of secrets!
Yes, well, you know
I do this because I love you.
Okay, that's
a little weird.
I'm sure it is.
Now if you don't mind,
I've got work to do.
Yeah. So do I.
Help... me!
- ( screams )
- Hmm.
( whistles )
You ever dip down
before, Sajak?
Yeah, me neither.
What a mess.
It's time to get organized.
No.
No!
Dip down, dip down,
dip down, dip down.
Dip down, dip down, dip
down, dip down, dip down.
Dip  down!
Down!!
Aquarium blast!
Fish blast.
Are you okay?
Dip down.
Nope.
( Marco screaming )
They're biting me!
That didn't work.
Stop eating
my flesh.
Hmmm.
Hmm. Hmm. Hmmmmm.
( exhales )
Ahem. Call Mom.
Star?
Hi, Mommy.
What did you do?
( stammering )
Okay, Marco's locked
in my closet,
and Glossaryck wants me to
dip down to get him out.
Dip down?
I didn't learn that
until I was 19.
Wow! So I'm, like,
advanced.
( chuckling )
I suppose.
Anyway, Glossaryck didn't really
give me any instructions, so...
Ha. That sounds familiar.
Well, it's not easy.
If you want to dip down,
you have to summon
everything you have.
Everything?!
Oh!
Everything.
Star, you do know
what I mean by everything...
Yeah, totally, totally.
Okay, I think
that's everything.
You want everything?
Everything you shall get.
Marco Diaz
makin' progress.
( crashing )
Okay, that's not good.
Well, Marco, looks like
I'm just a skimmer.
Skimmin' the surface
of the hobo gravy.
The watery hobo gravy.
How are things
goin' for you?
Not so good.
Actually, you thwarted
my progress.
I guess
it's not that bad.
I can slide sandwiches
under the door.
Bring you your homework.
Life could be good for you.
I don't wanna live
in your secrets closet.
( yells )
All right.
No more riddles,
little man.
Tell me what I'm
supposed to be looking for.
My eyes!
Oh! So this is
the thing.
Bingo.
Star, I found the thing.
It's a little book.
That's good.
Reading will keep
the mind sharp.
Like a horn.
It's in
Mewnian writing.
Oh, wait,
here's English.
"Chapter one.
Mom's a poop head."
Mom's a poop head?
Marco, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
Hang on, Star.
Just give me a sec.
Marco, no.
That's not the thing.
- That's not the thing!
- Skipping forward.
- Marco, put that down!
- "On my tenth birthday,
I put noxie frogs in
all the servants' beds."
Hey.
I'm out of juice.
Dip down!
Marco, it's not the thing,
it's not the thing!
"Chapter 11,
my thoughts on...
Marco."
( gasps )
Dip down.
I did it!
I dipped, I dipped,
I dipped, Marco!
I'm not a skimmer.
I dipped!
Ow!
Sorry. But don't
read my journal.
Well, this thing's
broken,
but give it a whirl.
Uh...
I'm gonna go
put on some pants.
Uh...
( coughs )
I call dibs on
the new tower.
Where is my castle?
It's gone.
And where is
your wand?
That's gone, too.
Everything?
We are no longer friends!
We never were friends.
You are now
my mortal enemy.
This day, I vow...
( screaming )
( screaming continues )
Adrift in the universe
that is infinitely expanding.
Toward nothing...
away from nothing.
A passage of time
marked by age.
Marked by hunger
of the spirit.
And hunger...
of the body.
Alone.
Infinitely...
Chips...
Food...
( straining )
Come back.
Where am I?
Ow!
Dirt...Ow! In my eye!
The sky is throwing
water at my face.
My chips!
Can I please...
Sushi come back.
I want my sushi.
Oh, yes, yes.
Excuse me, brother.
Lunch over?
You never loved me!
( stammering )
( squeaking )
( Ludo screaming )
Please don't let me go.
( straining )
Don't fight it, bro.
You're stuck.
Just let it happen.
Snow!
( crying )
Snow.
No, no.
( spits )
( laughter )
You taste bad.
Never mind.
I'll shut up.
Oh, that's horrible.
Tastes pretty good.
More, please.
Please, please, please.
How long have
I been asleep?
Where are you going?
Ow!
Gotcha!
My chips!
( high-pitched shriek )
Big mistake.
Come and get me.
( shrieking )
Ya-ha. Uh-oh.
Look out below.
I win, and to the victor...
the spoils!
Go get it.
Keep it comin'.
Good.
Whoa.
That's enough.
You'll get
the scraps later.
( screeching overhead )
It's time.
Hi.
Nature is a cruel mother.
And favors the merciless.
And so, in order
to survive,
Ludo in the wild
must find
the wild in Ludo.
Hey, Ludo.
Hi.
No, no, no.
Find somebody else to...
get the wand!
It's mine.
It will be mine!
( whistles )
Arachnid!
Bird!
Oh, no. No, no, no!
Where'd she go?
No!!
Cruel vision.
I'm...
on Mewni.
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty great place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers
are just friends ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking I could
call this place home ♪