♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna have a good time ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another woo-hoo! ♪
♪ Yea-ah ♪
♪ I'm talking rainbows ♪
♪ I'm talking puppies ♪
♪ Puh-puh-puh-puh-puh-
puh-puh-puuuhh ♪
♪ It's gonna get
a little weird ♪
♪ Gonna get a little wild ♪
♪ I ain't from round here ♪
♪ I'm from another dimension ♪
Eh.
Ugh.
Uh.
Eh.
Oh.
Ah!
Cacti for the win.
( puppies yipping )
Ah! Out of the way!
I overslept.
I'm gonna be late.
Ah, where's my hoodie?
Whoa, chill, Marco.
We can still get to school
by first period.
This isn't about learning.
This is about  love.
Every day,
I get there by 7:55,
because at exactly 7:56,
Jackie Lynn Thomas gets there.
And we share a nod.
It's kind of our thing.
( sighs )
Aww.
Wait, a nod?
You don't even say hi?
I'm working up to that.
See, it's all a part
of my 23-step plan.
I'm already on step 4:
Nodding every day.
Hmm.
Hey!
Down, boy.
Bad laser puppy.
It's 7:54!
I can't make it.
Can't you just, uh, uh,
magically stop time
or something?
( laughs )
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Easy peasy time freezie.
( clock ticking )
( yipping in slo-mo )
( singing in slo-mo )
Ow!
Do you know
what you just did?
Uh, froze time?
You froze time!
Now I can get to school
and nod at Jackie.
Hurry!
School?
But it's a ♪ freeze-day! ♪
Ha ha ha!
Whoo-hoo!
( both laughing )
Mmm! Mmm!
Yee-hee!
( laughing )
MARCO (laughing):
That was the funnest
60 hours of my life!
Oh, hey,
there's frozen Jackie!
I better get into
optimal nod position.
Ready.
Or, maybe, now's the time
to move on to the next step
of your crazy plan.
You could ♪ talk to her ♪
The--the--
The wind isn't right.
I've got a pimple coming in.
Uh, I'll just do the nod today.
Okay.
Easy peasy time unfreezie!
Huh.
Ooh.
Come on, Star.
What's going on?
Star?
Not you too.
Ha ha!
I'm just messin' with ya.
( grunts )
Okay, Magic Instruction Book,
instruct me.
Oh, no,
Glossaryck is frozen too.
Good.
I never liked that guy.
Scrape the sides, buddy.
Okay, let's see, let's see.
What to do if you make
a dimension explode.
What to do
if you delete gravity.
Oh.
Don't get any ideas.
Heh-heh. Sorry.
Ah!
What to do if you freeze time.
We can move time forward
if we go to the planes of time
and push the wheel
of progress.
Whoa.
This is definitely
one of the weirder places
we've been to.
Weirder than that dimension
of cats with human faces?
Here, kitty, kitty!
(demonic voice)
Look away!
( shivering )
Look!
That must be it.
Whoa.
Looks like
a giant hamster wheel.
STAR: Now,
how do we start this thing?
Hmm. I got this.
( grunting )
New plan.
Rainbow Raccoon Rotation.
Hmm.
Magic won't work on that.
You got to use
the magic of toesies.
Who are you?
I'm Father Time.
And this is Rocksworth.
He's  a rock,
but don't bring it up,
he's kind of sensitive
about it.
( makes motorboat sounds )
Father Time?
So you must push this thing.
Hey, look!
I'm over here.
And now, I'm over here!
Ha ha ha ha!
And how long
were you  on  the wheel?
Oh, you know, forever.
Until someone
cast a freeze spell
and knocked me off of it.
What is  that?
Uh, mud?
Oh, it's glorious!
I  love  mud.
( gags )
So, Mr. Time,
how would you feel about
getting the universe
started up again?
Oh, where has this been
all of my life?
Ah, look, look, look.
You can play with mud
on your wheel.
Huh?
Well, that is an enticing offer,
but nah.
Arrghh!
Oh! There's some mud
that's a slightly
different color.
And there's a twig,
and there's a bush,
and I don't know
what that thing is,
but it's waddling.
Wait! You can't just
leave time stopped!
Whoo!
But without time,
rainbows can't shoot
across the sky,
glitter can't glitter!
And everyone we know
will be frozen forever!
What's this?
Ooh!
( laughing )
YOLO! Ha ha!
Anything's possible.
Yah! Whoo-hoo!
( clock ticking )
I hate this dimension.
Ha ha ha! Whoo!
Oh! Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, my hearts.
Not a word.
Hee hee hee!
I think he went in there.
Wow.
It's the history
of the whole universe.
Ooh! Battle of Lexington.
Nailed it.
( gasps ) It--
It's me!
Oh, I remember that!
( chuckling )
Watching me is fun.
Oh!
Hi, me!
This place must keep track
of everything we've done
in our lives.
Wow. I've been nodding
for a long time.
FATHER TIME: Hey, guys!
Isn't this place incredible?
It's like we're living
in the future.
Father Time!
Emerald Snake Strike!
Great.
I think we got him.
Yuck. Okay, buddy,
let's get you
back to your wheel.
( gasps )
( clock ticking )
Ahh, all right.
I guess I'll get back
to doing that.
Oh, well,
it's only for all eternity.
( sighs )
We can't just make him.
Maybe there's some other way
to turn that giant wheel.
( chittering )
Are you thinkin'
what I'm thinkin'?
Actually, I was thinking we'd--
Never mind, it works.
Now you can go
anywhere you want,
and  keep the wheel moving!
Aww, thanks, guys.
I owe ya.
Please, help yourself
to any of my mud.
Even the nice stuff.
We're good.
Oh, and maybe
don't freeze time again.
It's kind of fragile.
You don't want to break it.
Know what I mean?
Well, so long. Ha ha!
Time hamsters away!
Yoo-hoo!
Wait, the wheel's moving.
TOGETHER:
We've got to get back!
( clock ticking )
( puppies yipping )
( singing )
Whoa!
Aaaah!
Hey, Jackie.
Hey, Marco.
Well, see ya.
You did it!
You finally talked to her!
What happened
to waiting for the perfect time?
Well, all of a sudden,
I thought,
if you have the time,
why waste it?
Looks like I'm finally
( slow-mo )
getting somewhere...
Ha ha! You guys really get me!
( yawning )
STAR: Morning, Marco!
Hey.
Aaaah! Whoaah!
( Marco screaming )
( laughing ) Whooo!
Oh, that was awesome!
I know, right?
Stairs are so boring.
I hope my parents don't flip
when they see this.
MAN: I'm flipping!
Dad!
Relax, son.
This is like the perfect getaway
without actually getting away.
( laughing ) Oh, boy!
( dolphin chattering )
( laughing )
I love living here!
If my parents found out
I've been using magic
for stuff like this...
How about that?
This was cool,
but next time,
maybe a little heads-up?
Wet socks are a form of torture
in some countries.
( doorbell ringing )
I'll get it!
( blows horn )
Oh, hey, Dad.
Dad?!
Hello--
Oh, no!
I need to hide everything.
( foghorn blaring )
What a pleasant surprise.
( fake laugh )
What brings you here
unexpectedly?
Well,
I was in the neighborhood and--
Agh.
Who am I kidding?
You mother has banished me
from the castle.
What did you do?
Nothing!
I just left a garment or two
laying around.
I thought perhaps,
I could stay here for a day
while this blows over.
Of course you can stay here.
You are  familia.
You can watch the kids while me
and the wifey actually get away.
Hasta mañana.
Ah, good show!
Huh? Oh, hello--
Aaah!
( yipping )
Star, if you mother was here
and knew you were using
your wand inappropriately,
she would send you
straight to St. Olga's.
But I'm not your mother!
I rather enjoy destructive
magical puppies.
This visit is actually
gonna be fun then!
TOGETHER: Father-Daughter Day!
Tour time!
Hey, guys, hold up.
I'm gonna go change my socks.
Ugh, it's like
I'm walking in pudding.
Check out  my  room.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
( creatures giggling )
Get him!
Gut him like a fish!
I got 20 bucks on Teddy!
ALL: Hi, Star!
I'm Kevin.
I'm new.
Magnificent!
If you like this,
let me show you
the most magical room
in the whole house.
The bathroom!
( gasping, grunting )
What a glorious throne!
Why does it have a hole?
Um, humans put things in there
and flush 'em down.
Flush?
What's a flush?
( water flushing )
My word,
where does the water go?
Nobody knows.
It's one of Earth's
greatest mysteries.
Does this go in it?
All the time.
( flushing )
( gasps )
( huffing, puffing )
This?
I don't see why not.
(flushing )
This?
Go for it.
DAD: This?
STAR: Go ahead!
What are they doing in there?
( laughing )
This?
Do it.
( flushing )
( growling )
Hey, Marco.
DAD: Love the bathroom!
Thanks. What's next
on the itinerary for the d--
Ohh-ohh-ohhhh!
Marco taught me
how to play this.
You are absolutely
gonna love it.
The goal is to knock
this tiny moon into that hole.
Ha ha!
What fun!
You're holding your club
upside-down.
This is a club?
There's one thing
we got better on Mewni.
Tally-ho!
Ha ha! How's that for
getting it into the hole?
What's that?
♪ ( music box ) ♪
That's the Candy Castle.
The next hole.
Lord Salivary
of the Weebler elf clan.
You sly dog!
( roars )
What?
Ha ha!
Mommy,
why is Santa doing that?
Dad!
I'll teach you to give my wife
the googly eye!
Dad, stop it!
( people screaming )
DAD: Ha ha!
The ball's in your court,
Salivary!
( moaning )
( sniffing )
( screaming )
Gross, gross,
gross, gross, gross!
Ew. What was that?
( commotion )
Aaaah!
Aaaaah!
( grunting, laughter )
Dad, what are you doing?
Ha ha ha! Hello, darling!
It's the middle of the night.
Ah, the perfect time
for a tussle.
Isn't that right, clowney?
The name is Kevin,
old man!
Arrr!
Give it up, clown!
Bring the pain!
I can do this all night.
DAD: Ha ha ha!
CLOWN: Chicky-wink.
Good morning, Star.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
It was ridiculously loud
last night.
It wasn't me, Oscar.
It was my dad.
He's insane!
He just thinks
he can come down to Earth
and do whatever he wants.
He is so inconsiderate.
Huh.
I can weirdly relate.
What do you mean?
Doesn't that sound  familiar?
Yeah.
He does this to my mom.
Never mind.
Well, I'm just glad
he's leaving today.
I don't know how much
more of this I can take.
Hello, Star.
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm hanging lights
for the party.
What party?
Oh, jeez!
I forgot to tell you.
I'm having
such a great time here,
I've decided to stay.
Isn't that great?
Greeeeeat.
Oh, and in celebration
of moving here,
I've invited some friends
to check out my new digs.
( doorbell ringing )
They're here.
( party chatter )
Chew, chew, chew,
chew, chew!
( giggling )
Don't wake him up, man.
We'll see if Salivary
recovers from this one.
( laughing )
Dad, I really need
to talk to you right now.
HELIOS: Hey, guys!
Well, here I am! Yeah!
Now the party can start.
Ha ha! Ooh, tight squeeze.
My bad.
Oh, no.
Who invited Helios?
That guy is the worst.
Gross!
Now he got his ear pierced?
There he goes,
eating all the appetizers.
He ruins every party
and is completely
oblivious about it.
Funny.
I can weirdly relate.
Look, people are already
going into orbit around him.
No, no, no! Please, somebody!
His gravitational pull--
So why don't you
just kick him out?
Along with  everyone  else?
No way.
I'm not talking to that tool.
Ugh!
Uh, hey, guys.
Are those water balloo--
Whoa!
Punch. Punch. Punch.
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoah!
Your feet are so soft.
Aaaah! No!
Whoo! Everybody, dancing really
sure works up my appe--
Oho, dessert!
Excuse me, I think
you've overstayed your welcome
and you gotta go.
Well,
you want to know something?
I may be filled with hydrogen,
but you're filled
with annoy-ogen.
You just got
burned by the sun!
( laughing )
Whoa!
MARCO:
I don't ask for much.
Just a pair of dry socks,
that's all.
It's like I'm mushing bananas
between my toes.
Marco, I am so sorry
that every time
I tried to have some fun,
I ended up soaking your socks.
Look, I love all the fun things
you want to do,
just a little heads-up
would be nice.
There's really nothing worse
than wet socks.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
Nothing worse than wet socks.
( laughing )
I'm still hungry,
but there's no more food.
I guess I'll just have to eat
the whole planet!
( gasp )
It's time to purge this party.
( groaning )
Hey,  two  pairs
of wet socks!
I'm outta here.
Because
I'm ridiculously apathetic
to the suffering of others,
I'm leaving too.
Gentlemen, gentlemen!
Wow.
I really made
a mess of things.
There's no way
I'm poopin' out on  this  party.
Ahchoo!
Um, sweetheart,
I perhaps
got a little carried away.
And I may have been
a little inconsiderate.
I guess that's why your mother
threw me out in the first place.
I'm sorry, you guys.
And you'll patch
things up with Mom?
Definitely.
Hugs!
What are you gonna do
with Helios?
Ooh, after party!
Where we gonna go?
I have no idea, but I'll
give you a ride! Ha ha!
Tally-ho!
( Helios screaming )
Hole in one! Ha ha ha ha!
I'll send my top serfs here
to make everything
better than new.
Farewell.
Bye, Dad.
Bye.
Whew. From now on, I'll always
give you a heads-up.
Thanks, but a surprise is good
every once in a while.
Wouldn't you agree?
Ah!
( laughing )
♪ I think Earth
is a pretty gre-at place ♪
♪ That's saying something ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
through outer space ♪
♪ I think it suits me,
it's just my style ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna stay
a little while ♪
♪ I think that strangers are
just friends you haven't met ♪
♪ I'm blasting monsters
and I never break a sweat ♪
♪ I'm really thinking
I could call this place home ♪