♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit
bip bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
[Lord Hater
laughing maniacally]
I hereby
conquer this planet
in the name of
Lord Hater,
the greatest
in the galaxy!
[evil laughter]
Hey, Hater, got
your team's flag.
Come tag me.
[roars]
Come back here.
Please, sir, no.
Just ignore him.
You know Wander's the reason
you're no longer the greatest
in the galaxy.
I'm sorry, sir,
but it's true.
You wasted so much time
chasing him around the universe
that you've lost
any standing you had
as a real villain.
And now there's bad guys
everywhere taking over
all the territory
you lost.
You're more like
29th-greatest in
the galaxy,
which is why we need
to get back in the game
and conquer as many
planets as possible.
Hater!
Peepers, that's totally
what I'm trying to do
but like Wander
totally took our flag.
Sir, the flag is
really just symbolic.
No. Get him!
( snoring )
WANDER: Yeeee-haaa!
That's my cue.
Ladies.
Nothing...
ever... changes.
Who is this guy?
Definitely new
to the neighborhood.
I think we should
go say hi.
Wander, buddy,
these are bad neighbors,
and I think
it's time to move.
Uh, sorry, Syl,
but what do I always say?
An enemy is just
a friend you haven't made yet.
Sometimes you have to look
beyond the demonic exterior
of someone's horrifying
battle cruiser,
find the person inside,
and offer them
your friendship.
No matter how terrified
you may be!
Besides, I have
a secret weapon.
Fruit basket!
Going up.
First floor,
scary lava ship.
Top floor,
friendship.
Whoo!
I got your back, buddy,
with two weapons of my own.
- Right, ladies?
- [shivering]
What just happened?
Gee, sir, maybe exactly
what I said was happening!
While you were busy
chasing Wander around,
you got planet-jacked.
What is this,
amateur hour?
He can't just swoop in
and steal a planet
after I already
planted a flag.
The flag is a symbol!
Sir, this guy's impressive.
Maybe too impressive.
I suggest we go and deal
with this foe
when we're better prepared.
Please. An enemy's just
an enemy I haven't defeated yet.
I'll show this chump
what happens
when you mess with
the greatest in the galaxy.
Be back in five.
WANDER: Hello.
Anybody here?
Welcome to
our galaxy.
Nobody home.
Let's go.
No way. Ship this big,
there's gotta be
someone onboard.
If you don't like fruit,
there's also a collection
of small cheeses.
Finally.
The welcome party.
SYLVIA: Not the vibe
I'm getting here.
Hello. Hey there.
Folks call me Wander,
and this is Sylvia.
Welcome to the galaxy.
We hope you'll accept
our humble gift--
( roaring )
- Owww!
- Sylvia, you okay?
Watchdogs are usually
so soft and mushy.
Cuffs? Please.
Okay, we're eating in.
Perhaps you did not
notice our gift.
From your new friends,
to whoever you are.
See, Syl? An enemy is just
a friend--
Hey, careful, careful.
There's a honeydew
here, man.
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ All right ♪
HATER: This guy's
not so cool.
He's the real deal, sir.
This is one
serious arsenal.
Level five
mega lasers?
( scoffs )
Whatever.
Nova combusters?
I didn't even think
those existed.
Big deal. I could have that;
I just don't want to.
And that. I don't know
what that is, but--
( shrieking )
It's super cool,
that's what it is.
I can't wait to put
this guy in his place.
First he steals
my stolen planet,
then he has the nerve
to have stuff that I want.
Why don't we have
awesome stuff like this?
This is your fault,
isn't it?
We could've had
all this,
but someone needed
a hot tub,
and an arcade,
and an entire research
team to develop
new barbecue sauces
for the food court.
A food court,
by the way,
we built instead of
an atom smasher,
which this guy
also has!
Well, I can have
all that and more!
For I am Lord Hater,
the greatest in the...
Twenty-ninth greatest.
Not so cool now, are you?
Ha ha ha.
Ah, so cool.
Hey, that was
thoughtfully arranged.
Do you have any idea
how hard it is
to balance bananas?
Wander, I know
you don't wanna hear this,
but these guys
are trouble.
Maybe you're right.
No, they're not friendly.
They're... what?
Wait, what?
I don't want to jump
to conclusions,
but I'm starting to feel
not very welcomed here.
SYLVIA: Tell me about it.
Maybe this enemy
is just an enemy.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I know you always want
to see the best in people,
but sometimes,
there's nothing there to see.
Either way,
these walls ain't budging.
We're not going
anywhere.
You'd almost think
they wanted us to stay.
Maybe this is how
they show hospitality
where they're from.
Maybe this is all
some kooky mix-up
that we'll all laugh about later
over ripe cantaloupe.
Maybe one of us has a hard time
dealing with rejection.
Welcome party
back on track!
Fruit basket!
Yeeee-haaaa!
( shrieking )
The basket!
- You!
- Me.
- Them!
Are you here to be
our new neighbor, too?
I don't see
a gift.
Haven't forgotten
about my flag.
No time.
Must go faster.
Much faster.
Oh, cuffs are seriously
slowing me down.
Who is this guy?
No.
I'm really sorry, Syl,
but I just gotta try.
I know this seems
bananas,
and I must be plum
out of my melon,
but I don't pear.
The way I fig-ure,
the rottenest apple
still has a sweet spot
at its core.
Kumquat!!
Wander, he's gonna
destroy you.
Sorry, I gotta try.
Hello to you.
Folks call me Wander,
and this is Sylvia.
Welcome to the galaxy.
We hope you will accept
our humble gift
of friendship.
Perhaps I was
a bit too formal.
( clear throat,
sighs )
Hello. Hi. Howdy.
Hi. How's it goin'?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Hello!
Nope. Less formal,
less formal.
What's up?
Salutations!
Hello! Howdy.
It's me. Hello.
Bee-boop, we come
in peace.
Hey, you narfin' frood,
I love the place.
Fruit basket!
This is for you,
and that, and that, and that.
I'm so sorry.
No!
Sylvia, I don't think
our friend
is very friendly.
You think?!
I think this calls
for the big guns.
Wander, please.
No, not that.
♪ Hello, it's nice
to meet ya ♪
♪ We brought something
to feed ya ♪
♪ Some berries
and bananas... ♪
Wander!
♪ And I hope we can
be friends ♪
BOTH: Whew!
Sir, I really must
insist we go,
and deal with this foe
when we're better prepared.
Maybe you're right.
What?! Wait, what?
I mean, good. Yes.
Now we just have to
break out of here
quietly and carefully.
Oh, I'll settle for
loudly and quickly.
Come on, sir.
Let's get outta here
so you can focus on
being the greatest in
the galaxy again.
Twenty-ninth greatest.
What?
If I'm gonna be the greatest
in the galaxy again,
I'm gonna start with
whoever this loser is.
Hey, robo-dork.
Let's rumba.
Sir, what are you doing?
I can't run.
I want to be number one.
Wander?
Wander!
Wander!!
( choking )
Oh, Wander, thank Grab.
Let him go.
You molten menace.
He was only trying
to be your friend.
Folks call me Sylvia.
And I'm not so nice.
Ladies.
Welcome to the galaxy!
No!
Finally.
My brilliant getting
captured plan
has led us right to
this two-bit terror.
Time to take
this sucker down.
Invaders apprehended,
Lord Dominator.
Lord Dominator?
That totally rhymes
with "Hater."
What?! He totally
looks like...
Hey, friend.
Aaargh, he's...
( enraged sputtering )
destroy my enemy...
Hate... jerk!
What I wanted to do.
Aaaarggh!
So cool, must destroy!!
Wander's my enemy.
Enemy? Come on, Hater.
You know an enemy is just
a friend you haven't made yet.
What? Ew! Shut up!
Wander! Are you
okay, buddy?
Impressive, sir.
Sorry for
doubting you.
After defeating
this guy,
you must certainly are
the greatest in the galaxy.
Accept no imitations!
Okay, time out.
Fine. You can be
the greatest in the galaxy.
Mercy, please.
Hey, watch the lava
round the guava.
Oh, yes,
you'll most definitely
conquer the entire
galaxy with those.
But you can't run
if you wanna be number one.
Commander Peepers!
Ha ha! Yes!
Let this be a reminder
that if you march into
my  galaxy,
you're gonna have to deal
with me!
Wander!
I have had enough.
I will have you know
I gave you a gift.
I complimented
your ship.
I even played
you a song.
All in the name
of friendship.
And you can't even
be neighborly
and make some small talk
like,
"Thanks for the fruit
basket, Wander.
Isn't that
an interesting name?
And I'd be, like,
"Well, I guess."
Funny story. That's
not really my...
But that's not important.
What is important
is I told you that
an enemy is just a friend
you haven't made yet.
But after your rude
and inconsiderate
behavior today,
I'm not sure I want
to be your friend.
And I must admit...
I'm coming, buddy.
...though it hurts
to say it,
I have to tell you...
that I don't think
that you deserve...
a fruit basket.
This is for
my real friends.
Tangelo?
( all screaming )
Whew!
( screaming )
Please,
he's a dope.
No, really,
he's not an idiot.
He totally knows
what he's doing.
( explosion )
- Who...
- Was that...
...guy?!
( deep demonic voice )
That... was...
( girlish voice)
...amazing!
They were all, like,
what, who is this guy?
Then I was, like,
serious,
then I was all...
( roars),
and then the lava was...
and they were all,
Ah, no way!
( laughs )
What a bunch of dorks.
This is going to be...
( demonic voice )
...fun.
( evil laughter )
So you think this guy
is, what,
Hater's brother?
Oh, maybe he's
Lord Hater's dad
come to show him
who's boss.
Wait, Lord who?
Uh, Lord Hater,
that skeleton guy
we work for.
I've been calling him
the wrong name
for six months.
Why didn't anyone
tell me?
What did you think
he was called?
I've been calling him
Lord Vad...
( explosion )