♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yoer wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
( engine sputtering )
( backfires,
engine dies )
SYLVIA (grunting):
Don't sweat it.
I love working
on these old beauts.
They may have a lot
of light years on 'em,
but they were built to last.
Sylvia will have you
up and runnin' in no time,
Miss Starbella.
Oh, please,
call me Stella.
But again, I really don't
need any help.
Oh, it's no trouble at all.
We saw you floatin' out here
all by your lonesome
and figured
it never hurts to help.
Suit yourself,
but there's no need.
That engine's been on the fritz
since I defeated
Mandrake the Malfeasant
in the Battle of Planet X,
thus ending
his tyrannical reign.
My pilot and man-at-arms Mittens
handles all the repairs himself.
But he's being
a bit aloof today.
Have you met Mittens?
Say hello, Mittens.
( Mittens yowling )
Aha! A loose screw.
Maybe that's it.
- ( clatter )
- Nope.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Self-destruct
system initiated.
Please enter your password
to deactivate
or prepare to implode
in 30 seconds.
Um, Miss Stella,
what's your password?
Is it in with
the instructions?
Or maybe you can call
the Customer Service.
Not sure we have
that kind of time.
Maybe you have it
written down?
Well, I don't know.
Is it "Mittens"?
Have you met Mittens?
Get off!
M-I-T-T-E-N-S.
Enter.
- ( buzzer )
- It's not "Mittens"!
Miss Starbella,
we really need your--
...8, 7, 6,
5, 4,
-  3, 2, 1...
- P-A-S-S-W-O-R-D.
( self-destruct powers down )
Oh,  that  password.
Mittens usually keeps track
of all those things.
Don't you, Mittens?
Sylvia,
I'm really worried that--
SYLVIA: It's not just
Miss Stella's engine
that needs a jump-start?
Yeah. And though
she says she doesn't,
I really think that--
( gasps )
She really  does
need our help?
Yeah. So I think--
We should stick around
and make sure that
she really is okay?
Yeah. 'Cause--
There's no telling
what being all alone in
deep space can do you you?
I knitted you both
sweaters.
The evenings out here
get awfully drafty.
Mayday! Mayday!
If anyone is out there,
Sherblorg 7 is under attack.
Please! Anyone!
We need help!
Wander, Sherblorg 7
needs our help right away!
I know, but we can't
just leave Stella here
alone and helpless.
We gotta make sure
she's okay.
Now: Who wants to play rummy?
All right, but in order
to fix the ship,
I need you to
ask Miss Starbella
if she has a supersonic
socket wrench. Hurry!
Oh, I  know  I had
a supersonic socket wrench
here somewhere.
Ooh, careful.
Saved it from when
I overthrew an organized
time syndicate.
Maybe it's in--
Ohh!
"Send Donnie Burns' grandson
a graduation card."
I did that.
Sherblorg 7,
come in, Sherblorg 7.
Oh, thank Grop.
Yes! Um, signal received,
we're coming to rescue you!
Oh, thank Grop!
We'll be there right away!
Oh, thank Grop!!!
STELLA: Maybe it's in
my pocketbook.
Please hold!
Ohh, Grop.
No. That's my change purse.
That's a  satchel.
Wait. What's that up there?
My cookie jar!
Been looking
all over for that.
You want some cookies?
I'll make cookies.
No--!
SHERBLORG KING:
Where are you?!
What in Grop's name
could be taking so long?
Miss Stella,
can we--
Silence.
Respect the baking process.
( Sherblorg king crying )
( oven timer rings )
SYLVIA: Oh, look.
Supersonic...socket wrench.
( engine revs )
SYLVIA: Fixed it!
Sherblorg 7, Sherblorg 7,
we are on our way!
Don't bother.
We've been captured.
You're too late.
Hope you got your wrench.
STELLA: Shame. Someone should
try and help those nice folks.
BOTH: Stella?!
That's Starbella!
And Sherblorg 7
needs  my  help!
( engine powers up )
( both scream )
Sylvia, I think--
She's completely
lost her marbles?
No. There they are!
Sherblorg 7, this is Vengastar.
We're entering your system,
so would you please be a dear
and prepare for rescue?
Thank you.
Oh! Starbella!
KING: Oh, thank Grop!
MAN: So, Starbella...
( wheezing )
...we meet again.
Mandrake
the Malfeasant!
I should have known.
( engine sputtering )
What happened?
And where's Stella?
We gotta find her before
she doesn't something really--
Kooky!
( Mittens yowls )
Prepare to meet your...
(wheezing)...doom.
Oh, poop.
I'm in no hurry
to do that.
( both roar )
Miss Stella!
Are you okay?
It's Starbella.
And I already told ya,
sweetie, I don't need your--
Help!
( evil laughter )
( wheezing )
( Mandrake coughing,
wheezing )
That's right.
I, Mandrake the Malfeasant,
am back to show these...these...
Lord Hatreds
and emperors and rock stars
with their skulls and fish faces
what a real--(coughs)--villain
is all about!
With Sherblorg 7
in my control,
I'm more vital--(wheezing)...
Now prepare--(coughs)--to die!
( coughing fit )
Starbella,
I may have conquered
many planets in my day,
but I never conquered
your heart.
( coughing )
Good Grop, Mandrake,
can't we just
have a good time?
You always gotta
complicate things
by throwing a  wrench
into the works!
Robots! Seize her!
( crashes )
MANDRAKE:
Gotcha, Starbella!
Now you're mine!
Bwah-hah-hah--(coughing)...
So long, old friend.
( loud crash )
( alarm blaring )
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Attention, Mandrake.
Self-destruct system activated.
Enter your password
to deactivate
or prepare to implode
in 30 seconds.
29, 28, 27...
Password. Password.
(gasps) Wow. Guess you really
didn't  need our help.
But we sure needed  yours.
( gasps )
"Evil one"? "QWERTY"?
"Canasta Champ"?
( alarm continues )
Ohh.
Uh...
"Starbella's Fella"?
♪ Starbella, interstellar ♪
♪ You're the light
in any feller's eyes ♪
♪ You hypnotize me... ♪
STELLA: And then
the missiles exploded,
and made for
quite the ballyhoo!
BOTH: Whoa!
Miss Starbella,
you are a delight.
And like this ship,
you may have a lot
of light years on you,
but you were
built to last.
Well, enough of my babbling.
You all probably
want to get going.
No! Don't leave me!
BOTH: No!
I, on the other hand,
really should be
saying my farewells.
I have a galaxy to conquer,
and--
( all laughing )
♪ Starbella, interstellar ♪
♪ You make me feel so young ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪
PEEPERS: Lord Dominator!
Boo! I hate that guy!
Well, you should, sir.
He's climbed to
the top of the Galactic
Villain Leaderboard
in record time!
I assume you mean
close  to the top.
After yours truly,
Lord Hater, #1 Superstar.
Sir, we're not even
in the Top Ten.
What?!
We're way down here,
between Something the So-and-So
and an empty blank space.
Oh, I see.
And how many planets
does Wander have?
None! Zero!
He doesn't conquer planets!
I don't even think
he has a house!
Sir, if you want to make it back
onto the Top Ten,
you have to stop viewing Wander
as a threat
and focus on actual villains
that are actual threats.
Like Dominator. Grrr!
Let's start with
General McGuffin.
Now, our spies have located
a weak spot in the force field
around McGuffin's
heavily fortified
military stronghold.
We sneak in, deactivate
the force field, take his base,
and steal his territory.
That'll pad our planetary
numbers quite nicely.
Point me at him!
I'll deep-fry
the feathers off him!
Love that enthusiasm,
but this will be a delicate
covert operation
with lots of twists and turns.
I need your undivided attention.
Do I have your
undivided attention?
Absolutely.
Nothing will distract me
from taking out these  losers
and re-becoming
the greatest in the galaxy!
( thunder crashes )
Tag! You're It!
Oh, no.
Commander Peepers.
I believe you were going to
brief us on your invasion plan.
You--You're not gonna flip out
and chase after him?
Please. Do you think
I'm going to let some silly game
ruin my chances
at galactic superiority?
Uh, you  do  seem
to do that a lot, so--
Of course not, sir.
Glad to see you've got
your eyes on the prize!
Now, General McGuffin's base
has 32 separate sentry turrets
surveying 45 degree angles
in varying intervals.
After fording
the perimeter moat,
which is crawling
with water wingmen,
we'll hit the infinity minefield
full of self-preparing mines.
I'm not gonna lie--
not all of you are gonna
make it back through that one.
I'm lookin' at you, Pap.
The secondary moat is tricky.
It's rigged with alarm sensors
that can tag our presence
and it alternates its pattern.
If you're tagged,
it is imperative
that you tag its it-it
while  it  tags the it-it tag.
It-it-tag-tag-it-tag-
it-it-tag-tag-it.
You all got that?
Great. 'Cause this is where
it gets tricky.
Because everything
we've just encountered
is actually a mass
hallucination induced by
General McGuffin's
psychic battalion.
We have to confront
our innermost fears
in order to defeat them,
awake from the dream state,
and then start the whole thing
over again from Step One.
The conference table is base!
What was that?
Nothing!
Totally paying attention.
Good. Now, once we've escaped
to that alternate timeline...
( Peepers continues )
Psst. Barry.
Take your hand
off the table.
Oh, no! There's a big,
scary monster under the  table!
And he's, like,
totally gonna eat you
unless you run away
from the  table!
Run, Barry, run!
Barry! As your Supreme Leader,
I'm warning you to take
your hand off the table!
Grrr!
( electrical crackling )
No tag backs!
( roars )
Which leads us to Step 47A,
subsection B, 4th appendix.
Now that we've cleared
the outer-inner
inner-outer perimeter,
we have to circumvent
the inner-inner-inner-outer...
LORD HATER: Okay,
who can I tag?
Who can I tag?
Who can I... Bingo.
...posted at the turrets
each grew up in different
time zones,
so their Circadian
sleep rhythms
will be all out of sync.
Question, sir?
Bathroom break!
I need a bathroom break.
( all roaring )
LORD HATE: Get back here!
Slow down!
Okay, new plan.
If we want to have any chance
of pulling this off,
one of you is gonna
have to let him tag you.
Uh, sir? Why don't  you
let him tag you?
(stammering) No!
Of course, that wouldn't work
because as his second in command
I can't be It because--
Ohh, fine!
You're all a bunch of babies!
( roaring, screaming )
Everybody get back here!
Sir, in the interest
of the invasion,
I have decided
to let you tag  me.
Thanks, CPeeps.
Tag, you're--
Oh! Sorry, sir,
I must have tripped.
Go ahead.
Peepers...
I don't know
what's come over me.
I promise, sir, this time
I will remain completely still.
Aaaah!
Sir, I don't wanna be It!
Peepers, get back here!
( Lord Hater roars,
Peepers screams )
Food court is a safe zone!
( mellow music plays )
( slurps )
Safe zone expired!
WANDER:
The floor is hot lava!
( swords clang )
( chuckles )
Tag.
PEEPERS: Freeze tag.
( muffled shouting )
Oh, no! You accidentally
froze Lord Hater
in Coldbrrnite!
Yes, accidentally.
And that's exactly
what we'll tell  him
when we unfreeze him
after we break into
General McGuffin's fortress.
Finally!
I have your undivided attention.
So...let's talk about
your feelings.
( muffled screams )
( birds shriek )
( beeping )
Have you ever considered
a healthier outlet
for your aggression?
You could be a pastry chef!
Eww. No, I've tasted
your cooking.
Ooh! Or a professional luchador!
El Esqueleto Electrico!
( muffled shouting )
I don't think
I'm getting through to you.
Lets try music therapy!
♪ Oh, wander ♪
♪ Over yonder... ♪
( beeping )
♪ When darkness
comes a-creepin' ♪
♪ And you're feelin' down ♪
♪ Just wander over yonder ♪
♪ And turn your life around ♪
I think I'm cracking through
your cold exterior!
( roars )
Whoop. Game on!
Taaaaaaag!
The force field generator.
Disable that, and our army
can descend on the fortress
before General McGuffin
even knows we're here.
( alarm wails )
What the-- How?!
Taaaaaaaag!
Oh, no.
Tag! Tag! Taaaag!
( weapons power up )
What in the Sam Hill
is goin' on in here?
Lord Hater's It!
Lord Hater's It?
Taaaaaag!
Wingmen! Scatter! Scatter!
Taaaaaaag!
Oh, yes.
This,  I can use.
Taaaaag!
( screams )
( bell rings )
Taaaaag!
Taaaaaag!
Taaaaaaag!
PEEPERS: We did it, sir!
We're back on the Top Ten!
( band plays, crowd cheering )
What? We did?
Everyone is terrified
of being It!
A true villain turns
a weakness into a strength!
We're going
all the way to the top!
We are?
We are. Yeah!
High-five!
Nooooooo!!!
( explosion )
I'm It?
I'm It!
I have the power!
( crazy laughter )
(sighs) Okay, here's
the elaborate, multi-part plan
to defeat
our  new  arch-nemesis,
Ted from Accounting.
Got your nose!
Give it back!
Sir, you don't  have
a nose.
Yeah, because Wander
stole it!
Get back here!
( crying )
There, there.
It's not gonna be okay.
Now, General McGuffin's base
has 32 separate sentry turrets
surveying 45 degree angles
in varying intervals.
After fording
the perimeter moat,
which is crawling
with water wingmen,
we'll hit the infinity minefield
full of self-preparing mines.
I'm not gonna lie--
not all of you are gonna
make it back through that one.
I'm lookin' at you, Pap.
This is where it gets tricky,
because everything
we've just encountered
is actually a mass
hallucination induced by
General McGuffin's
psychic battalion.
We have to confront
our innermost fears
in order to defeat them,
awake from the dream state,
and then start the whole thing
over again from Step One.