♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laugh )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( humming )
( rumbling )
( high-pitched squeal )
OKAY.
( humming backwards )
HUNGRY, LITTLE FELLER?
( rumble )
( sighs )
GOTTA BE SOMETHING.
( gasps )
THERE!
SYLVIA, SIX FINGERS!
LITTLE SHOWY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
NOTHING WRONG
WITH LOOKING GOOD
WHILE DOING GOOD.
HEY!
YOU STOLE MY CARROT!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
OH, THAT WAS YOURS?
YEAH, I PUT IT ON A STICK HERE
TO MAKE MY HUFFLERUMPLES GO.
NOW, THEY WON'T GO.
OOPS.
HUH, WELL, THAT'S WEIRD.
'CAUSE USUALLY WHEN YOU START
DOWN THE RIGHT PATH,
YOU END UP IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
EH, NOT ALWAYS I GUESS.
NOPE. I REFUSE
TO ACCEPT THAT.
THIS IS JUST A MINOR SETBACK,
MY SNAZZILY DRESSED FRIEND.
WE WILL SIMPLY MOSEY ON
OVER TO THE LOCAL STORE
AND BUY YOU A NEW CARROT!
( Hufflerumples exclaim )
YOU CAN BUY CARROTS IN A STORE?
WHAT ARE WE LUGGING
AROUND THIS GUY FOR?
( indistinct clamoring )
OH, GREAT! HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET TO MY WEDDING NOW?
WEDDING?
OH...
NO!
I WILL NOT LET OUR DO-GOODING
UNDO YOU, DUDE.
WE'LL NOT ONLY GET YOU
TO YOUR WEDDING ON TIME,
BUT I WILL PROVIDE
THE APPROPRIATE
RACING THE CLOCK ACTION MUSIC!
( playing quick-paced melody )
WHOA! THAT WAS FAST!
I WOULD HAVE MISSED
THE WEDDING ENTIRELY,
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU TWO.
THANKS!
JUST DOING THE GOOD
THAT DO-GOODERS DO.
SEE THAT, SYLVIA?
RIGHT PATH, RIGHT PLACE.
STOP THE WEDDING!
( everyone gasping )
I LOVE YOU, MARSHA!
I LOVE YOU, TOO,
FLEEBLEBORT.
WEDDING CANCELED!
( crowd murmuring )
UNBELIEVABLE.
THAT'S TWO GOOD DEEDS
GONE BAD.
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUDDY,
BUT WE'RE HAVING AN OFF DAY.
NO!
GOOD NEVER HAS AN OFF DAY!
WE CAN STILL RIGHT THIS WRONG.
( inhales )
SIR, I AM SO SORRY
WE CAUSED YOUR
TRUE LOVE TO LEAVE.
OH, SHE WASN'T MY TRUE LOVE.
REALLY?
NO, I WAS JUST MARRYING HER
TO STOP THE FEUD
BETWEEN OUR FAMILIES.
WHICH I GUESS NOW...
IS BACK ON!
( indistinct shouting )
UNBELIEVABLE.
( both scream )
OKAY, I ADMIT, TODAY IS A TEENSY
BIT OF A CHALLENGE,
BUT I BELIEVE WE
CAN END UP RIGHT!
RIGHT?
LET ME TRY SOMETHING.
( all shouting )
HEAR YE, HEAR YE,
ORDER IN THE COURT,
AS JUDGE, JURY,
AND PROSECUTIONOR,
I DEMAND JUSTICE.
PLAINTIFF, HOW DO YOU PLEA?
NOT GUILTY, YOUR HONOR.
SOLICITOR GENERAL?
ALSO, NOT GUILTY.
OVERRULED!
OBJECTION!
I SAID IT FIRST.
I SAID IT SECOND.
( indistinct arguing )
PROCEDURAL...
OVERRULED!
OBJECTION!
CONTEMPT OF COURT!
IN ABSENTIA...
I'M WARNING YOU.
I'M WARNING YOU!
OBJECTION!
OVERRULED!
PLEASE! WE'LL STOP FIGHTIN',
IF YOU STOP FIGHTIN'!
YES, ANYTHING, PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I HEREBY DECLARE THIS FEUD OVER!
A PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS
WITH YOU, FINE SIR.
DITTO.
OH, THAT MADE
NO SENSE WHATSOEVER,
BUT YOU DID IT, BUDDY!
GOOD DEED.
DONE AND DONE!
( all cheering )
UH, DON'T TELL ME.
AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
( cheering )
HMM?
( screaming )
BLEH!
( growling )
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
( all squeal, sigh )
( squeal, sigh )
( snarling )
( all screaming )
( sighs )
( out of breath )
FOLKS...
WE ARE SO SORRY...
FOR DESTROYING YOUR...
CITY.
( squeals )
SORRY? THIS PLACE IS WAY BETTER
THAN WHERE WE USED TO LIVE.
( all exclaiming )
( snorting, squealing )
YEAH, BUDDY! BAM!
YOU DID IT.
WE ENDED UP
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
EVEN THAT GRACKNORE'S HAPPIER
THAN HE WAS ALL FROZEN.
( screaming purr )
I DON'T KNOW, SYL.
I STILL HAVE A SNEAKY FEELING
DEEP DOWN IN MY BELLY
THAT SOMETHING BAD'S
STILL GONNA HAPPEN.
ALL I SEE IS HOG HEAVEN!
WAIT! THE SKIES HAVE SHIFTED!
THE STARS DO NOT SAY YOU WILL BE
A STRONG AND POWERFUL LEADER.
NOW, THE STARS SAY YOU
ARE IMMATURE, AWKWARD,
AND EMOTIONALLY UNSTABLE.
( shouting )
I AM NOT EMOTIONALLY UNSTABLE!
YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS, SUN!
UH... ANYTHING
ABOUT A GIRLFRIEND,
LIKE, MAKING OUT,
OR EVEN JUST HOLDING HANDS
OR...
( roaring )
PEEPERS, OBLITERATE THAT SUN!
SIR, YES, SIR!
RIGHT AWAY, SIR!
SIR, I THINK ANY GIRL
WOULD BE VERY LUCKY TO HAVE--
FIRE!
I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT I AM PRETTY SURE
THAT IS OUR FAULT.
SO WHAT? WE'VE RIGHTED
THESE WRONGS ALL DAY.
SO WHAT'S STOPPING US NOW?
SYLVIA, I'VE BEEN THINKING...
MAYBE, UM...
WE SHOULDN'T STOP IT.
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR
FLIP-PICKIN' LUPSORK?
BUT IF SOMETHING WORSE HAPPENS?
I ALWAYS BELIEVE THAT WHEN YOU
START ON THE RIGHT PATH,
YOU ALWAYS END UP
IN THE RIGHT PLACE,
BUT...
EVERY TIME WE TRY TO DO GOOD
IT JUST TURNS INTO
SOMETHING WORSE,
AND WORSE, AND WORSE.
IF WE STOP THAT MISSILE IT COULD
CAUSE THE WHOLE UNIVERSE TO...
( garbled )
WANDER, WITH THE DAY
WE'VE BEEN HAVING,
THAT IS ENTIRELY POSSIBLE.
BUT I'M ALSO SAYING
THAT IF DOING A GOOD DEED
LEADS TO THE UNIVERSE
GETTING DESTROYED...
PARTNER, THAT'S NOT A UNIVERSE
I WANT TO LIVE IN ANYWAY.
YA YA YA!
SYLVIA, SIX FINGERS!
( holds breath )
SEE, WANDER? START DOWN
THE RIGHT PATH,
YOU END UP IN
THE RIGHT PLACE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU CAN BREATHE NOW.
( exhales )
( cheering )
( groans )
WHAT IS TAKING THAT
STUPID MISSILE SO LONG?
SIR! SIR!
SIR!
( both screaming )
( moans )
A LITTLE HELP.
Wander and Sylvia:
NOPE.
( Peepers crying )
( sighs )
GOOD ONE, SIR.
YOU ARE TOO FUNNY.
THIS IS NO JOKE,
COMMANDER PEEPERS!
WANDER IS A SLY, CUNNING,
AND CRAFTY GENIUS
AND HE'S THE ONLY THREAT
TO MY POWER!
AT LAST, THE POWER CRYSTAL
SHALL BE MI--
HEY, NEAT!
( glass breaking )
Wander: WHOOPS.
BUTTER FINGERS.
AT LAST, THE LOST RING
OF POWER--
NEAT!
( clinking, breaking )
I HAVE THE POWER--
Wander: AH! HOT STUFF!
( screaming )
AND IF YOU DARE
UNDERESTIMATE HIM,
THEN YOU ARE A FOOL!
NOW, I'M GOING TO
MY TORTURE ROOM,
AND I WANT YOU TO BRING ME
WANDER IMMEDIATELY.
OR ELSE...
( screaming )
OW OW OW!
GOT IT, PAL?
PSYCH! WE'RE NOT PALS.
HATER OUT!
SERIOUSLY THIS IS NOT GOING
TO BE EASY. HE'S A TRICKY ONE.
HATER OUT!
( chirping )
( snoring, muttering )
OH, WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
AMAZING.
Peepers: PSST!
( engine idling )
HI.
♪ COMMANDER PEEPERS
OH, THAT WAS SO HARD!
"BUT SERIOUSLY,
THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE EASY."
"HE'S A TRICKY ONE."
( scoffs )
YEAH RIGHT, LORD HATER.
( line ringing )
AH, IF YOU ASK ME,
I SHOULD BE THE ONE IN CHARGE.
♪ WHO IN THE UNIVERSE
IS THE ULTIMATE EVILDOER ♪
♪ HATER
( phone ringing )
HATER'S AWESOME TORTURE ROOM.
OH, HEY,
LORD HATER, SIR.
JUST CALLING
TO LET YOU KNOW...
( singsongy )
I GOT WANDER.
UH-HUH. YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
EASY AS PIE.
YEAH. I'M LOOKING AT HIM RIGHT--
NOW.
WHAT? IMPOSSIBLE!
Hater:  PEEPERS!
( chuckling )
PROBLEM...
NO! THERE'S NO PROBLEM, SIR.
YES, I'LL BRING HIM
TO YOU RIGHT AWAY.
NO PROBLEMO.
( screaming )
OKAY, MINOR SETBACK.
CAUGHT HIM ONCE,
I'LL CATCH HIM AGAIN.
EASY AS PIE, PEEPERS.
EASY AS PIE.
( evil laugh )
♪ COMMANDER PEEPERS
WHOO!
WHOA!
( indistinct yelling )
WHOA...
THIS PLACE IS AMAZING!
WHOA! THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
WHAT'S THIS MACHINE DO?
ISN'T THAT INTERESTING?
NEAT!
HOW COOL IS THAT?
HOWDY, FRIEND. THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR INVITING ME ON YOUR SHIP.
THIS PLACE IS AMAZING!
NOW, I SURE WOULD
LOVE TO STAY AND CHAT,
BUT THERE'S STILL SO MUCH
OF THIS PLACE I HAVEN'T SEEN.
SO, CATCH YOU LATER!
NO. IT IS  I
WHO SHALL CATCH  YOU.
( panting )
NO NO NO!
HE IS NOT ONE STEP AHEAD--
WHOA-HA!
THIS IS AWESOME!
WHOA!
I THINK I'M GONNA THROW UP!
( siren )
HELLO, OFFICER.
LET ME EXPLAIN,
IT WASN'T ME WHO WAS--
( growling )
( gasps )
( various shrieks,
screams, growls )
( gasps )
WELL, THAT'S ONE STAR OFF
MY FIVE-STAR REVIEW.
THESE GUEST ACCOMMODATIONS
ARE LOUSY.
( humming )
HA! GOTCHA!
( all growling )
( indistinct shouting )
( roaring )
WHAT THE?
NOPE. SCRATCH THAT, REVERSE IT.
FIVE-STAR REVIEW,
BEST SHIP EVER!
( squeaks )
BOINK.
PHEW.
EEP!
( barking, screaming, growling )
( panting )
( Wander laughing )
AHA!
WHAT IS GOING ON?
♪ DO YOU KNOW THE BUTTON SONG
THE BUTTON SONG ♪
♪ THE BUTTON SONG
WHEN YOU PLAY THE BUTTON SONG ♪
♪ YOU FIND OUT
WHAT GOES WRONG ♪
STOP!
( gasping )
( phone ringing )
Hater:  PEEPERS! WHY HAVEN'T
YOU BROUGHT ME WANDER?
( strained )
I-I CAN'T.
UNACCEPTABLE. GIVE ME
ONE REASON WHY YOU CAN'T.
I...
PHEW.
( growling )
( screaming )
Hater:  WHAT'S THAT SCREAMING?
YOU BETTER NOT BE
TORTURING HIM WITHOUT ME!
( indistinct chatter,
Wander humming )
( squeaks )
SHUT UP!
THERE'S A FOOD COURT?!
( soft music plays )
I TELL YOU, FELLAS,
YOU'VE GOT YOURSELVES
ONE FANCY-SHMANCY SHIP HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU FOOLS DOING?!
GRAB HIM!
FOOD FIGHT!
( all clamoring )
AAH! HOT SAUCE!
OW! LEMON!
AAH! PEPPER!
( muffled screams )
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
REMEMBER, HE IS NOT SLY,
HE IS NOT CUNNING,
AND HE'S NOT A GENIUS!
( music plays )
AH! LORD HATER'S BEDROOM!
( heavy metal music plays )
( mellow synth music plays )
ENOUGH! YOU ARE COMING WITH ME!
NO, NOT THE SHIP'S REMOTE
SELF-DESTRUCT BUTTON!
I TOLD LORD HATER
THAT WAS A BAD IDEA.
DUH.
♪ COMMANDER PEEPERS
HA! I HAVE YOU NOW,
YOU HYPERACTIVE
WANDERING WEIRDO!
NOW, JUST STAY STILL.
( gasps )
I DID IT!
I CAPTURED HIM! AGAIN!
EASY AS--OW!
GEEZ, FOR A GUY WITH
AN EYEBALL FOR A HEAD,
HOW COULD YOU
NOT SEE THAT COMING?
( alarm sounding )
Automated voice:
BEGINNING SELF-DESTRUCT
SEQUENCE IN 30, 29, 28...
UH-OH.
Wander: SYLVIA!
SYLVIA, I AM SO GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
LISTEN, THIS SHIP
IS AMAZING!
Sylvia: NOT FOR LONG.
Wander: SEE YA, MR. PEEPERS.
THANKS FOR THE TOUR!
OH, NO! NOT THE SELF-DESTRUCT!
WHAT'LL I DO? WHAT'LL I DO?
THE ONLY ONE WHO KNOWS
THE DEACTIVATION CODE IS...
LORD HATER! HEY, BUDDY.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
Automated voice:  15...
I TOTALLY HAD HIM. I DID.
14...
BUT HIS SIDEKICK
SUCKER-PUNCHED ME...
( rumbling )
AND I DIDN'T GET A LOT
OF SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
13...
AND IT'S A MONDAY, SIR!
YOU KNOW HOW MONDAYS ARE.
SIR, PLEASE...
I-I-I...
I WAS WRONG AND YOU
WERE RIGHT, OKAY?!
HE IS A CUNNING, SLY,
AND CRAFTY GENIUS.
PLEASE, SIR.
PLEASE JUST SAY THE PASSWORD.
I DON'T WANNA DIE!
5, 4, 3, 2...
LORD HATER...
NUMBER ONE...
SUPERSTAR.
SELF-DESTRUCT DEACTIVATED.
HAVE A NICE DAY.
OH, MAN IT FEELS GREAT
TO GET THAT OFF MY CHEST.
I FEEL A LOT BETTER,
DON'T YOU, SIR?
NOT YET!
( Peepers screaming )
♪
♪ I'M LORD HATER
GOT A SKELETON FACE ♪
♪ BUT MY SHIP SURE
IS AN AWESOME PLACE ♪
♪ AAH
LASERS ♪
♪ SPACE DRAGONS
♪ EXPLOSIONS
♪ FOOD COURT
♪ RAWR
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I'M MAD!
YOU ARE COMING WITH ME!
( feedback )