♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER OVER OVER
YONDER YONDER WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER,
OVER YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
WANDER YONDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER WANDER
OVER, OVER ♪
♪ YONDER YONDER
WANDER WANDER ♪
♪ YIP BI DI DIT BIP
BI-EE-I-DI-DIT ♪
THANK GROP, THEY HAVE
AN ORBBLE PUMP.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
HAVE TO HOOF IT FOREVER.
WHEW!
Y'ALL TEED UP?
PRODUCE THE JUICE.
THIS MIGHT
TAKE A WHILE.
( sighs )
HEY, BUDDY, COULD YOU
RUN IN AND GRAB ME A DRINK?
I COULD USE A THUNDER BLAZZ
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
YOU GOT IT.
ONE THUNDER BLAZZ
COMING RIGHT UP.
SYLVIA, I AM HONORED
YOU HAVE CHOSEN ME
TO REQUISITION
THIS REFRESHMENT
FOR YOU,
AND I WILL NOT
LET YOU DOWN.
HE'S TAKING
ALL THE THUNDER BLAZZ.
AHEM.
SORRY. AFTER YOU.
NEVER HURTS TO HELP.
NO MORE THUNDER BLAZZ.
THAT'S FINE.
I'LL GET SYLVIA
SOMETHING JUST AS GOOD.
YEAH, IT JUST NEEDS
TO BE FIZZY,
REFRESHING, AND TOTALLY
BLORPED. GOT IT!
"FIZZY, BUT NOT REFRESHING
OR TOTALLY BLORPED."
"REFRESHING BUT NOT FIZZY,
AND ONLY SOMEWHAT
BLORPED."
"TOTALLY BLORPED
AND FUZZY AND REFRACTING"?
"FLATULENT, REFRUZZLED,
AND TERMINALLY BLARPED."
"FRAUDULENT, REFLARZLED,
AND ETERNALLY BLORKED."
"FREMBULOUS, REGARGLED,
AND ESSENTIALLY ZONKED."
"MID-GRADE INDUSTRIAL
ROCKET FUEL,
NOT FOR CONSUMPTION"?!
BOTTLES, BOTTLES EVERYWHERE,
BUT NO THUNDER BLAZZ
TO DRINK!
( panting )
OOPS. WATCH OUT FOR
THAT MAT.
OH, WHY, THANK YOU.
OH, WHY,
THANK YOU.
NEVER HURTS
TO HELP.
YEAH?
EXCUSE ME, FINE SIR,
BUT I CAME HERE LOOKING FOR
A BOTTLE OF THUNDER BLAZZ
FOR MY HEAT-STRICKEN
FRIEND OUT THERE
BUT THEN, I HELD THE DOOR
FOR A VERY LONG MAN
WHILE ANOTHER MAN
TOOK ALL BUT THE LAST BOTTLE
THEN I TRIED TO FIND
A REPLACEMENT BUT COULDN'T.
CAN YOU PLEASE USE
YOUR CONSIDERABLE EXPERTISE
TO HELP ME FIND
A SIMILAR BEVERAGE
THAT MIGHT BE PERFECT
FOR MY PARCHED PAL?
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
FOUNTAIN DRINKS.
YES! OF COURSE!
YOU ARE SO GOOD
AT YOUR JOB.
FIZZY FRUIT PUNCH.
REFRESHING
RASPBERRY.
TOTALLY BLORPED
BLORPBERRY! YES!!
IS IT OKAY IF I MIX
SOME OF THESE TOGETHER,
OR IS THAT FROWNED UPON
IN THIS FINE ESTABLISHMENT?
YEAH, MAN, IT'S FINE.
ARE YOU SURE?
DON'T MAKE A SPECIAL
EXCEPTION FOR ME.
YES, EVERYBODY
DOES IT, OKAY?
PERFECT. THAT'S A FINE
APPROXIMATION OF THUNDER BLAZZ
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
CAREFUL OF THE MAT.
AH, YOU GOT IT.
NICE WORK.
ONE FOUNTAIN BEVERAGE
REMINISCENT OF
THUNDER BLAZZ, PLEASE.
1.99.
( sighs )
YOU'RE A PENNY SHORT.
IT'S OKAY, MAN.
JUST TAKE ONE FROM THE DISH.
NO, I CAN'T.
WHAT IF SOMEBODY ELSE
NEEDS THOSE COINS MORE THAN ME--
LIKE A MOTHER BUYING
MEDICINE FOR A BABY,
OR A GRANDMOTHER BUYING
A CANE SHE NEEDS TO WALK,
OR A MAN BUYING A BOAT
SO HE CAN TAKE THE BOAT
TO AN ISLAND
TO RESCUE HIS LOST LOVE?
WHAT IF THEY NEED
THOSE PENNIES?
WE DON'T SELL
ANY OF THOSE THINGS.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
DID ANYBODY LOSE A PENNY?
HEY, YOU FOUND
MY PENNY. THANKS.
YAY, PENNY!
( frustrated groan )
DID ANYONE ELSE...
( whispering )
DID ANY OF THE REST OF
YOU FINE FOLKS LOSE A PENNY?
OH, SORRY, SORRY.
ONE THUNDER BLAZZ-ESQUE
DRINK, PLEASE.
YOU STILL WANT IT
OR WHAT?
NEVER... HURTS TO HELP.
( frustrated groan )
LOOK, MAN, I'M
GOIN' ON BREAK,
SO YOU TAKE SOME TIME
TO FIGURE OUT...
ALL THIS.
QUICKLY, CASHIER,
I NEED TO PURCHASE
THIS PURPLE JELLY,
THIS LENGTH OF HOSE,
AND THESE CHILI PEPPER
REFRIGERATOR MAGNETS.
- IT'S AN EMERGENCY!
- I'M SORRY, SIR.
- I'M NOT ACTUALLY--
- WHAT PART OF "EMERGENCY"
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
I NEED YOUR HELP!
LET'S DO THIS.
AND HERE IS YOUR CHANGE.
- KEEP IT!
- WATCH OUT FOR THE MAT.
TWO DOLLARS!
THAT'S... THAT'S
BLAZZ-BUYIN' MONEY.
IT NEVER HURTS TO HELP!
OH, SORRY, SORRY.
I KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
I'M GONNA TURN AROUND,
THERE'S GONNA BE
ANOTHER HUGE LINE,
AND SOMETHING'S
GONNA HAPPEN
THAT KEEPS ME FROM
GETTING SYLVIA
HER THUNDER
BLAZZ-ESQUE DRINK.
♪ HERE COMES WANDER NOW
♪ HERE COMES
WANDER NOW ♪
♪ GONNA BUY
HIS THUNDER BLAZZ ♪
♪ HERE COMES WA...
OH, NO!
THE MAT!
YOU GONNA  HELP
CLEAN THAT UP?
( sighs )
( bottle rattles )
HUH, A BOTTLE
OF THUNDER BLAZZ.
A BOTTLE
OF THUNDER BLAZZ!
MONEY, DRINK, NOW, PLEASE!
1.99.
( door opens )
OH, HONEY,
I KNOW.
YOU WERE GONNA PAY
FOR IT ALL BY YOURSELF.
FINALLY. I KINDA THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA ROB THE PLACE.
OH, MY.
ARE YOU SURE?
NEVER HURTS TO HELP.
HEY, BUDDY,
HOW'S IT GOIN'?
YOU WERE IN THERE FOREVER.
I FAILED YOU, SYLVIA.
I'M JUST A BIG OL'
FAILURE McFAILURESON.
I TRIED SO HARD
TO GET YOU A THUNDER BLAZZ,
BUT EVERY TIME
I ALMOST...
UH, THANK YOU.
SHE THOUGHT
YOU LOOKED THIRSTY.
NEVER HURTS TO HELP.
HM, NICE KID.
YEAH, SHE SURE IS.
♪ FEEL THE BLAZZ
♪ THUNDER BLAZZ!
OH, BY THE WAY,
WE HAVE, LIKE,
FIVE MORE HOURS
LEFT ON THIS THING.
REALLY? GREAT,
'CAUSE I GOT A MAT
TO NAIL DOWN.
COME ON, THE SUSPENSE
IS KILLIN' ME, WANDER.
WHAT'S THE SURPRISE?
WELL, IT TOOK
SOME DOIN',
BUT SYLVIA THE ZBORNAK,
I'M ABOUT TO MAKE
ONE OF YOUR BIGGEST
DREAMS COME TRUE!
YOU'RE GONNA BURY ME
IN JELLYFISH PIE
AND LET ME EAT MY WAY OUT?
NO. LOOK!
- DUM-DA-DA-DA!
- ( burps )
LADIES AND RACE FANS,
WELCOME TO THE 500th
ANNUAL...
ONCE A YEAR,
THE PLANETS OF THIS GALAXY
ALIGN TO FORM
THE DEADLIEST RACE COURSE
IN THE UNIVERSE.
ONLY THE BRAVEST RACERS
DARE FACE
THE INSANE-EST RACE
IN OUTER SPACE!
OH, WANDER, YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
I KNEW YOU'D
LIKE IT,
'CAUSE I REMEMBER
YOU TELLIN' ME THAT,
BACK IN THE DAY,
YOU USED TO RACE IN
THE GALACTIC
CONJUNCTION 6000!
AND IT WAS YOUR DREAM
TO FINALLY WIN IT.
BUT YOU NEVER DID,
'CAUSE...
I AIN'T GOT
WHAT IT TAKES.
YOU AIN'T GOT
WELL,
( blows raspberries )...
TO THAT, I SAY.
YOUR DREAM AWAITS YOU,
MY FAST BUT UNFULFILLED FRIEND.
YOU JUST HAVE TO TAKE
THE FIRST STEP.
OH, THIS IS BAD, WANDER.
THIS IS REAL BAD.
I DON'T DO WELL
AT THESE THINGS.
YOU'LL DO GREAT.
YOU'RE SO FAST
AND STRONG.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
I KNOW I'M FAST,
I KNOW I'M STRONG.
I ALSO KNOW THAT I'M...
TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
OH, NO.
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
AH, LOOK WHO'S BACK
IN THE RACE THIS YEAR, STOK.
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK.
HARVAX, NICE TO SEE YOU.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
THIS IS JUST A MISTAKE.
I'M NOT--
GONNA WIN.
I KNOW.
'CAUSE IT'S JUST
A MATTER OF TIME UNTIL...
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
BOOM.
( laughs )
WELL, THEY SEEMED
AWFULLY NICE.
EXCEPT WHAT WAS WITH
ALL THAT TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK?
IT'S BECAUSE OF
MY NICKNAME.
( buzzer sounds )
NICKNAME?
YOU HAD A RACING
LET'S SEE,
TICK-TOCK.
WAS IT QUICKY McQUICKERSON,
BECAUSE YOU RAN SO FAST,
YOU ALWAYS BEAT
THE CLOCK?
- NO.
- ( buzzer )
THE ROYAL LADY, LADY LATERSON,
BECAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS LATE?
- NO.
- ( buzzer )
ROGER? ROGER THE CLOCK MAKER,
BECAUSE YOU USED TO MAKE CLOCKS?
- NO.
- ( buzzer )
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK!
BOOM!
NAH, THAT AIN'T NO BOOM.
YOU AIN'T SEEN NO BOOM.
FIRST, HER EYES GO RED.
THEN, HER COMB STANDS UP
ALL POINTY-LIKE.
THEN THE VEINS
POP OUT OF HER NECK,
AND SHE STARTS
FOAMIN' AT THE MOUTH!
THEN JUST WHEN
SHE'S HAD ENOUGH,
BOOM, THAT'S WHEN
THE TIME BOMB REALLY GOES OFF!
AND THAT'S WHEN
SHE LOSES.
GET ZLORGED, PUNY.
COMIN' THROUGH.
YOUR BUTT IS MINE!
HEY THERE, SYL OLD GIRL.
IT'S YOUR OLD PAL WANDER
COMIN' AT YA ON YOUR A.M. DIAL.
IT'S TIME TO SIMMER DOWN NOW
AND LET THE SOOTHING SAX
OF DR. SMOOTH
SOOTHE YOUR SOUL.
( imitating sax music )
OH, THANKS, PAL.
SURPRISINGLY,
THAT ACTUALLY HELPED.
WHOOP, PARDON ME, MA'AM.
- OH, NO.
- YOU CUT ME OFF!
( stammering )
I DO APOLOGIZE, MA'AM.
I BELIEVE I WAS COMPLETELY
WITHIN MY RIGHTS,
ALTHOUGH, IF I OVERSTEPPED
MY BOUNDS--
I'LL OVERSTEP
YOUR BOUNDS!
( stammering )
MY MOST HUMBLE APOLOGIES,
YOUR TIME BOMBNESS.
SEE, WANDER?
COMPETITION.
THAT'S MY PROBLEM.
IT CHANGES ME.
IT TURNS ME INTO...
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL ME
THE TIME BOMB.
THAT'S WHY I'VE NEVER
WON THE RACE.
I SHOULD JUST QUIT
BEFORE I REALLY EXPLODE.
NO, YOU CAN
DO THIS, SYLVIA.
I'VE SEEN YOU FACE DOWN
A FIVE-FANGLED STAUNCHMONGER
AND BARELY BAT
AN EYELID.
IF YOU'RE STRONG ENOUGH
TO OVERCOME THAT,
THEN YOU'VE GOTTA BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO
OVERCOME YOUR ANGER,
AND WIN THIS THING.
NO, I'M BEYOND HELP.
YOU MIGHT BE BEYOND HELP,
BUT WE'RE NOT.
YOUR TRIED AND TRUE
TRUSTY OLD PAL WANDER
IS STICKIN' BY YOUR SIDE.
TOGETHER, WE CAN TAKE ON
ANY OBSTACLE THAT WE MAY FIND.
Sylvia:
EXCEPT THAT ONE.
OH, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
NOT GOOD, NOT GOOD,
NOT GOOD, NOT GOOD!
( breathing heavily,
grunting angrily )
YOU'VE GOT THIS, SYL.
HUH? WHAT?
JUST LISTEN TO MY VOICE,
AND I'LL GUIDE YOU.
FORGET THE RACERS,
FORGET THE RACE.
JUST ZONE ON OUT
TO YOUR HAPPY PLACE.
HAPPY PLACE?
MARSHFALAFFLE
APPLE MEADOW.
OOH, GOOD ONE.
( imitates sax music )
HERE WE GO.
LEFT, LEFT, STRAIGHT.
HARD RIGHT, DUCK,
LEFT, JUMP.
JUMP MORE,
SHIMMY STEP RIGHT.
SHIMMY STEP LEFT.
OOH, BACK FLIP.
NOW HERE COMES
THE TRICKY PART.
RIGHT, RIGHT, LEFT, LEFT,
LEFT, JUMP RIGHT,
LEFT JUMP, JUMP, JUMP,
LEFT, RIGHT,
DOWN SPIN, TURN RIGHT,
RIGHT, DUCK, DUCK, GOOSE.
SYLVIA, I'VE GOT
ANOTHER SURPRISE.
- WHAT?
- WE MADE IT.
WHAT?!
AND WE'RE IN THE LEAD.
WE'RE GONNA WIN?
YOU'RE GONNA WIN.
( revving sound )
TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
DON'T LISTEN TO
THEM, SYLVIA.
YOUR COMPETITION
IS WITH YOURSELF,
NOT THEM.
Both: TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
- SYLVIA!
- TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK.
- DON'T DO IT.
- TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK.
( growling )
ISN'T IT ABOUT TIME
YOU WENT OFF?
TIME BOMB!
SYLVIA, NO!
MARSHFALAFFLE APPLE MEADOW!
( imitating sax )
GET OFF MY BACK!
( gasps )
BOOM!
THAT SHE BLOWS!
WANDER!
EXCUSE ME, SORRY.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
SORRY. WANDER!
ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, WANDER,
WANDER, I'M SO SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT MY HORRIBLE TEMPER
MADE ME DO TO YOU.
I WANNA CONTROL THIS.
I REALLY DO.
I THINK...
I KNOW I CAN,
BUT NOT ALONE.
WILL YOU HELP ME?
TIME'S A-WASTIN'.
WE GOTTA GET A MOVE ON
IF WE'RE GONNA...
WIN THIS THING!
HERE COME OUR LEADERS AS WE GO
INTO THE FINAL STRETCH.
IT'S HARVAX AND STOK
OUT IN FRONT,
WITH WANDER AND SYLVIA
CLOSE BEHIND.
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK,
TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK...
MARSHFALAFFLE.
WHEW!
THANKS. I GOT THIS.
( breathes deeply )
♪ TAKE IT EASY, SYLVIA
♪ TAKE IT EASY,
SYLVIA ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY, SYLVIA
♪ TAKE IT EASY,
SYLVIA ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY, SYLVIA
THEY ARE NECK AND NECK!
WHO WILL IT BE?
AND HARVAX WINS
BY A NOSE!
( wild cheering )
OH, SORRY.
YOU OKAY, SYLVIA?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M FAN-FLEEVING-TASTIC!
I MAY HAVE GOTTEN
SECOND PLACE IN
THE GALACTIC
CONJUNCTION 6000,
BUT I GOT FIRST PLACE
IN THE RACE AGAINST MYSELF.
STILL WOULD'VE BEEN FUN
TO HAVE WON.
AAH!
YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE.
AFTER FURTHER REVIEW,
HARVAX AND STOK
HAVE BEEN DISQUALIFIED
FOR USING A FAKE
PROBOSCIS.
THEREFORE, I GIVE YOU
THE NEW WINNERS
OF THE GALACTIC
CONJUNCTION 6000,
WANDER AND SYLVIA!
OH, YES!
IN YOUR FACE, HARVAX,
'CAUSE YOU JUST
GOT DEFUSED.
OH!
MARSHFALAFFLE APPLE MEADOW
REPRESENT!
WELL, NOW THAT WE'VE GOT
YOUR TEMPER UNDER CONTROL,
WE'LL WORK ON YOU
BEING A SORE WINNER NEXT.
ALLOW ME.
( imitating sax music )
♪ WELL, THERE AIN'T NO DOUBT
ABOUT THE POWER OF THUNDER ♪
♪ LIFT YOU UP
WHEN YOU'RE FEELING UNDER ♪
♪ SO REFRESHING
AND OH, SO FIZZY, YEAH ♪
♪ CONSULT YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU'RE FEELIN' DIZZY ♪
♪ FEEL THE BLAZZ
♪ THUNDER, THUNDER,
THUNDER BLAZZ ♪
♪ FEEL THE BLAZZ
♪ THUNDER, THUNDER,
THUNDER BLAZZ ♪
♪ FEEL THE BLAZZ
♪ THUNDER BLAZZ!