♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
OUR TARGET, LORD HATER'S
TOP SECRET RESEARCH FACILITY.
OUR MISSION,
SNEAK IN AND DESTROY
HATER'S LATEST
DIABOLICAL INVENTION,
THE HT-125-F,
BEFORE HE CAN UTILIZE IT.
WHO ARE WE?
THE CRAZIEST RAG-TAG BAND
OF REBELS IN THE GALAXY.
THE INSURGENT GENERALS!
GENERAL OUTRAGE.
I'M ALL ABOUT MISSION,
MAYHEM, MANLINESS.
BRAINZ.
I COMPUTE OUR CHANCES
OF SUCCESS TO BE...
TOTALLY AWESOME!
WILD CARD.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN
I'M GONNA RUTABAGA CANDY CORN.
CLIPPER.
I'LL CLIP YOU.
SMASH & SASS.
HIII-YAAA!
OH, NO, I DIDN'T!
AND THE LOVABLE
WANDERING WANDERER, WANDER.
CAN I HELP YOU, SON?
SIR, SYLVIA,
AKA SMASH & SASS.
FIRST DAY ON THE TEAM.
HUGE FAN OF YOUR WORK.
REALLY APPRECIATE
THE CALL TO TRY OUT.
YOU GETTIN' TO
A POINT, SOLDIER?
LOOK, THIS LITTLE FUR BALL
IS MY BEST PAL.
I KNOW HE SEEMS LIKE
A SKINNY, CLUELESS WEAKLING.
BELIEVE ME, HE ALWAYS
MANAGES TO GET THE JOB DONE
IN HIS OWN
WEIRD LITTLE WAY.
( growls )
OKAY, SON,
LISTEN UP.
WE'RE GONNA SNEAK IN THERE
AND DESTROY
LORD HATER'S
LATEST EVIL TECHNOLOGY,
THE DREADED HT-125-F.
( Wander yelling )
WE'RE  GONNA DESTROY
THE HT-125-F.
YOU'RE  GONNA GUARD
THE FRONT DOOR,
AND MAKE SURE
NO ONE COMES IN.
IF HE FLINGS
THIS UP,
IT'S ON YOU.
LOOK, I REALLY WANNA
MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION
ON THESE GUYS,
SO JUST FOCUS,
AND IT SHOULDN'T
BE HARD, OKAY?
AND REMEMBER,
DON'T LET ANYONE IN.
I GOT THIS.
♪ I DON'T
LET ANYONE IN ♪
♪ I DON'T LET
ANYONE IN ♪
♪ NO, NO, NO,
DON'T LET ANYONE IN ♪
♪ DON'T LET
ANYONE IN ♪
THANK YOU.
♪ DON'T LET ANYONE IN
OH, NO!!
SYLVIA.
WANDER, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
WHY AREN'T YOU
GUARDING THE DOOR?
WELL, REMEMBER HOW YOU SAID
DON'T LET ANYONE IN?
WELL, I SORT OF
DID THAT THING.
WHAT?! OW!
SMASH & SASS, WHAT'S
GOING ON BACK THERE?
I-OKAY.
GO, INSURGENTS.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
FIND THE GUY,
KNOCK HIM OUT,
SAY SOMETHING SASSY.
YOU KNOW,
SMASH & SASS.
OKAY, OKAY.
DON'T DO THAT.
JUST FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
WHERE ARE MY KEYS?
I KNOW I LEFT THEM
SOMEWHERE.
EXCUSE ME,
MR. SCIENTIST.
YOU... GO AWAY!
YOU GO AWAY
FROM THIS BUILDING.
YOU GO AWAY NOW.
SHOO!
WHO ARE YOU?
SYLVIA?
NIGHT JANITOR.
OH, I SEE.
THEN WHO IS THAT?
SO HATER HIRED
A NEWER, YOUNGER
AND PRETTIER JANITOR, HUH?
WELL, YOU LISTEN
TO ME, PAL.
I AIN'T GOIN'
WITHOUT A FIGHT.
( screams )
WELL?
AH, YOU KNOW, I BET
I LEFT MY KEYS IN THE LAB
WITH THE HT-125-F.
THE HT-125-F?!
SYLVIA!
I THINK I SAW
YOUR KEYS OUTSIDE.
OH, LOOK, HERE THEY ARE
IN THIS BUSH.
NO, I HATE THAT BUSH.
I NEVER GO NEAR IT.
I WILL GO SEARCH THE LAB.
WAIT!
WHAT YOU GOT HERE
IS YOUR STANDARD
EVIL OVERLORD
SECRET LAIR LOCK.
SEEN IT A MILLION TIMES.
THANK YOU.
I HOPE THIS HUG
IS ACCEPTABLE
COMPENSATION.
JUST LET ME USE
YOUR RESTROOM,
AND WE'LL
CALL IT EVEN.
WELL, I'M REALLY
NOT SUPPOSED TO LET
ANYBODY IN THE BUILDING.
OH, COME ON.
PLEASE. I'LL LEAVE
AS SOON AS I'M DONE.
I PROMISE.
OH, RATS.
OUT OF ORDER.
WELL, GUESS YOU'LL
HAVE TO GO SOMEWHERE ELSE.
NO. I PROMISED I'D LEAVE
AS SOON AS I'M DONE,
AND A LOCKSMITH
NEVER BREAKS A PROMISE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T WORRY, I GOT A BUDDY
WHO CAN TOTALLY HANDLE THIS.
WAIT, NO!
IT'S WORSE THAN I THOUGHT.
GONNA BE HERE ALL NIGHT.
BETTER ORDER A PIZZA.
WAIT, NO!
UM, SYLVIA?
WANDER, WHO ARE
ALL THOSE PEOPLE?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY KEEP COMING AND COMING,
AND NEVER GOING.
WHAT DO I DO?
GET THEM OUT OF HERE BEFORE
THEY ACCIDENTALLY FIND US.
SMASH & SASS,
EVERYTHING OKAY?
I-OKAY.
GO, INSURGENTS.
BUT HOW?
I DON'T CARE HOW.
JUST DO IT QUICKLY.
AND DO IT QUIETLY.
PLASMA LEAK!
TOTALLY DANGEROUS,
POISONOUS.
SO EVERYBODY
BETTER LEAVE NOW.
HEY, BUDDY,
WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, NOTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT I REALLY
NEED YOU ALL TO LEAVE
SO MY BEST FRIEND'S DREAM
OF BEING A BIG TOP ACTION HERO
CAN COME TRUE.
NO BIGGIE, THOUGH.
SURE THING,
LITTLE GUY.
OUR JOB IS TO PUT
A STOP TO PLASMA LEAKS,
NOT DREAMS.
COME ON, FELLAS.
PIPE'S ALL FIXED.
I PROMISE.
Both: BECAUSE A LOCKSMITH
NEVER BREAKS A PROMISE.
SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
I GOT ANGER MANAGEMENT ISSUES.
PROBABLY WHY THEY
REPLACED ME.
GOOD LUCK,
PRETTY BOY.
WOWIE!
LOOK. THE HT-125-F.
WE NEED TO TURN OFF
ITS PROTECTIVE SHIELD. BRAINZ!
DEACTIVATING THE FORCE FIELD
BY PUTTING THE COMMAND KEY
INTO THE...
TWO KEYHOLES?!
WE'RE MISSING A KEY.
WAIT. WHAT'S
HE DOING HERE?
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
GUARDING THE DOOR.
INTRUDERS.
( alarm blaring )
DON'T MOVE. LORD HATER
WILL BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
OH, NO, I DIDN'T.
SMASH & SASS.
HATER'LL BE HERE
ANY SECOND,
AND HE'S GONNA TOTALLY
CARPET SQUARE ARTICHOKE!
YOU SAID HE WOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM.
YOU LET HIM IN,
HE LET THAT SCIENCE GUY IN,
AND NOW WE GOT HATER
COMIN' TO COOK OUR KEISTERS.
BRINGING YOU ALONG
WAS A MISTAKE.
IF WE MAKE IT
OUT OF HERE ALIVE,
YOU'RE OFF THE TEAM.
GUYS, DON'T BLAME SYLVIA.
BLAME ME.
I WAS A BIG DUMMY
TO THINK
I COULD BE AS COOL
OR HEROIC AS ANY OF YOU.
ESPECIALLY MY BEST FRIEND.
I'M NOT A HERO
OR A TOUGH GUY.
I'M JUST A WORTHLESS
WANDERING WANDERER, WANDER.
AND ALSO A JANITOR.
OH, HEY,
THE SCIENTIST'S KEYS.
( gasps )
THE KEYS!
THE SECOND KEY
FOR THE CODE BOX.
WANDER, GET OVER HERE.
LET'S BLOW THIS JOINT.
JUST A LITTLE SHORTER.
( beeping )
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
THERE'S ONE MORE MESS
TO CLEAN UP.
WANDER, NO!
WOW, WAY TO GO...
INSURGENTS!
I GET GREAT ENJOYMENT WHEN
A PLAN WORKS OUT ACCORDINGLY.
HATER MAY HAVE
HAD AN EVIL PLAN,
AND NOW, BECAUSE OF
THE BIG JOB WE PULLED OFF TODAY,
HE WILL NEVER BE ABLE
TO HEAT HIS HOT TUB.
WHOA, WHAT NOW?
HT-125-F HOT TUB.
HEAT IT TO 125 DEGREES
FLARGENHATZ--
JUST THE WAY
HATER LIKES IT.
YEAH, AND WHO KNOWS.
MAYBE HE'LL BE SO UPSET
THAT HIS HOT TUB WON'T WORK
THAT HE WON'T TRY
TO TAKE OVER THE UNIVERSE
OR SOMETHING
REALLY EVIL LIKE THAT.
( laughs )
POT HOLDER.
OKAY, NOW I KNOW
YOU'RE CRAZY.
( groans )
HEY, CUT IT OUT.
HE'S SENSITIVE.
WE DON'T WANT
HATER MAD AT US.
HAVE YOU SEEN THAT GUY?
HE'S SCARY.
INSURGENTS, HO!
SMASH & SASS,
UP TOP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE NAME'S SYLVIA.
AND I'M ALREADY
PART OF AN AWESOME TEAM.
SYLVIA, LOOK!
WHAT AM I LOOKIN' AT?
SEE IT NOW?
I SEE A MAN
CHANGING A TIRE.
YEAH.
AND?
AND...
HE NEEDS HELP.
HELLO!
YOU THERE. I COULDN'T
HELP BUT NOTICE
YOU'RE HAVING
SOME MECHANICAL ISSUES.
MY FRIEND AND I
WERE TRAVELING ALONG
WHEN WE SPOTTED YOU,
AND IT SEEMED LIKE, WELL,
MAYBE YOU COULD
USE SOME HELP.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT JUST SO HAPPENS
I REALLY, REALLY
LIKE TO HELP.
SO WHEN WE SAW YOU HERE,
I JUST COULDN'T RESIST.
PLEASE DON'T YOU
WORRY ABOUT A THING.
THERE IS NOTHING MORE
IN THE WORLD
I WOULD RATHER DO
THAN HELP.
HOW'D THAT GO?
OH, UH... HA.
OKAY, I GUESS.
FUNNY THING, THOUGH.
THAT GUY, HE--
DIDN'T NEED YOUR HELP?
( snaps fingers)
YEAH. HOW'D YOU GUESS?
STRANGE AS IT MAY SEEM,
WANDER,
THERE'S A TIME TO HELP,
AND THERE'S A TIME TO--
HELLO! HEY THERE!
HI, FRIEND.
WHICH WAY YOU HEADED?
WHAT?
I SAID, WHICH WAY
YOU HEADED?
YOU GOIN' UPWAYS,
DOWNWAYS, SIDEWAYS,
NORTHWAYS,
NORTH BY NORTHWESTWAYS?
WHY'D YOU ASK?
OH, THIS?
I WAS JUST GIVIN'
YOU A THUMBS UP.
I REALLY LIKE YOUR HAT.
LIKE THOSE SHOES, TOO.
SO THEN, YOU'RE NOT...
IN NEED OF A RIDE?
A RIDE? OF COURSE I AM.
BEEN WAITING HERE FOR HOURS.
HERE COMES MY RIDE NOW,
RIGHT ON TIME.
IT'S LIKE I TOLD YOU,
WANDER.
THERE'S A TIME TO HELP,
AND A TIME TO NOT HELP.
( quiet screeching )
SYLVIA, DID YOU
HEAR THAT?
YEAH, I DID.
IT SOUNDED LIKE--
SCREE, SCREE, SCREE.
SCREE!
DON'T WORRY,
LITTLE BIRDIE!
I'LL HELP YOU...
BIRDIE, WAIT.
BIRDIE, DO YOU NEED HELP
FINDING THE WAY SOUTH?
HOW ABOUT WHICH WORMS
TASTE GOOD?
NAME OF A GOOD DENTIST?
ANY... THING?
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
IT'S A GOOD THING
NOT EVERYBODY NEEDS
YOUR HELP ALL THE TIME.
WHY?
WELL, YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO SPRAIN YOUR HELP GLAND.
MY WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST MADE IT UP.
( sighs )
I'M SORRY, WANDER.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO--
NO, SYLVIA,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
NOBODY NEEDS
ANY HELP TODAY.
SO LET'S JUST RELAX
AND ENJOY THE REST
OF THE DAY.
EXACTLY.
HEY, LOOK, THERE'S A RELAXING
LITTLE TOWN DOWN THERE.
A TOWN? I BET THERE'S
LOTS OF PEOPLE THERE
WHO NEED HELP.
( sighs )
♪ MOPPIN' UP FLOORS,
OPENIN' DOORS ♪
♪ THERE AIN'T NOTHIN'
THAT I WOULDN'T DO ♪
♪ TO LIGHTEN YOUR LOAD
♪ SMOOTH OUT
THE BUMP IN YOUR ROAD ♪
♪ MAYBE SORT YOUR SOCKS
AND UNDERWEAR TOO ♪
♪ OH, H-E-L-P-E-R,
I'M A HELPER ♪
♪ MEANS I LIKE TO HELP
♪ OH, I'M JUST
AN ACCOMMODATIN' FELLA ♪
♪ LIFE IS HARD, YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO DO IT BY YOURSELF ♪
♪ PUT MY HAT IN THE MUD
♪ IF THAT'S
WHAT I HAVE TO DO ♪
HEY, WANDER, YOU KNOW
THIS TOWN IS ACTUALLY
PRETTY COOL.
THERE'S A KILLER
LEMONADE STAND
ON THE NEXT CORNER.
OH, I SEE YOU FOUND
THE FUDGE SHOP.
( slurping )
IT'S NOT FUDGE.
LOOK AT THIS
PAIR OF SHADES I PICKED UP
AT THE SECOND-HAND SHOP
DOWN THE STREET.
AREN'T THEY EVERYTHING?!
I GOT SOME
FOR YOU, TOO.
OH, AND THERE
WAS ALSO--
IT'S NOT FUDGE.
IT'S MUD.
OH, YOU FOUND
THE MUD PIE SHOP.
I LOVE MUD PIES.
WE SHOULD--
NOT MUD PIES!!
JUST MUD.
Woman: HELP!!
HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
HELP! OH, SOMEBODY,
HELP ME!
I'LL HELP YOU.
HOWDY, MA'AM.
Man: HOLD IT!
WOULD SOMEONE MIND
EXPLAINING TO ME
JUST WHAT IS
GOING ON AROUND HERE?!
( people muttering )
( muttering continues )
YOU MEAN...
( muttering stops )
All: THAT'S RIGHT!
WE'RE MAKING A MOVIE.
UH... HELP.
( excited yell )
HOLD IT!
WHAT'S THAT GUY
DOING ON SET?
( people muttering )
( gulps )
YOU MEAN...
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE MAKING
A MOVIE...
ABOUT MAKING
A MOVIE.
( yells )
THERE YOU ARE, WANDER.
MAN, THERE IS A REALLY
GREAT STREET MARKET
JUST DOWN THE...
UH, STREET.
I PICKED UP
THIS FESTIVE SCARF.
OH, AND CHECK THIS OUT.
WHOA. HOW ABOUT
WE GRAB A BITE AND RELAX?
( Wander sighs heavily )
GOSH, YOU WERE RIGHT, SYL.
THERE'S NOTHING THAT
A TRIPLE PICKLE CREAM PIE
CAN'T SOLVE.
( slurping
and chewing loudly )
I GUESS I DID GET
A LITTLE CARRIED
AWAY BACK THERE.
YOU THINK?
SOME DAYS, FOLKS
DON'T NEED A-HELPIN'.
EXACTLY. I MEAN,
IT'S NOT LIKE
HATER IS GONNA SHOW UP
WITH HIS ARMY
OF WATCHDOGS,
AND TRY TO TAKE OVER
THE TOWN OR SOMETHING.
( slurping )
HATER. WATCHDOGS.
TAKING OVER THE TOWN.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS?
CHECK, PLEASE?
NO.
IT MEANS IT'S TIME
TO HELP!
FEAR NOT, FOLKS.
I GOT THIS.
( humming heroic tune )
SAVING THE DAY!
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
I'M SO GLAD YOU ASKED...
MICHELLE.
BECAUSE WE WOULD LIKE TO...
THREE, FOUR...
OH, FORGET IT.
JUST LET ME HAVE 5,075
FRIVOLITY MEALS,
689 PIES,
AND TWO DIET COLAS--
HOLD IT!
OKAY, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE HERE
FOR, LORD HATER,
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
I'M HERE TO HELP THESE PEOPLE,
SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO GET RIGHT BACK
ON YOUR SHIP.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON
OVER HERE, MICHELLE?
I'M NOT SURE, SIR.
HE JUST HOPPED UP
THERE AND, UH...
I'M SORRY, SON,
BUT I'M GONNA
HAVE TO ASK YOU
TO COME DOWN FROM
THERE RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE SIMPLY NOT INSURED
FOR THAT KIND OF--
BUT HE'S GONNA
TAKE OVER YOUR TOWN,
AND I'M HERE TO HELP.
TAKE OVER? HE'S HERE
TO TAKE OUT HIS LUNCH.
SORRY, MICHELLE.
NOW PLEASE COME DOWN
FROM THERE BEFORE
SOMEONE GETS HURT.
HIS LUNCH?
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
OF COURSE IT'S POSSIBLE!
THESE GUYS HAVE THE BEST
TRIPLE PICKLE PIES
IN THE UNIVERSE.
THANK YOU. WE TAKE
GREAT PRIDE IN OUR PIES.
THANK YOU.
COME AGAIN.
NOW, SON...
I GOTTA HELP!!
YOU, NEED YOUR NECKTIE
STRAIGHTENED?
HOW ABOUT YOU?
SHOELACES TIED?
YOUR GLASSES POLISHED?
CAN I HELP YOU CARRY
YOUR ICE CREAM CONE?
I ONLY WANTED
TO HELP.
( whispering )
WAKE UP, SON.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
SON, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
SORRY ABOUT
THE PIES.
THAT'S OKAY.
WE CLEANED 'EM UP.
DID YOU NEED ANY... HELP?
NO, SON,
WE TOOK CARE OF IT, BUT...
THERE IS ONE THING WE COULD
REALLY USE YOUR HELP WITH.
REALLY? WHAT IS IT?
ANYTHING, ANYTHING!
WELL, THERE'S SOMEBODY
WE NEED YOU
TO RUN OUT OF TOWN.
OF COURSE.
WHERE IS HE?
SHOW HIM TO ME.
OH!
SO THIS IS THE GUY
YOU WANT OUT OF TOWN.
I GET IT.
YOU DO?
LOOK, SON, WE ONLY...
I WILL NOT REST UNTIL
THAT GUY IS OUT OF HERE
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
SO YOU'RE THE ONE THEY WANT
RUN OUT OF TOWN.
( whip cracking )
SO THEY SAY.
WELL, LUCKY FOR THEM,
I'M HERE TO HELP.
HEY!
OH, YOU CAUGHT ME.
( all gasping )
I'M GOIN',
I'M GOIN'!
AND STAY OUT!
( all cheering )
OOH!
SON?
THANKS.
HAPPY I COULD HELP.
THAT MAKES
TWO OF US.
PASS THE MUSTARD.
DID THEY CHANGE THESE FRIES?
OH, SO GOOD.
OH, MAN, I AM MAKING
SUCH A MESS.
HEY, PEEPERS, PASS ME
SOME OF THOSE NAPKINS.
AH! OH, THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT. MMM!
SO GOOD!