♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Cruising through
outer space ♪
♪ With his handsome
skeleton face ♪
♪ Traveling the galaxies ♪
♪ Conquering all he sees ♪
♪ Smart men fear him,
ladies want to be near him ♪
♪ Lord Hater never fails ♪
♪ Opening secret doors,
hang-gliding past dinosaurs ♪
♪ Hater, the greatest
in the galaxy ♪
Sir, is this a--
Brilliant idea?
Absolutely.
I needed to remind the universe
how evil and awesome I am.
So I ordered the Watchdogs
to make a propaganda film
using the most sophisticated
and respected art form
in the universe.
This is to impress
Dominator, isn't it?
What?! No!
But if she happens
to see this,
and finally realize
how awesome and kissable
I am, so be it.
Now shut up. I want to hear
what I sound like
as a cartoon
character.
( deep movie star voice )
Today shall be
the final reckoning
as I, Lord Hater,
the greatest in the galaxy,
finally become
the greatest in the galaxy.
Dead on.
Great casting, Watchdogs.
I've located the all-powerful
staff of power.
Ooh, sounds... powerful.
The staff of power
is so powerful,
it can do the impossible--
make me even more powerful
than I am now.
It will do this by
charging me with a power
which I will use
to power up,
thus giving me more power
than I currently have.
Power!
Solid writing, too.
Peepers!
( stammering )
Y-yes, sir.
Oh, no, my glasses.
( both Haters laughing
and cheering )
REAL PEEPERS:
Are you kidding?
This is totally
inaccurate.
BOTH PEEPERS:
This is a terrible plan.
It'll never work.
REAL HATER:
Seems pretty accurate to me.
There. Viper Mountain.
( cheesy dramatic
organ music )
Now no one shall stop me from
getting the staff of power.
(gurgly voice )
Ah, not so fast,
Hater.
Emperor Awesome?
The staff of power
will be mine.
( coughing and sputtering )
Watchdogs, attack!
( Watchdogs yelling )
PEEPERS:
Oh, come on.
Oh, yeah!
Get him!
Whoo!
Wow, what an impressive
fight.
Awesome doesn't stand
a chance.
We should stop
describing it
and watch in silence.
What's going on?
Why aren't I seeing
all my cool moves?
WATCHDOG ONE: We kind of blew
all our animation budget
on the Watchdog fight.
WATCHDOG TWO: We thought
it was more important
to the story.
( fight continuing )
Finally, the staff
of power is mine!
And I win,
just like in real life.
Dominator's gonna
love... I mean...
Great work, guys.
( goofy laughter )
CARTOON WANDER:
Hey, Hatey.
Oh, no.
You didn't.
Hater, it's me,
your old pal.
( laughing )
They totally did.
You put Wander
in my cartoon?!
( goofy laughter )
I don't know
about this, Wander.
It seems like
a baaaa-ad idea.
( goofy whinny )
( triumphant yell )
Oh, that is perfect!
You nailed him!
Oh, and I was totally gonna
destroy you guys.
What happens?
Don't tell me.
No spoilers, but I bet
I destroy them
with my staff of power.
Finally, I can now destroy
you, Wander,
with my staff
of power.
Knew it!!
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
But I just wanted
to sing you a song.
Banjo!
Wait. What's
going on?
Ow. Ooh.
Ow. Ow!
Ouch. Oh!
Ouch. Ow!
Oof. Ow, ow!
No, please, stop.
My back-up
back-up glasses.
( yelling )
Oh, no. These Watchdogs
are too tough.
I'm done for.
Wander, help!
I am the Wanderer!
What?!
Oh, I get it.
You made Wander all strong
so it will be more impressive
when I finally beat him.
This is a smart
cartoon.
This ends now.
Not if I can help it.
This... seems like
it's going on for a while.
Uh, yeah.
We were 15 seconds short,
so we had to
pad it out.
Just give it a minute.
Any second now.
Yeah! Go, me!
Although I could've done it
so many times before this time,
now, because I am so much
more powerful this time,
this is the time when I will
finally destroy you, Wander.
This is the time to die!
Yes!
Guys, I think I've got
something real special here.
But, Hater,
all I ever wanted
was to be your friend.
BOTH HATERS:
Wait, what?
I just wanted
to be your friend
in the hopes
it would stop you
from bein' so evil.
Wow. All of a sudden,
out of nowhere,
I've come to realize
that I have a tendency
to compensate for
my insecurity and loneliness
by being evil
and scary.
But you, Wander,
saw the one thing
that I really needed
was not an army
or planets or power...
No, no, no, no, no!
...but a friend.
♪ Take my hand,
friend ♪
♪  We'll skip through
the flowers ♪
What's going on?!
♪  Because our friendship ♪
( Peepers laughing )
This is too good!
♪  Is the real
staff of power ♪
♪ My heart is dancing ♪
♪  Each day's
a fantasy ♪
I said I wanted this
to be true to life!
All you did was
make a cartoon
where I almost succeed,
then Wander shows up,
tries to be my friend,
and ruins everything!
Yeah, but...
That's what
always happens.
Burn it.
Burn it all!
Never let anybody
see this cartoon ever!
Especially not
Dominator.
Well, sir,
we would,
but we're broadcasting
this live.
And ratings are
through the roof.
- ( chuckles )
- ( laughing )
What? No!
We gotta animate a new ending
where I destroy Wander.
( screams )
Animation is so hard!
People who do this
for a living
deserve more credit
and respect.
Great day, buddy.
What do you say
we end it with
a big old hug?
Only if it's
the biggest.
( goofy laugh )
( laughs )
( shrieks )
Aw, it's okay, Hater.
I think this show
is amazing!
Gotta change
the ending right now!
Too bad. I think
Lord Hater would really like
- the twist ending.
- Twist ending?
You fool.
This was all a trick.
What better way
to crush your spirits
than to make you think
we were actually friends?
( evil laugh )
My spirits are crushed.
Now...
before an audience
of billions,
I will finally
destroy you.
You're putting me
on your TV show?
Oh, that's awful
sweet of you.
What? No.
Don't step on my lines.
( crowd cheering )
HATER: Nooooo!!
( cheering continues )
Ugh. Lame.
ANNOUNCER:  It's
the Mystery Kids Mysteries.
This week, the gang
solves the case of...
Mavis' haunted
sweatshirt.
Crikeys!
( nervous shivering )
( growling )
Driving. Mysteries.
Ruff, ruff.
Ruff. I'm a dog, dudes.
( laughing )
Now that's a cartoon.
Hi, boys and girls.
I'm TV's Wander.
Lord Hater sure wanted
that staff of power,
but what he really wanted
all along
was a friend.
Actually, that was
just a trick
to destroy you,
Wander.
Oh, right.
But he sure worked hard
to get there,
and if you work hard, too...
Not really.
His Watchdogs did
most of the fightin' for him.
Oh, right.
So then the lesson was...
uh...
Don't know.
It sure was funny, though.
WANDER:  But there's nothin'
funny about bicycle safety.
Always wear
a helmet.
That's just
good horse sense.
( both laughing )
Probes, get in here.
Oh, please tell me
one of you found
a non-lame planet
to dominate.
We're running low on
Volcanium X.
You, Bot 42,
show me what you've got.
Scouting Measlon 3.
Trace elements
detected.
Population zero.
Seriously?
Just one planet?
And this useless hunk of rock
is the best you've got?
I wouldn't even get
out of bed to destroy this.
Recommendation:
Do not dominate.
Gee, ya think?
Bot 13, show this
poor, pathetic bot
how it's done.
Scouted: Thebulon 9.
Volcanium X detected.
Scouted: Strualiax.
Scouted: Aggrothia.
Volcanium X detected.
Recommendation:
dominate
Yes! That is what
I'm talkin' about.
Why can't the rest of you
be more like Bot 13?
As for you,
you've disappointed me
for the last time.
Now the rest of you,
get back to work!
Affirmative,
Lord Dominator.
Target acquired.
Seacironicus 12.
Commence scouting protocol.
Sylvia, look.
Sylvia, look at me!
Sylvia,
you're not looking!
That's nice, Wander.
After all the running
we've been doing lately,
I'm gonna make the most
of this place
before Dominator
wrecks it, too.
Good golly,
I am so sorry.
Are you...
( gasps )
A Dominator probe?
Still, the poor guy sure looks
like he needs some help.
Hello there.
You okay?
What's your name?
- ( probe beeping )
- Beep Boop, huh?
Nice to meet you,
Beep Boop.
Folks call me Wander.
What brings you round
these parts?
( beeping )
( distorted voice )
Explore planet.
Identify planet's
valuable resources.
Hey, me, too.
Aw, you don't
seem so bad.
- Wanna be travel pals?
- ( beeping )
Sylvia, I'd like
you to meet--
Wander, buddy,
I promise to be
super interested
after my post-sleep nap.
Why don't you go
check out the boardwalk?
Sure thing, Syl.
Come on, Beep Boop.
Yeah, beep boop,
wazzle fazzle.
Whatever...
A vacation's twice as fun
when you have
a travel pal
to share it with.
Scanning for
Volcanium X.
( distorted )
Volcanium X detected.
Great idea,
Beep Boop.
I love games.
Volcanium X detected.
Hmm.
I really think
it's that one.
Oh, well,
better luck next time.
Volcanium X.
Eggs? Oh,
you're hungry.
It's kind of hot
for eggs,
but I know
just what you need.
Analyzing.
Sample consists of
sugar,
dairy substances,
c-c-corn syrup.
Ice cream isn't just
a bunch of ingredients.
It's the smiles
of children.
The joy of a delicious
cold treat on a hot day.
The best things in life
are more than just
a list of their parts.
But between
you and me,
the secret ingredient
is love!
Volcanium X detected.
What is it,
travel pal?
Volcanium X detected.
Oh, I get it.
Oh, you look great!
- Let's try on everything!
- Negative, negat...
♪ ♪
Whoo-hoo!
Beep Boop, you've been
such an amazing travel pal,
so I got you
a present.
I saw how much
you wanted it,
so I went back
and I won it for you.
Volcanium X!
Wander, where are you, buddy?
( gasps )
A Dominator bot?
Wander, no!
Well, hey, Sylvia.
Meet my friend Beep Boop.
Friend?
That hunk of metal
is one of Dominator's
probes.
Well, sure,
on the outside.
And on the inside,
it's all lava and lasers,
and a computer brain
programmed only for destruction.
He also likes ice cream,
and making silly faces, and--
Wander! That thing
is gonna signal Dominator
to come destroy
this planet with
us on it.
Oh, Beep Boop
loves this place.
He would never
do anything...
Volcanium X obtained.
System repair
in progress.
...like that.
Beep Boop!
Stop!
Please don't leave.
We had so much fun today,
didn't we?
We could have fun
tomorrow, too,
if you wanted.
Beep Boop!
Get a grip, buddy.
That's an evil robot.
He's not evil.
He's my pal,
and he'll be back.
- I know it.
- Yeah, back to destroy
this planet.
We need to warn people
to get outta here
before Dominator
shows up.
I'm not leaving
without Beep Boop.
Wander.
Bot 13, report.
You better have
something good for me.
What? No way!
No one planet has
that much Volcanium X.
( evil laugh )
With all that, I could power
my entire army forever!
Bot 13,
you are the man!
I am gonna
rock this world.
Literally. I'm gonna turn it
into a rock about this big.
Where is the place?
Bot 13,
display coordinates.
Bot 13?
Bot 13, I said
display coordinates.
Access your stupid memory chip,
and download your data file.
I built you,
and I can unbuild you,
you bucket of bolts.
The best things in life
are more than just
a list of their parts.
Bot 13!
- I am Beep Boop.
- What?!
No. No! No, no, no, no, no!
Cancel deletion.
No, reverse, reverse!
Noooo!!
You ruined everything!
You... you...
you piece of junk!
Oh, what a disappointment.
I am Beep Boop.
( voice distorts )
I thought Beep Boop
would be back by now.
Hm, so did I.
Buddy, don't
you see?
He didn't sell us out
to Dominator after all.
Maybe you really did
get through to that bot.
Huh. I guess so.
Hey, look,
a shooting star.
Make a wish.
Good luck,
Beep Boop.