♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder,
wander over, over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
SYLVIA: Wander!!
Sorry, Syl.
I was sure
Hater recycled.
What a shame.
It's gonna be a shame
if we're flattened
like... like...
- Like a piece of paper?
- Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Now find something
to get us out of here.
- Sylvia.
- What?
- This is it!
- Great.
- This will solve everything.
- Awesome, buddy.
This is sure to get
Dominator to like Lord Hater.
Wait, what now?
It's a love letter from
Hater to Dominator.
I just
knew it, Sylvia.
I knew he liked her.
I knew, I knew, I knew!
Wander, focus.
This is no time
for getting gushy.
Help me find
a way outta here.
Oh, sorry.
3-2-6-3-8-2-8.
Oh, I wonder
what it says.
But I dare not
open it,
for it is not
addressed to me.
But I bet it's
an elegant and eloquent list
of all of the things he finds
so fascinating about her.
Oh, yeah, like how she
heartlessly destroys
everything in her path.
Well, yeah, she can be
a bit of a pill,
but once we get
Hater's letter to her,
she'll realize
someone thinks she's special.
( kazoo fanfare )
Wander, why would
you want to get
those two terrible
terrors together?
♪ Daddy strummed hard ♪
♪ Mama strummed light ♪
♪ All the little babies
kept the beat all right, ooh ♪
( shivering )
Ugh! Wander, this is one of
those really, really bad ideas
that you're gonna do
no matter what, right?
Sylvia, I know that
this whole thing might
seem a bit loony,
but I have to do it.
Love depends
on it.
Okay, Sylvia, how do you
distract Wander
from a crazy plan?
( train whistle blows )
Wander! Runaway train!
SYLVIA: Help!
Someone please help me!
Don't worry, Sylvia.
I'll save you.
Gotcha.
Ooh, wow.
Thanks for that, buddy.
I really need
to be more careful.
I'm just glad
you're safe and sound.
And lucky for us, this
station is the perfect place
to help get
the letter to Dominator.
( kazoo fanfare )
Dominator bots.
If Wander finds out
they're here,
he's sure to turn himself
in to them
just to deliver
that stupid letter.
Gotta do something.
Say, pal,
what's the rush?
Why don't we
grab a bite?
I am starved.
( blubbering )
Ah, that was amazing.
I gotta tell you, buddy,
after that, I am
ready for...
( snoring )
No problem.
You get your rest,
and I'll get back
to playing...
( kazoo fanfare )
( blows raspberry )
Wander, no!
Uh, not so fast,
space commuters,
for it is I, um,
Something the So-and-So,
and, yeah, so I'm gonna be maybe
doing some evil, perhaps.
Maybe. So, uh...
( sighs )
Conquer the galaxy.
Yeah, um...
'cause that's
a thing, right?
Enslave everyone,
cackle, be all evil...
treasures steal...
Treasures... trains!
The trains.
I am gonna do...
something evil with the trains,
or, ya know,
whatever.
Oh, no, Wander.
Not Something the So-and-So.
Maybe you should
stop him.
It'll probably
take hours. Drat!
Now we will never
get that letter
to Dominator.
Excuse me,
Mr. So-and-So.
Normally, I would spend
at least 11 minutes
on this sort of thing,
but since love is
compelling me toward
another quest,
I'd just like to ask,
is this really what
you want to do with
your life?
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
Probably not.
Seemed like a good idea.
So I don't know.
Maybe not.
'Cause... yeah, sorry.
Thanks. Okay, bye.
Sorry. Bye.
Sorry.
( kazoo fanfare )
Wander, look.
Let's go find
a scary ghost monster.
It'll just turn out
to be Old Man Jenkins
in disguise.
Search for lost
antiquities?
We'll just end up in
a temple solving
a bunch of riddles,
dodging poison darts
and getting chased by
a giant boulder,
just to find out
that the greatest treasures
are friendship,
which we already knew.
Okay. Then how about
returning to places
we've already enjoyed?
Old Shlooshy, the Museum of
Giant Antiquities, Phunulon,
Shatterton, Ballzeria X,
the Statue of the
Galactic Guru.
Been there. Seen it.
Loved it. Loved it!
Seen it.
Been there.
Ye Olde Tiny
Candlestick Makers.
What?
That sounds like...
And we're definitely
going there after I
get this letter to Dominator.
( kazoo fanfare )
Wander, look,
a missing sock.
Is that baby lost?
What's in the box?
Who cares?
I sure could use
a cold drink.
Sylvia, you're not trying
to keep me from being...
Oh, stop you
from being...
Me? Wander, how could
you even...
I am so surprised.
No, I'm shocked.
I'm shocked and hurt.
Yes, I'm deeply,
maybe irreparably hurt,
that you could think
that I could ever, ever
ever stand in the way of...
Grop.
Wander, sometimes
you come up with crazy ideas
that I would classify
as, well, bad.
But I only say that
because you're my best friend,
and I'm worried
you'll get hurt.
You see where
I'm comin' from?
I sure do, Sylvia.
But I have to
ask you something.
Do you trust me?
( sighs )
Buddy, if you wanna
deliver that letter
to Dominator's ship,
well, I'll be with you
every step of the way.
Whoa. Whoa!
Sylvia, are you nuts?
We can't just go up
to Dominator's bots.
We'll get killed.
I was just gonna
put it in the mail.
- So now...
- I guess it's time for...
"Do you like me?
Check 1."
Who is this from?
All right, sir.
If we are
to have any hope
of stopping
Dominator's invasion force,
we need to use the most
powerful weapon of them all.
Please be giant lasers.
Please be giant lasers!
- Our brains.
- Doh!
I have recently been
experimenting
with the extremely rare,
extremely unstable isotope,
Frostonium 17.
If we expose Dominator
to a blast of Frostonium
at close range, the subsequent
exothermic process will--
Boring!
Boring?! Sir, this weapon will
neutralize not only Dominator,
but her ship
and entire army.
Yeah, but will it
impress her?
Rock her world?
Get her lava flowing?
No! The exact opposite.
- What?!
- Just watch.
HATER: Oh, no. The powerful
and beautiful Dominator
has conquered
another planet.
( falsetto ) Nobody
in the galaxy is strong
or hunky enough
to stop me.
Ha ha ha!
( normal voice )
Guess again, Dominator.
Prepare to surrender
and swoon. It's...
( falsetto )
That's so amazing,
and totally excellent!
( normal voice )
The H.A.T.E.R.V.
equipped with missile launcher,
punching fists,
grab-action claw, buzz-saws,
slime launcher,
laser beam, pizza shooter,
and more!!
Hey, babe, why don't you
come take a ride
on the Hater side?
( falsetto swooning )
The H.A.T.E.R.V.,
coming soon to a galactic
battlefield near you.
Potential choking hazard
for Kremlons and Mikkelops.
I love you, Hater.
I know.
I can't...
I don't...
Sir, do you wanna destroy
Dominator or marry her?
Both. So get the watchdogs
and build a full-size
one of these ASAP.
I gotta do
some push-ups real quick.
No. We are not building
the Haterv.
You're saying it wrong.
H.A.T.E.R.V.
Dominator's ship
is refueling on
the planet Argite 7.
We have a very narrow
window for action.
We can't waste any resources
on an oversized toy.
Toy?! No H.A.T.E.R.V.,
no Hater.
Handle the attack yourself.
Really?
You mean it?
Yep. You're gonna have
to lead the watchdogs alone.
Good luck with...
( growling )
Push forward.
No surrender.
Be ready.
As soon as our forces
reach Dominator,
we need to hit her with
the Frostonium at close range.
Wait. What is...
- Oh, no.
- Hey, Peepers.
Guess what!
He built it himself.
I built it myself!
Oh, yeah,
perfect entrance.
Show me the love,
baby.
( watchdogs yelling )
Um, hello.
Super cool guy with
totally tricked-out ride here.
Way cooler than
some stupid battle.
PEEPERS: Important battle.
Very important battle.
Uh, should
we restack?
I gotta get my ride
in her line of sight
for maximum impact.
Oh, I like stacking
though.
Hey, Dominator,
look at me.
Never mind.
Don't look.
Do over,
do over.
Hey, Dominator...
Ah, dang it!
Oh, my tailbone.
Nice.
Hey, Dominator.
No, no, no.
( sighs )
Okay, new plan.
Did she see
the cool part?
This is it, men.
We have her
full attention.
Oh! It's fine.
Play it cool, lover boy.
Stick to the plan.
Time to activate
flight mode!
Stupid thing.
Looked cooler
in the commercial.
Yeah, flight mode!
Come on, go higher!
Whoo-hoo!
Hold formation.
Stay focused.
There's no room...
what was that?!
Hey, Dominator,
look at my...
cool thing;
it can totally...
fly!!
Why isn't she looking?
It's like all she cares about
is stopping you guys.
Tell me about it!
Time to pull out
the big guns.
Literally.
Hey, Dominator,
check this out!!
( Hater screaming )
( sighs )
Okay.
New new plan.
What... what happened?
Oh, no,
the H.A.T.E.R.V.
Whew. Good as new.
Come on, men, we're almost
at the top.
This is going to work!
I can't feel
my feet.
Man, she is really playing
hard to get.
It's time to activate...
boat mode!
( panting )
- ( air hisses )
- ( frustrated yell )
Yeah! Boat mode!
Why is nobody paying
attention to me?
Dominator, look.
Look now.
Look at my ooze
and saws and pizza.
Uh-oh. No matter.
Time for Sub Mode!
Peepers, there is
no sub mode.
Save me!
Find a way that doesn't
make me look stupid
in front of Dominator.
Should we help him?
No. Don't help him.
With Lord Lovesick
out of the way,
we can finally
finish this thing.
Go, go, go!
♪ Commander Peeper ♪
( all screaming )
( Hater yelling )
BOTH: Watchdogs,
we're not giving up yet.
- Fix the H.A.T.E.R.V.
- Frostonium ray.
At once.
So do we fix
the freeze ray thing
or the car thing?
- Car!
- Ray!
Sir, I'm sorry, but Dominator
is never going to notice
- your Haterv.
- You're saying it
wrong on purpose.
In fact, it's pretty much
the only thing
on the battlefield
she's not paying attention to.
( gasps )
Oh, wait a second.
Sir, we can use
your car,
which Dominator considers
literally no threat at all,
to sneak the Frostonium
close to her.
The what now?
The Frostonium.
My plan.
The big presentation
I gave this morning.
Is it like
a cool gift for her?
Yes. It's a gift.
A very cool gift.
Just get close to her,
set it off,
and I promise
she'll be really impressed.
Okay, watchdogs,
this is it.
Coordinated
four-way ambush.
Land!
( watchdogs yelling )
Air!
Sea!
And H.A.T.E.R.V.!
Hey, babe, wanna come
take a ride on...
Hey, babe, why don't you come
take a ride on the Hater side?
ey, babe, why don't   you   come
ake a ride on the Hater side?
Hey, babe, why don't you come
take a ride on the Hater side?
I did it.
This is it.
( exhales loudly )
Hey, babe, ahem,
why don't you come take a...
on the right side?
Hey. Cool car.
What?
Uh, really?
You like it?
Oh, yeah.
The fists,
the pizzas.
The incredibly powerful
Frostonium weapon.
That was... gift.
I got you gift.
Oh, really?
In that case,
mind if I take it
for a spin?
Oh, yes, come on.
You got her.
Now set off
the Frostonium.
Come on, set it off.
Wait. What are you doing?
Don't give her the keys.
Don't let her drive it!
Retreat!!
( shrieking )
I love you.
Ugh, I know.
HATER: Peepers,
she likes my car.
( Peepers groans )
( sighs )
( whip cracks )