♪
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WANDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ YONDER WANDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( evil laughter )
♪ WANDER, WANDER, OVER, OVER
YONDER, YONDER ♪
♪ WONDER YONDER
♪ WANDER OVER YONDER
( snoring, whistling )
♪
( sighs )
WHAT A VIEW.
( alarm blaring )
Computer ( over P.A. ):
EMERGENCY BRIEFING!
ALL WATCHDOGS
REPORT TO HALL B.
EMERGENCY BRIEFING!
YES!
( screaming )
GUYS! WAKE UP!
( groans )
AW, COME ON, MAN.
SHUT UP, WESTLEY.
IT'S PROBABLY ANOTHER DRILL.
THIS IS NOT A DRILL!
GUYS! COME ON!
( Watchdogs yawning )
IS MOOSE UP?!
SOMEBODY WAKE UP MOOSE!
WAKE UP, MOOSE!
( groans )
GOOD ONE, MOOSE.
Westley: COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S KEEP IT MOVING.
RANK AND FILE. LET--
( groans )
UH, HEY, DOES ANYBODY
HAVE A STEPSTOOL?
OKAY, YEAH, THAT'S PROB--
THAT'S WHAT I FIGURED.
WATCHDOGS! OUR SENSORS
JUST DETECTED
TWO HIGH-PRIORITY TARGETS
ON A NEARBY PLANETOID!
THESE TWO ARE NUMBER ONE
AND NUMBER TWO ON LORD HATER'S
"MOST HATED" LIST.
THEY OPERATE AGAINST EVERYTHING
LORD HATER STANDS FOR...
ALL IN THE NAME
OF "HAVING FUN."
( growling )
FUN....
THEY'RE CUNNING,
DEVIOUS TRICKSTERS.
SHIFTLESS, INDOLENT,
AND THEY DON'T SHOWER
VERY OFTEN.
THEY ARE ENEMIES
OF THE HATER EMPIRE,
AND THAT MAKES THEM
YOUR  ENEMIES.
ENEMIES!
( growls )
AND EVEN THOUGH, TECHNICALLY,
WE  ARE THE BAD GUYS,
THESE TWO ARE THE REAL
BAD GUYS!
♪
( groans )
IF WE CAN STOP THESE TWO,
THERE WILL FINALLY BE NO ONE
TO STOP  US  FROM SPREADING FEAR
AND HATE THROUGHOUT
THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE!
( all chanting )
HATE'S GREAT!
BEST VILLAIN!
Westley: BEST VILLAIN!
( chanting continues )
HATE'S GREAT!
BEST VILLAIN! HATE'S GREAT!
( chanting stops )
BEST VILLAIN!
( groans )
( Westley groaning )
♪
GUYS! GUYS!
( groans )
( Westley yelling )
WOW! WANDER AND SYLVIA!
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
WHAT AN EXCITING DAY!
( groaning )
( gun squeaks )
( grunting )
( groans )
OH, MAN,
WHAT IF  I  CAPTURED THEM?
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
I BET I'D GET TO MEET
LORD HATER HIMSELF.
YEAH. HE'D PROBABLY
GIVE YOU A MEDAL OR SOMETHIN'.
( Watchdogs snickering )
A MEDAL!
MY WHOLE LIFE...
WOULD BE...
COMPLETE.
♪ WESTLEY
♪ YOU'RE THE BEST-LEY
♪ IT'S THE MEDAL OF EVIL
( Watchdogs chanting )
WESTLEY! WESTLEY! WESTLEY!
( dreamily )
WOW...
( screaming )
( groaning )
( groans )
( Watchdogs chanting )
HATE'S GREAT! BEST VILLAIN!
HATE'S GREAT!
BEST VILLAIN!
( Westley groaning )
( chanting continues )
( weakly )
HATE'S...GREAT.
BEST...VILLAIN.
( sighs )
THIS IS THE LIFE.
HUH, PAL?
SURE IS,
ALTHOUGH THE WEATHER
LOOKS TO BE CHANGIN' SOON.
( birds chirping )
( Wander strumming banjo )
( loud, rhythmic thudding )
WATCHDOGS!
( Wander scatting )
( all yelling )
WAIT! GUYS!
LORD HATER! MEDAL!
( panting )
♪
( weapons zapping )
BOING BOING?
( Wander shouting )
WAH-HOO!
( all yelling )
( groaning )
HEY, GUYS!
DON'T WORRY!
I'M COMING!
OH, BOY.
( sighs )
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
HATE'S GREAT!
BEST VILLAIN!
( groans, yells )
( all groaning
and murmuring )
Peepers:
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
OF ALL THE INCOMPETENT,
BUNGLING, INEPT,
AMATEURISH, BUSH-LEAGUE
TROOPS IN THE UNIVERSE!
( Westley panting )
WAIT! YOU FORGOT...
( dejectedly )
ME.
AW. LOOK AT HIM THERE,
ALL SAD AND HELPLESS.
CAN WE KEEP HIM?
PLEASE?
WHAT?! NO WAY!
WANDER, THAT AIN'T
SOME LOST CRITTER.
THAT IS A WATCHDOG,
A TRAINED KILLER, A--
COMMANDER PEEPERS!
SIR! THIS IS PRIVATE
WESTLEY REPORTING IN!
( garbled radio transmission )
NO. N-NOT LESLIE.
WESTLEY, WITH A "W,"
AS IN "WANDER."
ANYWAY, YOU KIND OF,
UM, LEFT ME BEHIND.
COULD YOU COME PICK ME UP?
( garbled radio transmission )
NO, SIR. I-I-I HAVEN'T
CAPTURED WANDER AND SYLVIA.
THAT'S NOT THE  ONLY  REASON
YOU'D COME BACK FOR ME, RIGHT?
( garbled radio transmission )
WELL, MAYBE BECAUSE I'M A GOOD
SOLDIER AND YOU LIKE ME?
( Peepers laughing
over radio )
SO, UH, JUST
TO BE TOTALLY CLEAR,
I SHOULD N-NOT BE EXPECTING
A PICKUP?
( Peepers laughing
over radio )
( bird squawks )
( sighs )
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
JUST DO WHAT I DO.
OH, NO! A WATCHDOG!
HOW DREADFUL!
( sighs )
( flatly )
I HOPE HE DOES NOT
TAKE US PRISONER
AND THEN USE US TO MAKE HATER
COME AND RESCUE HIM.
THAT TRULY WOULD BE A DARK DAY
FOR WANDER AND SYLVIA.
OKAY!
REACH FOR THE SKY!
COMMANDER PEEPERS, SIR!
PRIVATE WESTLEY REPORTING IN!
AGAIN!
( garbled radio transmission )
WESTLEY.
WE JUST TALKED,
LIKE, TWO MINUTES AGO.
( garbled radio transmission )
NEVER MIND.
I'M HAPPY TO REPORT
THAT  I'VE  CAPTURED
WANDER AND SYLVIA.
( Peepers laughing
over radio )
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
I DID. I TOTALLY DID.
THEY'RE MY PRISONERS
AND EVERYTHING.
( garbled radio transmission )
FLOPPY HAT,
BIG, GOOFY GRIN,
AND A DUMPY, GRUMPY ZBORNAK.
"DUMPY"?
POOR LITTLE FELLA.
HE'D NEVER MAKE IT
OUT HERE ALL BY HIS LONESOME,
ESPECIALLY WITH THE WEATHER
CHANGING REAL SOON.
( squeaks )
WEATHER? WHAT DOES WEATHER
HAVE TO DO--
BOOP.
( whinnies )
Westley: YES, SIR.
I PROMISE YOU I HAVE THEM.
( garbled radio transmission )
THANK YOU, SIR.
GREAT. I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
OKAY, PRISONERS.
WE HAVE TO MEET
LORD HATER'S SHIP
ON THE TOP OF THAT MOUNTAIN
TOMORROW MORNING.
TOMORROW? THERE?!
HE CAN'T JUST FLY
TO MEET YOU RIGHT NOW?
HE'S VERY BUSY WITH IMPORTANT
APPOINTMENTS, OKAY?
OTHERWISE, HE TOTALLY WOULD.
( gun hums )
NOW MARCH!
LOOK, HATER'S
COMING TO GET HIM.
HE'LL BE FINE ON HIS OWN
FOR ONE DAY.
LET'S JUST GET OUT OF HERE.
I SAID, "MARCH"!
( yelling )
Westley: I'M OKAY!
I-I ACTUALLY
JUST SEEM TO BE STUCK
ON THE SAME BRANCH!
JUST DON'T--
YOU'RE STILL MY PRISONERS,
OKAY?!
( sighs )
I'LL GET THE FISHING POLE.
♪
ISN'T THIS THE MOST AMAZING
OF AMAZING DAYS,
WESTLEY, OLD PAL?
( sighs )
I MEAN, LOOK AT THIS PLACE!
LOOK AT THAT CRAZY GUY...
AND THAT THING.
( indistinct ) ALL ABOUT.
Wander: BET YOU DON'T GET A
CHANCE TO SEE THIS KIND OF THING
VERY MUCH, DO YOU, WES?
Westley: STOP!
( rapid electronic
beeping )
( bats chittering )
( device buzzing )
( beeping )
( buzzing )
OH, WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT!
YA KNOW, IF WE TAKE
THAT PATH OVER THERE,
I BET WE'D GET TO SEE
SOME INCREDIBLE THINGS.
COULD BE A LOT OF FUN...
( excited quavering )
( imitating retching )
I'M NOT HERE TO HAVE  FUN.
I'M HERE TO CAPTURE
MY  ENEMIES,
A COUPLE OF REAL
BAD GUYS,
FOR LORD HATER
AND ALSO GET A MEDAL.
BESIDES, I DON'T NEED YOUR
NATURE-LOVING WISDOM.
I HAVE THE KNOWLEDGE
OF THE HATER EMPIRE
IN MY HANDS,
AND IT SAYS WE GO LEFT.
( birds chirping )
LEFT.
REMIND ME WHY WE HAVE TO WATCH
OUT FOR THIS WHACK-A-DOODLE.
HEY, COME ON.
THIS ISN'T YOURS.
( groans )
( critter squeaking )
NICE TRY, NATURE!
BACKUP LOCATOR.
( monkey hooting )
HATER REGULATION 85--
ALWAYS CARRY
AN EXTRA BACKUP.
THIS ONE HAS A HANDY
WRIST STRAP.
( yelling )
♪
( Westley groaning )
( groaning )
( groans )
OUT OF THE WAY!
I'M NOT A DOCTOR!
PULSE PULSING.
HEART YEARNING.
BLOOD PRESSURE 2,000
OVER 13.
EYE, BEAUTIFUL.
REFLEXES FLEXING.
STEP ASIDE.
THIS MAN NEEDS C.P.R.!
GET OFF!
I'M FINE!
I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
I WAS JUST HAVING FUN,
IS ALL.
BUT IF YOU ASK ME, YOU COULD
USE AN ATTITUDE ADJUSTMENT.
THAT'S ENOUGH!
NOW MARCH!
WE CAN'T KEEP HATER WAITING.
AH! AH!
THIS WAY.
( squeaking )
( sloshing )
HUH?!
AAH!
( yelling )
AW. MY LITTLE BITTY BLASTER.
HEY! COME ON!
GIVE IT BACK!
( grunting )
( growls )
( gun hums )
WAH!
( Westley panting )
( gun hums )
COME ON, WESTLEY!
YOU CAN DO IT!
( whimpering )
ALMOST THERE, BIG GUY.
AAH...
Wander: GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
OH, YOU'RE SO CLOSE.
( quavering )
ATTABOY!
YAY!
OH, GOOD! YOU DID IT!
ALL RIGHT!
YEAH!
YOU DID IT!
( gun hums )
( insects chirping )
AW. YOU KNOW, HE'S--
HE'S ACTUALLY KINDA CUTE
WHEN HE'S NOT--
( gun hums )
♪
WE MADE IT!
YES!
Sylvia: WESTLEY, WE SHOULD
PROBABLY STICK TO THE TRAIL.
NOPE! SORRY!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH
OF YOUR SO-CALLED FUN.
( growling )
( roaring )
( Westley screams )
( Westley screaming )
( creature roaring )
( yelling )
( yelling continues )
( Wander and Sylvia laughing )
HUH?
YA-HOO!
( Wander and Sylvia laughing )
( Westley laughs )
Westley:
CLIFF! CLIFF! CLIFF!
( creature roaring )
DO THAT AWESOME
JUMPY THING.
THAT'LL STOP HIM!
"STOP"?
O-KAY!
( brakes squealing )
( steam hisses )
WHOO! THAT WAS AMAZING!
( splashing )
HEY, MAN, THANKS
FOR LEADING ME TO THIS RIVER.
THE OLD FIRE-MANE
WAS FLARING UP AGAIN.
HAPPENS WHENEVER I GET
TO THINKING ABOUT STUFF
THAT MAKES ME ALL MAD.
I JUST--FOOM!
THEN I'M ALL "RAH!"
YOU KNOW?
( chuckling )
THAT OR WHEN I HAVE
TOO MUCH DAIRY.
WELL, SEE YA.
Wander: WELL HOW ABOUT THAT?
SOMETIMES IT TURNS OUT
YOUR ENEMY'S NOT SUCH
A BAD GUY AFTER ALL.
NO! YOU THINK I CAN'T
TELL WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'RE JUST BEING NICE TO ME
BECAUSE YOU WANT ME
TO BETRAY LORD HATER.
HE SAID YOU WERE CUNNING,
DEVIOUS TRICKSTERS,
AND HE'S RIGHT.
YOU  ARE  BAD GUYS.
WELL, TOUGH BANANAS.
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
"TOUGH BANANAS"?
WESTLEY, WE'RE HELPING YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE OUR FRIEND.
WE LIKE YOU.
RIGHT, SYLVIA?
HUH? OH, YEAH!
YEAH, YOU'RE A PRETTY
OKAY GUY, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU'RE...ASLEEP.
OH, SURE.
EVERYBODY'S  FRIENDS.
YOU'RE  MY FRIENDS.
THAT FIRE LION WAS MY FRIEND.
THIS GIANT COBRA-BEAR
IS MY FRIEND.
( cobra-bear hissing )
. NOT YOUR FRIEND.
UH-UH.
( hissing )
( roaring )
( snoring )
Sylvia: THANK GOODNESS
YOU DISCOVERED THAT
COBRA-BEAR'S WEAKNESS.
Wander:
I KNOW  I  CAN'T KEEP ANYTHING
DOWN WHEN  I'M  BEING TICKLED.
WHA--I DON'T--
HUH?
Westley: I KNEW IT.
THEY WERE JUST WAITING
UNTIL I WAS ASLEEP
SO THEY COULD TAKE MY BLASTER
AND DO WHO KNOWS WHAT KIND
OF HORRIBLE THINGS.
( growling )
( groans )
( yelling )
( gun hums )
( plucking )
( yelling )
( gun hums )
( Wander strumming banjo )
( grunts )
( gun hums )
( stomach growling )
( loud slurping )
( gun hums )
AHH.
( continues strumming )
( gun hums )
( stomach growling )
OH. GOOD. SO GOOD.
MMM.
( continues munching )
( slurping loudly )
( wind whistling )
YOU WERE RIGHT, BUDDY.
WEATHER'S DEFINITELY CHANGING.
♪
( birds chirping )
( yawns )
HUH?
( sighs )
WHAT A VIEW.
YEAH.
MORNIN', PAL?
MORNIN'.
( slurping )
( yelling )
THIS BETTER BE WORTH IT,
PEEPERS!
I HAD A BRUNCH TODAY!
I'M SORRY, SIR.
I JUST THOUGHT IT
WAS WORTH CHECKING OUT.
IF HE DOESN'T SHOW UP
WITH WANDER AND SYLVIA
IN FIVE SECONDS,
WE'RE LEAVING!
FIVE--HATER'S AWESOME--
FOUR--HATER'S AWESOME--
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE GUY.
ENJOY YOUR LIFE
OF EVIL AND NEFARIOUSNESS.
IT'S BEEN A BLAST,
BUT WE ARE OUT OF HERE.
YA KNOW, THERE'S A VIEW
UP AHEAD
THAT'S ABOUT A GAZILLION
TIMES NICER THAN THIS ONE.
WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH US?
♪
TWO--HATER IS AWESOME!
ONE--HATER'S AWESOME!
I'M SORRY, SIR!
I KNEW HE WASN'T
WATCHDOG MATERIAL.
Peeper: I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE EVEN SENT HIM
ON THIS MISSION!
NO.
I'M NOT COMING WITH YOU.
YOU'RE  COMING WITH ME!
( Watchdogs chanting )
WESTLEY! WESTLEY!
STUPID,
UNPREDICTABLE WEATHER.
Lord Hater: PRIVATE WESTLEY,
TODAY, YOU HAVE
MADE US ALL TRULY PROUD.
FOR YOUR TOTALLY EVIL DEED
OF CAPTURING WANDER
AND SYLVIA,
I AM PROUD
TO PRESENT YOU
THE OFFICIAL HATER
MEDAL OF EVIL!
♪ IT'S THE MEDAL
OF EVIL ♪
♪ YOU DESERVE--
NO LONGER WILL WANDER
AND SYLVIA
BE FREE TO SPREAD
THEIR DANGEROUS,
FUN-LOVING WAYS
THROUGHOUT THE GALAXY!
ACTUALLY--
( flatly )
HATE'S GREAT.
BEST VILLAIN.
♪ HATE'S GREAT,
BEST VILLAIN ♪
( all chanting )
WESTLEY! WESTLEY! WESTLEY!
( chanting continues )
♪ WESTLEY
♪ YOU'RE THE BEST-LEY
( snoring and whistling )
( alarm blaring )
LORD HATER! WAKE UP!
( groaning,
mumbling indistinctly )
Peepers:
THERE'S BEEN AN EXPLOSION
ON THE PRISON LEVEL!
WHAT?! W-WHAT HAPPENED?
WE'RE NOT SURE.
I'M HAVING THE SECURITY FOOTAGE
FROM THE PAST HOUR
UPLOADED NOW.
Lord Hater:
OH, YES, THAT'S VERY GOOD.
A LOCKED CELL.
NOTHING UNUSUAL HERE.
WHAT?! WANDER
AND SYLVIA ESCAPED?!
SOUND THE ALARM!
OH, LOOK, IT'S WESTLEY!
GET 'EM, WESTLEY!
YOU GOT THIS, LITTLE GUY!
YEAH! UH,
BLAST 'EM, WESTLEY!
PEW! PEW!
( beeping )
WESTLEY, NO! WATCH OUT!
THERE'S A BOMB!
Lord Hater:
NO! NOT WESTLEY!
I'M GONNA--
( clears throat )
I'M GONNA NEED A MOMENT
WITH THIS.
( sobbing )
WESTLEY...
( Lord Hater clears throat )
TODAY WE HONOR
OUR BAD FRIEND WESTLEY.
WE DID NOT KNOW HIM LONG.
( whispering indistinctly )
...three years.
WE KNEW HIM SEVERAL YEARS.
AND NEVER BEFORE
HAD A WATCHDOG
DISPLAYED SUCH...
M-MALICE,
( voice breaking )
SUCH CONTEMPT...
SUCH...CRUELTY.
HE SINGLE-HANDEDLY
CAPTURED MY MOST
HATED ENEMIES.
WE--
WE MAY NEVER KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
( choking up )
BUT WE WILL--
WE WILL ALWAYS--
( clears throat )
KNOW...
( sobbing )
HE TRULY WA--
A BAD GUY!!!
( sobbing loudly )
DON'T LOOK AT ME!
( sobbing )
( door slams )
♪
YOU THINK
WE GOT AWAY WITH IT?
WELL, WE'RE STILL SITTING HERE,
AREN'T WE?
OF COURSE IT WORKED!
I'VE BEEN STUDYING
HATER'S SHIP.
ALL HIS CAMERAS WILL SEE
IS ME GETTING SUCKED
OUT INTO SPACE
TRYING TO STOP YOU GUYS.
I'LL PROBABLY BE REMEMBERED
AS A HERO
OR SOMETHING DUMB LIKE THAT.
♪ OH, WANDER
♪ OVER YONDER
♪ AND CHECK OUT
THIS AND THAT ♪
♪ IF YOU WANDER
OVER YONDER ♪
♪ BEST BE SURE
TO WEAR YOUR HAT ♪
♪ ALL THE THING
THAT YOU WILL SEE ♪
♪ AND YOU CERTAINLY
WILL BE FREE ♪
♪ IF YOU WANDER OVER YONDER,
JUST YOU AND ME ♪
AAH!
♪ IF THE DARKNESS
COMES A-CREEPIN' ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE FEELING DOWN
♪ JUST WANDER OVER YONDER
♪ AND TURN YOUR LIFE AROUND
♪ OH, WANDER
♪ OVER YONDER
♪ BE SURE TO LEND A HAND
♪ ALL YOUR HELPFUL
♪ FRIENDLY GOOD DEEDS
♪ WILL SPREAD
ACROSS THE LAND ♪
♪ ALL YOUR HELPFUL,
FRIENDLY GOOD DEEDS ♪
♪ WILL SPREAD
ACROSS THE LAND ♪
Westley: ♪ DOODDLEY DOOT
DA DOOT DOOT ♪
WHOO!
( song ends )
♪ WESTLEY, YOU WERE
THE BEST-LEY ♪
( Lord Hater sobbing loudly )
♪ OUR NUMBER-ONE WATCHDOG
♪ WESTLEY, YOU
WERE THE BEST-LEY ♪
♪ OUR NUMBER-ONE WATCHDOG
Peepers: THERE, THERE, SIR.
WE'RE ALL GONNA MISS WESTLEY.
HUH?! I'M UPSET BECAUSE WANDER
AND SYLVIA GOT AWAY AGAIN!
WHO'S WESTLEY?!
( Lord Hater sobbing loudly )