♪♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
All right!
Hater!
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder ♪
PEEPERS: Oh, no.
If the Black Cube gets
the Ring of Invincibility,
he'll be unstoppable.
( laughter )
- ( knocking at door )
- Cube! Hey, Cube!
I know you're
in there.
Where's my rent,
blockhead?
( loud chanting )
Oh, no, you ain't pullin'
that soul-sucking
Latin mumbo-jumbo again.
E pluribus
you owe me money, Cube.
You got 24 hours,
or you're out on
your hexahedronic heinie.
Got it?
Ah, that's what I get
for renting to
a has-been villain.
♪ I'm just
a little black cube ♪
♪ Of darkness,
♪ Of darkness ♪
♪ Black cube
of darkness ♪
♪ A little black cube ♪
♪ My edges are sharp ♪
♪ My corners are pointy ♪
♪ My complexion's opaque ♪
♪ Just looking, yeah, looking
for a place to fit in ♪
♪ But I'm never
the right shape ♪
( phone rings )
( answering machine
beeps )
WOMAN:  Hi, Cube.
It's Stacy.
Listen.
We have to break up.
I mean, I'm a nice girl,
you're a concentrated block
of pure evil.
It's just not
a good fit.
Bye.
( machine beeps again )
♪ I'm just
a little black cube ♪
♪ Of darkness ♪
♪ A little black cube
of darkness ♪
♪ A little black
cube of darkness ♪
♪ A little black cube ♪
Good morning.
Need a hand?
( Cube chants angrily )
Wander, that is
the Black Cube
of Darkness.
We gotta get outta here
before he sucks out
our souls.
Aw, Syl, it never
hurts to help.
Do you know how often
you say that
immediately before
we actually get hurt?!
( angry chanting )
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey there, friend.
Yeah, you.
Having a rough day?
Been there.
But take it from me,
a bad attitude only
makes it rougher.
Learn to let go
of anger,
and you won't
have to suffer.
It's a beautiful day.
♪ Listen to the birds sing,
look at the sunshine ♪
♪ Let them be your guide,
and you'll be feelin' fine ♪
( celestial choir
vocalizing )
That's the spirit.
♪ Takin' a positive
attitude now ♪
♪ Won't let things
drag me down ♪
♪ Folks start to panic,
I won't get all manic ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm floating
off the ground ♪
♪ My contours are sleek,
my surface is shiny ♪
♪ Nothing gets in my way ♪
♪ My upbeat composure's
gonna help me find closure ♪
♪ What a wonderful day ♪
♪ I'm a little black cube
of sunshine ♪
♪ A black cube
♪ Black cube of sunshine ♪
- ♪ A little black cube ♪
- ♪ He's a little black cube ♪
( screaming )
( whistling )
( horns honking )
Look at this joker.
He's all, like,
"Good day to you, sir.
I am a shape."
What a square.
It's funny 'cause
he's different from us.
Oh, my stars and garters.
Oh, why, thank you
so much.
What a polite young...
( shrieks )
It's the villainous
Black Cube of Darkness.
He's come to steal
my soul.
Help, police! Help!
Well, well, well.
Look who finally decided
to show up for his shift.
You're lucky I need you
on the register,
or I'd kick you out on your
parallelepiped posterior.
Now get out there!
What a coinky-dink.
Hello again.
Uh, yeah, hi.
I trust you enjoyed
your brisk morning walk.
I can't believe
you work here.
You are so lucky.
What a noble profession--
feeding the hungry,
brightening up people's day.
I would like
a triple pickle pie
and the honor of
providing you
with a gratuity
for all of your fine work.
Ahem.
What a coinky-dink.
If it isn't
our old friend.
Let's see.
I'll take a quadruple splatty
melt, no cheese,
no pickles, extra cheese,
seven pickles...
ketchup, catsup, no sesame seeds
of the top bun,
glue 'em onto the bottom bun,
throw out the bun
and put the whole thing
in a wrap,
a jumbo extra-small half-curly
half-straight fries,
and a diet
Thunderblazz.
Now my associate
will have...
You know
you're fired, right?
♪ Actin' all chummy,
try to help out somebody ♪
♪ But they freak out,
then I freak out ♪
♪ Try to make conversation,
but before I am able ♪
♪ Well, I freak out ♪
♪ Then they freak out ♪
♪ Black cube
of darkness ♪
♪ Little black cube
♪ Black cube
of darkness ♪
♪ Little black cube ♪
Oh, look at me.
I'm having a sad moment
of soul searching.
( derisive laughter )
Must've lost
his edge.
Cubes have edges.
Ooh, I'm so scared.
Look, I'm chicken, too.
Ooh, what a loser.
( laughs )
Help me. Help me!
He spent so much time
working on sick burns
that he never
learned to swim.
What are we gonna do?!
Ew! Get your cube
off of me, you cube.
I don't want your...
What... what happened?
Oh, my grop.
He totally sucked out
your soul!
That was your plan
the whole time, wasn't it?
In fact, I think maybe
you pushed me off that bridge.
♪ Take a deep breath,
don't do anything crazy ♪
♪ Just don't freak out,
no, don't freak out ♪
♪ It's a misunderstanding ♪
♪ Sure that they'll
understand it ♪
♪ Unless they don't
♪ They never do
understand it ♪
♪ But don't freak out ♪
♪ Never freak out ♪
( voice distorts )
We gotta help him, Syl.
Wander, no. Wait.
Black cube, please,
don't freak out.
Wander!
This is all your fault!
He was only trying
to help you.
How could you
do this to him?
You should all be
ashamed of yourselves.
This guy saved
that kid's life.
All he wanted
was to be a good guy for once,
but you're all so focused
on the bad stuff
that you never looked for
the good stuff inside him.
I mean, heck, after what
you all put him through,
I don't blame him
for freaking out.
Haven't any of you
ever had a lousy day?
My twin brother forgot
to call me on my birthday.
to call me on  my  birthday.
I didn't make
the soccer team.
I did make the soccer team,
but I hate soccer.
I'm suffering from
a distinct case of ennui.
Also, I use words
I don't understand
to sound important.
And my best friend and I
are on the run
from a series of
evil villains,
but that doesn't mean
we go out and ruin
someone else's day.
Sometimes, the only solution
is to tell someone,
I'm sorry
you had a bad day.
♪ We're all just
little black cubes ♪
♪ Of darkness ♪
♪ Little black cubes
of darkness ♪
♪ Little black
cubes of darkness ♪
♪ Little black cubes ♪
Sector G, hall one,
all clear.
Sector G, hall two,
Sector G, hall three...
Oh! Hi.
I didn't see you there.
Hey, you know, you're not
really allowed in here.
Top secret security stuff.
( laughs )
But if you've ever
wondered about what keeps
Lord Hater's galactic
domination machine running,
well, then, you're in for
a real treat,
because it's time for...
This is
Eye On the Skull Ship.
I'm Andy,
your humble host,
and I'd like to welcome you
to a very special episode.
We all know that life
on the skull ship
can be tedious at times.
One routine work day
seamlessly blending into
the next.
But today
is going to be different.
Today, I'm proud
to bring you...
( imitates drum roll )
A one-on-one
with Lord Hater!
( chortles )
That's right.
I put in a formal request
to interview
our esteemed leader and...
- ( buzzer sounds )
- Oh, my gracious!
Maybe that's Hater now.
Okay.
Hello. You're live on
Eye On the Skull Ship
with Andy,
chief security monitor--
I know who you are,
Andy.
This is Commander Peepers.
Once again, your request
to interview Lord Hater
has been rejected on grounds
that it's not your job
to make this stupid show!
Well, it's not
my job, per se,
but you know, I think
it's my duty to help enlighten--
Just keep an eye
on your sector.
Yes, sir. Always do.
No, you don't!!
Well, slight change
of plans.
Looks like we won't be
talking to Lord Hater.
But fret not,
dear viewers.
I know you're
dying to see him,
and I won't give up
until I give you...
( stammering )
what you want.
In the meantime,
I bet you're wonderin'...
What's for lunch?
( sighs )
That's right.
It's the 453rd time
we find out
exactly what the Watchdogs
are eating for lunch.
Excuse me,
fellow Watchdog.
What refreshing
and replenishing meal
has been graciously
given to you
by our generous leader
Lord Hater?
Oh, wow.
Uh, hi.
Um, apparently, I have never
been on live television before,
and apparently,
I'm having enchiladas.
Apparently.
Fascinating.
- And what delicious--
- Enchiladas!
( all cheering )
Enchiladas!
Chef, tell us,
enchiladas.
Was this meal
specifically chosen
by Lord Hater's decree?
Uh... no.
Taco Tuesday
was yesterday,
so there was
leftovers,
and I decided
to make, uh,
enchiladas.
Hmm, interesting.
So does Lord Hater
like enchiladas?
I don't know.
All I know is, I didn't want
the stuff to go to waste,
so I reused it today.
Hm, yes.
But Lord Hater--
See, the thing with...
The thing with
ground beef is,
you gotta...
Self-defense, where
the Watchdogs closest to Hater,
his elite ground troops,
learn the fine art
of conquering.
And if we're lucky,
Lord Hater might make
a surprise pop-in
to inspect the troops.
To be the best takes
months of intense training
in areas like
Advanced Sylvia Defense...
And, of course,
Wander Avoidance Tactics.
I know he wants
to be your friend.
to play carnival games.
I know he knows
all your names,
and birthdays,
and how you like
to spend a rainy Sunday
with a crossword
and a cup of chamomile.
I mean, he is really
not such a bad guy.
No! Wander is pure,
unadulterated love.
I'm sure our resident
drill instructor
has a host of exciting
Hater stories
to share with us.
You're darn right I do.
One time...
Andy!
Why aren't you
at your post?
Uh, gotta go.
See you next time.
We are live from
Level H8,
Hater's private floor.
Only Watchdogs in
Hater's inner circle
are allowed on
this level.
I hope to speak with someone
close to the big man himself.
Though it's risky,
it's worth it,
because this is the story
every Watchdog is waiting for.
I wonder who we'll...
Oh, my gosh.
That was Captain Tim,
Lord Hater's personal pet.
This is a sure-fire
exclusive.
We're here with Lord Hater's
personal pet and dog walker.
Wow. What I wouldn't give
to work so closely
- with our great leader.
- Be my guest.
Welcome again to
Eye On the Skull Ship.
Thanks to some of the guys
in the infirmary,
I was able to secure
an exclusive place
at one of Hater's rallies!
Whoo... ow, ow!
( Hater speaking
indistinctly )
Fear not, viewers.
Though I can barely
see or hear
our esteemed leader,
I assure you,
I will get at least some of
the Hater coverage you demanded.
( Hater continues
speaking )
He's talking about
his hated rival Lord Dominator.
Boo!
And now he's saying...
he'll conquer... her heart?
That can't be right.
( Peepers shouting
indistinctly )
Well, Peepers seems to be
getting very upset about this.
Hater's pulling out what appears
to be some kind of...
It's the T-shirt cannon!
( groaning )
Oh... "I heart Dominator."
Oh, boy.
Hello, all.
After a serious close call
with Commander Peepers,
your humble host
has decided to do the show
entirely from the safety of
his security office,
so he won't get fired.
But you won't believe
who stopped by
for a little chat with us.
The one and only
Lord Hater!
Hi, Andy. It sure is
an honor to be here.
Huge fan of the show.
Really?
Oh, well, sir,
that really means
the world to me.
And each and every one
of you Watchdogs
mean the world
to me, Andy.
In fact, I'd like to thank
all the Watchdogs
for their
tireless service.
They're truly the backbone
of the skull ship, and...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm sorry, everyone.
I was a fool to think
I could give you
a good show.
I'll never get
a Lord Hater interview.
Hey, uh, my printer
stopped working.
It says I need toner.
Are you Toner?
I, uh... I, uh...
You do TV here?
( stammering )
Uh, yes, sir.
Unless that would
get me in trouble,
in which case, no.
How many people
watch your show?
- Oh, it goes out
all over.
- All over, huh?
Dear viewers, it is with
the deepest pride
that I present to you
the man, the myth,
the leader
I'm honored to serve.
The greatest
in the galaxy.
Lord Hater.
Lord Hater, how are you?
Good to be here,
Toner.
Listen up,
and listen good.
All you poser villains
out there
better recognize
who the G-est in the G is.
It's Lord Hater,
number one superstar.
You want a piece of me,
Emperor Dork-some?
Got beef, Sandwich?
Then bring it on,
losers.
I will lightning you
so hard
that you'll be all, like...
Oh, sir.
Excuse me.
How dare you interrupt
my righteous rant
to the galaxy?!
I'm sorry, sir.
It's just that,
you see,
when I said the show
went out all over,
I meant all over
the skull ship.
( nervous laughter )
Not the galaxy.
Wait. So who actually
watches this?
Well, I don't have
the exact figures handy.
It certainly has
the potential to be
viewed by,
you know, anyone
on the ship,
so mostly Watchdogs,
I think.
Watchdogs? You make
a show for Watchdogs?
That's the stupidest,
lamest thing ever!
I mean, really?
This show is stupid.
You're stupid.
You should both be cancelled.
Hater out.
Sector G, hall one,
all clear.
Sector G, hall two,
Sector G, hall three,
all clear.
Commander Peepers.
I promise I stopped
doing my stupid show.
Nothing is going on.
I know.
That's the problem.
Andy fan, best show!
Andy fan, best show.
The Watchdogs
are rioting.
Apparently, they wanna
watch your weird little
show about them.
They claim your interviews made
them feel special. Yuck!
Well, you mean, I didn't
need a Hater interview?
I was making the show
the Watchdogs wanted all along?
A show that made them
feel special?
Wow. I mean, that...
that makes me feel special.
Yeah, yeah, just make
your stupid show.
Enchiladas!
Welcome to
Eye On the Skull Ship,
the only show for Watchdogs,
about Watchdogs,
by a Watchdog,
for Watchdogs,
I am your humble host,
Andy the Watchdog,
and today, I am here with
Giuseppe,
the ship's tailor.
So what's your secret?
You see, the Watchdogs
have the very big heads,
and the very
skinny necks.
So it's all about
the stretchy shirts.
Then it's about the beanies
and the booties and the glovies.
If the Watchdogs
don't look good,
- Giuseppe no look good.
- Fascinating.
Yuck! Why would anyone
watch this?
I don't know, sir.
I just don't know.