♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
Used to be great
until Dominator showed up.
Stunning views until Dominator
set everything on fire.
Ruined by Dominator.
Dominator!
Huh. She must've
missed this one.
Oh, this is great.
This place is so small
and dark
that no one knows
it exists.
It's the perfect place
to hide from Dominator.
It sure is.
I'm gonna record a review,
and let everyone know
about this planet
so they can all come
and enjoy it, too.
No, not so fast, pal.
We can't tell anyone.
If word gets out,
then Dominator will show up
and ruin this place.
This has to be
our little secret, okay?
Sh!
Oh, a secret.
I can keep a secret.
It's no secret that
I am a great secret keeper.
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna go
figure out a shelter.
Just remember... sh!
( whispers )
Secret.
Oh, I'm sure they've
got things under control.
Yeah, they're fine.
What are
you doing?
Oh, nothing.
Just... doing a dance
to celebrate finding this still
totally secret planet.
Yeah, well, tone it down.
You haven't said anything about
this planet to anyone, have you?
Said   anything? No.
Good job, buddy.
Now why don't you help out
and gather some palm fronds
- for the thatching.
- Yes, perfect.
It will give me a chance
to go check on...
all the other secrets
this secret planet
has to offer.
Sh!
Hello.
Is everyone okay
over here?
Oh, it's the king
of the planet.
King? Oh, no, I'm not--
O gracious king,
have mercy on us.
We are but poor refugees
fleeing the crushing might
of Dominator.
Give us sanctuary,
we beg of you.
Well, of course
you can stay.
But can you keep
your voices down
just a little because--
The king has granted us
sanctuary.
Let us raise our voices
in tribute to
his graciousness.
Huzzah!
ALL: ♪ Hail to the king!
♪ Hail to the king!
Wise and generous king,
we have prepared a lavish feast
in your honor.
Well, that was
very kind of you
I really
don't want any...
The king is displeased
with the feast.
Prepare a bigger feast!
No, no. I meant...
( squealing )
It was very thoughtful
of you to prepare this feast,
and it will be quite
adequate for me
to satisfy
my kingly hunger.
I'm just going to go
eat this in the jungle.
If you please,
just keep it down.
(European accent )
Ugh, the service at
this resort is terrible.
We've been waiting
for at least two minutes.
I'm going to find
the manager.
I will give him
a piece of my mind.
Yes, and make a big,
loud fuss doing it.
Harumph. Harumph,
harumph!
Thank you for
your patience, monsieur.
If you'll come this way,
I will show you to
your table.
We saw your fire pit
as we were passing by.
This is a most charming
resort you have.
We are, of course,
Clancy and Nancy Schmancy
of the Fancy Schmancys.
We too are in
the resort business.
Oui.   Very good, monsieur.
Although I must ask you
to keep off the beach,
s'il vous plait,
as it is being...
sanded.
Is there anything else
I can do for you?
- Fruity drinks,   ja?
- Mm,   ja.
Excusez-moi.
Oop. Excuse me.
I don't mean to be a bother,
but would it be too much trouble
for you to whip me up
a couple of fruity drinks?
( yelling )
The king demands
fruity drinks!
Thank you.
This will do nicely.
We are your eternally
loyal subjects.
♪ Hail to the king,
hail to the king! ♪
♪ Hail to the king!
Hey, thanks, buddy.
I am parched.
( slurping )
Ah!
What are you wearing?
Nothin'.
Okay.
Still waitin' on
those palm fronds.
I'm gonna get you
those fronds.
Only the best fronds
for my best friend.
( dance music playing )
( squealing )
Ooh la la.
Much too bright for
such a lovely moonlit night, no?
Ahem.
The Fancy Schmancys
do not share.
Wow! Good thing we saw
that fire and that disco party,
or we totally would've
missed this secret and
exotic planet.
Dad, when are we gonna
see some animals?
DAD: Look, a wild
Zbornak.
Sh. Don't spook it
now, son.
( making monkey sounds )
Whoa, monkey!
Hey, that monkey
stole my juice box.
( insects chirping )
Danke.
Sacre bleu!
We'll put the pool here,
and the hot tubs over there,
and I think sun lamps
everywhere so it won't
be so dark all the time.
We are going to make this
the hottest new vacation spot.
If only there were
a real estate agent.
As you can see,
these distant foothills
are the perfect spot
for your resort.
Great views and plenty
of room for expansion.
And most importantly,
as far from the beach
as possible.
Ja,   that is perfect.
Whew!
- Men, blow up
the foothills.
- What?!
These are Dominator's spies,
sent to threaten our king.
Wander!
King disco monkey want
schmancy palm fronds!
What in flarnation
is going on?
Be right back.
Wander, are you keeping
secrets from me?
No. Yes. I mean,
I was trying to keep
the planet a secret,
but then there were
these people who needed help,
so I told them
about the planet,
and they built a fire
to me, their king,
and then more people came,
so in an attempt to keep
all of them secret
naturally I had to be
a waiter, a monkey,
and a real estate agent
and now
they're all fighting,
and it's all my fault
and I never did get you
those palm friends,
because I'm a bad frond,
but worst of all
I'm a big ol' liar.
Okay, I'm gonna pretend
I understood that,
and focus on
the problem at hand.
All this commotion
is gonna attract
Dominator's attention!
I don't think
we're attracting
that much attention.
Buddy, it's time to fess up
and fix all this.
I have a confession
to make.
I'm not really a king.
Waiter.
Monkey.
- Or real estate agent.
- ( gasps )
I'm just a goofy,
wandering wanderer
who wanders around
the galaxy
trying to help people
and make a mess of things
like I did today.
Sorry.
Wait. You're Wander?
We've heard tell of you.
- So have we.
-   Ja.
We all have.
You've helped
so many people.
How can we
help you?
( all screaming )
The lights!
The statue!
- ( all cheering loudly )
- Sh!
( cheering quietly )
WANDER: But how can folks
stay here now?
If we light the place up again,
Dominator will see us.
I've got a secret.
Ooh, that's nice,
Sylvia,
but I don't know how
we're all gonna...
Knowing you, I assumed
we'd have guests.
( happy squealing )
Help, Dominator.
Sanctuary.
What's the password?
The monkey stole
my juice box.
Best secret hideaway
ever!
Some secrets
are worth sharing.
Sir, what were you thinking,
giving Dominator flowers?
Girls are supposed
to like flowers.
It's her stupid fault
she doesn't know that.
Should've given her
a cooler gift,
like chocolates,
or maybe a toaster.
No. No presents
for the enemy.
( snoring )
Wake up, Syl.
It's a beautiful morning.
I got just the thing
to stop your snornin'!
Oh, no!
Where's my banjo?
Banjo?
Banjo!
Uh, buddy,
everything okay?
Where's my banjo?
Banjo?
Where's your hat?
Oh, no, my chapeau!
Now I want you to go
to your room and think
about what you've done.
Oh, yeah?
You go to your room.
Think about
what you've done.
Love killer!
Stupid Peepers
doesn't understand me.
Doesn't care about
my needs.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wander, I'm really
upset right now.
The last thing I need
is your stupid sunshine games.
Get out of there!
What the what?
Oh, yeah.
That hits the spot.
Kinda dry.
Wander, if this is
some kind of trick.
Oh, this is exactly
what I needed.
Oh, my grop,
it's magic!
It's a magic hat that can
give me exactly what I need...
to impress Dominator.
Ah, silly me, it's probably
under this rock.
Or maybe
I know.
It's under this rock.
Or this rock.
Or this rock or...
Maybe try
retracing your steps.
Super duper idea.
We'll just orbble back
to the last planet...
No hat, no orbble juice.
Then I'll just
check the map...
No hat, no map.
Okay, an inspirational ditty
should lift my spirits...
No hat, no banjo.
No hat! No hat, no map.
no hat, no orbble juice.
No hat, no Wander!!
Easy, buddy.
Easy.
The hat is
just a thing.
I've never known you
to get so worked up
over stuff.
You're right, Sylvia.
It's only a silly hat.
That's the spirit.
Oh, grop.
Gotta find that hat.
So, magic hat.
I have this friend
named Hater.
I mean traitor.
And I... I mean, my friend
kind of likes this girl.
And I... I mean,
he was wondering
what one would need to make
her fall in love with me. Him!
Overcoming
Your Severe Temper.
Not Being A Jerk
For Jerks.
How To Accept Your Flaws
And Change Your Entire
Personality.
So You're
A Totally Different Person.
Come on, hat.
Girls don't like to read.
What will make her happy?
Fine, Mr. Smarty Hat.
What's the one thing
she likes the least?
( screams )
Just give me what I need!
Breath mints?
( frustrated shriek )
Come on, buddy.
If your old hat's gone,
we will find a new one
you like just as much.
( British accent )
I forthwith hereby
proclaim this hat
to be most agreeable.
Pip, pip.
( French accent ) A chapeau
is merely a construct
of the mind, is it not?
Hat's great.
Best headpiece.
( Southern accent )
Why, I do declare!
♪ Hallelujah,
hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah
You did it, Wander.
That one is perfect.
Do you feel better?
But... my hat...
is... green!!
So, hat, if you won't
give me what I want,
you should feel
the wrath of my...
hat rack!
Good one, me.
Now girls.
Gimme something for girls.
Fuzzy? Pink?
Now we're talkin'.
More. Gimme more stuff
girls like.
Lipstick. Salads.
A bag of glitter.
Dominator will love these!
What else? What else?
Ooh, I know.
A unicorn!
Yes!!
So stupid, so girly.
( still saying "green" )
Okay, okay.
You want
your old hat back.
I want to like
these, Sylvia,
I really do.
But none of them have
that same... magic.
Somebody say magic?
We sell those.
Huh. Firm.
Tall. Voluminous.
Can you pull stuff
out of it?
Of course.
Go ahead.
( gasps )
Sylvia, look.
Just like my hat.
What else will it give you?
Items that you need
and not what you want,
forcing you to improvise
and take things as they come,
sort of like a physical
manifestation of the challenges
we all face in life?
A banjo?
Pretty much
handkerchiefs.
But it's magic?
Not real magic.
You know how rare
those are?
Son, if I had a real
magic hat,
I'd never let it
out of my sight ever.
( squealing )
( coughs )
Mrs. Dominator Hater.
Hey, hat, monogram
some Mrs. Hater towels for me.
Thanks.
( hat coughs )
Sir, a unicorn is chewing up
the engine room.
What is going on?!
( gasps )
Is that what I think it is?
It's not a magical,
mystical hat
that gives you anything
you want, if that's
what you're implying.
Shut up, it's mine!
I need it to conquer
Dominator's heart.
Conquer her heart?
We can use this
to actually conquer her.
But it's really good at
making lady presents.
Forget presents.
We can make super weapons.
Gifts, gifts.
Nightgowns and baby dolls
and leg hair wax.
She will be mine!
Weapons, weapons.
Bazookas and laser blasters
and sonic cannons.
The universe
will be mine!
Uh-oh.
Really? You're
sure you're fine?
Yeah. I just have
to face we're not
gonna find my hat,
and I'll never
replace it.
But knowing that
old hat,
it's probably out there
helping some other
deserving soul
who needs it
more than me.
I guess, from now on,
I'm just regular old Wander,
the guy with nothing
on his noggin.
Oh. Did not see
that coming.
My hat!
Whoa, whoa, what makes
you think the hat is up there?
'Cause this is
exactly what happened
- when I stole it.
- When you what?
You stole something?
Back in my past,
I wandered to a galaxy
in the middle of a civil war.
Two former allies
discovered the hat
could give them
wonderful things,
but they got too greedy
and turned against each other.
In an attempt
to conquer the galaxy,
they forced the hat to
give them whatever they wanted
without a thought to how
the poor, helpless hat felt.
I felt so bad for it,
I did the only thing I could.
I took it, and kept it
safe on my head.
Eventually, it learned
to trust me
and was nice enough
to help me.
- And right now...
- We need to help it.
But how? We don't
have orbble juice.
( whinnying )
( shrieking )
What do we do, what do we do?
Sir, get rid of the hat.
But I still haven't
found the perfect thing--
Sir!
My hat!
Hey, Hater.
I was wondering,
if it's not too much trouble,
- if I could get my--
- Take it.
- Oh. Hey, thanks.
- Sure. No problem.
- That's really nice of you.
- Whatever. It's fine.
- Okay.
- Okay, fine.
- Just get outta here,
take that stupid hat with you.
- Okay.
This hat may give me
whatever I need,
but it turns out what I really
need is my hat.
Looks like it needs
you, too, pal.