♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander wander over over
yonder yonder wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
♪ Wander over,
over yonder ♪
♪ Wander yonder
wander yonder ♪
♪ Yip bi di dit bip
bi-ee-i-di-dit ♪
♪ Wander over yonder
( slowly ) DON'T WORRY,
MR. AND MRS. BRITTLE.
WE'LL HAVE YOU
AND YOUR FAMILY
MOVED IN NO TIME.
FOR SUCH TINY
LITTLE FOLKS,
YOU SURE DO HAVE
A TON OF STUFF.
WELL, HOPE YOU LOVE
THE NEW PLACE, FOLKS.
REMEMBER, IT'S NOT JUST
A HOUSE, IT'S A HOME.
SYLVIA!
WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
SO MR. BRITTLE'S
READING CHAIR.
I'M THINKING
THIRD FLOOR STUDY.
( squeaking )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE EAST BEDROOM
WOULD GET SOME GOOD SUN
DURING THE WINTRY MONTHS.
WANDER, IS IT JUST ME,
OR HAVE OUR LATEST ADVENTURES
LACKED A CERTAIN
ELEMENT OF, YA KNOW...
ADVENTURE?
I KNOW JUST WHAT
YOU NEED, SYLVIA.
WE'LL BUST INTO
HATER'S SHIP...
YEAH?
AND GIVE BARRY
A BIRTHDAY CAKE!
BARRY?
ONE OF THE WATCHDOGS?
TURNING 30?
HASN'T TOLD ANYBODY BUT
HOPES THEY REMEMBER ANYWAY?
POOR BARRY.
( sighs )
LOOK, I'M ALL
FOR HELPING.
I COULD JUST USE
A LITTLE MORE...
I DON'T KNOW,
ACTION.
( loud rumbling )
YOU!
- YOU.
- YOU!
SURRENDER NOW, THIEF,
AND YOUR DEATH WILL BE
SLIGHTLY LESS PAINFUL.
WAIT. YOU?!
DRAT. THESE WINDOW TREATMENTS
ARE JUST ALL ASKEW.
FORTY-TWO.
( raucous coughing )
HUH? HUH? HM?
HUH?!
OH, MAN!
WELL, YOU AIN'T
ANY LIGHTER.
AND THAT SADDLE OF YOURS
SURE AIN'T ANY SOFTER.
GOOD THING I WAS AROUND
TO SAVE THAT UGLY MUG OF YOURS.
LIKE I'VE EVER NEEDED HELP
FROM YOUR CRAGGY OLD HIDE.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONE FOREVER.
TAKES WAY MORE THAN SOME
FLAB DRASSIT BLACK HOLE
TO TAKE ME DOWN.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
LET ME KNOW
YOU WERE STILL ALIVE,
YOU NARFIN' FROOD?
I TRIED, BUT FOR
A TEN-FOOT TALL
FLARF NARBLER,
YOU'RE MIGHTY HARD
TO TRACK DOWN.
IT IS SO GREAT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
( both laughing )
IT IS GREAT
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
OH, GROP.
WANDER, I'M SO SORRY. I...
I GOTCHA, LITTLE GUY.
WANDER, THIS SORRY
SON OF A STAR CHASER
IS MY OLD PARTNER.
GOES BY THE NAME OF...
RYDER.
USED TO RIDE HER.
SO YOU REPLACED ME
WITH A HAIRY CHICKEN LEG.
OH, COME ON,
HE'S NOT THAT BAD.
LOOK, HE LIKES YOU.
ANY OLD FRIEND
OF SYLVIA'S
IS A NEW FRIEND
OF MINE.
SO WHY WAS HATER
TRYING TO BLAST
YOU INTO ATOMS?
PROBABLY JUST BECAUSE
I STOLE THE KEY TO HIS
HIDDEN GALACTIC
STORAGE STATION.
THE PLACE HE KEEPS
ALL THE LOOT HE'S STOLEN
THROUGHOUT THE GALAXY?
I THOUGHT THAT PLACE
WAS A MYTH.
IT'S REAL, ALL RIGHT.
NOW THAT I GOT THE KEY,
I JUST GOTTA FIND
THE LOCATION OF
THE DARN THING.
OH, MAN, SOUNDS LIKE
A REAL ADVENTURE.
SAY, SYLVIA, YOU'RE
THE ROUGHEST, TOUGHEST,
PUNCHIEST PARTNER
I EVER HAD.
YOU MAY JUST
COME IN HANDY.
YOU UP FOR
A RIP-ROARING,
ACTION-PACKED,
TRANS-GALACTIC ADVENTURE
TO BREAK INTO HATER'S
HIDDEN STORAGE STATION
TO STEAL THE MOST
PRICELESS TREASURES
IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE?
RIP-ROARING?
TOP SECRET?
ACTION-PACKED?
COUNT ME IN!
RIGHT, WANDER?
I DON'T KNOW.
BREAK INTO? STEAL?
SOUNDS A BIT
DISHONEST,
DON'T YOU THINK?
OH, YEAH.
SORRY, RYDER.
SINCE YOU AND I SPLIT,
WANDER AND I HAVE BEEN
FOCUSED ON HELPING OTHERS
AND DOING GOOD.
NOT SURE THIS IS
A JOB FOR US.
UH-UH, YOU DIDN'T
LET ME FINISH.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO JOIN ME ON
A RIP-ROARING,
ACTION-PACKED,
TRANS-GALACTIC ADVENTURE
TO POLITELY CHECK IN ON
HATER'S HIDDEN
STORAGE FACILITY
AND HELP RETURN
THE UNIVERSE'S
MOST PRICELESS TREASURES
TO THEIR
RIGHTFUL OWNERS,
THUS MAKING THEM HAPPY?
POLITELY? HELPING?
MAKE PEOPLE HAPPY?
WHOO-HOO!
OH, SORRY.
I'LL JUST...
( muttering )
SEE? ROOM FOR BOTH OF US.
( screaming )
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I CAN USE THE EXERCISE!
WEASEL'S WATERING HOLE.
I HAVEN'T BEEN HERE
IN YEARS.
BRINGS BACK
MEMORIES, DON'T IT?
WORD IS, WEASEL KNOWS
HOW TO FIND HATER'S
HIDDEN STATION.
READY TO ASK HIM
REAL NICE-LIKE IF
HE WANTS TO HAND HIM OVER?
( knuckles cracking )
ASKING REAL NICE-LIKE
IS MY SPECIALTY.
MIGHT I RECOMMEND
STARTING WITH
A SMALL GIFT
OR COOKIE BOUQUET?
WELL, WELL.
TOGETHER AGAIN.
IT'S RYDER AND SYLVIA.
HOWDY DO!
AND, UH, WEIRD LITTLE
FURRY GUY.
I HEAR YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR HATER'S
HIDDEN STATION.
INFORMATION LIKE THAT
SURE WOULD FETCH A PRETTY PRICE.
FIGURED YOU MIGHT
GIVE US A DISCOUNT,
FOR OLD TIME'S SAKE.
EXCUSE ME, SIR, BUT
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
YOU'D BE HELPING
A CHARITABLE ENDEAVOR?
IT MIGHT BE
TAX-DEDUCTIBLE.
WANDER, WHY DON'T YOU
GO OUTSIDE
SEE IF SOME FOLKS
NEED YOUR HELP OUT THERE?
OH, OKAY. SURE.
NOW, ABOUT THOSE
COORDINATES.
RYDER, I FOUND
SOME FOLKS TO HELP.
THAT'S GREAT, BUDDY.
IN FACT, THEY SAY
THEY'RE FRIENDS OF YOURS.
THEY'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
TO SHOW UP WITH THAT KEY
TO HATER'S STATION THAT
YOU PROMISED TO GET FOR THEM.
SO, NOW THAT YOU'RE
ALL BACK TOGETHER,
YOU CAN GIVE 'EM THE KEY,
JUST LIKE YOU PROMISED.
YEAH, RYDER.
( gulp )
RYDER, YOU DOUBLE-CROSSED
THE SCUZZ BUCKETS
FOR THAT THING?
NINETY-EIGHT.
YOU FLAB DRASSIT GLORF.
THAT SURE IS A FUNNY WAY
TO GREET OLD FRIENDS.
AIN'T FORGOT HOW TO
HOT-WIRE A CRUISER, HAVE YOU?
IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE,
REMEMBER?
BESIDES, WE'LL
BRING IT BACK.
I PROMISE.
SPREAD OUT.
COVER ME.
WITH A BLASTER,
FLAB DRASSIT.
YOU KNOW HOW TO USE
ONE OF THESE, RIGHT?
ZAP, ZAP.
ZAP, ZAP, ZAP!
ZAP-ZAP, ZAP!
I'M SORRY. IS IT
MORE OF A "PEW-PEW"
OR A "BZZ"?
ON THREE, WE POP UP
AND RETURN FIRE
REAL FIRE, OKAY?
ONE, TWO...
EXCUSE ME, OPPONENTS.
WE WILL SOON BE
RETURNING FIRE.
I SUGGEST DUCKING
TO AVOID SERIOUS INJURY.
THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
ARE YOU...
WE'RE TRYING TO INJURE THEM.
WHY WOULD WE
WANNA DO THAT?
YOU STINKIN'
GROFFLEZOP.
AND WE WILL
RETURN YOUR SHIP UNDAMAGED,
ALONG WITH
A FRESH FRUIT BASKET.
DO YOU PREFER HONEYDEW
OR BINGLEBERRIES?
GOT THE KEY,
GOT THE COORDINATES.
NOT HALF BAD FOR
OUR FIRST ROUND
BACK IN THE GAME.
YEAH!
WANDER, I'M GLAD
YOU WANNA HELP,
BUT RYDER AND I
USED TO DO THIS
KIND OF THING
ALL THE TIME,
SO...
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST LEAVE THIS
TO THE PROFESSIONALS.
UH-OH. WE GOT COMPANY.
( evil laughter)
GRAB THE WHEEL
SO I CAN BLAST
THESE BOZOS.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
I WAS, UH, I WAS ACTUALLY
TALKING TO RYDER.
I THOUGHT THAT
WAS PRETTY OBVIOUS.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO TO HELP?
YES, TOTALLY. JUST, UM...
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
Ryder: SURE HOPE
YOUR AIM'S IMPROVED
SINCE THE SHADOW MOON
OF LANDAU.
JUST TRY AND KEEP UP.
( laughs )
QUICK UPDATE: HAVE NOT
PUT MY HANDS ON ANYTHING.
THE ENTIRE SHIP REMAINS
REMARKABLY UNTOUCHED.
UH, RYDER, WE'RE HEADING
TOWARD A WHOLE MESS OF STUFF.
Ryder: I KNOW. WE'RE GONNA
CRASH RIGHT THROUGH IT.
AND USE THE DISTRACTION TO BLAST
THE LAST OF THESE LOSERS.
NICE.
ALSO, IT'LL LOOK
REALLY COOL.
BUT WHAT ABOUT--
NOT OUR PROBLEM, BUDDY.
I HAVE YOU NOW.
( screaming )
SORRY.
PARDON. EXCUSE ME.
HUMBLEST APOLOGIES.
FRESH FRUIT.
FRESH FRUIT
FOR SALE.
WHY AREN'T WE MOVING?
( Wander humming )
THERE YOU GO.
ONE CRATE OF
BINGLEBERRIES,
GOOD AS NEW.
WANDER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
I WAS JUST...
THOUGHT I COULD HELP.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A HIGH-SPEED CHASE HERE.
WHY CAN'T YOU BE
MORE LIKE RYDER?
( crashing )
( evil laughter )
HOW WE LOOKIN'?
NOT GOOD.
WEAPONS ARE GONE,
SO'S THE ENGINE.
ONLY SHELTER NEARBY...
IS THAT MOON.
THAT'S NO MOON.
THAT'S HATER'S
GALACTIC STORAGE FACILITY.
Both: WE MADE IT!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
NUMBER NINE THOUSAND,
SIX HUNDRED...
NINETY-NINE?
NEVER TRIED ONE OF
THOSE BEFORE.
TO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT.
OKAY, I'M ON IT.
TINY QUESTION.
WHAT DOES 9,699 MEAN?
GOT IT, CHIEF.
CAN I ADJUST
THE VECTOR?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
I CAN CHECK THE OIL.
JUST SIT DOWN!
THAT WAS...
AWESOME!!
NOTHIN' BETTER THAN
A RIP-ROARIN' ADVENTURE,
EH, SYLVIA, OLD GIRL?
NOPE. NOTHIN'.
WOW, GUYS,
THAT WAS AMAZING!
YOU TWO REALLY DO
MAKE A PRETTY GOOD...
...TEAM.
NICE. WAIT,
WHERE'S WANDER?
HM, I DON'T KNOW.
I LOST TRACK OF HIM
AFTER THAT AWESOME
SPACE CHASE.
AM I RIGHT, PARTNER?
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GO FIND HIM.
THAT LITTLE
FREAKY FURBALL?
ALL HE'S DONE
IS GET IN OUR WAY.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
BUT LET'S FINISH
THE MISSION FIRST.
HATER'S MAIN TREASURE
ROOM IS JUST AHEAD.
Sylvia: GOOD GROP!
WHOO-HOO!
I'M RICH!
I'M SO RICH!
I'M GONNA BUY
A BIG GALACTIC CRUISER,
AND A LITTLE ONE TO GO INSIDE
THE BIG ONE. HA HA!
WAIT. YOU'RE RICH?
WHAT HAPPENED TO GIVING
THIS STUFF BACK
TO THE PEOPLE
HATER STOLE IT FROM?
PLEASE. YOU DIDN'T REALLY
BELIEVE THAT, DID YOU?
( growling )
YOU DID?
THAT LITTLE WEIRDO
IS TURNING YOU
ALL KINDS OF SOFT.
THANK GROP I CAME ALONG.
HEY, JUST 'CAUSE WANDER
LIKES HELPING OUT
DOESN'T MAKE HIM SOFT.
SURE, IT DOES.
WHILE HE'S OUT THERE
GIVIN' OUT FREE HUGS
OR SOMETHING,
WE'RE IN HERE WITH
ALL THE TREASURE.
WE WIN!
( alarm blaring )
INTRUDER ALERT.
NOT GOOD.
WHAT'LL IT BE?
NUMBER 19?
NUMBER 46?
I'M THINKIN'
NUMBER ONE.
AS IN,
LOOKIN' OUT FOR.
SO LONG, SYL.
TOLD YOU YOU'D COME IN HANDY.
WHOO-HOO!
NOT GOOD AT ALL.
NOW, WANDER,
DON'T BE SELFISH.
IF SYLVIA WANTS TO HAVE
HARDCORE, VIOLENT,
INCONSIDERATE
SPACE ADVENTURES
WITH A GUY LIKE RYDER,
YOU GOTTA LET HER.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO FIND
ANOTHER PARTNER...
SOMEONE STRONG,
AND SMART.
AND BRAVE.
SOMEONE WHO,
THOUGH THEY ACT ALL TOUGH,
HAS A CREAMY CENTER
OF GOOEY GOODNESS.
AND WHEN YOU INEVITABLY
GET YOURSELF
INTO TROUBLE
IN SITUATIONS,
THEY'LL ALWAYS FIND
A WAY TO GET YOU OUT,
NO MATTER HOW BAD
THINGS SEEM.
LOOK, FELLA, HER
AND THE LITTLE FURRY GUY
ARE WHO HATER
REALLY WANT.
LET ME GO AND I'LL
MAKE A DEAL WITH...
OH, I ALWAYS FORGET
WHAT A JERK RYDER WAS,
AND WHAT A JERK
HE MAKES ME.
I LET THE ONLY PARTNER
WHO'S SEEN THE GOOD IN ME
JUST WANDER AWAY.
FLAB DRASSIT.
I'M SURE GONNA MISS
THE GOOFY LITTLE GUY.
THE WAY HE'D MESS UP A PLAN
JUST TO DO SOMETHING NICE.
AND HE'D ALWAYS FIND
SOME CRAZY WAY TO GET OUT OF IT.
IT'S LIKE HE'S MAGIC.
LADY, I'M SORRY YOU LOST
YOUR DOG OR WHATEVER,
BUT NOBODY CARES.
SYLVIA!
WANDER? WHAT, HOW, WHO?
REMEMBER THAT TIME
ON KEE-TON 6
WHEN WE HELPED
THE IMMENSAPEDE
FIND HIS MISSING
CONTACT LENS?
TURNS OUT,
THIS IS HIS COUSIN.
OH, SYLVIA,
I KNOW YOU AND RYDER
ARE ALL TOUGH AND COOL,
AND I'M OFTEN NOT,
BUT...
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU REMEMBER THE TIME
YOU BUSTED INTO HATER'S
SECRET STORAGE UNIT
ON A GIANT SPACE WORM
JUST TO HELP YOUR
BEST FRIEND?
THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
WOULD YOU SAY
US BEING FRIENDS
IS THE GREATEST
ADVENTURE OF ALL?
NO, BECAUSE THAT WOULD
BE WAY TOO SAPPY.
BUT I'M KINDA
THINKIN' IT.
FREDERICK, THANKS SO MUCH
FOR THE ADVICE.
IT TOTALLY WORKED.
WHY, THAT'S SPECTACULAR,
WANDER.
REMEMBER, ACKNOWLEDGING
YOUR DIFFERENCES
CAN OFTEN MAKE
A RELATIONSHIP EVEN RICHER.
( roaring )
YOU KNOW, HE WAS
GONNA EAT ME.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
OH, WANDER.
WHY AM I NOT SURPRISED?
SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
BUT I WAS ASKING
A SPACE WORM
ABOUT FRIENDSHIP...
I DON'T CARE.
SEIZE THEM!
WHAT DO YA THINK?
NUMBER 9,042?
NUMBER ELEVENTY-SEVEN?
JUST DO YOUR THING.
( gasps )
BARRY!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BARRY!
DUDE, IT'S
YOUR BIRTHDAY?
YOU OUGHTA
CELEBRATE YOU, BARRY.
YOU'RE THE MAN!
CAN'T KEEP
STUFF SECRET, MAN.
STOP THEM!
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING
BOTH ME AND YOURSELVES.
DREADFULLY SORRY,
BUT I THINK I KNOCKED OVER
SOMETHING RATHER IMPORTANT
DURING MY RAMPAGE.
IT SEEMS THE STATION
WILL SOON BE, UH, WELL...
EXPLODED.
CHEERIO!
BACK TO THE SHIP!
RUNAWAY! STOP HER!
WELL, TIME TO GO.
ONE MORE THING.
Hater: CURSE YOU, WANDER!
SYLVIA, I KNEW YOU'D
COME BACK, OLD BUDDY, OLD PAL.
YOU'RE JUST LUCKY
MY PARTNER MAKES ME
A BETTER PERSON.
NO! MY TREASURE!
"AND WE WILL RETURN
YOUR SHIP UNDAMAGED."
THAT OLD SHIP
WAS ALL I HAD.
WHOO-HOO!
I COULD'VE BEEN
SO RICH.
AW, FROOD IT.
YOU WIN SOME,
YOU LOSE SOME,
RIGHTY, SYL?
SO WHAT'S NEXT?
A GRIFT, A SCAM,
GRAND THEFT SPACESHIP?
I ASKED WANDER
TO COME, TOO.
I HAVE A HUSTLE THAT CAN
USE THE LITTLE NERT MUNCHER.
SHE'LL BE BACK.
HELLO THERE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
YOUR HONESTY ISSUES.
NOOOO!
SO, PARTNER,
WHAT IS NEXT?
HELP A MULTI-ARMED
VETRUVIAN WITH
A PESKY HANGNAIL?
FIND THE MISSING CORNER
OF THE RUBIKIAN PUZZLE PLANET?
Hater: YOU DESTROYED
ALL MY STUFF!
FOR THAT,
YOU WILL PAY!
POSSIBLY WITH MONEY,
BUT DEFINITELY
WITH SUFFERING!
HOW'S ABOUT A LITTLE
ADVENTURE?
HI-DY HO, SYLVIA.
AWAY!
I HATE YOU
SO MUCH, WANDER!
Wander:
I LOVE YOU, TOO!
I HATE YOU
SO MUCH, WANDER!
I LOVE YOU, TOO!
( evil laughter )