♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
THAT COULD HAVE GONE...
A LOT WORSE.
COULD HAVE GONE
A LOT BETTER, TOO.
CONNIE: Steven,
I got your message.
Steven?
What happened?!
WE WON!
[ LAUGHS ]
WUHHHHHH!
Is that Amethyst?
[ PURRS ]
Uh, what --
what's going on?
YOU SAID THERE'S
SOME KIND OF GIANT SPACE HAND
AND YOU ALL MIGHT DIE?
AMETHYST: Whoo-hoo!
YEH-HEH-HEAH!
CONNIE! YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
BELIEVE WHAT HAPPENED!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHERE DO I EVEN START?
WHOOOOO!
IT'S BEEN A MADHOUSE
OVER HERE!
Pearl: AMETHYST!
THAT'S ENOUGH CELEBRATING!
[ HORN HONKING ]
HUH?
STEVEN!
DAD!
CONNIE, I HAVE TO GO.
I PROMISE I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
DAD'S BACK!
OH! THANK GOODNESS!
YOU'RE OKAY!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
I SAW THE SPACESHIP
START TO LEAVE,
AND THEN IT CRASHED,
AND I CAME BACK, AND --
UGGGGH! YOUR EYE.
BUT YOU'RE OKAY!
I GUESS THOSE JERKS WERE
NO MATCH FOR THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
NO WAY!
THEY WERE SUPERSTRONG!
BUT YOU WERE ABLE
TO BEAT THEM BACK?
NO.
THEY TOTALLY STOMPED US!
THIS WARRIOR JASPER
WAS SUPER-BEEFY
AND KNOCKED ME
UNCONSCIOUS.
THEN THEY ABDUCTED ME
ONTO THE SHIP
BECAUSE THEY WANTED
TO TAKE ME AWAY FOREVER.
AND THEN WE CRASHED THE SHIP,
AND I ALMOST DIED!
WHAT DID THEY WANT
WITH YOU?
THEY THINK I'M MOM.
A-ARE MORE HOMEWORLD GEMS
GONNA COME AFTER YOU?
I -- UH...
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE?
STEVEN, I'M SUPPORTIVE
AND VERY PROUD OF YOU,
AND I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ PANTING ]
GOT TO CALM DOWN.
WHERE'S MY --
WHERE'S
MY RELAXING-MUSIC CD?!
THIS ONE?
[ HEAVY METAL PLAYS ]
WRONG ONE!
STOP! EJECT!
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
[ VOLUME INCREASES ]
[ RUMBLING ]
NOW, CONNIE,
PLEASE DON'T FREAK OUT,
BUT A GIANT LASER HAND
TRIED TO STEAL ME INTO SPACE.
BUT IT DIDN'T.
IT DIDN'T.
I'M BACK,
AND EVERYTHING IS F-FINE...NOW.
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
UH...
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
UM, CONNIE, FUNNY STORY --
AS IT TURNS OUT,
THERE'S A LOT MORE GEMS
OUT THERE THAN WE THOUGHT,
[ BUZZING, RINGTONE STOP ]
AND I THINK THEY WANT TO...
KILL ME?
UHHHHH!
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
UHH!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
HEY, CONNIE,
THAT -- THAT MESSAGE I LEFT YOU
WAS -- WAS JUST A DREAM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
EH, SHE'S TOO SMART FOR THAT.
[ BUZZING, RINGTONE CONTINUE ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GROANS ]
[ BUZZING, RINGTONE CONTINUE ]
[ SIGHS DEEPLY ]
[ BUZZING, RINGTONE STOP ]
YO!
OH. HEY, RONALDO.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR?
MAYOR DEWEY'S CALLING EVERYONE
BACK INTO THE CITY.
WE CAN GO HOME NOW.
OH. I SEE.
YOU COME UP HERE
TO BROOD, TOO!
BROOD?
YES, STEVEN.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
PEOPLE LIKE US DO --
SUFFER QUIETLY,
SHOULDERING THE KNOWLEDGE
NO ONE ELSE CAN BEAR.
HMPH.
AS AN AFICIONADO
OF "THE WEIRD" YOURSELF,
YOU'VE PROBABLY NOTICED
ORDINARY PEOPLE FEAR
THE COLD, LEADED ANCHOR
OF THE TRUTH.
THE ABYSS IS
NO SUNDAY SWAN RIDE.
I KNOW! MY DAD FLIPPED OUT
WHEN I TOLD HIM!
SOUNDS TYPICAL.
BUT IT'S A GOOD REMINDER.
THIS IS NO EASY PATH
WE'VE CHOSEN HERE.
THERE ARE...
SACRIFICES.
LOOK AT THEM ALL
DOWN THERE, STEVEN.
IT'S OUR DUTY
TO LET THOSE SIMPLE PEOPLE
LIVE OUT
THEIR SIMPLE LIVES
WITHOUT EVER KNOWING THE BURDEN
OF BEING FRIENDS WITH US.
AT LEAST WE CAN BE THERE
FOR EACH OTHER.
IS THAT GIANT HAND
FROM THE SKY
SITTING RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE BEACH?!
I GOT TO GET SOME OF THIS
FOR MY BLOG!
[ SIGHS ]
♪ EVERYBODY TOLD ME
GEM STUFF'S DANGEROUS ♪
♪ I GUESS I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT
UNTIL NOW ♪
♪ DAD ALWAYS SEEMED
APPREHENSIVE ♪
♪ AND NOW
HE'S REALLY FREAKING OUT ♪
♪ WHAT DO I DO? ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT THAT FOR YOU ♪
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
[ BUZZING, RINGTONE STOP ]
♪ EVERYBODY TELLS ME
LIFE IS PRECIOUS ♪
♪ ON THE PLANET EARTH ♪
♪ AND THAT MEANS YOU,
AND I HAVE TO PROTECT YOU ♪
♪ WHAT IF SOMEHOW
YOU GET HURT? ♪
♪ WHAT DO I DO? ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT THAT FOR YOU ♪
[ RINGTONE PLAYING ]
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
[ RINGTONE STOPS ]
♪ WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL YOU? ♪
♪ YOU'RE BETTER OFF
NOT KNOWING THE TROUBLE I'M IN ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT YOU TO WORRY ♪
♪ ABOUT WHAT I'VE JUST SEEN,
ABOUT WHERE I'VE JUST BEEN ♪
♪ YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
A PART OF THIS ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK
I WANT YOU TO BE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T NEED THIS ♪
♪ YOU DON'T NEED ME ♪
[ RINGTONE PLAYING ]
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING ]
[ BUZZING CONTINUES ]
♪ OOH-OOH-OOH-OOH ♪
[ BUZZING STOPS ]
[ WIND BLOWING ]
AWW, COME ON!
NO WHINING. WE NEED TO START
CLEANING UP THE DEBRIS.
GARNET'S RIGHT.
PEOPLE ARE ALREADY
COMING BACK INTO TOWN.
WE'VE GOT TO KEEP THEM
OFF THE BEACH.
IF ANY HUMANS
GOT ACCESS TO GEM TECHNOLOGY,
THEY COULD
REALLY HURT THEMSELVES.
MAYBE WE SHOULD SHUT THEM OUT
FOR GOOD.
YOU KNOW,
WE DID ONCE HAVE A FENCE.
LET'S GET A NEW ONE --
WITH BARBED WIRE!
THIS TIME,
LET'S BUILD A MOAT.
I COULD BE...
♪ THE CROCODILE! ♪
JAZZ HANDS.
NO.
WHY NOT?!
YOU ALWAYS SAY
YOU'LL BE THE CROCODILE,
BUT YOU NEVER COMMIT.
NO FENCE,
EITHER.
Both: GARNET!
STEVEN NEEDS TO SEE
HIS FATHER AND HIS FRIENDS.
NO, I DON'T!
I CAN'T KEEP CLINGING
TO THE VESTIGES OF MY HUMANITY.
IT'S TIME I GOT SERIOUS.
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
AAAAAEHHHHH!
STEVEN, WHY IS
YOUR COMMUNICATION DEVICE
PLAYING THAT SONG?
IT'S CONNIE
TRYING TO CALL ME.
BUT I CAN'T FACE HER
ANYMORE.
SO...YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO IGNORE HER FOREVER?
IT'S THE RESPONSIBLE THING
TO DO.
THAT'S GONNA BE HARD,
'CAUSE SHE'S COMING UP
THE STEPS RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?!
OHHH!
HELLO...CONNIE.
IS STEVEN HOME?
NO.
[ GRUNTS ]
IS HE OKAY?
I'M JUST REALLY WORRIED.
HE HASN'T BEEN
ANSWERING HIS PHONE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UHH...
I-I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOUR HUMAN RELATIONSHIPS.
SO...UM...
GOODBYE.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
STEVEN!
STEVEN!!
[ PANTING ECHOES ]
STEVEN?
[ WHEEZING ]
STEVEN!
[ SIGHS ]
ARE YOU IN TROUBLE?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
DID I DO
SOMETHING WRONG?
[ GROANS ]
WHY ARE YOU AVOIDING ME?
[ GROANS HEAVILY ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ Speed-dialing ]
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS,
BUZZING, RINGTONE STOP ]
STEVEN,
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE!
WHY ARE YOU
HIDING FROM ME?!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ CELLPHONE CHIMES ]
"I DON'T WANT
TO BE FRIENDS ANYMORE"?
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ Speed-dialing ]
[ CELLPHONE BUZZING,
RINGTONE PLAYING ]
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
STEVEN?
I CAN'T BE WITH YOU
ANYMORE.
I HAVE A DESTINY.
SAY IT TO MY FACE!
SAY YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE FRIENDS ANYMORE!
IF YOU CAN DO THAT --
IF YOU CAN DO THAT,
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
AND I'LL JUST GO BACK
TO HAVING NO FRIENDS.
BUT I WON'T BELIEVE IT
UNTIL YOU SAY IT TO MY FACE.
[ METAL CLATTERS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ STRAINING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL?!
[ SOBBING ]
I STILL WANT
TO BE FRIENDS!
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN, YOUR EYE!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'VE BEEN WORRIED SICK
ALL DAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
I'M DOING HERE?
I JUST WANTED
TO PROTECT YOU.
STOP.
JUST TELL ME EVERYTHING.
[ SNIFFLES ]
SO...LAPIS AND JASPER
ARE SOMEWHERE UNDERWATER.
YEAH. AND PERIDOT ESCAPED
WHILE THE SHIP WAS COMING DOWN.
SHE COULD BE ANYWHERE.
THAT IS A LOT
TO TAKE IN.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S
BEEN THROUGH EVERYTHING.
THE LEAST I COULD DO
IS JUST LISTEN.
I CAN'T ASK YOU
TO DO THAT.
I WANT TO, STEVEN.
I WANT TO BE
A PART OF YOUR UNIVERSE.
[ VEHICLE APPROACHES ]
KIDDO!
THERE YOU ARE.
OH, HEY, CONNIE.
DO YOU NEED A RIDE HOME?
OH. DAD.
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
I GOT IT
OUT OF MY SYSTEM.
I'M BACK TO BEING
YOUR COOL DAD.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪