>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: HMM.
THIS SPOT SHOULD BE SAFE.
AMETHYST, DO YOU HAVE THE
ROBONOID?!
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
I JUST REPAIRED THAT!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S FINE.
>> Pearl: UGH!
OKAY.
WE HAVE EVERYTHING WE NEED FOR
THE EXPERIMENT.
AND STEVEN IS HOME, FAST
ASLE-E-E-E-EP!
>> Steven: HEY, GUYS!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
IT'S WAY PAST YOUR BEDTIME!
YOU SHOULD REALLY GO BACK TO THE
HOUSE.
>> Steven: WHAT?
I DON'T WANT TO MISS...
WHATEVER THIS IS.
WHAT IS THIS?
>> Amethyst: PEARL GOT LONELY,
SO SHE MADE HERSELF A ROBOT
FRIEND.
>> Pearl: IT'S NOT A ROBOT
FRIEND -- IT'S A ROBOT
DISRUPTOR!
IT SHOULD PRODUCE A LOCALIZED
ENERGY BLAST.
SO WHEN PERIDOT SHOWS UP TO...
MEET WITH US, WE'LL HAVE
SOMETHING THAT CAN KNOCK OUT ALL
HER ROBONOIDS.
NOW, STAND BACK, EVERYONE!
[ WHIRRING ]
[ POP! BOOM! ]
>> All: UGH!
[ ALL GROAN ]
>> Steven: WE DID IT!
>> Amethyst: UGH.
>> Steven: WELL, YOU KNOCKED OUT
ALL THE LIGHTS IN TOWN.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THAT WAS NOT
THE POINT OF THE -- [ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT. THAT WAS A START!
NOW I'M GOING TO NEED TO TAKE
SOME PARTS OUT OF THE WASHING
MACHINE.
STEVEN, YOU MIGHT HAVE TO WEAR
THE SAME SHIRT FOR A WHILE.
>> Steven: NO PROBLEM.
[ GULLS CRYING ]
HMM.
[ YAWNS ]
HMPH.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE MICROWAV--
OW!
[ GROANS ]
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?!
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
HUH?
MAYOR DEWEY?
>> HELLO, THERE, YOUNG UNIVERSE.
ANY OF YOUR...SISTERS HOME?
>> Steven: MY SISTERS?
>> YOUR CARETAKERS, YOU KNOW --
THE TALL ONE, THE PURPLE ONE,
THE HOT ONE?
LOOK, THE POWER'S OUT, AND I'VE
BEEN MAYOR LONG ENOUGH TO KNOW
THEY HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH
IT.
>> Steven: MY SISTERS?
>> IS THERE ANYONE ELSE I CAN
TALK TO ABOUT THIS?
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: COMING!
OH! UH, CAN I HELP YOU?
>> [ Wistfully ] YES.
[ Normal voice ] OH, HI!
UH, BEACH CITY IS CURRENTLY
EXPERIENCING A WIDESPREAD POWER
OUTAGE.
>> Pearl: OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THAT.
THE POWER SHOULD BE BACK ON AS
EARLY AS TONIGHT OR AS LATE
AS...NEVER.
>> NEVER COMING BACK?!
>> Pearl: YES?
>> NO, NO, NO!
IT HAS TO COME BACK!
THE PEOPLE OF BEACH CITY CAN'T
HANDLE A SITUATION LIKE THIS!
THEY NEED THEIR ELECTRONIC
DISTRACTIONS SO THEY WON'T
NOTICE THAT THIS TOWN IS A
MAGNET FOR DISASTER!
>> Pearl: OH, DON'T BE DRAMATIC.
I SAW HUMANS GET ON FINE WITHOUT
POWER FOR MILLENNIA.
YOU USED TO HUNT AND GATHER.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ Laughing ] WHAT HAPPENED TO
THAT?
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SURE, THINGS SEEM CALM NOW, IN
THE LIGHT OF THE DAY, BUT WHEN
THE SUN GOES DOWN, SO DOES...
THE TOWN.
>> Steven: HE'S RIGHT.
MAYOR DEWEY, THIS IS OUR
RESPONSIBILITY.
WE'LL HELP YOU CLEAN UP THIS
MESS!
>> Garnet: NO, WE WON'T!
>> Steven: I'LL HELP YOU CLEAN
UP THIS MESS!
>> OKAY.
BUT YOU'RE NOT GETTING PAID.
>> ♪ MAYOR DEWEY ♪
♪ MAYOR -- ♪
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT TO GO DO DAMAGE CONTROL
NOW, OR THE BOARDIES ARE GONNA
GET RESTLESS.
>> Steven: BOARDIES?
>> HELLO, YOUTH RESIDENT OF
BEACH CITY.
>> IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> YOU MEAN BESIDES THE POWER
KNOCKING OUT THE FREEZERS
[GRUNTS] AND MELTING ALL THIS
ICE CREAM!
>> Steven: WHAT?! ICE CREAM?!
>> IT'S A REAL PAIN IN THE --
YAH! UGH!
>> I'D OFFER YOU SOME, BUT IT'S
PRETTY SOUPY.
>> Steven: IS THIS HAPPENING TO
ICE CREAM ALL OVER TOWN?!
THIS REALLY IS A CRISIS!
>> NOW LET'S ALL CALM DOWN HERE.
I HAVE EVERYTHING UNDER CONTROL.
>> Steven: YOU DO?
>> OF COURSE!
THE POWER WILL BE BACK, AND THE
FREEZERS WILL BE WORKING BY
SUNDOWN.
NO NEED TO CRY OVER, UH, FROZEN
MILK.
[ CHUCKLES ] HERE.
I'LL CATCH YOU KIDS ON THE SIDE
THAT FLIPS!
YOU TAKE CARE NOW.
>> Steven: SEE YOU LATER!
>> THANKS FOR THE GLOWSTICK!
>> Steven: SO, EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO BE OKAY?!
>> WHAT? NO!
>> Steven: Y-YOU LIED TO THEM?
>> LOOK, STEVEN, IT'S NOT LYING
WHEN YOU'RE THE MAYOR.
IT'S POLITICS.
>> Steven: IT IS?
>> OF COURSE IT IS.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WHEN YOU WORK FOR THE
GOVERNMENT, YOU CAN'T CONTROL
WHAT HAPPENS IN THE WORLD, BUT
YOU CAN CONTROL HOW PEOPLE FEEL
ABOUT IT.
THAT'S THE REAL WEIGHT I
CARRY -- MAKING THE GOOD PEOPLE
OF BEACH CITY FEEL BETTER,
SAFER, MORE SECURE.
>> Steven: BUT --
>> WHAT'S MY OTHER OPTION --
LET THE PEOPLE PANIC AND RIOT?
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT SO WELL
FOR OCEAN TOWN!
>> Steven: I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
OCEAN TOWN.
>> EXACTLY!
THAT'S WHY YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE
THE PEOPLE SOMETHING TO BELIEVE
IN.
WHEN THEY SEE MY GIANT HEAD ON
THIS CAR, ROLLING DOWN THE
BOARDWALK, THEY THINK, "HERE
COMES HELP."
WELL, SOME PEOPLE THINK, "HERE
COMES THAT EXTERMINATOR GUY,"
BUT THEN THEY REALIZE IT'S ME,
THEIR MAYOR!
HAVE YOU SEEN THAT EXTERMINATOR
TRUCK WITH THE HEAD ON IT?
HE'S TOTALLY COPYING ME.
>> Steven: UH...
>> HERE. TAKE THESE.
>> ♪ MAYOR DEWEY ♪
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ ALL TALKING AT ONCE ]
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ FEEDBACK SQUEALS ]
ATTENTION, MY GOOD CITIZENS!
AS YOU MAY OR MAY NOT BE AWARE
OF, THERE IS A POWER OUTAGE
AFFECTING ALL OF BEACH CITY AREA
PROPER.
>> OH. REALLY?
>> THIS PROBLEM IS JUST A
TEMPORARY ONE, NOT A BIG WORRY
AT ALL!
THINGS COULD BE WORSE!
WE COULD BE IN...OCEAN TOWN!
[ LIGHT LAUGHTER ]
>> TOO SOON!
>> ANYWAY, THE POWER WILL BE
BACK ON BY SUNDOWN, SO, IN THE
MEANTIME, JUST ENJOY THIS
BEAUTIFUL, PEACEFUL DAY OUTSIDE.
THE POWER WILL BE BACK ON BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT.
I PROMISE!
>> All: OHH!
>> I TRUST THIS MAN!
>> OKAY.
MAKE SURE EVERYONE GETS A BUTTON
AND A GLOWSTICK.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: HAVE A GLOWSTICK.
HERE YOU GO.
UH, HERE.
>> HEY, SCHTU-BALL.
YOU GET SOME SORT OF SECRET
GOVERNMENT INTERNSHIP I NEED TO
KNOW ABOUT?
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES
NERVOUSLY ]
HERE.
>> APPARENTLY, YOU CAN NEVER
HAVE TOO MANY MAYOR DEWEY
BUTTONS.
SOUNDS LIKE I'M NOT GONNA BE
NEEDING THIS GLOWSTICK, THOUGH.
SEE YOU LATER, BUDDY!
>> Steven: BUT, DAD!
NOOOOOOOOOO.
>> Amethyst: SO WHAT IF SHE
SHOWS UP WITH MORE?
I SAY WE JUST MASH 'EM ALL!
>> Garnet: IT'S NOT JUST THE
ROBONOIDS.
ACCORDING TO LAPIS, SHE'S GOING
TO HAVE BACKUP.
>> Pearl: WHO KNOWS WHAT SHE'S
GOING TO HAVE?
WE WON'T STAND A CHANCE AGAINST
THEIR WEAPONS, BUT IF WE CAN
JUST KNOCK THEM OUT --
>> Garnet: IT'S NOT ABOUT THE
ROBONOIDS, PEARL.
SHE'S COMING WITH OTHER GEMS!
>> Amethyst: SAYS WHO?!
WHO CARES?!
WHAT DOES LAPIS EVEN KNOW?!
>> Garnet: CALM DOWN, AMETHYST.
>> Amethyst: YOU CALM DOWN-UH...
HEY!
LOOK WHO IT IS!
IT'S STEVEN!
[ CHUCKLES ]
OUR -- OUR BEST FRIEND STEVEN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, BUDDY?
>> Steven: I...LIVE HERE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> Pearl: OF...COURSE!
>> Garnet: IN FACT, WE WERE JUST
ABOUT TO PLAY...CARDS.
>> Pearl: YES, CARDS!
>> Amethyst: WANT TO PLAY WAR?
>> Pearl: [ GROWLS ]
>> Amethyst: I MEAN...PEACE?
>> Steven: YEAH, BUT HOW ARE WE
GONNA PLAY CARDS IN THE DARK?
>> Garnet: WE CAN LIGHT A FIRE
IN THE FIREPLACE.
>> Pearl: YES! LIKE EARLY MAN!
>> Amethyst: COME ON, EARLY MAN!
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
>> WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN, SO
DOES...
>> Steven: THE TOWN.
[ ALL SHOUTING ANGRILY ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH, MY GOSH!
>> HOW COME THERE'S STILL NO
POWER?!
>> YOU SAID IT WOULD BE ON BY
SUNDOWN!
>> [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
EVERYONE JUST CALM DOWN.
I'M SURE IF WE JUST TALK
RATIONALLY, WE CAN COME TO AN
AGREEMENT.
>> NO AGREEMENT!
YOU PROMISED US!
>> WITHOUT POWER, I CAN'T TAKE
CARE OF MY FAMILY!
WELL, THIS ONE'S FINE.
BUT HE CAN'T TAKE CARE OF
HIMSELF!
>> I'M SURE THE POWER WILL BE ON
TOMORROW, I THINK...MAYBE.
>> STOP PULLING OUR LEGS!
YOU LIED TO US, AND YOU'RE LYING
AGAIN!
[ ALL SHOUTING ANGRILY ]
>> PLEASE!
GOOD CITIZENS OF BEACH CITY --
OW!
>> LIAR!
>> YOU'RE A LIAR!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
>> IF YOU'D ALL JUST CALM
DOWN --
>> TIP THE TRUCK!
WHOO-HOO!
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
EVERYONE, PLEASE!
[ ALL GASP ]
THE POWER MIGHT NOT BE BACK ON
TONIGHT.
IT MIGHT NOT BE BACK ON FOR EVEN
A YEAR!
>> A YEAR?
>> WHAT?
>> Steven: BUT I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE ALL GOING TO BE OKAY
BECAUSE I KNOW EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF YOU.
YOU'RE SMART AND YOU'RE TOUGH
AND YOU'RE RESOURCEFUL, AND YOU
ALL CARE ABOUT EACH OTHER MORE
THAN YOU CARE ABOUT MICROWAVE
DINNERS OR VIDEO GAMES OR BEING
ABLE TO SEE IN THE DARK.
I KNOW IT'LL HURT YOUR
BUSINESSES.
I KNOW IT'LL HURT YOUR LIVES.
BUT ARE WE REALLY GOING TO HURT
EACH OTHER?
[ ALL MURMURING ]
OF COURSE NOT!
WE'LL FACE THE NIGHT TOGETHER,
AND WE'LL SURVIVE, BECAUSE WE
ARE THE LIGHT OF BEACH CITY!
>> All: YEAH!
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> UH, YES.
THANK YOU, STEVEN!
I COULDN'T HAVE SAID IT BETTER!
>> DON'T TRY TO WORM YOUR WAY
OUT OF THIS!
>> OH, NO, NO!
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY! IT'S OKAY!
MAYOR DEWEY WAS HIDING THINGS
FROM YOU, BUT HE DID IT BECAUSE
HE DIDN'T WANT YOU TO WORRY.
HE WAS JUST SHELTERING YOU FROM
THE TRUTH BECAUSE HE -- HE LOVES
YOU.
[ ALL MURMURING ]
[ SCATTERED CHEERS ]
>> [ Chanting ] MAYOR DEWEY!
>> Pearl: OH, HEY, STEVEN.
IF I CAN JUST CONCENTRATE THE
WAVE A LITTLE MORE...
>> Steven: UM...DO YOU GUYS WANT
TO TALK?
>> Pearl: AND WHY WOULD WE NEED
TO DO THAT?
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN, YOU
STILL OWE US A GAME OF CARDS!
>> Garnet: YEAH, GET IN ON THIS.
>> Steven: N-NO!
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY CARDS!
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT PERIDOT!
>> Pearl: OH, YES!
WELL, EVERYTHING IS FINE!
>> Steven: NO, IT'S NOT!
I KNOW IT'S NOT.
I KNOW YOU -- YOU JUST DON'T
WANT ME TO BE SCARED, BUT JUST
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
>> Garnet: PERIDOT IS COMING,
AND WE DON'T KNOW WHO OR WHAT
SHE'LL BE COMING WITH.
SHE'S A MODERN GEM WITH MODERN
GEM TECHNOLOGY THAT'S BOUND TO
OVERPOWER US.
STEVEN, THE TRUTH IS...
WE'RE SCARED.
>> Steven: WE'VE BEEN SCARED
BEFORE, RIGHT?
NONE OF US KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN, BUT THAT'S OKAY.
WE CAN FIGURE THINGS OUT...
TOGETHER.
[ ALL GASP ]