>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: A 5, 6, 7, 8!
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
SYNCHRONIZE!
>> Steven: UNH!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Pearl: BE SERIOUS.
PAY ATTENTION NOW, STEVEN.
SEE?
>> Steven: MM.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
WHA!
UNH!
I DON'T GET IT.
I THOUGHT I ALMOST HAD IT.
>> Pearl: NOBODY EXPECTS YOU TO
BE ABLE TO PERFORM FUSION RIGHT
AWAY, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: YEAH!
IT'S REALLY HARD, EVEN FOR US.
>> Garnet: NOT FOR ME.
>> Pearl: WE'LL KEEP WORKING ON
THE DANCE FOR NOW, AND WHO
KNOWS?
IN A FEW YEARS...
I WONDER, THOUGH, IF STEVEN'S
BODY IS CAPABLE OF FUSION.
FUSION MERGES THE PHYSICAL FORMS
OF GEMS.
BUT STEVEN IS HALF HUMAN.
HE'S ORGANIC.
>> Steven: ORGANIC?
>> Amethyst: AWW, COME ON.
IT'S STEVEN!
WHO KNOWS WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Garnet: WELL, I THINK STEVEN
CAN DO IT.
>> CAN YOU GET THEM TO WRITE OUT
THE STEPS?
>> Steven: NO, I-I DON'T THINK
IT'S JUST ABOUT THE DANCING.
WHEN THEY FUSE, THEY GLOW AND
KIND OF PHASE INTO EACH OTHER.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN EVEN DO
THAT.
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S AMAZING
YOU WERE ABLE TO DANCE WITH THEM
AT ALL.
I COULD NEVER DO THAT.
>> Steven: HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I'VE...NEVER DANCED IN FRONT
OF ANYONE BEFORE.
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> [ SIGHS ] YEAH.
THERE WAS A DANCE AT MY SCHOOL,
AND I WAS REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT IT.
BUT...I JUST COULDN'T BRING
MYSELF TO GO.
I JUST COULDN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT EVERYONE STARING AT ME.
>> Steven: WELL...
NO ONE'S STARING RIGHT NOW.
>> UM...YOU ARE.
>> Steven: OH. YEAH.
UH, ONE SEC.
[ CLICKS ]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
SO, WHAT I WAS TRYING TO SAY
WAS...
COME DANCE WITH ME!
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
>> WHOA!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WHOA!
>> Steven: [ GIGGLES ]
>> HUNH!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> YEAH!
>> Steven: UNH!
UHH!
>> WHOA!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GIGGLES ]
>> Stevonnie: WHOA.
WHY AM I?
WHY IS...
YOUR SANDAL...
TOO SMALL FOR MY -- YOUR FEET?
STEVEN.
CONNIE!
I -- I DID IT!
YOU DID IT?
WAIT.
[ GRUNTS ]
THIS -- NO.
THIS IS...GREAT!
HA!
OH, MY GOSH.
LOOK AT YOU NOW!
I'M A FUSION.
[ LAUGHING ]
UNH! [ COUGHING ]
I HAVE TO SHOW EVERYBODY.
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
>> Pearl: HE FUSED?
WITH HIS FRIEND CONNIE?
>> Amethyst: [ GIGGLES ]
Pearl, look at Garnet.
>> Pearl: THIS IS UNPRECEDENTED.
A GEM FUSING WITH A HUMAN BEING?
I-IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
OR, AT THE VERY LEAST,
INAPPROPRIATE.
>> Amethyst: W-O-O-O-O-OW!
YOU TWO LOOK GREAT TOGETHER!
HOW DOES IT FEEL, STEVEN?
CONNIE?
STEVONNIE?!
>> Stevonnie: IT FEELS AMAZING!
>> Pearl: YES, WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE ENJOYING YOURSELVES, BUT
YOU TWO SHOULD UNFUSE THIS
INSTANT.
>> Stevonnie: WAIT. WHAT?!
PEARL, YOU WERE SO WORRIED
STEVEN WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO
THIS.
AREN'T YOU PROUD OF HIM?
>> Pearl: OF...COURSE I AM.
I --
GARNET, HELP ME OUT HERE.
>> Garnet: STEVONNIE...
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU ARE NOT TWO PEOPLE, AND YOU
ARE NOT ONE PERSON.
YOU...ARE AN EXPERIENCE!
MAKE SURE YOU'RE A GOOD
EXPERIENCE.
NOW GO...HAVE...FUN!
>> Stevonnie: WAAAAAH-HOO!
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
[ GIGGLING ]
[ STOMACH GURGLES ]
>> NO...
>> SURE...
>> LARS, SERIOUSLY, HE'S REALLY
NICE.
[ BELL DINGS ]
>> H-H-HOW...CAN I HELP...ME?
>> Stevonnie: TWO DOUGHNUTS,
PLEASE.
WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
>> UH...
>> OH, NOTHING!
I-IT'S ON THE HOUSE.
>> Stevonnie: REALLY?
>> Both: MM-HMM!
>> Stevonnie: OKAY!
BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW, THAT ISN'T
A VERY SOUND BUSINESS PRACTICE.
[ BELL DINGS ]
SWEET!
TWO DOUGHNUTS!
ONE FOR ME AND ONE...FOR...
UH, ME.
ARE YOU OKAY?
WE CAN STOP IF YOU...
NO!
NO, DON'T WORRY.
MMM.
OH, HEY, SOUR...FACED STRANGER.
WOW! COOL PANTS.
>> COO'.
RAVE TONIGHT.
>> Stevonnie: LIKE...A DANCE?
>> YEAH, AT THE WAREHOUSE.
I'M DEEJAYING, AND A BUNCH OF MY
FRIENDS FROM THE INTERNET ARE
GONNA BE THERE.
THERE'S GONNA BE FREE...
UH, GLOW STICKS.
>> Stevonnie: YES!
I'LL DEFINITELY BE THERE!
YES, THANKS!
>> COO'.
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> YEESH.
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> I'M AMAZING.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> Stevonnie: AH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
I...THOUGHT THIS WAS A DANCE
PARTY.
WHY ISN'T ANYONE ELSE DANCING?
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
THIS IS WHAT BEING COOL AT A
COOL DANCE IS, RIGHT?
THIS IS HOW IT'S...
SUPPOSED TO BE.
WHY...ISN'T IT LIKE IT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UH...
>> HEY, BABY.
>> Stevonnie: HUH?
>> GET READY.
IT'S KEVIN TIME.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> Stevonnie: UH...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S WRONG.
YOU HAVE FUN DANCING, BUT THIS
DANCE ISN'T FUN!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO LIKE THIS.
WHY DON'T WE LIKE THIS?
[ SIGHS ]
I WISH YOU WERE HERE.
IF WE WERE TOGETHER, IT WOULD BE
OKAY.
BUT WE ARE TOGETHER, AND IT'S
NOT.
I'M ALONE.
>> NOT TONIGHT.
HEY, BABY, WHY'D YOU LEAVE ME ON
THE DANCE FLOOR?
>> Stevonnie: I DON'T --
I DON'T WANT TO DANCE ANYMORE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE THE BEST THING THAT'S EVER
HAPPENED TO THIS PLACE.
COME BACK OUT WITH ME.
>> Stevonnie: WHY SHOULD I?
>> BECAUSE WE'RE ANGELS WALKING
AMONG GARBAGE PEOPLE.
WE'RE PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER.
>> Stevonnie: HOW CAN YOU SAY
THAT?!
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW US!
>> WHOA, WHOA.
I'M JUST LOOKING FOR A DANCE.
DON'T GET CRAZY.
>> Stevonnie: NO ONE IS CRAZY!
I JUST DON'T LIKE FEELING ALONE
HERE!
>> IF YOU'RE SO LONELY, THEN
DANCE WITH ME.
>> Stevonnie: UGH!
FINE.
YOU WANNA DANCE?
LET'S GO.
>> HUNH!
>> Stevonnie: AND IT'S
STEVONNIE.
I AM NOT YOUR BABY.
[ MUSIC INTENSIFIES ]
[ GRUNTING ]
>> OKAY, BRING IT BACK, GIRL.
>> Stevonnie: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Both: UNH!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> IT'S TWO KIDS!
I'M OUT!
>> Steven: WE'RE BACK.
>> [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
>> YE-E-E-E-E-AH!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ RAIN FALLING ]
>> Steven: OOH-HOO!
YOU GOT FREEZER BURNED, PEARL!
LOOKS LIKE YOU LOSE ALL YOUR
FISH STICKS.
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
I NEEDED THOSE FOR MY
"BACHELOR MEAL COMBO."
NOW I CAN'T RING THE DINNER
BELL.
[ SIGHS ]
THESE RULES MAKE NO SENSE.
>> Steven: THE GAME OF
CITCHEN CALAMITY MAY BE PLAYED
FOR FUN, BUT THE HUNGER IS REAL!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHING ]
TOUGH BREAK, PEARL.
"THE SPONGE IN YOUR SINK IS
COVERED IN MOLD."
BUT I CAN STILL EAT IT, RIGHT?
>> Steven: NO, NO, THAT MEANS
YOU LOSE TWO TURNS.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S BOLOGNA!
>> Pearl: WAIT!
YOU HAVE A BOLOGNA CARD?
>> Steven: GARNET, YOUR MOVE.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
>> Garnet: I'M NOW THE OWNER OF
THE GOLDEN CAN OPENER.
YESSSS.
>> Steven: NOW YOU CAN CHECK
YOUR SOUPS FOR THE ALPHABET
BONUS!
>> Pearl: WHO WROTE THIS GAME?
>> Steven: MY TURN!
[ MUMBLING ]
[ GASPS ]
I'VE GOT TO ROLL THE DICE TO
ESCAPE THE EGGQUAKE!
[ MOTOR WHIRRING ]
COME ON.
PAPA NEEDS A NEW SKILLET!
[ WHIRRING STOPS ]
YEAH! DOUBLE SUNNIES!
I DID IT!
I WIN!
YEAH!
THIS CITCHEN CALAMITY HAS BEEN
CLEANED UP!
WHOO-HOO!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Amethyst: I DON'T GET IT,
BUT NICE JOB.
>> Pearl: YES, WELL DONE.
THAT WAS VERY...VERY
COMPLICATED.
>> Garnet: WELL PLAYED.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO PLAY
NEXT?
>> Pearl: THERE ARE MORE?
>> Steven: OH, SURE!
I'VE GOT POLYPOLY, TOPPLER, AND
CONQUERORS OF ELDERMORE...
NOT THAT SORRY,
DON'T WAKE FATHER FIGURE, AND
NONINVASIVE OPERATION.
I THINK THAT ONE'S MISSING A
COUPLE ORGANS.
I ALSO HAVE CHECKERS, IF YOU
WANT TO TAKE TUR--
[ CLATTERS ]
[ GASPS ]
THE SEA SPIRE STATUE.
>> Amethyst: PFFT!
OH!
SO THAT'S WHERE YOU LEFT IT.
>> Steven: I...FORGOT I STILL
HAD THIS.
[ SIGHS ]
I -- I'M REALLY SORRY I FORGOT
IT ON OUR MISSION THAT TIME.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN...
>> Steven: IF I'D JUST
REMEMBERED TO PACK IT, THEN
MAYBE THE SEA SPIRE WOULD STILL
BE AROUND.
BUT NOW IT'S GONE FOREVER 'CAUSE
OF ME.
>> Amethyst: WELL, YEAH, BUT...
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, GUY.
>> Garnet: YOU DID YOUR BEST ON
THAT MISSION, AND THAT'S WHAT
COUNTS.
>> Steven: BUT THE SEA SPIRE!
IT WAS A SPECIAL, IMPORTANT
GEM...PLACE.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN, NO, NO,
NO.
IF THE SPIRE HAD BEEN CRUCIAL,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE USED IT AS A
TEST FOR YOU.
IT'S FINE, REALLY.
>> Steven: TEST?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "TEST"?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> Pearl: EH...
WELL, IT WASN'T REALLY A "TEST,"
PER SE, NOT IN THE TRADITIONAL
SENSE.
WE JUST WANTED TO SEE IF YOU
WERE READY TO GO ON MISSIONS.
>> Steven: THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT A
TEST IS!
>> Pearl: EH...
>> Garnet: STEVEN, IT WASN'T
SOMETHING WE PLANNED BEHIND YOUR
BACK.
WE JUST SAW AN OPPORTUNITY, AN--
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
AND I FAILED IT.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
I FAILED THE TEST.
>> Amethyst: NO WAY!
YOU GOT AT LEAST A 50%.
>> Pearl: OH! AND YOU HAD THAT
RAFT, SO WE DIDN'T HAVE TO SWIM
HOME.
THAT'S A SOLID 75!
NOT FAILING AT ALL!
BESIDES, THAT SPIRE WAS IN MUCH
WORSE SHAPE THAN WE THOUGHT.
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN EVEN EASIER.
>> Steven: I FAILED AN EASY
TEST?!
>> Amethyst: NICE ONE.
>> Garnet: [ GRUMBLES ]
>> Pearl: THAT'S NOT WHAT I
MEANT! I --
>> Steven: NO!
I NEED ANOTHER TEST -- A HARD
ONE!
>> Pearl: BUT, STEVEN, YOU'VE
COME SO FAR.
>> Steven: LET ME PROVE IT!
TEST ME! TEST ME!
>> Garnet: HMM...
>> Pearl: ALL RIGHT, STEVEN.
WE'VE ADJUSTED THE METAPHYSICAL
PROPERTIES OF THE TEMPLE TO
CREATE A CUSTOMIZED DUNGEON FOR
YOU.
NOW JUST BEYOND HERE ARE THREE
CHAMBERS DESIGNED BY EACH OF US
TO SIMULATE THE CHALLENGES OF A
MISSION.
SHOULD YOU SUCCEED, YOU'LL
UNLOCK THE FINAL DOOR, WHERE WE
WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, THIS WON'T BE
EASY.
BE CAREFUL IN THERE.
>> Steven: RIGHT.
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN THIS TIME.
>> Pearl: THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
>> Amethyst: YEAH!
GET AMPED, STEVEN!
>> Steven: I'M READY.
[ BELL CHIMES ]
>> Amethyst: GOOD LUCK!
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT!
[ BELL CHIMES ]
>> Steven: ROOMER-O UNO.
I WONDER IF AMETHYST MADE THIS
ONE.
[ GATE THUDS ]
[ GASPS ]
DEFINITELY AMETHYST.
[ PANTING ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
THE DOOR!
[ PANTING CONTINUES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
UNH! WHOA!
UNH!
>> Steven: WHA? UH-OH.
UH...
[ POP! ]
OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
HOW DO I GET UP THERE?
[ CHORDS PLAY ]
HUH?
HMM...
OH! A MUSIC PUZZLE.
MUST BE PEARL'S ROOM.
ONLY SHE WOULD MAKE ME THINK.
OKAY. LET'S SEE...
UM...
BING.
♪ BING ♪
DID THAT DO IT?
[ UPBEAT CHORD PLAYS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
EASY!
AAH!
NOT EASY!
[ PANTING ]
WHOO-HOO!
THAT...WAS CLOSE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
THAT WAS REALLY CLOSE.
[ SIZZLING ]
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE WHAT WE
GOT.
LOOKS LIKE GARNET...
TURNED UP THE HEAT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NICE ONE, STEVEN.
[ GASPS ]
AAAAAH...
HUH?
WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO.
IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
[ GRUMBLES ]
WHAT?!
[ CHORDS PLAY ]
[ UPBEAT CHORD PLAYS ]
IT DIDN'T EVEN MATTER?!
[ GASPS ]
THIS TOO?!
[ RUMBLING ]
EVERYTHING'S RIGGED!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
AH!
I...CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
AAH!
"IT WON'T BE EASY."
"GOOD LUCK!
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT!"
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO PROVE
MYSELF IF YOU GUYS KEEP --
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S TAKING HIM
SO LONG?
>> Pearl: I DIDN'T THINK MINE
WAS VERY DIFFICULT.
DO YOU THINK HE HURT HIMSELF?
>> Garnet: THERE'S NO WAY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR HIM TO FAIL.
>> Amethyst: UGH!
SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
>> Pearl: THE POINT IS THAT HE'S
COME SO FAR.
HE CAN MAKE ROSE'S BUBBLE, AND
HE'S PULLED OUT ROSE'S SHIELD
TWICE.
BUT HE'S LOST HIS HEALING
POWERS.
WE HAVE TO GIVE HIM ANOTHER
SUCCESS.
HE CAN'T LOSE HIS CONFIDENCE
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
>> Amethyst: WE'RE BAD AT THIS.
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YOU CAN'T
CONTROL HIM, AND HE SHOULDN'T BE
TAKING ADVICE FROM ME, AND WE
DON'T HAVE ROSE TO TELL US WHAT
TO DO!
>> Pearl: BUT HE NEEDS US TO
SHOW HIM HOW TO BE A GEM!
>> Garnet: STEVEN IS NOT JUST A
GEM.
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN ANYTHING OR
ANYONE LIKE STEVEN.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HE NEEDS.
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Garnet: CONGRATULATIONS.
>> Pearl: CONGRATULATIONS,
STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: YE-EAH!
CONGRATS, LITTLE MAN!
HOO HOO HOO HOO!
>> Pearl: YES. WELL DONE.
>> Garnet: YEAH, STEVEN!
YOU DID IT.
>> Amethyst: HOO!
HOO!
HOO.
>> Pearl: THANK GOODNESS YOU
MADE IT.
HOW DID IT GO?
>> Steven: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
GUYS.
THAT WAS SO...
INSANE!
WHERE DO I EVEN BEGIN?
MAN, YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN ME!
THAT BOULDER WAS COMIN' AT ME,
AND I JUST JUMPED FOR IT!
AND THEN, THE TILES WERE GOING
LIKE...
♪ BING BONG BING! ♪
AND I WAS LIKE, "I SEE WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE!"
AND I THOUGHT, "THERE'S NO WAY I
COULD'VE BEEN READY FOR ALL THAT
FIRE AND LAVA AND SPIKES," BUT I
DID IT!
I REALLY...
DID IT.
I...
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR DOING THIS
FOR ME.
THIS WAS JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: AWW!
SHUCKS, GUY!
>> Garnet: MMM.
>> Pearl: I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> Amethyst: YEAH! YOU DA MAN!
>> Garnet: I KNEW YOU COULD DO
IT.