>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHOA!
WHAT MAGICAL PLACE OF MYSTERIES
IS THIS?
>> Amethyst: WELL --
>> Pearl: OH, I'M SO GLAD YOU
ASKED.
THIS WAS ONCE A COMMUNICATION
HUB FOR GEM KIND.
BUT LATELY, IT'S BEGUN
TRANSMITTING BURSTS OF
ELECTROMAGNETIC INTERFERENCE.
>> Steven: WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
>> Garnet: IT'S HURTING
TELEVISION.
>> Steven: NO!
I'LL SAVE YOU, TELEVISION!
HYAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> Amethyst: SORRY, BUT WE NEED
A STEVEN AT LEAST [Deep voice]
THIS STRONG FOR THIS JOB.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
IT'S ALL THE ME I COULD BE!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, WE COULD BE
HERE ALL DAY TAKING OUT EACH OF
THESE PILLARS INDIVIDUALLY.
>> Amethyst: [ Normal voice ]
UGH, I HATE IT WHEN YOU'RE
RIGHT.
YOU GET THIS LOOK ON YOUR FACE.
YEAH, THAT'S THE ONE.
>> Pearl: WHAT WE NEED IS A
WELL-THOUGHT-OUT PLAN.
>> Garnet: NO.
WHAT WE NEED IS SUGILITE.
AMETHYST, FUSE WITH ME.
>> Both: WHAT?!
>> Amethyst: [ SQUEALS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH!
LET'S MASH IT UP!
BIGGER! BADDER! BETTER!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
>> Steven: HOLD YOUR HORSES!
ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO BECOME A
GEM FUSION?
>> Amethyst: AHH!
>> Both: AHHHHHHH!
>> Pearl: WAIT!
[ SIGHS ] GARNET, THINK ABOUT
THIS.
YOU AND AMETHYST CAN BE A LITTLE
[CHUCKLES] UNSTABLE WHEN YOUR
PERSONALITIES COMBINE.
WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL.
FUSE WITH ME INSTEAD.
>> Garnet: WE DON'T NEED TO BE
CAREFUL.
WE JUST NEED TO BE HUGE.
>> Amethyst: OH, YEAH!
LET'S WRECK THIS JOINT!
>> Garnet: SYNCHRONIZE.
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: WHAT -- WHAT --
PEARL, COME ON.
I WANT TO SEE.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
I FORGOT HOW GREAT IT FEELS TO
BE ME.
>> Steven: THAT'S SUGILITE?
>> YOU GOT IT, BABY.
HEY, STEVEN, WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING COOL?
>> Steven: YEAH!
[ GASPS ]
>> YOU LIKE THAT, LITTLE MAN?
>> Steven: ARE YOU GONNA SMASH
STUFF WITH YOUR WRECKING-BALL
THINGY?
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
WHERE SHOULD I START?
>> Steven: DO THAT ONE!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, I THINK WE
SHOULD GO.
>> Steven: NO WAY!
THIS IS AWESOME!
>> Pearl: WATCH IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
UGH! YOU'RE JUST TOO MUCH!
>> MAYBE YOU'RE JUST TOO LITTLE!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WE'RE GOING.
>> Steven: WHAT?! I'M FINE!
WHAT ABOUT SUGILITE?
>> Pearl: SHE CAN FIND HER OWN
WAY HOME.
>> Steven: AW.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
'SUP?
>> WHOA, STEVEN!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> Steven: OH, JUST A LITTLE
BATTLE DAMAGE FROM OUR LAST
MISSION.
>> REALLY?
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> Steven: I GOT HIT BY A ROCK!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> IT MUST NOT HAVE BEEN A VERY
BIG ROCK.
>> Steven: WELL, THERE'S...
INTERNAL BLEEDING.
MY HURT IS ON THE INSIDE!
>> OH, OKAY.
>> TOUGHEN UP, STEVEN.
>> Steven: YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SOFT.
>> IF I WEREN'T SO MODEST, I'D
WHIP OUT MY SWEET SIX-PACK AND
SHOW YOU WHAT [Straining] A REAL
MAN LOOKS LIKE.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ LID POPS ]
YEAH, I'M NOT GONNA SAY THANKS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: THAT'S IT!
WE ALL NEED A WORKOUT.
LET'S DO IT.
LET'S WORK OUT TOGETHER.
YOU COULD BEAT UP LARS, AND YOU
DON'T HAVE TO STARVE TO DEATH IF
SADIE DIVORCES YOU.
>> WE'RE NOT MARRIED.
>> Steven: AND I KNOW JUST THE
GUY TO HELP US OUT.
>> [ SNORING ]
>> Steven: WOW, THIS LOOKS
GREAT.
>> WHA-- WHAT?
>> Steven: HEY, DAD.
>> HEY, STEVEN.
YOU LIKE IT?
IT'S THE BEST I COULD DO ON SUCH
SHORT NOTICE.
>> NO KIDDING.
>> WELL, I MIGHT JOIN YOU KIDS,
SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
I'VE BEEN SLACKING ON MY WORKOUT
ROUTINE FOR A FEW WEEKS --
MONTHS -- YEARS.
[ Coughing ] DECADES.
>> Steven: SURE.
THE MORE THE MEATIER!
OH! WE'LL NEED SWEATBANDS.
[ PANTING ]
>> HEY, PEARL.
COME TO CHECK OUT SOME BUFF
STUDS?
>> Pearl: NO.
STEVEN, WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU UP
TO?
>> Steven: WE'RE STARTING A GYM.
I'MA GET SUPA-STRONG!
LIKE SUGILITE!
>> Pearl: YOU KNOW, MAYBE THIS
ISN'T A GOOD IDEA.
>> Steven: WHAT?
I WANT TO BE STRONG SO I CAN BE
USEFUL TO THE TEAM.
>> Pearl: THERE ARE DIFFERENT
WAYS OF BEING STRONG.
>> Steven: BUT I WANT TO BE
STRONG IN THE REAL WAY.
COME ON, PEARL.
LET'S GET BEEFY!
>> Pearl: I'D RATHER NOT.
[ SIGHS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
STEVEN.
♪ WHY DO YOU HAVE TO LOOK UP TO
HER? ♪
♪ ASIDE FROM IN A LITERAL
SENSE ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW THAT A POWER
THAT BIG ♪
♪ COMES WITH A BIGGER EXPENSE? ♪
♪ AND CAN'T YOU SEE THAT SHE'S
OUT OF CONTROL AND
OVERZEALOUS? ♪
♪ I'M TELLING YOU FOR YOUR OWN
GOOD ♪
♪ AND NOT BECAUSE I'M... ♪
♪ I COULD SHOW YOU HOW TO BE
STRONG ♪
♪ IN THE REAL WAY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT WE CAN BE
STRONG ♪
♪ IN THE REAL WAY ♪
♪ AND I WANT TO INSPIRE YOU ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE YOUR ROCK ♪
♪ AND WHEN I TALK,
IT LIGHTS A FIRE IN YOU ♪
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: WHO'S READY TO GET
BUFF?!
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOUR GUT!
I WANT TO SEE YOUR GUTS!
♪ I CAN SHOW YOU HOW TO BE
STRONG ♪
♪ IN THE REAL WAY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT WE CAN BE
STRONG ♪
♪ IN THE REAL WAY ♪
♪ AND I WANT TO INSPIRE YOU ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ I WANT TO BE
YOUR ROCK ♪
>> Both: ♪ AND WHEN I TALK,
IT LIGHTS A FIRE IN YOU ♪
♪ I WANT TO INSPIRE YOU ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE YOUR ROCK ♪
♪ AND WHEN I TALK,
IT LIGHTS A FIRE IN YOU ♪
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ ALL GROAN ]
>> [ Panting ] HEY, STEVEN,
MAYBE, UM, YOU COULD WORK OUT A
BIT, TOO.
>> Steven: HUH?
I HAVE BEEN.
>> WE'VE BEEN WORKING OUT.
YOU'VE JUST BEEN SINGING SOME
DUMB SONG.
>> BUT YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB
PUMPING US UP.
>> Steven: THANKS, BUT I NEED TO
GET STRONG, TOO.
I'M SWITCHING TO FOUR-WHEEL
DRIVE.
[ PANTING ]
[ SEA GULLS SQUAWKING ]
>> STEVEN, COME ON!
WE'RE READY TO GET STARTED.
WE CAN'T WORK OUT WITHOUT YOUR
MAD COACHING SKILLS!
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
BE THERE IN A SEC!
[ GROANS, GRUNTS ]
[ GROANING ]
SO SORE FROM GETTING RIPPED.
>> Pearl: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
AMETHYST AND GARNET STILL AREN'T
BACK YET.
I TRIED TO WARP BACK TO CHECK ON
THEM, BUT THE WARP PAD IS DOWN.
[ THUDDING ]
>> AAH!
>> WHAT'S THAT OUT IN THE WATER?
>> ARE YOU SEEING THIS, TOO?
>> Pearl: WHA--
>> Both: WHA--
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
[ THUDDING CONTINUES ]
>> WHAT THE HEY IS THAT?
>> AAH! [ GRUNTS ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> I'M BORED!
>> Steven: IT'S SUGILITE!
>> Pearl: Y-YOU'RE BACK!
>> YOU LEFT ME BEHIND.
>> Pearl: WE JUST THOUGHT YOU
DIDN'T NEED ANY HELP.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU SEPARATE, AND
WE CAN ALL SIT DOWN AND RELAX?
>> NO!
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'VE BEEN FUSED FOR TOO LONG.
YOU'RE LOSING YOURSELVES.
>> I AM MYSELF, AND I'M SICK OF
BEING SPLIT UP!
SO YOU BETTER GET USED TO ME,
BABY, AND GET THIS JUNK OFF MY
BEACH!
>> Steven: WHY IS SHE WRECKING
DAD'S GYM?
WHY IS SHE ATTACKING YOU?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> Steven: AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
I CAN'T MOVE.
>> WHAT? YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
>> Pearl: YOU'LL THANK ME LATER!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> COME ON, KID!
>> Steven: DAD, NO!
PEARL!
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE SOMETHING?
YOU...
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
>> ...AIN'T...
NOTHING!
>> Both: AAH!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
MY MUSCLES.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
[ GROANS ]
I'M SORRY, STEVEN...
GARNET, AMETHYST.
I WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH TO
PROTECT YOU.
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> Steven: COME ON, PEARL!
DON'T GIVE UP!
I KNOW YOU CAN TAKE HER DOWN!
>> Pearl: I CAN'T.
>> Steven: YES, YOU CAN!
COME ON.
YOU ALWAYS KNOW WHAT TO DO!
YOU'VE GOT TO SHOW HER WHAT YOU
SHOWED ME -- THAT YOU'RE STRONG,
PEARL -- STRONG IN THE REAL WAY!
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
>> WHAT?! YOU WANT SOME MORE?!
>> Pearl: ANYTIME!
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR ME!
NOT EVEN CLOSE!
>> Steven: GO!
>> GET BACK HERE!
[ LAUGHS ] NICE TRY.
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
YOU THINK THAT'S ENOUGH TO
BEAT -- UGH!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST! GARNET!
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Garnet: [ Weakly ] YEAH.
SUGILITE JUST OVERWORKED OUR
BODIES.
IT'S A LITTLE PAINFUL.
>> Amethyst: AND I'VE GOT A
MONSTER HEADACHE.
[ BOTH GROANING ]
>> Pearl: OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
WHOOPS.
>> Steven: PEARL, YOU DID IT!
>> Pearl: [ PANTING ]
THANKS.
YOU MAKE A GOOD COACH.
>> Garnet: PEARL [GROANS] WE
SHOULD HAVE LISTENED.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
>> Pearl: YEAH. I WAS RIGHT.
>> Steven: GO, PEARL!
>> Pearl: COME ON! I FEEL GREAT!
WHO'S UP FOR A MISSION?
>> Amethyst: HOW LONG IS SHE
GOING TO KEEP THIS UP?
>> Garnet: WE DESERVE IT.
TAKE IT LIKE A GEM.
>> UH, WHAT THE HECK JUST
HAPPENED?
>> Steven: DROP AND GIVE ME 20!
>> Steven: THIS IS IT, FOLKS.
ROOKIE SENSATION STEVEN UNIVERSE
READIES HIS LAST SPOONFUL OF
KERNEL'S CLASSIC CREAMED CORN.
AS THE CROWD WAITS WITH BATED
BREATH, ONE BITE BETWEEN HIM AND
DESTINY.
[ CHOMP! ]
[ GULP! ]
AND HE'S DONE IT!
HE'S EATEN FOUR CANS OF CREAMED
CORN!
>> Pearl: GOOD AFTERNOON,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: GUYS, CHECK THIS OUT!
>> Amethyst: STU-MAN IN THE
HOUSE.
WHATCHA GOT? WHATCHA GOT?
>> Steven: I GOT FOUR EMPTY CANS
OF COLONEL KERNEL'S CLASSIC
CREAMED CORN.
>> Garnet: COOL.
>> Steven: YEAH.
AND ON THE BACK ARE $5 COUPONS
FOR MINI GOLF.
I ATE FOUR CANS SO THAT WE COULD
ALL GO TOGETHER.
>> Pearl: THAT'S SO THOUGHTFUL,
STEVEN.
UNFORTUNATELY, THOUGH, UH...
>> Amethyst: WE GOT TO GO ON A
MISSION.
>> Steven: WHAT?
NOT AGAIN!
BUT YOU GUYS PROMISED WE'D HANG
OUT.
>> Garnet: A DANGEROUS ARTIFACT
HAS APPEARED IN THE NORTHERN
HEMISPHERE.
WE NEED TO GO RETRIEVE IT.
>> Steven: BUT MINI GOLF IS SO
MUCH FUN!
THERE'S CASTLES AND WINDMILLS
AND I LIKE IT AND -- OH, LOOK!
LOOK WHAT I BROUGHT.
I PULLED OUT MY DAD'S OLD CLUBS
AND ALSO FOUND A PAIR OF HIS OLD
GOLF PANTS.
THEY'RE A LITTLE BIG ON ME, BUT
YOU CAN WEAR THEM, GARNET.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
>> Amethyst: SEE YOU, BUDDY.
>> Pearl: WE'LL BRING YOU
SOMETHING BACK.
>> Steven: WELL, YOU'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONES WITH A DANGEROUS
ADVENTURE TO TACKLE.
OH, YEAH!
YOU RECEIVED THE MYTHRIL PUTTER.
DOO-DOO-DOOT-DOOT DOOT-DOO!
"DON'T WORRY, PROFESSOR, WE'RE
GONNA SINK 'EM ALL!"
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH-OH!
OH, WINDMILL, WHY MUST WE ALWAYS
FIGHT?
>> PAR!
>> Steven: MAN, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN JUST LIKE THIS.
[ BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: "I CAN'T LOSE!
I AM THE GREATEST GOLFER IN THE
UNIVERSE!"
[ MIMICS EXPLOSIONS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
ALL RIGHT!
SECRET ENDING!
>> Pearl: HEY, STEVEN.
WE'RE BACK.
>> Steven: HEY.
>> PROJECT F.L.O.G.?
THAT'S "GOLF" BACKWARDS.
WHAT IS THIS?
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN.
WANT TO HEAR ABOUT WHERE WE'VE
BEEN?
>> Steven: UH, OH -- WAIT! WAIT!
HOLD ON.
>> JUNE 9, 2014?
BUT THAT WAS THE DAY HE
DISAPPEARED...
>> Steven: HEY!
>> Garnet: STEVEN, LOOK AT THIS.
>> Amethyst: IT'S THE
WAILING STONE WE FOUND.
>> Garnet: THE WAILING STONE I
FOUND.
>> Pearl: ISN'T IT NEAT?
IT USES HIGH-FREQUENCY SOUND
WAVES...
>> Steven: GUYS...
>> Pearl: ...WITH A MESSAGE
RELAY BETWEEN TWO FIXED
POINTS...
>> Amethyst: YOU JUST HAVE TO
PUSH THIS!
[ WHIR! SCREECH! ]
[ POP! ]
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, I TOLD YOU
NOT TO TURN IT ON IN THE HOUSE.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
CHILL OUT, P.
IT'S NOT LIKE ANYONE GOT HURT,
AND STEVEN LOVED IT.
STEVEN?
>> Steven: THAT WAS THE SECRET
ENDING!
NOW I HAVE TO REPLAY THE FINAL
DUNGEON ALL OVER AGAIN.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
I CAN'T GO MINI GOLFING, I CAN'T
PLAY MY GAME, I CAN'T STOP GOING
TO THE BATHROOM 'CAUSE I ATE ALL
THAT CREAMED CORN.
[ SIGHS ]
I JUST WISH I HAD A PLACE FOR
MYSELF.
[ HUMMING ]
HUH?
MY GEM!
[ HUMMING INTENSIFIES ]
>> Pearl: ROSE'S DOOR.
STEVEN, YOUR GEM IS OPENING YOUR
MOTHER'S ROOM.
>> Steven: WHOA.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WAIT!
>> Garnet: STEVEN, DON'T GO IN
THERE!
>> Steven: IT'S NEVER ABOUT WHAT
I WANT TO DO, IS IT?
WELL, NOW I HAVE A PLACE WHERE
I'M GOING, AND YOU CAN'T COME!
>> All: STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
YES!
WHOA.
SO, THIS IS MY MOM'S ROOM?
SHE MUST HAVE LIKED CLOUDS A
LOT.
BUT WHAT KIND OF ROOM DOESN'T
EVEN HAVE A BED?
AAH!
COOL.
HMM.
THIS BED IS PRETTY NICE, BUT YOU
KNOW WHAT WOULD BE REALLY NICE?
QUADRUPLE BUNK BEDS!
[ GASPS ]
WITH A SLIDE.
WHOO-HOO!
A PARACHUTE!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT NEXT?
HMM.
UM...
A TINY FLOATING WHALE?
[ WHALE SINGS ]
>> Steven: [ GIGGLES ]
WOW.
HERE I GET ANYTHING I ASK FOR.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I REALLY WANT?
I WANT TO SEE THE END OF MY GAME
WITHOUT BEING INTERRUPTED.
>> IT'S ME, YOUR FATHER.
AFTER DECADES OF CRYO-STASIS,
I'M FINALLY FREE.
>> SAVING THE DAY IS JUST PAR
FOR THE COURSE.
>> Steven: AWESOME.
[ YAWNS ]
HMM. KIND OF HUNGRY NOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
ALL RIGHT.
WHA--?
HEY!
I WANT A REAL DOUGHNUT.
WHAT?!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
[ WHALE SINGS ]
NOW I HAVE TO GO OUT FOR
DOUGHNUTS.
>> Steven: DON'T GET EXCITED,
GUYS.
I'M ONLY BACK FOR A SECOND.
WELL...GOOD.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SEE YOU ANYWAY.
>> Steven: HEY!
HOW'S MY FAVORITE FINE-FOODS
FRANCHISE?
SO, I'M THINKING
DOUBLE-CHOCOLATE CINNAMON TWIST
WITH SPRINKLES ON THE SIDE.
YOU KNOW I LIKE TO DIP.
UH...
STEVEN TO SADIE AND LARS.
IS THIS, LIKE, A JOKE OR
SOMETHING?
>> Together: HELLO, STEVEN.
WHAT KIND OF DOUGHNUT WOULD YOU
LIKE?
>> Steven: UH, I JUST SAID --
>> Together: IT'S VERY NICE TO
SEE YOU, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WELL, IT'S VERY NICE
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
>> Together: HERE ARE YOUR
DOUGHNUTS.
>> Steven: WAIT.
YOU GUYS, I ONLY ORDERED --
>> Together: OKAY.
WE LOVE YOU, STEVEN.
BYE-BYE NOW.
>> Steven: WAIT!
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS GOING?
I STILL HAVEN'T PAID FOR THESE.
YOU GUYS, HOLD ON A --
SEC.
HUH?
HEY, ONION!
HAVE YOU SEEN LARS AND SADIE?
THEY SHOULD HAVE JUST BEEN OUT
HERE.
HEY, IF YOU SEE THEM, LET ME
KNOW, OKAY?
HERE. HAVE A DOUGHNUT.
I'LL LEAVE IT HERE FOR YOU.
SEE YOU LATER.
ALL THE LIGHTS ARE ON, BUT NO
ONE'S HERE.
PEE DEE?
OH.
FRY BITS.
USUALLY I'M ALL ABOUT THE BITS,
BUT I'M FEELING KIND OF SPOOKED
RIGHT NOW.
GAH!
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M GONNA GO LOOK AROUND
SOME MORE.
SEE YOU LATER, FRYBO.
AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
CONNIE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S YOU.
WHEN DID YOU GET BACK IN TOWN?
HUH?
AAH! THE WATER!
CONNIE, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
>> HE WAS INCREDIBLE!
>> Steven: UH?
HE WAS INCREDIBLE!
>> Steven: WH-WH-WHAT?
>> HE WAS INCREDIBLE!
>> Steven: GET ME OUT OF HERE!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR FACES?
LION, YOU TOO?!
[ GASPS ]
CAN SOMEONE PLEASE EXPLAIN
THIS?!
HUH!
[ EXCLAIMS ]
[ THUD! ]
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: DAD?
IS THAT YOU?
>> WHAT? OF COURSE.
ARE YOU DOING ALL RIGHT?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU SAW A GHOST.
EITHER THAT OR YOU STAYED UP ALL
NIGHT PLAYING A VIDEO GAME.
>> Steven: DAD, I'M FREAKING
OUT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M STUCK INSIDE OF
SOME CRAZY DREAM.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHY DON'T WE SHARE SOME OF THOSE
DOUGHNUTS AND YOU CAN TELL ME
ABOUT THIS CRAZY NIGHT YOU'RE
HAVING?
[ CHOMP! ]
>> Steven: THE GEMS WERE TRYING
TO TELL ME SOMETHING ABOUT MOM'S
ROOM.
BUT I WAS SO MAD I DIDN'T
LISTEN.
THEY'RE ALWAYS LEAVING ME
BEHIND, AND I GUESS I WANTED TO
DO IT TO THEM, TOO.
>> THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
EVERYONE NEEDS SOME ALONE TIME
NOW AND THEN.
[ MIMICS GUITAR RIFF ]
[ CHOMP! ]
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, IT WAS REALLY FUN FOR A
WHILE.
BUT NOW, THE WHOLE CITY --
EVERYONE AND EVERYTHING IS
ACTING REALLY WEIRD.
>> WELL, THE IMPORTANT THING IS
YOU TOLD THE TRUTH.
>> YEAH...I...GUESS I DID.
[ MIMICS GUITAR RIFF ]
[ CHOMP! ]
>> Steven: UH, DAD?
YOUR ADVICE IS MAKING LESS SENSE
THAN USUAL.
>> WELL, THE IMPORTANT THING IS
FAMILY AND FRIENDSHIP, HONESTY,
VALUES, AND NO ONE GOT ARRESTED.
[ MIMICS GUITAR RIFF ]
[ CHOMP! ]
>> Steven: AAH!
I'M STILL IN THE ROOM!
ALL OF THIS -- IT'S ALL A
FAKE-A-ROO!
>> [ MIMICS GUITAR RIFF ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
AAH!
THIS IS ALL WRONG!
HUH?
AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EXCLAIMS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
I DON'T WANT THIS.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: I WANT TO BE BACK
WITH THE GEMS.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ] GARNET!
[ CHOMP! ]
>> Garnet: OW.
>> Steven: YOU'RE NOT CLOUDS!
>> Amethyst: ALL RIGHT, STEVEN!
[ CHOMPS! ]
>> Pearl: [ EXCLAIMS ]
>> Steven: GUYS, IT WAS AWFUL.
I WAS TRAPPED IN A MESSED-UP
VERSION OF BEACH CITY.
EVERYONE WAS ACTING SUPER WEIRD
AND --
>> Amethyst: YOU HAD ROSE'S ROOM
BUILD THE WHOLE TOWN?!
>> Pearl: IT CAN'T HANDLE A TASK
LIKE THAT.
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE OKAY.
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
I'M SORRY I GOT MAD, GUYS.
I GET IT NOW.
THINGS CAN'T ALWAYS GO EXACTLY
HOW I WANT.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN, WE'RE
SORRY, TOO.
>> Amethyst: MM-HMM.
>> Garnet: BUT GUESS WHAT.
WE HAVE TIME TO HANG OUT NOW.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: I ALWAYS GET WHAT I
WANT.