>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ SIREN WAILING ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
I CAN SEE WHY THIS IS YOUR
FAVORITE FILM FRANCHISE!
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IN A WORLD WHERE HUMANITY IS
PUSHED TO THE BRINK, IT TURNS
OUT THAT THE ONE WHO IS MOST
HUMAN IS A DOG...COPTER.
>> Steven: AND DID YOU SEE WHERE
THAT MISSILE CAME OUT OF?!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH.
I JUST HOPE IT STAYS FAITHFUL
TO THE BOOK.
[ GASPS ]
AH...
>> Steven: THE GEMS ARE BACK.
>> Garnet: GREETINGS.
>> Pearl: OH!
W-WELL, HELLO, CONNIE!
WHAT A SURPRISE TO SEE YOU!
>> Steven: WE'RE GONNA WATCH A
MOVIE ABOUT A WACKY FLYING DOG!
SHOW THEM, CONNIE!
>> I MEAN, IT'S ABOUT MUCH MORE
THAN THAT.
[ DOG BARKS ]
>> Amethyst: OH, THAT'S EASY.
>> WHA?
>> Amethyst: WHO NEEDS TO GO
SEE MOVIES WHEN YOU'VE GOT
MAGIC?!
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Pearl: UGH.
>> Steven: AW, STOP SHOWING OFF,
AMETHYST.
CONNIE PROMISES THIS MOVIE'S
EVEN BETTER THAN ANY MAGIC!
>> I DID NOT SAY THAT.
>> Steven: AND CHECK THIS OUT!
WE GOT OUR OWN SNACKS!
>> MY PARENTS SAY I'M NOT
ALLOWED TO BUY SNACKS AT THE
THEATER.
SO WE'RE NOT BUYING ANYTHING AT
THE THEATER.
>> Amethyst: NOM NOMS!
FEED ME!
>> Steven: HANDS OFF, AMETHYST!
THESE ARE FOR CONNIE AND ME TO
SHARE AT THE MOVIE.
>> SPEAKING OF WHICH, HOW ARE WE
GETTING TO THE THEATER?
IT'S KIND OF FAR.
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT IT COVERED.
TODAY WE'RE GONNA TRAVEL IN
STYLE.
INTRODUCING THE FINEST IN LUXURY
TRANSPORTATION...
LION!
>> [ YAWNS ]
>> Steven: AW, YOU LITTLE
GOOFBALL.
>> YOU HAVE A PET LION?!
>> Steven: LION IS SORT OF LIKE
A PET.
HE DOES HIS OWN THING MOST OF
THE TIME, THOUGH.
>> [ CHOMPING ]
>> Steven: SEE?
WHO KNOWS WHERE HE GOT THAT?
>> WOW, STEVEN.
EVERYTHING IN YOUR LIFE IS SO
AWESOME AND MAGICAL.
THE MOST EXCITING THING IN MY
LIFE IS TENNIS PRACTICE.
FOREHAND!
BACKHAND!
OVERHEAD DEATH STRIKE!
>> Steven: WHOA! TENNIS IS RAD!
>> WELL, I MADE UP THAT LAST
ONE.
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> Steven: I THINK LION SAYS WE
SHOULD HURRY UP AND GO.
OR MAYBE HE WAS JUST YAWNING.
ANYWAY, LET'S GO TO THE MOVIE!
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: AND WE'RE OFF!
UHH...
LION, I WANT YOU TO TAKE US TO
THE MOVIE.
OKAY, YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO
ME.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
LION ISN'T TRAINED VERY WELL.
BUT I'M NOT TRAINED VERY WELL
EITHER, SO WE'RE A --
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Both: WHOA!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
WHOA!
>> Steven: WAIT, LION!
DON'T GO IN THE OCEAN!
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
YOU CAN WALK ON WATER?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME YOU CAN
DO THESE THINGS YOU DO?!
HEYO!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> UH...
ARE YOU SURE HE KNOWS WHERE HE'S
GOING?
>> Steven: MAYBE IT'S A SHORT
CUT.
>> [ ROARS ]
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
>> HAS HE EVER DONE THIS?
>> Steven: NO, THIS IS NEW!
[ BOTH GROAN ]
>> Both: WHOA!
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> THAT WAS REALLY COOL.
>> [ ROARS QUIETLY ]
>> Steven: LION!
WAIT! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
[ GASPS ]
>> OOF!
WHOA!
IS THIS ONE OF THOSE...
MAGIC GEM PLACES THAT YOU'VE
TOLD ME ABOUT?
>> Steven: YEP.
MAGIC GEM PLACE.
LION, NORMALLY I'M ALL ABOUT
THIS STUFF, BUT THIS IS NOT THE
MOVIES.
>> [ ROARS QUIETLY ]
>> Steven: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN,
LION?
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
>> WHAT IF HE BROUGHT YOU HERE
FOR A REASON?
>> Steven: WELL, MAYBE, BUT IF
WE DON'T HURRY, WE'RE GONNA MISS
THE COMMERCIALS, AND THEN WE
MIGHT MISS THE PREVIEWS, AND WE
STILL HAVE TO FIND THE PERFECT
SEATS NEAR THE FRONT BUT NOT TOO
CLOSE.
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> HEY.
I THINK IT LIKES YOU!
>> Steven: AH! AAAH!
MY HAND'S STUCK!
IT WON'T [GRUNTS] COME OFF!
>> HANG ON!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
MAN, THAT'S REALLY STUCK ON
GOOD.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO CHOP IT
OFF.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> HEY, SWORDS!
>> Steven: NO!
>> WHOA! HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW.
>> DO IT AGAIN! DO IT AGAIN!
>> Steven: UM, OKAY.
[ GRUNTING ]
ANYTHING?
>> NO.
HERE.
>> Steven: OW! WHAT ARE YOU --
HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MAYBE IF I DO...THIS!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
WAIT, I'M TICKLISH.
[ LAUGHING ]
WAIT. STOP. STOP.
I'M GONNA PEE!
>> WHOA.
LOOK AT ALL THIS ARMOR!
>> Steven: PRESS MY NOSE.
PRESS MY NOSE!
>> BOOP!
>> Steven: ARE THOSE LIGHT
CANNONS?
>> NEXT!
>> Both: AXES!
SPIKY CHAIN BALLS!
A GIANT...
>> Steven: PENNY?
>> DOES THAT MEAN ITS WORTH MORE
THAN A REGULAR PENNY?
>> Steven: WELL, THAT WOULD
MAKE "CENTS."
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> THIS IS SO GREAT, BUT...
I GET THE FEELING, THOUGH, I'M
NOT REALLY SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
>> Steven: I WANT YOU HERE!
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT YOU HERE.
I GUESS LION WANTS US HERE.
BUT I WANT US TO BE AT THE
MOVIES!
AND I WANT TO SEE LOTS OF
EXPLOSIONS.
[ GASPS ]
[ WHIRRING]
>> [ GASPS ]
SHOULD WE BE WORRIED ABOUT THIS?
>> Steven: UH...
>> [ YAWNS ]
>> Steven: LION DOESN'T SEEM TO
BE WORRIED.
[ CRACKLING ]
RUN!
[ GASPS ]
CONNIE!
>> STEVEN!
LOOK OUT!
>> Steven: AH!
HUH?
>> STEVEN!
WHAT DO WE DO?!
AH!
>> Steven: CONNIE!
[ GRUNTING ]
AH!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
MY BUBBLE.
[ GASPS ]
LION!
GET US OUT OF HERE!
LION, PLEASE!
[ WHIRRING, CRACKLING ]
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: WHAT?
NOW YOU TAKE US TO THE MOVIES?
>> Both: WHOA!
[ BOTH GROAN ]
>> AH.
>> Steven: CONNIE, HERE.
I HAVE SOMETHING FOR THAT.
SORRY.
THEY'RE NOT THAT COLD.
>> THANKS.
>> Steven: WELL, WE'RE HERE.
SHALL WE GO IN?
>> THAT'S OKAY.
L-LET'S JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
>> Steven: HUH?
I-I'M SORRY!
UGH!
I RUINED EVERYTHING, DIDN'T I?
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU HANG OUT
WITH ME.
I MESS STUFF UP ALL THE TIME.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU HANG OUT
WITH ME!
I'M SO MUCH MORE...LESS
INTERESTING THAN YOU!
AND OBVIOUSLY YOU HAVE SOME
SORT OF MAGICAL DESTINY.
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN CARE ABOUT
SOMETHING LIKE DOGCOPTER?
>> Steven: WHY?!
BECAUSE IT'S DOGCOPTER!
HE'S A DOG AND A HELICOPTER AND
A COP!
HE SHOOTS MISSILES OUT HIS BUTT,
AND HE'S GONNA SAVE THE WORLD!
DOGCOPTER IS VERY COOL AND
IMPORTANT...
TO ME.
>> WELL, I'M NO DOGCOPTER.
>> Steven: WHAT THE --
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> OH, NO!
>> Steven: IT'S THE ROBOT
SHOOTY THING!
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BEAT IT?
LION, WHAT DO WE DO?
UH...
THIS IS WEIRD, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE A SWORD IN YOUR HEAD?!
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME YOU CAN
DO THESE THINGS YOU DO?!
>> IT CAME THROUGH!
>> WHOA!
>> Steven: WHAT DO I DO WITH
THIS?!
>> WATCH OUT!
FOREHAND!
BACKHAND!
>> Both: OVERHEAD...
DEATH STRIKE!
[ WHIRRING, CLANGING ]
>> JUST LIKE TENNIS PRACTICE.
>> Steven: MAGICAL DESTINY
PRACTICE.
HI!
>> UH, HELLO.
>> Steven: TWO KIDS AND ONE LION
TO SEE "DOGCOPTER."
>> [ SNORTS SOFTLY ]
>> UM, DO YOU HAVE A REWARDS
CARD?
[ BEEPING ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
WAS THAT IN THE BOOK?
>> EH, THEY'RE TAKING SOME
LIBERTIES.
>> [ ROARS QUIETLY ]
>> Amethyst: AAAAAAAH!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Amethyst: OOMPH!
>> Pearl: UGH!
>> Garnet: UH!
>> Pearl: YOU OKAY, STEVEN?
>> Steven: I'VE SEEN BETTER
DAYS.
>> Amethyst: PEARL, I GOT A
BOO-BOO.
>> Pearl: OH, WALK IT OFF.
>> Garnet: HERE IT COMES.
YOU ALL DISTRACT IT!
>> Pearl: LET'S SHOW THIS THING
WHAT WE'RE MADE OF, GUYS!
>> Amethyst: WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE'VE BEEN DOING FOR THE PAST
HOUR?
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
DUCK!
>> Amethyst: HUH?
MAN, I DON'T SEE ANY D--
QUACK!
>> Steven: STEVEN'S TURN!
[ GRUNTS ]
YUP! IT'S GOT SPIKES!
>> Amethyst: IT'S OKAY!
HERE COMES GARNET!
>> Steven: SMASH THAT PUFF!
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
HURRRRRR!
UUUUH!
AAAAAH!
>> Steven: AW, MAN!
WE BLEW IT!
>> Amethyst: UGH, WHATEVER!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRACK ]
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
SMACKING IT REALLY FAR AWAY
DOESN'T SOLVE ANYTHING!
WE NEEDED TO DESTROY IT.
NOW IT'S JUST GONNA COME BACK
LATER.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, SO WE'LL DEAL
WITH IT LATER.
>> Pearl: UGH.
>> Steven: LET'S GET GARNET.
SHE LANDED BY THE BOARDWALK.
>> WOULD YOU ANSWER ME?!
YOU'VE WRECKED MY SIGN AND NOW
YOU'RE JUST SITTING UP THERE!
ARE WE ENGAGED IN A SECRET
STARING CONTEST?!
>> Steven: GARNET!
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Garnet: I'M FINE.
>> HI, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
THIS PLACE IS WRECKED!
GIVE ME ONE DOWN LOW.
>> Pearl: NO ACCOLADES FOR YOU,
AMETHYST.
SHE KNOCKED THE PUFFER FISH BACK
OUT INTO THE OCEAN!
>> Amethyst: NARC!
>> Garnet: LET'S REGROUP BACK AT
THE TEMPLE.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHAT ABOUT MY SIGN?
STEVEN!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
ONE OF THEM BUSTS UP MY SIGN,
THEN THEY ALL JUST JUMP INTO THE
SKY LIKE SOME CIRCUS ACT WITHOUT
EVEN OFFERING TO HELP!
>> Steven: BUT, MR. PIZZA!
>> DAD, PIPE DOWN!
>> OH!
DID I INTERRUPT YOUR BEAUTY
SLEEP?
>> [ YAWNS ]
I DON'T NEED SLEEP TO LOOK
PRETTY.
>> NOW YOU LISTEN HERE, YOUNG
WOMAN!
>> KOFI, YOU ARE GOING TO WAKE
THIS FISH FROM THE DEAD WITH ALL
THE NOISE YOU'RE KEEPING.
OH! TOO LATE.
"KOFI, YOU SO LOUD!
AAAAAH!"
BLEH.
>> GUNGA, YOU'RE SO FUNNY.
>> MOM, QUIT JOKING AROUND!
LOOK WHAT THEY DID TO MY SIGN!
>> CHEESE ON BREAD!
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
YOU'RE SUCH A NICE BOY, STEVEN.
WHY DO YOU HANG OUT WITH THOSE
ANIMALS?
>> Steven: THEY'RE NOT ANIMALS!
THEY'RE THE CRYSTAL GEMS AND
THEY PROTECT HUMANIT--
>> I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
>> HEY, GIRLS, I THINK I HEAR
ALL OF OUR CELLPHONES RINGING.
>> GUNGA, YOUR HEARING IS SO
GOOD.
>> STEVEN, YOU CAN TELL YOUR
FRIENDS THAT THEY ARE OFFICIALLY
BANNED FROM FISH STEW PIZZA!
>> Steven: WAIT! WHAT?!
KOFI, THAT'S NOT FAIR!
THIS WAS JUST AN ACCIDENT!
>> Amethyst: WHAT IF WE JUST,
LIKE, LET IT ROAM FREE?
>> Garnet: THAT'S NOT AN OPTION.
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN.
>> Steven: I'VE GOT BAD NEWS,
EVERYONE.
YOU'VE ALL BEEN BANNED FROM
FISH STEW PIZZA.
>> Pearl: OH! UH, THAT'S OKAY.
>> Amethyst: THAT PIZZA WASN'T
EVEN GOOD.
>> Steven: AREN'T YOU GUYS UPSET
ABOUT THIS?
>> Garnet: NOT AT ALL.
>> Steven: BUT THESE ARE OUR
NEIGHBORS.
>> Garnet: THERE'S NOTHING WE
CAN DO ABOUT THAT NOW.
>> Pearl: RIGHT NOW WE HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO TAKE CARE OF
THAT PUFFER FISH.
>> Steven: WHAT'S THE POINT OF
SAVING PEOPLE IF THEY'RE JUST
GONNA BAN YOU FROM THEIR PIZZA
SHOPS?
>> Garnet: WE DON'T DO IT FOR
THANKS.
>> Steven: YEAH, SEE?
THAT IS SO NICE OF YOU!
THE PIZZAS DON'T EVEN KNOW!
IF THEY GOT TO SPEND SOME TIME
WITH YOU, THEY'D SEE HOW FUN AND
SMART AND MYSTERIOUS YOU ARE.
>> Garnet: HEH. MYSTERIOUS.
>> Steven: HMM.
[ GASPS ] I KNOW!
I'LL THROW A LITTLE PARTY ON THE
BEACH IN FRONT OF THE TEMPLE!
JUST US AND THE PIZZAS!
>> Amethyst: I DON'T KNOW,
STEVEN.
I MEAN --
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING!
MAN, THIS IS GONNA BE SO GOOD!
[ SNIFFS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN.
>> Steven: HEY!
>> Pearl: GOT EVERYTHING READY
FOR YOUR LITTLE PARTY?
>> Steven: YEAH.
THERE'S ONE MORE THING.
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THIS FOR?
>> Steven: I WAS THINKING YOU
GUYS COULD CHANGE YOUR OUTFITS.
>> Pearl: WHAT'S WRONG WITH WHAT
WE HAVE ON NOW?
>> Steven: NOTHING!
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULD BE NICE
TO GO KIND OF CASUAL.
>> IS THIS THE RIGHT ADDRESS?
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS SIDE OF
THE BEACH BEFORE.
>> Steven: OH, MAN, THEY'RE
HERE.
HURRY UP AND CHANGE.
OVER HERE, EVERYONE!
HI!
>> HEY, STEVEN.
>> HELLO.
>> Steven: HOW'RE YOU ALL DOING
TODAY?
>> THE SHOP IS CLOSED TODAY
BECAUSE IT'S BROKEN.
>> Steven: UH...UH, OH!
THAT SOUNDS, UH...
>> HEY, DO I SMELL HOT DOGS?
SHOW ME WHERE THE HOT DOGS ARE.
>> Steven: OH!
RIGHT THIS WAY, EVERYONE.
FIRST, LET ME INTRODUCE --
>> Garnet: WE ARE THE CRYSTAL
GEMS!
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
BUT YOU ALREADY KNEW MY NAME.
>> OH! YOU'RE ALL SO TALENTED!
>> SO, YOU ARE A CIRCUS ACT.
>> Pearl: CIRCUS ACT?
>> Steven: HEY, LET'S EAT!
>> Amethyst: AAH! [ CHOMPS ]
>> EVERYTHING CAME OUT GREAT.
>> Steven: THANKS, KIKI.
>> AREN'T YOU GIRLS HUNGRY?
YOU BARELY TOUCHED YOUR FOOD.
>> Garnet: WE DON'T NEED TO EAT.
>> OH, YOU YOUNG PEOPLE AND YOUR
EXPERIMENTAL DIETS.
>> Garnet: I AM MUCH OLDER THAN
YOU.
>> SO, YOU ALL LIVE IN THAT TINY
HOUSE UP ON THAT HILL?
>> Garnet: WE INHABIT THE INNER
SANCTUMS ONLY ACCESSIBLE THROUGH
MAGICAL EXTRADIMENSIONAL DOORS.
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOUR HAND?
>> WHY'S THIS PLACE LOOK LIKE
IT'S FALLING APART?
>> Pearl: WELL, THE TEMPLE HAS
BEEN HERE FOR THOUSANDS OF
YEARS.
>> OH, I SEE HOW IT IS.
WHEN SOMETHING BREAKS AROUND
HERE, YOU JUST LEAVE IT ALONE,
JUST LIKE THE SIGN AT MY SHOP!
>> Steven: UM...WHO WANTS TO
PLAY VOLLEYBALL?
OKAY, EVERYONE, THE COURT IS ALL
SET.
NOW TO GET INTO OUR TEAMS.
>> Pearl: BUT, STEVEN, WON'T OUR
ABILITIES GIVE US AN UNFAIR
ADVANTAGE?
>> Steven: THAT'S WHY I'M
PICKING THE TEAMS.
♪ AMETHYST AND JENNY! ♪
♪ PEARL AND KIKI! ♪
♪ GARNET AND KOFI! ♪
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST --
♪ YOURS TRULY AND NANEFUA! ♪
>> I HAVEN'T PLAYED IN AGES, BUT
I BET I COULD WHOOP ALL YOUR
BUTTS.
>> Steven: THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
YOU GUYS READY?
LET'S PLAY!
>> Amethyst: HOPE YOU'RE READY
TO LOSE, PEARL!
>> Pearl: THERE'S NO WAY I'D
LOSE TO SOMEONE LIKE YOU!
>> Amethyst: HERE WE COME!
>> [ GRUNTS ] HYAH!
>> Pearl: NICE ONE, KIKI!
>> AND POW!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Steven: AMETHYST, NO KICKING!
>> Amethyst: PSH!
WHAT KIND OF GAME IS THIS?
>> Pearl: NICELY DONE, KIKI.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: TRY AND STICK TO THE
RULES, AMETHYST.
>> TRY HARDER, JENNY.
>> HERE IT COMES.
UGH! COME ON, JENNY!
>> WHAT?
I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
>> Amethyst: HA! MY MOVE!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> YES!
>> Pearl: THAT WAS UNCALLED FOR,
AMETHYST.
>> YOU AFRAID OF GETTIN' A
LITTLE SAND IN YOUR HAIR, KIKI?
>> NO, JUST TRYING TO KEEP TIDY.
>> Pearl: THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH TRYING TO KEEP TIDY.
>> SO EXCITING!
>> Steven: YEAH!
>> OUR TURN.
>> Garnet: I'M READY.
>> I GOT THIS ONE.
>> JENNIFER, YOU TOUCH THAT
BALL, YOU'RE GROUNDED!
>> WHOA!
DADDY, YOU CHEATIN'!
>> [ LAUGHING ]
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE!
>> Garnet: THIS IS GOING TO BE
EASY.
>> IT'D BE NICE IF THEY STUCK TO
THE BASICS.
>> Amethyst: TAKE THIS, GARNET.
HYAH!
>> Garnet: HUUUUR!
>> WE SHOULD PROBABLY MOVE, HUH?
>> Amethyst: YEAH, WE SHOULD.
>> OH! OH, GEEZ!
>> [ LAUGHING ]
YOU'RE ALL RUNNING LIKE WILD
CHICKENS!
>> Both: WHOA!
>> DID YOU KNOW THAT WHEN SAND
IS SUPERHEATED, IT TURNS INTO
GLASS?
>> Steven: I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> WHOA.
>> Amethyst: LET'S PLAY!
>> AAH!
>> Amethyst: WHOO!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
>> HYAH!
>> Pearl: AAAAAAH!
OVER HERE, AMETHYST. OVER HERE!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: AAH!
>> KOFI TIME!
>> JENNY TIME!
>> YOU CAN'T USE THE CAR FOR A
MONTH!
>> DADDY!
>> Amethyst: WHY ARE YOU
CHEATING SO MUCH?
>> Garnet: YOU CHEATED FIRST.
>> THAT IS NOT TRUE.
>> THIS IS GETTING OUT OF HAND.
[ INDISTINCT ARGUING ]
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
I'LL RUN AND GET THE BALL.
[ ARGUING CONTINUES ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
HEY, WHY'S IT GETTING SO...
WINDY?!
AH, NO! IT'S BACK!
PUFFER FISH MONSTER'S BACK!
>> WHAT'S ALL THE --
>> Steven: NANEFUA, RUN!
>> Amethyst: WE SHOULD WIN
'CAUSE WE'RE THE BEST.
>> Y'ALL CHEATED!
>> Pearl: CHEATERS!
>> Garnet: YOU'RE OUT OF LINE.
>> EVERYONE IS GROUNDED HERE.
>> Steven: GARNET!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
OH, NO!
GEMS, PROTECT THE PIZZAS!
>> HEY! WHAT IS GOING ON?!
>> Steven: THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I WAS TRYING TO GET EVERYONE
TOGETHER, BUT NOW EVERYONE'S IN
DANGER.
>> I'M NOT AFRAID OF THAT THING.
LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN KEEP UP
WITH ME!
>> Steven: OF COURSE I CAN!
>> [ GRUNTS ] OVER HERE!
>> Steven: NO! OVER HERE!
COME ON!
>> Pearl: OH, MY GOSH! STEVEN!
>> WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
>> Steven: EVERYBODY, GET READY!
>> MOM, YOU ARE CRAZY!
>> Garnet: NOT CRAZY. BRAVE.
>> GUNGA, CAREFUL WITH YOUR
BACK!
>> Steven: AMETHYST, TURN
YOURSELF INTO A BALL!
>> Amethyst: OKAY!
>> JENNY, ROLL AMETHYST TO THE
NET AND THEN HOLD ON!
>> SURE THING!
>> PEARL, HEAD OVER TO JENNY AND
AMETHYST!
>> Pearl: YES, MA'AM!
>> HIT AMETHYST INTO THE AIR AS
HARD AS YOU CAN!
>> Pearl: WITH PLEASURE.
[ KNUCKLES CRACK ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> KOFI, KIKI, GET OVER TO THE
NET.
>> Steven: GARNET, SPIKE THE
BEACH!
>> Garnet: I UNDERSTAND.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: BE GENTLE.
>> Garnet: I'LL TRY.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: YOWCH!
UUURRRREEEEE!
>> HERE COMES THE TRICKY PART.
>> Steven: I'M READY!
>> EVERYONE, TAKE THE NET TO THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE COURT.
>> Steven: OKAY, EVERYONE, PULL
THE NET INTO ITS FACE!
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
>> IT'S NOT ENOUGH!
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY!
HERE COMES GARNET!
>> THANKS FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY.
>> AND?
>> AND FOR SAVING MY FAMILY.
YOU ARE ALL OFFICIALLY UNBANNED
FROM MY SHOP.
>> Steven: AWW!
THANK YOU SO MUCH, KOFI!
WE REALLY APPRECIATE IT, RIGHT,
GUYS?
>> Garnet: OKAY. YES. THANKS.
>> Steven: AAAAND?
>> Pearl: WHAT WERE WE BANNED
FROM AGAIN?
>> Steven: HE-HE-HE...HEH...EHH.