>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: HYAH!
>> Steven: HELP ME! SAVE ME!
HELP ME!
SAVE ME!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Pearl: WHAT ON EARTH?
>> Steven: TAG! YOU'RE IT!
>> Pearl: CARE TO EXPLAIN --
UGH! -- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> Amethyst: IT'S STEVEN TAG.
STEVEN TAGGED YOU.
NOW YOU HAVE TO TURN INTO
STEVEN.
>> Garnet: IT'S THE RULES.
>> Pearl: OH, PLEASE.
>> Steven: AW, NO FAIR!
>> Amethyst: SO, THAT MEANS
WE'RE OUT OF PLAYERS.
GET READY FOR STEVEN TAG.
ADVANCE -- UNH!
>> Garnet: TAG.
>> Amethyst: AAH!
[ GROANS ]
>> Garnet: GARNET WINS.
>> Steven: ♪ I GUESS I CAN'T WIN
EVERY GAME OF STEVEN TAG ♪
♪ IT MAY BE MY NAME ♪
♪ BUT IT'S JUST NOT MY GAME ♪
>> STOP!
THIS IS A RESTRICTED ZONE!
ONLY THOSE WITH SPECIAL
CLEARANCE MAY ENTER!
>> Steven: MAY...I HAVE SPECIAL
CLEARANCE?
>> HMM.
GRANTED.
NOW THAT YOU'RE PROPERLY SUITED,
LET'S INVESTIGATE!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> SEE THOSE HOLES?
THEIR SHAPE AND PATTERN IS
REPEATED OVER AND OVER.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
SOME MIGHT SAY IT'S COINCIDENCE.
I SAY THERE'S SOMETHING...MORE!
>> Steven: LIKE WHAT?
A DOUBLE COINCIDENCE?
>> YOU'D ALREADY BE IN THE KNOW
IF YOU FOLLOWED MY BLOG --
KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD!
I DOCUMENT ALL THE WEIRD THINGS
THAT HAPPEN IN BEACH CITY!
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS TRUST FACTS AND
BOOKS!
I'M OUT HERE HUNTING THE TRUTH!
>> OH, THERE YOU ARE!
DAD WANTS YOU BACK AT THE SHOP!
YOU'RE MISSING OUT ON VALUABLE
FRYING TIME!
>> IT'S WEIRD TIME, PEEDEE!
I'M DOING BIG STUFF!
COVER FOR ME!
>> FINE.
BUT THIS IS THE LAST TIME, OR
I'M TELLING DAD!
BIG STUFF...
I'LL GIVE YOU BIG STUFF.
>> SO, YOU WANT TO GET YOUR
HANDS REALLY DIRTY?
THEN FOLLOW ME.
>> Steven: YEAH!
I CAN'T WAIT TO FIND SOMETHING
PARANORMAL!
>> Shh!
I'M PICKING UP A QUANTUM FLUX
ON THE WEIRDOMETER.
THERE!
>> Steven: WHOA!
DID THEY FALL FROM THE SKY?
>> MY RESEARCH SUGGESTS THEY
GREW UP FROM THE GROUND.
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
RONALDO!
LOOK AT THIS.
>> ACCORDING TO AN ONLINE
ENCYCLOPEDIA, WHICH I AM A
USER/EDITOR OF, THIS SPECIES
ISN'T INDIGENOUS TO THIS REGION.
OR THIS
DIMENSION-SION-SION-SION!
WE LIVE IN A STRANGE WORLD,
STEVEN -- STRANGER THAN MOST
KNOW -- STRANGER THAN THEY CARE
TO KNOW.
TAKE MY BROTHER, FOR INSTANCE.
HE'S ALWAYS GETTING ON MY CASE,
TELLING ME TO WORK MORE.
HE'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
BUT, STEVEN, I CAN TELL YOU'RE
LIKE ME.
>> Steven: YEAH!
>> I KNOW YOU'RE SOMEONE I CAN
TRUST.
YOU'RE READY FOR WHAT I'VE
FOUND -- THE CAUSE OF
BEACH CITY'S PARANORMAL
ACTIVITY.
>> Steven: WAIT. WHAT?
>> WELCOME TO MY OFFICE.
GO THAT WAY.
WELCOME...TO THE TRUTH.
>> Steven: SNAKE PEOPLE?!
>> SNAKE PEOPLE, OR "SNEOPLE",
CONTROL OUR GOVERNMENT AT THE
HIGHEST LEVEL.
LOOK, THE SNAKE REPRESENTS THEIR
HOLD ON OUR COUNTRY.
THE DIAMOND REPRESENTS THEIR
UNDERGROUND MINES OR THEIR
SHARP TEETH.
THE DETAILS AREN'T IMPORTANT!
THEY PIT US MAMMALS AGAINST EACH
OTHER WITH ELECTIONS, SPORTS,
AND ANIME MESSAGE BOARDS.
WE SPEND SO MUCH TIME FIGHTING
OVER "DUBS" OR "SUBS" THAT WE
MISS THE BIG PICTURE!
>> Steven: WHAT'S THAT?
>> THAT THE WORLD IS UNDER THEIR
CONTROL.
>> Steven: AAAAAAH!
[ PANTING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, DON'T SLAM THE
DOOR!
>> Steven: AMETHYST! PEARL!
WE NEED TO SNAKE-PROOF THE
HOUSE!
>> Pearl: WHY?
>> Steven: TO STOP THE
SNAKE PEOPLE!
>> Amethyst: UH...SNAKE PEOPLE?!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: WHAT'S SO FUNNY ABOUT
SNEOPLE?!
LOOK AT THIS!
>> Pearl: THAT MUST BE FROM WHEN
WE FOUGHT THOSE DRILL PARASITES
ON THE BEACH.
>> Steven: WHA?
WELL, WHAT ABOUT THIS?
>> Amethyst: THAT LOOKS LIKE
PIECES OF THAT RED EYE THAT WE
BLEW UP.
>> Steven: WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THIS?!
>> Pearl: OH, IT'S THE FLOWERS
FROM ROSE'S MOSS!
>> Steven: IS ALL THE WEIRD
STUFF THAT HAPPENS AT BEACH CITY
BECAUSE OF US?
>> Pearl: WELL, YEAH, OBVIOUSLY.
>> Steven: I NEED SOME AIR.
RONALDO?
>> STEVEN!
DID YOU SEE THIS CRATER?
I THINK THE SNAKE PEOPLE MIGHT
HAVE LEFT IT AS A SIGN.
>> Steven: YEAH...
UH, RONALDO?
>> YES, STEVEN?
>> Steven: ARE YOU TOTALLY SURE
ABOUT THIS SNAKE PEOPLE THING?
>> STEVEN, ARE YOU HAVING
DOUBTS?
>> Steven: NOT REALLY JUST...
DOUBTS.
I FOUND OUT THOSE WEIRD HOLES IN
THE CLIFF WERE 'CAUSE OF
SOMETHING ME AND THE GEMS DID.
>> WELL, OKAY, BUT THOSE RED
ROCKS --
>> Steven: THAT WAS US.
>> BUT...THE FLOWERS.
>> Steven: US TOO.
>> BUT -- BUT THE TRUTH!
>> Steven: MAYBE THE TRUTH JUST
ISN'T WHAT YOU THOUGHT IT WAS.
>> SURE IT IS!
DON'T GET SO HUNG UP ON THESE
MINOR FACTS.
TRUTH IS ABOUT MORE THAN THAT.
TRUTH IS A FEELING IN YOUR GUT
THAT YOU KNOW IS TRUE.
TRUTH IS SEARCHING FOR ANYTHING
THAT PROVES YOU'RE RIGHT, NO
MATTER HOW SMALL, AND HOLDING
ON TO THAT, NO MATTER WHAT.
>> Steven: THAT KIND OF SOUNDS
LIKE THE OPPOSITE OF TRUTH.
>> LOOK! THE PROOF!
THIS CAST WILL SHOW THE TRUE
FACE OF THIS CONSPIRACY!
OH, HUH?
>> Steven: THAT'S PROBABLY FROM
STEVEN TAG.
>> WHAT?!
>> Steven: IT'S A GAME WHERE,
WHEN I TAG ONE OF THE GEMS,
THEY --
>> I'M REALLY NOT AT THE CENTER
OF ANYTHING.
[ WIND BLOWING ]
I'M NOTHING.
>> Pearl: WHAT'S WRONG, STEVEN?
>> Steven: I THINK I BROKE
RONALDO'S HEART.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN.
HUMANS JUST LEAD SHORT, BORING,
INSIGNIFICANT LIVES, SO THEY
MAKE UP STORIES TO FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE A PART OF SOMETHING
BIGGER.
THEY WANT TO BLAME ALL THE
WORLD'S PROBLEMS ON SOME SINGLE
ENEMY THEY CAN FIGHT INSTEAD OF
A COMPLEX NETWORK OF
INTERRELATED FORCES BEYOND
ANYONE'S CONTROL.
>> Amethyst: IT'S SAD.
AND FUNNY!
>> Pearl: DON'T FEEL BAD ABOUT
IT, OKAY?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE WAS EVER GOING
TO BE RIGHT.
STEVEN?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> Steven: I'M GONNA GO FIX
RONALDO!
I'LL BE BACK IN AN HOUR.
>> [ WHISTLING ]
YO, RONALDO!
EH, SO...
SEE ANYTHING WEIRD LATELY?
>> NO.
EVERYTHING'S NORMAL.
>> Steven: [ HISSING ]
SNAKEMEN ARE REAL, AND WE'RE
PUPPETING THE GOV'MENT!
[ HISSING ]
>> AAH!
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
[ LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY ]
HYAH!
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
WAKEY WAKEY, MISTER SNAKEY.
WAVE FORMS SEEM TYPICAL FOR A
12th-DIMENSIONAL BEING OF THIS
SIZE.
ARMS APPEAR TO BE...VESTIGIAL.
>> R-RONALDO?
IS THAT...
ONE OF THE MONSTER PEOPLE YOU'VE
BEEN HUNTING?
>> Steven: [ MUFFLED SHOUTING ]
>> NO, NO, NOT MONSTER, PEEDEE.
SNERSON.
IT'S VERY SCIENTIFIC!
STILL...
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
>> WHAT'S THIS FOR?
>> FOR ME, IN CASE THE
AMPHIBINOIDS TURN MY BODY INTO A
HOST VESSEL!
>> N-O-O-O!
>> PEEDEE, PEEDEE, PEEDEE!
YOU GOT TO LOOK AT THE BIG
PICTURE HERE!
SOMETHING IMPORTANT IS FINALLY
HAPPENING TO ME!
[ CRASHING, RUMBLING ]
>> Garnet: HELLO.
>> Pearl: WE KNOW YOU HAVE OUR
STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: GIVE HIM UP, CURLY!
[ GRUMBLES ]
ROWR ROWR!
>> [ GASPS ]
YOU SNAKE PEOPLE...
HIDING LIKE COWARDS IN YOUR
FALSE HUMANOID EXTERIORS!
STEVEN'S GOT NOTHING TO DO WITH
THIS!
IT'S ME YOU WANT!
OHH!
RRRRRRR-AAH!
AAH!
AH! AH! AH!
YOU SNONSTER!
AAAAAAAH!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
AAH! UGH!
>> STEVEN?!
>> OKAY, OKAY!
YOU'VE FORCED ME TO USE MY
ULTIMATE WEAPON!
STAND BACK!
PSYCHIC GHOST POWERS...
ACTIVATE!
[ INDISTINCT CHANTING ]
[ CHANTING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: EVERYBODY STOP!
I'M OKAY!
>> Garnet: NICE PANTS.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> STEVEN, YOUR LEGS!
WHEN DID THEY GET TO YOU?
>> Steven: RONALDO!
IT'S NOT REAL!
IT WAS JUST ME...AGAIN.
>> THAT...MAKES NO SENSE.
>> Steven: I JUST WANTED TO
INSPIRE RONALDO TO BE WEIRD
AGAIN.
>> NO! IT -- IT JUST ISN'T THAT
SIMPLE!
THERE'S GOT TO BE MORE TO IT
THAN JUST...YOU!
>> UM...
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> BUT THERE IS MORE!
STEVEN IS JUST UH...UH...
A SMALL PIECE OF THE PUZZLE.
LOOK AT THIS!
I THINK IT'S GOT TO BE...UM...
[ GASPS ]
LEVEL-8 BEINGS PULLING THE
STRINGS.
>> GET REAL, PEEDEE.
LEVEL-8 BEINGS ARE A WORKER
SOCIETY INCAPABLE OF SUCH
ORGANIZATION.
WHOA. WAIT A MINUTE!
HOW DID I NEVER SEE THIS
BEFORE?!
I KNOW WHAT THE DIAMOND MEANS.
POLYMORPHIC-SENTIENT ROCKS!
[ LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY ]
>> Steven: YOU SURE HE'LL BE
BETTER LIKE THAT?
>> YEAH.
HE'S HAPPY, YOU KNOW?
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> THEY'RE HERE TO HOLLOW OUT
THE EARTH!
IT'S PART OF THE GREAT DIAMOND
AUTHORITY!
THEY'LL TAKE ON ANY FORM!
YOU CAN READ ALL ABOUT IT ON
MY BLOG!
>> DOCTOR, IT'S MY SON.
THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I --
>> I KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
NURSE!
>> YES, DOCTOR?
>> PREP THE PATIENT FOR
EMERGENCY SURGERY.
WE'RE GONNA GO...
UNDER THE KNIFE.
>> UGH! THIS SHOW IS SO GOOD!
AAAH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR LETTING ME
WATCH "UNDER THE KNIFE" HERE,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: HOW COME YOU CAN'T
WATCH THE SHOW AT HOME?
>> MY MOM SAYS THIS DOESN'T
REPRESENT A REAL EMERGENCY ROOM.
>> HOW DID HIS LEGS...
GET INTO...HIS BRAIN?!
>> SHE JUST DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
THAT IT'S SATIRE.
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
>> Steven: IS THAT YOUR PHONE?
>> IT'S PROBABLY MY MOM.
CALLED IT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
HI, MOTHER. IT'S CONNIE.
MM-HMM. YES, MA'AM.
I'M AT THE HOME OF
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
MM-HMM.
YES, MA'AM.
WE'RE -- WE'RE JUST HANGING OUT.
OH. STEVEN'S PARENTS.
THEY'RE, UH -- THEY'RE IN THE
OTHER ROOM.
YOU WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO
STEVEN'S MOM?
OH, OKAY.
HOLD ON A MOMENT.
>> Steven: THAT'S GONNA BE
PRETTY HARD SINCE MY MOM GAVE UP
HER PHYSICAL FORM TO MAKE ME.
>> I CAN'T TELL HER THAT.
[ BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Steven: GARNET, QUICK -- YOU
HAVE TO PRETEND TO BE MY MOM TO
CONNIE'S MOM.
>> Garnet: HELLO.
THIS...IS MOM UNIVERSE.
YES.
THE CHILDREN ARE PLAYING SWORDS.
SORRY -- PLAYING WITH SWORDS.
THEY'RE BLEEDING.
OH, NO. THEY ARE DEAD.
DON'T CALL AGAIN.
SORRY. I PANICKED.
[ BOING! ]
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOUR MOM WON'T LET YOU COME
OVER?
IT'S THE MIDSEASON PRE-FINALE OF
"UNDER THE KNIFE"!
>> STEVEN, MY PARENTS ARE REALLY
UPSET.
THEY SAY THE WILL NOT LET ME SEE
YOU AGAIN UNTIL THEY MEET BOTH
OF YOUR PARENTS IN PERSON.
>> Steven: BUT THAT'S
IMPOSSIBLE!
>> I KNOW, BUT THEY WANT BOTH OF
OUR FAMILIES TO GO OUT TOGETHER
FOR DINNER.
>> Steven: IT SOUNDS SO...ADULT.
I WONDER IF FISH STEW PIZZA WILL
TAKE RESERVATIONS FOR -- PEARL,
GARNET, DAD, AMETHYST -- ALL
EIGHT OF US.
>> YOU CAN'T BRING EVERYBODY!
>> Steven: WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE -- BECAUSE...
I TOLD MY PARENTS YOU HAVE A
NUCLEAR FAMILY.
>> Steven: NUCLEAR?!
SURE, THEY MAKE STUFF BLOW UP
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE MAGIC, NOT RADIOACTIVE!
>> STEVEN, "NUCLEAR" MEANS TWO
ADULTS AND THEIR CHILD AND/OR
CHILDREN.
MY PARENTS THINK YOU LIVE WITH
YOUR MOTHER AND FATHER.
>> Steven: BUT NONE OF THAT IS
TRUE.
YOU NEVER TOLD YOUR MOM AND DAD
ABOUT THE CRYSTAL GEMS?
>> NO, AND IT HAS TO STAY THAT
WAY.
IF THEY FIND OUT I LIED TO THEM,
THEY'LL NEVER LET ME HANG OUT
WITH YOU AGAIN.
>> [ GRUNTING ]
AHH.
>> Steven: HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
CHOOSE JUST ONE OF YOU TO BRING
TO DINNER?
YOU'RE ALL SO...COOL!
>> Pearl: WHY DOES IT HAVE TO BE
DINNER?
WE GET ALL THE ENERGY WE NEED
FROM OUR GEMS, AND WHILE OUR
HUMAN CONSTRUCTS ARE CAPABLE OF
EATING, I FIND IT VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> Amethyst: I LOVE EATING!
[ CHUCKLES ]
FEELS WEIRD.
[ MUNCHING ]
>> Steven: OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S FOCUS.
WHICH OF YOU WOULD MAKE THE BEST
AND MOST NUCLEAR MOM?
GARNET, YOU KEEP US SAFE BY
SCARING OFF THE BAD GUYS, JUST
LIKE A MOM WOULD.
BUT YOU'RE NOT THE BEST
CONVERSATIONALIST.
AMETHYST, YOU WOULD BE A
SUPERFUN MOM!
>> Amethyst: [ MUNCHING ]
>> Steven: CAN MOMS BE GROSS?
>> Amethyst: WHY NOT?
>> Steven: PEARL!
YOU'RE ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT ME,
YOU TEACH ME LOTS OF STUFF,
YOU'RE APPROACHABLE, AND YOU'RE,
LIKE, TOTALLY NOT GROSS.
>> Amethyst: [ MUNCHING ]
>> Pearl: UH...
>> Steven: BUT YOU CAN'T EAT
DINNER.
MAN, WHY DID CONNIE HAVE TO SAY
I HAVE ONE MOTHER INSTEAD OF
ZERO...OR THREE?
>> WE'LL FIGURE THIS THING OUT.
WE JUST HAVE TO PUT OUR HEADS
TOGETHER.
>> Steven: WHY DIDN'T I THINK OF
THIS BEFORE?
IT'S SO OBVIOUS!
YOU CAN ALL COME TO DINNER --
ALL THREE OF YOU, FUSED INTO
ONE!
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
>> WHAT?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU KNOW WE
ONLY FUSE IN DEADLY SITUATIONS!
>> Steven: IT'D BE LIKE -- LIKE
I'M ACTUALLY BRINGING MY WHOLE
FAMILY!
>> Amethyst: THAT'S INSANE.
>> Garnet: FUSION IS SERIOUS
MAGIC, NOT A TRICK FOR DINNER
PARTIES.
>> Steven: I KNOW.
THEN I GUESS THIS IS IT.
I'LL NEVER GET TO SEE CONNIE
AGAIN.
OH, CONNIE!
I'LL NEVER KNOW A STAR THAT
SHINES AS BRIGHT AS YOU.
[ CRYING ]
>> Garnet: [ SIGHS ]
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
[ SLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> [ GROANS ]
>> WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR NEARLY
20 MINUTES.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GULLS CRYING ]
>> [ GASPS ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ RUMBLING CONTINUES ]
>> UH...OH.
>> Steven: HI, CONNIE!
HI, MR. AND MRS. MAHESWARAN!
>> THANKS...HONEYBUNS.
>> Alexandrite: YOU'RE
WELCOME...GREG.
>> I'M GREG UNIVERSE.
AND THIS MASSIVE DRINK OF WATER
IS MY WIFE, ALEXANDRITE.
>> Alexandrite: [ Awkwardly ]
H-I-I-I-I-I-I.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ MUNCHING ]
>> I HOPE THIS PLACE HAS
UNLIMITED BREADSTICKS.
>> DON'T BE RUDE.
>> Alexandrite: [ MUNCHING
CONTINUES ]
BLEH.
>> [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
ISN'T MY WIFE A RIOT?
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
>> SO, TELL ME -- HOW DID YOU
TWO MEET?
>> HUH? HOW DID WE MEET?
WELL, WE, UM --
>> Steven: THEY MET ON A ROLLER
COASTER!
SHE WAS TOO TALL TO RIDE!
>> UH...
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
I REMEMBER IT LIKE IT WAS
YESTERDAY.
RIGHT, HONEY?
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
EH...SORRY.
>> Alexandrite: HAVE SOME MORE
BREADSTICKS...DEAR.
>> UH [COUGHS] WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU TWO DO FOR A LIVING,
MR. AND MRS. UNIVERSE?
>> WELL, YOU SEE, I OWN A LOCAL
CAR WASH, AND MY SWEET, DEAR
WIFE HERE --
>> Steven: MY MOM WORKS ON AN
APPLE FARM!
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT DID WE SAY ABOUT HEADS
ON THE TABLE?
>> Steven: SHE USES ALL HER ARMS
TO PICK APPLES OUT OF HUGE
TREES.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY
SAY -- AN APPLE A DAY KEEPS THE
DOCTOR AWAY.
>> YES. I HATE DOCTORS.
>> WELL, I'M A DOCTOR.
>> STEVEN, HELP ME FIND THE
RESTROOM!
>> Steven: THINGS ARE GOING
PRETTY GOOD SO FAR, HUH?
>> STEVEN, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
WHAT IS THIS THING THAT YOU
BROUGHT TO DINNER?!
>> Steven: IT -- IT'S MY FAMILY.
IT'S ALL THE GEMS FUSED TOGETHER
INTO A SIX-ARMED, GIANT WOMAN.
>> WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST BRING
ONE OF THE GEMS?
>> Steven: 'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE
A LIE.
YOUR GLASSES.
>> WHAT ABOUT THEM?
>> Steven: I HEALED YOUR EYES.
YOU DON'T EVEN NEED TO WEAR
THOSE ANYMORE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> Steven: ALL THAT STUFF YOU
TOLD YOUR PARENTS ABOUT MY
FAMILY -- YOU'RE JUST ASHAMED OF
ME!
>> OH, WHATEVER, STEVEN.
LET'S JUST FOCUS ON GETTING
THROUGH THE EVENING.
>> SO, STEVEN WAS TELLING ME
THAT ON HIS MOM'S APPLE FARM,
THEY'RE BIOENGINEERING A
GALA-FUJI HYBRID.
>> Steven: YES, THAT'S
DEFINITELY TRUE.
>> ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
MRS. UNIVERSE?
>> [ SNIFFS ]
UGH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M HUNGRY!
I DON'T THINK SO.
CUT IT OUT, YOU TWO.
[ GRUNTING ]
GRRRRR-UGH!
[ CHOMPS ]
>> Steven: STOP!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EAT IT!
>> Alexandrite: [ MOANING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Alexandrite: [ GROANING ]
[ POP! ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
OHH. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW HORRIFIED IT
WAS WHEN THAT DRECK NEARLY FELL
INTO OUR MOUTHS.
EATING FOOD IS SO DISGUSTING!
YOU CHEW IT INTO NASTY MUSH,
SWALLOW THAT GOOP, AND IT COMES
OUT OF YOU?
WHAT A COMPLETELY HORRID
EXPERIENCE!
>> Amethyst: UH, SPEAK FOR
YOURSELF.
HA! I LOVE IT WHEN MUSH PASSES
THROUGH MY BODY.
>> Garnet: IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU TWO THINK.
WE'RE DOING THIS FOR STEVEN!
>> Both: AAH!
>> WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
WHO ARE THEY?!
>> I KNEW I SHOULD HAVE TRUSTED
MY BAD FEELINGS ABOUT THIS NEW
FRIEND OF YOURS, BUT I NEVER
THOUGHT I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
TRUST MY OWN DAUGHTER.
>> Steven: CONNIE!
[ OWL HOOTING ]
CONNIE.
>> STEVEN, I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S NOT THAT I'M ASHAMED OF
YOU.
I WAS SO WORRIED THAT MY PARENTS
WOULD THINK ALL THIS MAGIC STUFF
IS WEIRD.
WHAT IF THEY DON'T LET ME HANG
OUT WITH YOU ANYMORE?
[ CRYING ]
>> Steven: I-I'M SORRY I MESSED
EVERYTHING UP.
I WISH THERE WAS A WAY WE COULD
JUST HANG OUT WITHOUT HAVING TO
WORRY ABOUT STUFF.
>> STEVEN, LET'S JUST HOP ON A
BUS AND LIVE SOMEWHERE ELSE
WITHOUT TELLING ANYONE!
>> Steven: THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
WHERE'S THIS BUS TAKING US?
>> WHEREVER WE END UP.
WE'LL FIND A WAY TO SURVIVE.
I'VE BEEN READING ABOUT
SUSTAINABLE LIVING.
>> Steven: MAYBE IT'LL TAKE US
TO A REAL APPLE FARM!
>> WHAT'S UP WITH YOU AND APPLES
TODAY?
[ THUMPING ]
>> Both: HUH?
[ THUMPING CONTINUES ]
>> Alexandrite: STEVE-E-E-N!
>> Both: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Alexandrite: YOU TWO, COME
OUT OF THAT BUS THIS INSTANT!
>> Steven: AAH! OKAY!
J-JUST PUT THE BUS DOWN FIRST.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
BEGIN WITH YOU, YOUNG LA--
>> Pearl: WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING, RUNNING OFF WITH
CONNIE LIKE THAT?
YOU COULD HAVE GOTTEN YOURSELVES
HURT!
>> Garnet: OR GOTTEN MANGLED IN
TRAFFIC.
>> Amethyst: OR THROWN IN
PRISON.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU ARE IN
VERY BIG TROUBLE, AND WE HAVE NO
CHOICE BUT TO PUNISH YOU.
>> Steven: BUT...
>> Garnet: NO DINNER FOR
1,000 YEARS.
>> Steven: 1,000?
>> Pearl: WE WOULD NEVER STARVE
YOU, BUT YOU WILL LOSE YOUR TV
PRIVILEGES...FOR 1,000 YEARS.
>> Steven: NO!
THE MIDSEASON PRE-FINALE OF
"UNDER THE KNIFE"!
HOW CAN YOU DO THIS TO ME?!
>> BECAUSE WE LOVE YOU, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
>> WOW.
THAT WAS A MASTERFUL USE OF THE
"BECAUSE WE LOVE YOU" SHUTDOWN.
I'M QUITE PARTIAL TO THE
"IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD" MYSELF.
>> THAT "1,000 YEARS OF NO
DINNER" BIT [CHUCKLES] WAS
PRETTY FUNNY.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Garnet: ALL COMEDY IS DERIVED
FROM FEAR.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YOU ARE TOO MUCH.
>> I DID NOT KNOW WHAT TO MAKE
OF THE TWO OF -- EXCUSE ME --
FOUR OF YOU, BUT I SEE THAT YOU
ARE RESPONSIBLE PARENTS -- UH,
CAREGIVERS?
GUARDIANS.
>> SO, I CAN STILL HANG OUT WITH
STEVEN?
>> SURE.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> UH...
[ GRUNTS ]
[ POP! ]