>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: OOH.
>> AHEM.
SO, WHAT DID YOU THINK OF THE
ENDING?
>> Steven: UH...I THOUGHT IT WAS
ON PAGE 917.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS A DISASTER!
>> Steven: UH...
>> ALL THE BOOKS LEADING UP TO
THIS SEEMED TO BE TAKING ON AND
SUBVERTING THESE WITCH TROPES --
REALLY SELF-AWARE ABOUT BEING A
PASTICHE, YOU KNOW?
>> Steven: UM...
>> BUT IN THE END, NONE OF THAT
EVEN MATTERED.
LISA AND HER TALKING FALCON,
REBELS CHALLENGING THE STIFLING
TRADITIONS OF THE MAGICAL
BUREAUCRACY -- I LOVED THAT.
THEN HER FALCON TURNS INTO A
HUMAN AND THEY GET MARRIED?!
IT COMPLETELY DROPPED ALL THE
ANTI-AUTHORITARIAN STUFF AND
DESCRIBED HER WEDDING CAKE FOR
50 PAGES!
>> Steven: YEAH!
THAT CAKE WAS WORTHY OF
20 PAGES, TOPS!
THERE WEREN'T EVEN STRAWBERRIES
ON IT!
>> I BET SINCE THE BOOKS GOT SO
POPULAR, THE PUBLISHER PUT
PRESSURE ON THE AUTHOR TO WATER
DOWN THE END FOR A LARGER
AUDIENCE APPEAL.
UNLIKE ART, THE REAL WORLD CAN'T
ALWAYS WIN AGAINST THE IRON
CHAINS OF AUTHORITY.
[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S MY THEORY, ANYWAY.
>> Steven: HMM.
>> IT'S JUST DISAPPOINTING,
CONSIDERING I INVESTED EXTRA
MONEY IN THE HARDCOVER COPIES...
WITH MAPS.
>> Steven: I WISH I COULD GIVE
YOU A NEW ENDING.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
THE TEMPLE DOOR --
IT OPENED FOR ME!
[ GASPS ]
I CAN MAKE ANYTHING I WANT IN
THERE!
I CAN MAKE US A NEW ENDING!
>> REALLY?
WELL, WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UH...TA-DA!
>> COOL!
>> THIS IS MY MOM'S ROOM.
I CAN CONTROL IT, LIKE THIS.
I WANT A TINY, FLOATING WHALE TO
GIVE ME SOME FIN.
[ POOF! ]
>> [ SQUEALS ]
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
HOW DOES IT WORK?
>> Steven: THE ROOM CAN MAKE
STUFF OUT OF CLOUDS.
WE CAN MAKE ANYTHING.
>> ANYTHING?
HOW 'BOUT THE INFINITY FAIR FROM
BOOK 4, WITH MERCHANTS FROM A
MILLION LANDS SELLING GOODS FROM
CULTURES LONG GONE AND YET
TO BE?
>> Steven: WE SHOULD PROBABLY
KEEP IT SIMPLE.
WE DON'T WANT TO OVERLOAD THE
ROOM.
>> HOW 'BOUT HALF THE INFINITY
FAIR?
OH. THAT'S STILL INFINITY.
SIMPLE. OKAY.
WELL, WHAT REALLY MATTERS ARE
THE CHARACTERS.
YOU SHOULD BE ARCHIMICARUS.
>> Steven: OKAY.
ROOM, I WANT TO BE A FALCON!
[ FALCON SCREECHES ]
OH, YEAH.
GOT TO KEEP IT SIMPLE.
[ POOF! ]
>> AMAZING!
OKAY, MY TURN.
ROOM, I WANT TO BE LISA.
DO I NEED TO BE MORE SPECIFIC?
YOU WERE PRETTY GENERAL WITH THE
FALCON THING.
>> Steven: OH, SORRY.
I GUESS THE ROOM ONLY MAKES
STUFF WHEN I WANT IT.
MAYBE THIS WON'T WORK AFTER ALL.
>> WHY DON'T YOU JUST HAVE IT
MAKE A COSTUME SHOP?
>> Steven: OH, YEAH! GOOD IDEA!
I WANT A COSTUME SHOP!
[ POOF! ]
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WOW! THIS PLACE HAS
EVERYTHING -- EVEN HER CHILDHOOD
TUNIC!
WAIT. YOU THOUGHT IT WAS RED?
>> Steven: YEAH, THE COLOR OF
THE SETTING SUN!
>> THE SUN SETS BLACK OVER THE
MINES, STEVEN.
>> Steven: ARE YOU GONNA BE
YOUNG LISA?
>> WELL, IF WE'RE REALLY
REWORKING THIS THING, I'M GONNA
MAKE THE ULTIMATE LISA WITH THE
BEST GEAR FROM EVERY BOOK.
LIKE, WHAT IF SHE NEVER LOST HER
IRON SWORD?
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> AND THE CLOAK AND THE CLASP
ARE TOO SIGNATURE NOT TO DO.
>> Steven: FOR SURE!
>> AND I ALWAYS LIKED THE
DRAGON WHISKER BOOTS FROM THE
VOLCANO STUFF IN BOOK 3.
>> Steven: ARE YOU ALMOST DONE?
>> WAIT A MINUTE!
>> Steven: COME OUT!
I WANT TO SEE YOU!
[ GASPS ]
WHOA! YOU LOOK AWESOME!
>> THANKS!
>> Steven: OKAY. LET'S DO THIS.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
SO, AT THE END OF THE SERIES,
LISA AND HER FALCON FAMILIAR,
ARCHIMICARUS, ARE AT THE
ALTAR...
WITH A CLERIC...
ABOUT TO GET MARRIED.
BUT WE DON'T WANT THAT ENDING.
SO, INSTEAD -- HMM.
UH...I-I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HMM. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> Steven: UH...WELL...
H-HOW 'BOUT A DIFFERENT
PROPOSAL, LISA -- A BUSINESS
PROPOSAL?
WE CAN START A BUSINESS TOGETHER
AND SELL -- SELL...TURKEY LEGS
TO MAKE MONEY TO HELP OUT OUR
FELLOW REBEL COMRADES!
>> YEAH, THAT'S GREAT!
[ POOF! ]
>> Steven: I WANT AN UMBRELLA
WITH THAT, IF YOU WOULD, ROOM.
[ POOF! ]
TURKEY LEGS!
GET YOUR REBEL TURKEY LEGS!
YOU THINK IT'S OKAY FOR ME TO
EAT THIS IF I'M A FALCON?
>> YOU ARE A BIRD OF PREY.
>> Steven: SO, WHAT SHOULD OUR
NEXT MOVE BE AS BUSINESS
PARTNERS?
>> YOU TELL ME.
>> Steven: YEAH? OH.
UM...
LET'S FEED THE WIND LIZARD.
[ POOF! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
LOOK AT THIS GUY!
HE TOTALLY LOOKS LIKE A REBEL!
>> WOW! FROM BOOK 4!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: NOW, I KNOW HE LIVES
IN THE MOUNTAINS, BUT HE'S JUST
VISITING BECAUSE HE HEARD ABOUT
THESE TURKEY LEGS.
LISA, WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO THE
HONORS?
>> OKAY.
>> [ ROARS ]
[ CHOMPING ]
>> HE ATE THE BONES!
>> Steven: OKAY!
I GUESS OUR BUSINESS IS A
SUCCESS.
>> IF YOU THINK SO.
>> Steven: SO, WHAT NOW?
DIDN'T YOU HAVE A BUNCH OF IDEAS
THAT IT NEEDED TO BE MORE
ANTI-AUTHORITY AND STUFF?
>> SURE.
>> Steven: OKAY.
[ POOF! ]
SO...WE'RE...
WE -- WE'RE STOPPED BY THE
AUTHORITIES BECAUSE -- BECAUSE
WE'RE SELLING WITHOUT A PERMIT
AND WE'RE NOT OLD ENOUGH TO
DRIVE A CART.
BUT THESE ARE, UH, FREE-RANGE
TURKEYS, AND THEY DIDN'T LISTEN
TO ANYBODY, AND THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO, RIGHT?!
>> WHATEVER YOU THINK.
>> Steven: REALLY?
ALL RIGHT.
AND THEN I THINK THEY...
DON'T LIKE THAT...
AND THEY ATTACK US.
[ SHING! ]
YOU CAN'T STOP US!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLUNK! SHING! ]
[ SHING! CHOP! CHOP! CHOP! ]
GEEZ! THESE GUYS ARE CORRUPT.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO ABOUT 'EM,
HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DO?
>> Steven: C-COME ON!
I'M REALLY TRYING HERE!
HOW DO YOU WANT THE STORY TO
END?
>> HOW DO YOU WANT THE STORY TO
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST WANTED TO DO THIS FOR
YOU.
THIS ISN'T REALLY LIKE YOU.
I -- [ SIGHS ]
I DON'T WANT YOU TO JUST DO WHAT
I WANT.
>> UH...UH...YOU WANT ME TO NOT
D-DO WHAT YOU WANT?
>> Steven: CONNIE, ARE YOU ALL
RIGHT?
>> I WANT WHAT YOU WANT -- WHAT
YOU WANT -- WANT -- WANT --
WANT -- WANT -- WANT -- WANT --
WANT...
>> Steven: I WANT A TINY
FLOATING WHALE TO GIVE ME SOME
FIN.
[ POOF! ]
I WANT A COSTUME SHOP!
I WANT TO SEE YOU!
>> ...WANT -- WANT -- WANT --
WANT -- WANT -- WANT -- WANT...
>> Steven: I-I CREATED YOU.
>> ...WANT -- WANT -- WANT...
>> Steven: YOU'RE NOT CONNIE!
I MUST HAVE LEFT THE REAL CONNIE
BACK AT THE COSTUME SHOP!
SH-SHE COULD BE ANYWHERE!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
I'M DONE! I'M DONE PLAYING!
[ POOF! ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ZAP! ZAP! ]
WHY DIDN'T YOU DISAPPEAR WITH
EVERYTHING ELSE?!
>> YOU TOLD ME NOT TO DO WHAT
YOU WANTED.
>> Steven: OHH.
[ GROWLS ]
WHERE IS CONNIE?!
>> [ In distance ] STEVEN!
STEVEN!
>> Steven: CONNIE?
C-CONNIE?! IS THAT YOU?!
PLEASE LET ME GO.
I WANT TO FIND THE REAL CONNIE!
>> YOU TOLD ME YOU WANTED --
>> Steven: IT DOESN'T MATTER!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
PLEASE DON'T FOLLOW ME.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO FOLLOW ME!
CART!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAH! UH...UH, WIND LIZARD!
[ POOF! ]
AAH!
>> [ ROARS ]
UH...UH...UH...
CONNIE, CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
>> [ In distance ] STEVEN?
STEVEN!
>> Steven: CONNIE!
I'M ALMOST THERE!
JUST A LITTLE BIT FURTHE-- AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Steven: PLEASE!
I DON'T WANT YOU!
I WANT THE REAL CONNIE!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> I KNOW WHAT YOU REALLY WANT.
I KNOW HOW YOU REALLY FEEL.
>> [ In distance ] STEVEN?!
AH, STEVEN, FINALLY!
THERE YOU...ARE.
>> Steven: UGH! UGH!
HELP!
>> UGH!
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> KEEP AWAY FROM HIM!
[ CREAK! POOF! ]
[ POOF! ]
>> I KNOW YOU LIKE HER.
[ SHING! ]
AND I KNOW YOU WANT HER TO LIKE
YOU, TOO.
>> Steven: NO! DON'T LISTEN!
[ SHING! ]
[ POOF! ]
>> THAT'S WHY YOU CAN'T TELL HER
THE TRUTH, BUT YOU WANT TO!
>> Steven: OW!
>> YOU WANT TO TELL HER!
>> Steven: NO!
>> GET OFF HIM!
>> TELL HER, STEVEN!
>> Steven: I... [ GROANS ]
>> TELL HER!
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
I LIKED THE ENDING OF THE BOOK!
[ SHING! ]
>> WHAT?
>> Steven: I-I-I THOUGHT IT WAS
SWEET THAT LISA AND ARCHIMICARUS
GOT TOGETHER IN THE END.
THEY WERE ALWAYS SO THOUGHTFUL
TOWARDS EACH OTHER, AND I WAS SO
HAPPY WHEN THEY FOUND THE SPELL
TO MAKE HIM HUMAN, AND I LOVED
EVERY PAGE ABOUT THE CAKE!
I WANTED TO DRAW A PICTURE
OF IT!
I'M -- I'M SORRY I PRETENDED NOT
TO LIKE IT.
I JUST -- I JUST DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO THINK LESS OF ME.
>> AHH. THAT'S BETTER.
[ POOF! ]
>> Steven: DO -- DO YOU THINK
I'M A BAD PERSON FOR LIKING THE
ENDING?
>> OF COURSE NOT.
I -- STEVEN, IT'S JUST A BOOK.
>> Steven: BUT YOU REALLY CARE
ABOUT IT.
>> I CARE ABOUT YOU MORE.
>> Steven: EVEN THOUGH I LIKED
THE WEDDING?
>> OH, OF COURSE YOU LIKED THE
WEDDING.
YOU'RE STEVEN.
YOU LOVE SCHMALTZ.
[ TWINKLE! ]
>> Steven: YOU MAKE A GOOD
POINT, BUT DON'T YOU REMEMBER
HOW ARCHIMICARUS CRIED IN
BOOK 3?
>> I THOUGHT THAT WAS BECAUSE
THEY LOST THE SWORD.
>> Steven: NO!
SHE ALMOST FELL INTO THE
VOLCANO!
HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT HER.
>> BUT SHE HAD ACCESS TO FROST
SPELLS.
>> Steven: YEAH, BUT
ARCHIMICARUS DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
EVEN BIRDS CAN FALL IN LOVE.
>> I GUESS YOU COULD READ IT
THAT WAY.
[ ZOOM! POP! ]
♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ PANTING ]
DO WE REALLY HAVE TO
GET EVERY PIECE?
[ PANTING,
GASPS ]
YES!
YES.
HAVING A WRECKED GEM SHIP
LYING AROUND IS TOO DANGEROUS.
WE'VE GOT TO TAKE CARE OF IT --
ALL OF IT.
AND WE'LL NEED TO START LOOKING
FOR PERIDOT'S ESCAPE POD, TOO,
ASSUMING SHE EVEN MADE IT
TO EARTH.
WE'VE GOT LOTS OF WORK
AHEAD OF US.
ON IT.
[ GRUNTS, STRAINING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA, THAT'S A BIG ONE.
[ SEAGULLS SQUAWKING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Jenny: STEVEN?
STEVEN?
STEVEN!
HUH?
YO.
HEY, STEVEN.
WELCOME BACK TO EARTH.
WHAT?
WHO TOLD YOU?
YOU LOOKED
A MILLION MILES AWAY, MAN.
OH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SORRY.
I WAS ZONING OUT.
WE WERE ABOUT TO GO CHILL
AT A PARKING LOT
AND FREAK OUT
SOME SQUARES.
YOU SHOULD COME WITH.
OH, BUT I-I DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANYTHING AGAINST SQUARES.
I LIKE ALL BASIC SHAPES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU GOT THAT
MUCH-NEEDED COUNTER-POINT
TO OUR CYNICAL WORLD-VIEW.
YOU HAVE TO COME.
IT'S GOOD ENERGY FLOW.
SORRY, GUYS.
I'VE GOT A LOT OF IMPORTANT
GEM WORK TO DO.
MAYBE LATER.
AWW.
BUMMER.
WELL, WE'LL CATCH YOU
LATER, THEN.
[ GROANS ]
THE CALLUSES ON MY HANDS
HAVE CALLUSES.
[ GROANS ]
THE WORKING MAN'S BURDEN IS
TRULY A HEAVY ONE.
[ MUFFLED THUMP ]
[ GASPS ]
PIZZA RAIN.
BUT NO PIZZA CLOUDS.
WHA--
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING HERE?
AND WHY ARE YOU MAKING IT
PIZZA RAIN?
I ONLY WANTED TO SEE YOU
LAUGHING...
IN THE PIZZA RAIN.
IS THAT A REFERENCE
TO SOMETHING?
COME ON.
IT'S TIME TO HANG OUT.
YOU CAN'T HANG OUT
AT NIGHT.
NIGHT IS FOR DREAMING.
NIGHT'S WHATEVER
YOU WANT IT TO BE.
TIME'S AN ILLUSION.
HMM.
AREN'T YOU DONE WORKING
FOR THE DAY?
MM. YEAH, OKAY.
LET'S HANG OUT.
NICE.
BUT FIRST WE NEED TO DELIVER
THE REST OF THIS PIZZA
TO MR. SMILEY.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
WHOO!
WIND IN YOUR FACE --
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT.
BREATHE DEEP, STEVEN.
THIS IS THE SMELL
OF FREEDOM.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
FREEDOM SMELLS
LIKE PEPPERONI.
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S JUST THE CAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT FOOD
DEFINITELY DOESN'T SMELL
LIKE FREEDOM?
FISH.
WHY FISH?
UH-OH. HERE WE GO.
I JUST
DON'T GET WHAT'S WRONG
WITH WANTING TO BE
A DEEJAY.
BUT MY STEP-DAD WAS ALL ON
MY CASE AGAIN TODAY, SAYIN'...
[ BABBLING ]
UGH.
I'M JUST LIKE,
"I DON'T WANT TO BE A FISHERMAN.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU CAN'T RAVE
IN A RAINCOAT, STEP-DAD."
AT LEAST HE ONLY BUGS YOU
ABOUT ONE THING.
MY DAD'S GOT TO SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT EVERYTHING I DO
'CAUSE I'M THE MAYOR'S SON.
AND I'M LIKE,
"YOU CAN'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
I'M THE MAYOR'S..."
WAIT.
[ LAUGHS ]
PUH-LEASE!
YOU'RE JUST WALKING IN CAKE
WITH THAT TALK.
YOU GUYS DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
BAD IS UNTIL YOU HAVE A SISTER.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHY
I HAVE TO SPELL IT OUT
THAT I'M THE EVIL TWIN
AND SHE'S THE GOOD ONE.
DON'T ASK ME TO HELP YOU
WITH YOUR HOMEWORK.
I'M AT
SOME METAL CONCERT.
FAMILY STUFF IS TRICKY.
MM-HMM.
YEAH.
A FEW MONTHS BACK,
MY DAD AND THE GEMS
GROUNDED ME FROM TV.
BUMMER.
THAT'S THE WORST.
NO WAY!
AND THEN I FOUND OUT
THAT THE GEMS ARE ALIEN REBELS
AND THAT THERE ARE OTHER GEMS
OUT IN SPACE
THAT WANT US DEAD 'CAUSE
THEY THINK WE'RE TRAITORS.
AND THEY TRIED
TO TAKE ME HOSTAGE
'CAUSE THEY THINK
I'M MY MOM.
AND...MAYBE I KINDA AM?
I WISH I COULD TALK TO GARNET,
AMETHYST, AND PEARL ABOUT IT,
BUT I THINK THEY KINDA BLAME ME
FOR MY MOM NOT BEING AROUND.
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
THAT'S HEAVY.
I GUESS.
BUT YOU ALWAYS SEEM
SO UPBEAT.
YOU'RE A REAL CHAMP,
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
Sour Cream: YEAH, MAN.
I'D TURN TO FISHING
IN A HEARTBEAT
IF IT MEANT NOT DEALING
WITH THA-- THAT!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
LOOK AT THAT!
WHAT?!
WHAT DID I HIT IT?
WHAT IS IT?!
GLOOOOWING.
WE GOT TO CHECK IT OUT.
I'M DOWN.
ALL RIGHT. HOLD ON.
THAT'S AS BRIGHT
AS LIKE 600 GLOW STICKS.
PERIDOT'S ESCAPE POD!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
OKAY, EVERYBODY STEP BACK!
THIS IS A GEM MACHINE
AND COULD BE
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
CHECK IT OUT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[ GRUNTS ]
BOOM!
WHOA, STOP!
PERIDOT MIGHT STILL
BE IN THERE!
PERI-WHAT?
THIS BIZ IS EMPTY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT LOOKS SO BUSTED.
YOU NEED TO GET AWAY
FROM THERE!
WHOA!
YOU NEED TO RELAX.
IT'S NOT DOING ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT JUST THE POD.
THIS MEANS PERIDOT
IS JUST OUT THERE SOMEWHERE,
TRYING TO HURT THE EARTH.
NOT COOL.
EARTH FOREVER.
[ GRUNTS ]
HERE COME THE ROCKS.
STEVEN, COME TAKE A SELFIE
WITH ME AND THIS THING.
NO, JENNY, I'M SERIOUS.
SO AM I.
SOUR CREAM,
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
SURE.
I'M DOWN FOR WHATEVER.
BUCK?
NAH.
I LIKE TO JUST EXPERIENCE THE
MOMENT FOR WHAT IT IS SOMETIMES.
PLUS,
THE LIGHTING IS WEIRD.
UGH, OKAY.
STEVEN? LAST CALL.
MMMM....
I GOT FUNNY STICKERS!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
THESE ARE SO GOOD!
HOW DO I LOOK?
YOU LOOK GREAT!
LOOK, STAY RIGHT THERE.
I WANNA TAKE ONE MOR--
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN, GET IN IT!
W-WHAT?
JUST FOR A SECOND!
ONE PICTURE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, READY.
THREE, TWO...
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
WHA--
[ GASPS ]
DUDE!
OH, MY GOSH, STEVEN!
WHA?
THIS IS SO COOL!
[ POD THRUMS ]
WHOA!
AAH! WHOA!
[ GRUNTS ]
Jenny: STEVEN!
WHOA!
HOW ARE YOU DOING THAT?
[ Shakily ] UH...
[ GASPS ]
I THINK IT LISTENS
TO WHAT MY HANDS DO.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T BE
PLAYING WITH THIS.
I HAVE TO TAKE THIS BACK
TO THE TEMPLE IMMEDIATELY.
NO WAY.
YOU JUST GOT IT WORKING!
COME ON,
AREN'T YOU YOUR OWN MOM?
YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YEAH, YOU GOT TO DO SOME DONUTS
IN THAT THING.
AT LEAST A DOZEN.
BAKER'S DOZEN.
SERIOUSLY, STEVEN, YOU'VE BEEN
UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU DESERVE
TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN?
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHOO!
[ TIRES SQUEAL ]
HEY!
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU REALLY GOT THE HANG
OF THAT THING, HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH!
IT ALWAYS HOOKS
TO THE LEFT.
WHOA!
I SHOULD REALLY GET IT BACK
TO THE GEMS, THOUGH.
NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO.
OR RIGHT AFTER
I JUMP THAT HAYSTACK!
YEAH! COME ON!
YEAH! DO IT!
MESS IT UP!
WRECK IT, STEVEN!
GO, STEVEN!
YEAH!
YEAH! WHOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M OKAY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S NOT ACTUALLY SO BAD
IF YOU JUST GIVE IT A LITTLE --
[ GASPS ]
[ POD WARBLES ]
AAH!
[ POD THRUMS ]
STEVEN?
AAH!
GUYS?
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ PANTING ]
[ POD WARBLES ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
AAH!
STEVEN!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
GUYS, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
[ GASPS ]
I KNEW IT! THAT FLARE LED US
RIGHT TO THE ESCAPE POD!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
HELP!
HELP US!
OVER HERE!
GARNET, AMETHYST, PEARL!
WE'LL SAVE YOU,
HUMANS!
AAH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
PERIDOT'S STILL INSIDE.
SHE'S PROBABLY WEAK
FROM THE LANDING.
DON'T HOLD BACK.
GOT IT!
NO!
WHOA!
Garnet: YOU GOT A LOT OF NERVE
TAKING REFUGE HERE,
OF ALL PLACES!
GARNET?
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU GET OFF
ATTACKING DEFENSELESS HUMANS
IN YOUR DEADBEAT ESCAPE POD.
GARNET!
IT'S ME, STEVEN!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
GARNET!
AND IF YOU THINK YOU'RE SAFE
HERE, WELL, I GOT NEWS FOR YOU.
YOU LOST!
NOW...
GARNET! GARNET! GARNET!
...STAY OFF MY PLANET!
STOP!
[ PANTING ]
STEVEN'S IN THERE.
Pearl: OH, STEVEN!
Amethyst: STEVEN,
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?!
YOU FOUND
PERIDOT'S ESCAPE POD,
AND YOU DIDN'T
COME GET US IMMEDIATELY?
DUDE,
WE ALMOST WRECKED YOU.
STEVEN,
THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE.
I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HEY!
CUT HIM SOME SLACK.
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT!
JUST LET HIM BE
A DEEJAY!
WHA?
WE JUST WANTED STEVEN
TO HAVE SOME FUN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH ALIENS
TRYING TO ABDUCT HIM
AND HIM BEING HIS OWN MOM,
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE HE'S GOT
A LOT ON HIS MIND.
I'M SURE WHATEVER YOU'RE
HAVING HIM DO IS IMPORTANT,
BUT EVERYONE NEEDS A BREAK
ONCE IN A WHILE.
HE'S JUST A KID.
OH, MAYBE WE HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE HARD ON HIM.
HE DID JUST BREAK US
OUT OF SPACE JAIL.
STEVEN.
YOU'RE UNGROUNDED
FROM TV.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING ]
Sour Cream: I'M INVINCIBLE!
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪