>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ SEA GULLS SQUAWKING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Steven: OOH.
>> Pearl: I DON'T THINK THEY ARE
EARTHQUAKES.
THEY'RE TOO FREQUENT.
>> Amethyst: HEY, LOOK.
STEVEN'S GOT A BIKE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, STEVEN?
>> Steven: JUST OUT FOR A RIDE.
>> Pearl: IN THE SAND?
>> Steven: YEP.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTING STOPS ]
[ GRUNTING RESUMES ]
[ PANTING ]
SM-SMOOTH RIDE.
FIVE SPEEDS.
HAND BRAKES.
ELECTRIC-BLUE FINISH WITH A
TIGER BELL.
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
I BET THERE ARE A LOT OF KIDS
WHO'D LOVE TO RIDE THIS BA--
WHOA!
[ GASPS ]
UH...
AAH!
[ PANTING ]
WHAT UP?
>> Pearl: WHO WERE YOU TALKING
TO?
>> Steven: HUH?
>> Garnet: THAT GIRL.
>> Steven: YOU SAW?
SHE'S JUST A GIRL I KNOW...
EXCEPT SHE DOESN'T KNOW ME.
WE'VE NEVER TALKED.
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
YOU LIKE HER!
>> Steven: UH, I LIKE EVERYONE.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ] LET'S SET UP
A PLAYDATE.
I'LL WRITE UP AN INVITATION AND
WORK OUT A SCHEDULE.
[ GASPS ] OH, WE'LL HAVE TO FIND
OUT HER FAVORITE KIND OF TEA.
>> Garnet: NO.
JUST TALK TO HER.
>> Steven: OKAY.
BUT YOU GUYS CAN'T WATCH THIS
TIME.
IT'LL MESS UP MY FUNKY FLOW.
>> Both: "FUNKY FLOW"?
>> Garnet: WE WON'T WATCH.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT.
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THAT?
>> Steven: NOTHING!
"HI. MY NAME IS STEVEN.
HI. MY NAME IS STEEV-EN.
HI. MY NAME IS STEV-IN."
[ RUMBLING ]
OOH! OOH!
AAH!
HI! MY NAME IS STEVEN!
[ SHATTERING ]
WHOA!
HOW DID I DO THAT?
HI.
MY NAME IS STEVEN.
>> CONNIE.
WHAT...HAPPENED?
>> Steven: I'M MAGIC -- WELL,
HALF-MAGIC ON MY MOM'S SIDE.
>> YOU DID THIS?
>> Steven: APPARENTLY.
I'M A MEMBER OF THE
CRYSTAL GEMS.
WE FIGHT MONSTERS AND PROTECT
HUMANITY AND STUFF.
>> OH, THAT'S KIND OF LIKE MY
DAD.
HE'S A COP.
WELL, MORE LIKE A PRIVATE
SECURITY GUARD.
SO, HOW LONG DOES IT USUALLY
LAST?
>> Steven: OH, RIGHT.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTING STOPS ]
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> Steven: IT, UH, DOESN'T SEEM
TO WANT TO GO AWAY.
>> OH.
[ CREAKING ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
SO, I DON'T SEE YOU AROUND THAT
OFTEN.
>> MY DAD WORKS FOR A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT BEACHES, SO WE'RE
NEVER IN THE SAME PLACE LONG.
>> Steven: I GO ON ADVENTURES
WITH THE GEMS SOMETIMES.
THEY USUALLY SAY IT'S TOO
DANGEROUS FOR ME, THOUGH.
[ GRUNTING ]
UGH!
>> DO YOU ALWAYS GO IN A BUBBLE?
>> Steven: NO. THIS IS NEW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS IS.
BUT IT'S OKAY.
THE GEMS WILL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
OHH, WHAT?
[ GRUNTING ]
HEY! GUYS!
GARNET, HELP!
>> I DON'T THINK THEY CAN HEAR
YOU.
>> Steven: OHH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I TOLD THEM NOT TO WATCH.
>> WE CAN JUST WAIT HERE UNTIL
THEY COME OUT.
>> Steven: NO, NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
I'VE GOT OTHER FRIENDS THAT CAN
HELP.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
WAY TO GO, STEVEN.
IS THIS YOUR MAGIC LOVE BUBBLE
OR SOMETHING?
DID YOU MAKE IT...
BECAUSE YOU'RE IN LOVE?
>> Steven: THAT'S LARS.
WE'RE BASICALLY BFFs.
>> HE MAKES WEIRD FACES.
>> OOH. OOH.
BLEHHHH.
>> LARS, QUIT BEING A JERK AND
HELP!
>> WHAT?
I'M HELPING STEVEN ON HIS DATE.
>> YOU'RE EMBARRASSING HIM.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> Steven: HE AND SADIE RUN
THE BIG DONUT.
>> DO THEY GET ALONG?
[ BOTH ARGUING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> Steven: THEY'RE CRAZY ABOUT
EACH OTHER.
>> I'M GONNA GO TRY SOMETHING
ELSE.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
>> Steven: ANYWAY, THIS PLACE
HAS THE BEST DOUGHNUTS.
I COME HERE LIKE EVERY DAY.
>> MY PARENTS DON'T LET ME EAT
DOUGHNUTS.
THEY HAVE TRANS FATS.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> MWAH! MWAH!
>> Steven: WELL, IT'S STILL A
COOL PLACE TO HANG OUT.
[ DOOR CHIMES ]
>> AAH!
HA!
[ WOOD CLATTERS ]
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ] I HAVE A
BETTER IDEA.
>> WHOA! A TRAWLER.
AND A LITTLE SKIPJACK.
>> Steven: YOU KNOW A LOT ABOUT
BOATS.
>> THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
HANG OUT AT THE BEACH AND DON'T
SWIM AND DON'T HAVE FRIENDS.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ] YOU LOOK
AT BOATS.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
OH! HEY!
ONION!
WE NEED A HARPOON GUN.
>> WHAT?
>> Steven: TO POP THE BUBBLE.
>> CAN'T WE JUST GO BACK TO YOUR
HOUSE?
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY.
I'M A GEM.
ONION, WE NEED A HARPOON GUN.
HAR-POON GUN!
[ SIGHS ]
[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
HAR-POON...GUN.
[ SQUEAKING ]
UGH!
>> LET ME TRY.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
[ SQUEAKING ]
IT JUST MADE MORE SENSE.
[ HORN BLOWS ]
>> Both: AAH!
[ HARPOON CLANGS, SHATTERS ]
>> THE TRAWLER.
FUNLAND?
>> Steven: YEAH, TONS OF
HORRIBLE ACCIDENTS HAPPEN HERE
EVERY DAY.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING TO
BREAK THIS BUBBLE.
>> UM...
>> Steven: WE JUST GOT TO FIND
THE RIGHT ROCK.
[ RIDERS SCREAM ]
YEAH!
THE KIDDIE COASTER!
[ RIDERS SCREAM ]
ALL RIGHT, WE JUST ROLL DOWN
THIS RAMP AS THE CARTS ARE
COMING AT US, AND THE CRASH WILL
BREAK US FREE.
>> WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THE BUBBLE
POPS?
>> Steven: WE'LL BE FREE.
>> STEVEN, THIS IS A BAD IDEA.
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Both: AAH!
>> Steven: THIS WILL WORK!
>> AAH!
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Both: AAH!
[ THUD ]
>> WHERE ARE WE?
>> Steven: THE BOTTOM OF THE
OCEAN.
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY.
>> ARE WE EVEN CLOSE TO THE
SHORE?
>> Steven: YEAH.
SURE.
>> LET'S START ROLLING.
>> Steven: IT'S A GOOD THING
THIS BUBBLE IS AIRTIGHT.
OTHERWISE, WE'D BE DROWNING
RIGHT NOW.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
DON'T WORRY, CONNIE.
I HAVE AN IDEA THAT WILL
DEFINITELY WORK.
WHEN WE GET BACK --
[ GRUMBLING ]
>> AAH! AAH!
>> Steven: A HUGE WORM!
IT'S OKAY.
LOOK -- IT ONLY WANTS TO EAT
THAT BRIGHT STUFF.
[ WORM GRUMBLES, CHOMPS ]
>> Steven: SEE?
NOT SCARY AT ALL.
[ WORM ROARS, SCREECHES ]
WHOA!
>> AAH!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
OOH.
UH, SORRY!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT'S NOT SO BAD.
UH, IT'S -- IT'S OKAY.
I, UH --
>> IT'S NOT OKAY!
>> Steven: HUH?
>> YOU KEEP SAYING THAT, BUT YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO SUFFOCATE OR
STARVE AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
OCEAN, AND ONLY MY PARENTS WILL
NOTICE, BECAUSE NO ONE ELSE
CARES ABOUT ME!
>> Steven: HUH?
>> [ Voice breaking ] I'M GONNA
DISAPPEAR WITHOUT EVER MAKING A
SINGLE FRIEND.
[ CRYING ]
>> Steven: WE COULD BE FRIENDS.
I SAW YOU AT THE
BOARDWALK PARADE LAST YEAR.
YOU DROPPED YOUR BRACELET.
I PICKED IT UP, BUT THEN I
COULDN'T FIND YOU.
I SAVED IT IN THE FREEZER SO IT
WOULD LAST LONGER, IN CASE I SAW
YOU AGAIN.
>> OH!
YOU WERE THE KID ON THE CAR-WASH
FLOAT.
YOU HAD SOAP BUBBLES IN YOUR
HAIR.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ] I WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE A SCRUB BRUSH.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
I'M SORRY, CONNIE.
IF I HAD RETURNED YOUR BRACELET
BACK THEN, YOU WOULDN'T BE STUCK
IN THIS BUBBLE WITH ME NOW.
>> NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAVING FUN.
[ BOTH INHALE DEEPLY ]
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
[ WORM SCREECHES, ROARS ]
>> Both: AAH!
[ WORM SCREECHES ]
>> COME ON! COME ON!
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
>> HIDE IN THE ROCKS, STEVEN!
[ WORM ROARING ]
>> AAH!
>> Steven: WHY IS IT CHASING US?
THE BRACELET.
IT EATS BRIGHT STUFF.
CONNIE!
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: GIVE ME THE BRACELET!
>> WHAT?
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY!
[ PANTING ]
NOW, GO! GO!
RUN THAT WAY!
OOH! I'M SORRY!
[ WORM SCREECHING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
[ SCREECHING, ROARING CONTINUE ]
[ SCREECHING, ROARING STOP ]
>> Together: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WHAT'S GOING
ON?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> HE WAS INCREDIBLE!
>> Steven: REALLY? YOU MEAN IT?
HERE'S YOUR BRACELET...AGAIN.
>> THANKS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Amethyst: SO, ARE YOU GOING
TO INTRODUCE US?
>> Pearl: STEVEN WAS SO EXCITED
TO MEET YOU.
RIGHT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: UH...
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
>> Garnet: HEY.
DON'T MESS WITH HIS FUNKY FLOW.
>> "FUNKY...FLOW"?
>> Steven: UH...[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GROANS ]
[ SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
>> Garnet: PAY ATTENTION,
STEVEN.
THIS IS GOING TO BE YOUR FIRST
SERIOUS MISSION.
YOU NEED TO BE READY.
>> Steven: YES. I'M READY.
I'M SO READY!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, COME ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE YOURSELF
SICK.
[ THUD ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHY DID YOU BRING THAT?
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS EXCITED AND IT'S MINE AND
I LIKE IT.
WHA--
>> Pearl: STEVEN, GET BACK HERE!
YOU COULD GET SERIOUSLY...
HURT.
[ POP! ]
[ THUD ]
[ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, ARE YOU --
>> Steven: I'M FINE.
I'M GOOD.
I'M JUST GOOEY.
MMM.
[ WHAP! ]
AAH!
AAH, THEY'RE IN MY EYES!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Garnet: THEY'RE JUST
BUTTERFLIES, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, THEY LOOKED A LOT BIGGER
WHEN THEY WERE ON MY EYEBALLS.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
STEVEN, YOU'RE A RIOT.
>> Pearl: I'M SUDDENLY HAVING
SECOND THOUGHTS ABOUT BRINGING
STEVEN ON THIS ONE.
>> Garnet: SHH.
JUST LOOK AT HIM.
NOW, LET'S GO RECOVER THE
GEMSTONE.
>> Pearl: UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS WAS ONCE A GEM BATTLEFIELD.
NOW IT'S WILD STRAWBERRIES AS
FAR AS THE EYE CAN SEE.
OH, THAT'S WHAT I LOVE ABOUT THE
EARTH.
MAYBE THIS WILL BE A LIGHT
MISSION AFTER ALL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ THUD ]
OH!
>> Garnet: MAYBE NOT.
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ GIGGLES ]
WHOA!
STEVEN'S THE BEST!
[ Echoing ] STEVEN'S THE BEST!
WHY, THANK YOU, TEMPLE.
>> Amethyst: YOU'RE A DOOF.
>> Steven: HEY.
WHAT'S THIS THING?
IT'S LIKE A COOL FLOATY TRIANGLE
THING.
>> Pearl: W-WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T TOUCH IT.
[ RUMBLING ]
STEVEN!
WHAT HAVE WE TOLD YOU ABOUT
TOUCHING MAGICAL THINGS?
>> Steven: DEFINITELY ALWAYS...
NEVER DO IT.
>> All: AAAH!
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO SPLIT UP.
>> Pearl: RIGHT.
STEVEN AND I WILL STAY RIGHT
HERE WHERE IT SEEMS TO BE SAFE
WHILE YOU GUYS GO AND SOLVE THE
MYSTERY OF THIS PLACE.
>> Steven: WAIT.
I WANT TO HELP SOLVE THE
MYSTERY.
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
COME ON, STEVEN.
LET'S SOLVE THE MYSTERY.
>> Steven: YEAH!
MYSTERY SOLVERS!
>> Pearl: NOPE.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU TWO ARE A DISASTER WAITING
TO HAPPEN.
>> Garnet: STEVEN GOES WITH ME.
>> Steven: REALLY?
AWESOME!
>> Garnet: BUT REMEMBER -- THIS
IS A SERIOUS MISSION.
>> Steven: UNDERSTOOD.
SERIOUS STEVEN...
PEARL, CAN YOU PUT ME DOWN?
>> Pearl: WHAT?
OH, YES. OF COURSE.
>> Steven: I NEED TO BE
STANDING, OR ELSE IT DOESN'T
WORK.
SERIOUS STEVEN...ACTIVATE!
>> Pearl: BUT THIS COULD BE THE
TEACUPS ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> Steven: HEY!
I'VE PUT THAT BEHIND ME.
♪ WELL, WE'RE ON A MAGIC
TREASURE HUNT ♪
♪ FOR SOME MAGIC TREASURE JUNK ♪
♪ SOMETHING, SOMETHING, MAGIC
SOMETHING ♪
HUH?
>> Garnet: WE NEED TO STAY ON
THE GLOWING PANELS.
>> Steven: RIGHT.
SERIOUS STEVEN...GO!
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, YEAH!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
UH...WHOA.
[ THUD ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GROANING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WHOO-HOO!
THAT WAS...UH, SERIOUSLY
DANGEROUS.
THANK YOU, GARNET.
[ SIGHS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ MOANING ]
>> Garnet: WE CAN TAKE A BREAK
IF YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: HUH?
OH, NO.
I-I'M OKAY.
LET'S KEEP GOING.
>> Garnet: ALL RIGHT, BUT BE
CAREFUL.
YOU MIGHT TRIGGER A TRAP WITH
THAT GUN SHOW.
>> Steven: RIGHT.
I'LL PUT THESE BABIES AWAY AND
USE MY MINDS.
MAYBE THERE'S A CLUE HIDDEN IN
THESE ANCIENT DRAWINGS.
IT LOOKS LIKE...THERE'S LOTS OF
TRIANGLES HIDDEN SOMEWHERE IN
THIS ROOM.
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Garnet: RUN!
>> Steven: [ SCREAMS ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Steven: OH, MY UKULELE!
[ UKULELE TUNING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
NOW IS PROBABLY NOT THE BEST
TIME FOR THAT.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: OH.
UH -- UH, RIGHT.
>> Garnet: NOW, THAT WAS A
PRETTY CLOSE ONE.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH.
THAT WAS A PRETTY...CLOSE...ONE.
[ GASPS ]
UH...
>> Garnet: GET READY, STEVEN.
THIS IS GONNA BE INTENSE.
>> Steven: I'M READY!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Amethyst: [ SNORING ]
>> Pearl: I MISUNDERSTOOD THE
POINT OF THIS RIDE.
>> Garnet: THIS IS FUN, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ MOANING ]
I THINK...I NEED TO GET OFF THIS
RIDE NOW.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, NO!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
[ THUD ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
STEVEN, YOU ARE BANNED FROM ALL
THE RIDES FOREVER!
>> Steven: WHOA.
WE MADE IT?
>> Garnet: I CARRIED YOU WHILE
YOU TOOK A NAP.
>> Steven: B-BUT...NAP?!
>> Garnet: WE'RE BACK WHERE WE
STARTED.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> Pearl: GARNET, THERE YOU ARE!
THE DOORS AND ROOMS HERE MAKE NO
SENSE.
THEY ALL BRING YOU BACK HERE.
>> Amethyst: [ PANTING ]
[ GROWLS, SCREAMS ]
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
>> Pearl: THERE ARE 16 DOORS,
AND WE ENTERED FROM THE
NORTHEAST AND WENT THROUGH THREE
CONSECUTIVE ROOMS IN A STRAIGHT
LINE...
>> Amethyst: OW!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> Pearl: ...BUT ARRIVED BACK
HERE OUT THE SOUTHERNMOST DOOR,
WHICH CAN ONLY MEAN -- W-WELL,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT MEANS.
I --
THIS IS A DEATH TRAP!
>> Steven: WHAT -- WHAT DO WE
DO?
>> Garnet: WE GO BACK IN AGAIN
AND AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN.
>> Steven: I CAN'T!
>> Pearl: STEVEN.
>> Garnet: IT'S OKAY.
>> Steven: NO.
NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU WERE ALL RIGHT ABOUT ME.
I WANTED TO DO THIS SO BAD, BUT
NOW I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA THROW
UP.
THIS IS JUST LIKE THE TEACUPS!
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN.
I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN THAT.
>> Steven: WAIT!
AH! WAIT, YOU GUYS!
WHAT IF THIS IS JUST LIKE THE
TEACUPS?
THAT'S WHY WE'RE GETTING SO
LOST.
THAT'S WHY I'M FEELING SO SICK.
ALL THE ROOMS ARE SPINNING US
AROUND SO WE END UP HERE.
>> All: AAH!
>> Steven: [ SCREAMS ]
WHOA!
>> Pearl: THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS GEM-POWERED MECHANISM --
IT'S MANIPULATING THE ROOMS
ABOVE.
EVERY ROOM WE ENTERED SPUN US
UNTIL WE CAME BACK TO THE
CENTRAL CHAMBER.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE TEACUP RIDE
AT FUNLAND.
>> Garnet: STEVEN ALREADY
FIGURED THAT OUT.
>> Pearl: OH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
GARNET, I NEED TO GET OFF THE
RIDE NOW.
>> Garnet: SERIOUS STEVEN...GO!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
WHOA!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
HUH?
AH!
>> Amethyst: HUH?
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN?
STEVEN!
WHERE IS HE?
>> Amethyst: OH, HE'S OVER HERE.
>> Steven: THE GEM.
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ]
I'D SAY YOU HANDLED THAT
ADVENTURE VERY WELL.
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
NICE JOB, SERIOUS STEVEN.
>> Garnet: I PREFER REGULAR
STEVEN.
>> Steven: HEY! MY UKULELE.
[ UKULELE TUNING ]
♪ OH, THAT'S THE END OF ANOTHER
DAY ♪
♪ IT WAS MIGHTY SERIOUS, I'D
HAVE TO SAY ♪
♪ THE CRYSTAL GEMS LOOKED REALLY
COOL WHEN THEY MADE THE TEMPLE
EXPLODE ♪
AAH! THEY'RE IN MY EYES AGAIN!
[ SCREAMS ]