>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Garnet: Shh. THIS WAY.
[ RUSTLING ]
>> Pearl: UGH. STEVEN!
THIS IS A STEALTH MISSION.
YOU'RE MAKING TOO MUCH NOISE!
TAKE OFF THAT JACKET.
>> Steven: UH, BUT I DON'T WANT
TO CATCH A COLD!
>> Pearl: THEN WHY ARE YOU STILL
WEARING SANDALS?
>> Steven: I CAN BE QUIET! SEE?
STEALTH.
>> Garnet: WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
>> Pearl: COME ON, THEN.
[ RUSTLING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: [ IMITATING
RUSTLING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: IT WASN'T ME!
AMETHYST, YOU'RE MAKING ME LOOK
BA--
[ SCREAMING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: STEALTH!
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCRAPING ]
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Both: STEVEN!
>> Garnet: STAY BACK.
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Amethyst: COME ON, POOFY.
>> Steven: WHAT ABOUT GARNET?
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: GO, GARNET! GO!
WOW.
SHE'S SO FAST!
GARNET, YOU'RE AMAZING!
HOW'D YOU EVEN DO THAT?
>> Pearl: LOOK.
THE LITTLE ONES DIDN'T EXPLODE!
THEY'RE DRILLING AWAY!
>> Amethyst: I GOT IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Garnet: LET THEM GO.
THEY'RE JUST PARASITES.
IF THEY WANT TO BE A PROBLEM,
THEY'LL HAVE TO ANSWER TO ME.
>> Steven: SO COOL!
>> Amethyst: I SWALLOWED A ROCK.
>> Steven: WE ALL WORKED SO
HARD, WE DESERVE A REWARD.
>> Pearl: SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAVE
SOMETHING IN MIND.
>> Steven: [ CACKLING ]
I'M TAKING YOU GUYS TO THE BEST
PLACE IN BEACH CITY --
FUNLAND ARCADE!
>> Pearl: DO WE HAVE ANYTHING
ELSE TO DO?
>> Garnet: WE DON'T.
>> Amethyst: UH, DON'T YOU NEED
MONEY FOR THAT PLACE?
>> Steven: OH, DON'T WORRY.
THIS ONE'S ON...
M-E-E-E-E-E-E-E!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ COINS CLATTERING ]
WELCOME TO A WONDERLAND OF
FUN-TRONIC GAME-VENTIONS!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Pearl: HUMANS FIND SUCH
FASCINATING WAYS TO WASTE THEIR
TIME.
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: HUH?
>> Steven: PEARL, COME ON!
YOU'LL LOVE THIS GAME!
>> Pearl: IF YOU SAY SO.
"ROAD KILLER"?
>> Steven: YEAH!
PICK THE CAR YOU LIKE.
THEN JUST GO FOR IT!
>> Pearl: W-WHICH ONE OF THESE
BUTTONS IS MY TURN SIGNAL?
>> Steven: NONE OF THEM.
HAVE FUN!
>> VROOM, VROOM! KILL THE ROAD!
>> Pearl: O-KAY...?
>> Steven: THIS IS SKEE-BALL.
ROLL THE BALL INTO THE HOLE, AND
YOU CAN EVEN WIN TICKETS FOR
PRIZES.
WHOA!
ONION'S THE TICKET MASTER!
>> Amethyst: COOL.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT. GOOD LUCK.
>> TEENS OF RAGE!
>> Steven: GARNET, THIS GAME IS
PERFECT FOR YOU!
YOU SEEM LIKE A JOE ROCK KIND OF
GAL.
HIS SPECIAL MOVE IS FORWARD,
FORWARD BACK, TOP TOWARDS HALF
CIRCLE, MEDIUM KICK...
OH, WAIT.
MAYBE THAT'S AN AERIAL MOVE!
JUST PUNCH, AND YOU'LL BE FINE.
>> COME ON, CHUMP!
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ MACHINE POWERING DOWN ]
[ ZAPPING, HISSING ]
>> Garnet: I DID IT.
>> Steven: UH...LET'S TRY
SOMETHING ELSE.
O-O-OKAY!
THIS IS A GAME YOU CAN ACTUALLY
PUNCH!
TELL MY WIFE I'M SORRY!
>> Garnet: I WIN AGAIN.
>> Steven: UH...
UM...
UH, HOW 'BOUT THAT ONE?
MEAT BEAT MANIA!
THERE'S NO VIOLENCE IN THIS
GAME.
JUST SHAKE THE MEAT TO THE
BEAT!
>> ARE YOU READY?
LET'S MEAT IT!
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
SHAKE IT! SHAKE IT!
THAT'S IT! WELL DONE!
KEEP IT UP! NOW YOU'RE COOKING!
OOH, TASTY! KEEP IT UP!
>> Steven: AWESOME!
GARNET, YOU'RE SO GOOD AT THIS!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHEW!
I WONDER HOW THE OTHERS ARE
DOING.
>> YOU'RE HORRIBLE!
>> Pearl: STOP SAYING THAT!
>> Steven: UH, HAVING FUN?
>> Pearl: WHY AM I DOING SO
BADLY?
I HAVEN'T CRASHED INTO ANYTHING.
>> Steven: YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
CRASH INTO EVERYTHING.
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
THAT'S HORRIBLE!
>> YOU'RE HORRIBLE!
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: [ BLOWING
RASPBERRIES ]
>> Steven: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> Amethyst: I'M-A WIN A
AIRPLANE!
>> Steven: THAT'S CHEATING!
YOU'RE GONNA GET US IN SO MUCH
TRO--
>> HEY!
DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO TEENS OF RAGE?
>> Steven: LET'S RUN!
>> Amethyst: THIS PLACE IS FUN!
>> Steven: PEARL, WE'RE LEAVING!
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ] GOOD!
[ EXPLOSION ]
>> YOU'RE FANTASTIC!
>> Steven: GARNET, WE'RE
LEAVING!
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO PUNCH BUDDY?
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?!
>> Steven: AAH!
UH, SEE YOU AT HOME!
>> Steven: SO, W-WHAT'S TODAY'S
MISSION?
I HOPE IT'S...
FIGHTING...A GIANT...
FOOT!
>> Pearl: IF WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
FIGHT A "GIANT FOOT"...
GARNET WOULD LET US KNOW.
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
GARNET'S THE BOSS.
>> Pearl: WELL, WE'RE ALL A
TEAM.
GARNET JUST HAS HEIGHTENED
PERCEPTION THAT GUIDES US
TOWARDS OUR MISSION OBJECTIVES.
>> Amethyst: YEAH...
SHE'S THE BOSS.
>> Steven: SO, WHERE IS SHE?
[ CHOMPS ]
F-FIGHTING THE FOOT?
>> Pearl: SHE'S NOT "FIGHTING
THE FOOT."
YOU KNOW GARNET GOES OFF ON
MISSIONS WITHOUT US ALL THE
TIME.
SHE'S PROBABLY DOING SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT.
>> Amethyst: OH, WAIT, STEVEN!
I JUST REMEMBERED -- GARNET HAD
A SPECIAL MISSION FOR YOU.
>> Steven: REALLY?!
>> Amethyst: YEAH!
SHE SAYS, UM...
YOU HAVE TO SLAM YOUR FACE INTO
THAT BOWL OF CEREAL.
>> Steven: OKAY.
>> Amethyst: GOOD JOB, STEVEN!
YOU STOPPED THE FOOT!
>> Pearl: THERE IS NO FOOT!
>> Steven: NOT ANYMORE.
>> Pearl: UGH!
>> Steven: WELL...
[ GRUNTING ]
...NOW THAT THAT'S DONE, TIME TO
COMB THE BEACH FOR QUARTERS WITH
MY...METAL MUTT!
[ METAL DETECTOR SQUEALING ]
[ BARKING ]
>> Steven: SILVER DOLLAR?
USELESS!
COME ON.
[ BARKING ]
THIS BETTER NOT BE ANOTHER CAT.
DOUBLE DOGS!
[ BARKING ]
[ GASPS ]
QUARTERS!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ WHIFFLE! ]
HELP!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: IT'S THE LITTLE
GUYS!
>> Pearl: THEY'RE EVERYWHERE!
WHY DIDN'T WE SEE THIS COMING?!
>> Steven: WE NEED GARNET!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Pearl: WE DON'T KNOW WHERE
SHE IS!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
MEAT BEAT MANIA!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING?!
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
HUH?
[ FAST MUSIC PLAYING ]
GARNET! YOU GOT TO COME QUICK!
WHEW! GARNET!
[ Panting ] THOSE LITTLE GUYS
ARE BACK, AND -- AND THEY'RE A
PROBLEM!
WHOA.
WH-O-O-A-A!
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE GET THIS
FAR!
B-B-BUT YOU GOTTA GET BACK AND
HELP THE OTHERS!
UH, GARNET?
GARNET, COME ON!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ STRAINING ]
GARNET! HEY!
[ GRUNTING ]
THIS IS SERIOUS!
PEARL AND AMETHYST ARE IN
TROUBLE!
GARNET, WHY...ARE YOU...SO...
HARD...TO CLIMB?!
GARNET!
>> THAT'S RARE!
>> Steven: OH, MY GOSH!
[ GASPS ]
I'LL SAVE YOU, GARNET!
>> WELL DONE! TASTY!
NOW YOU'RE COOKIN--
>> Steven: [ WHIMPERS ]
>> MEAT THE BEAT!
TIME TO TURN UP THE HEAT.
>> Steven: THE RHYTHM HAS HER.
THE ONLY WAY TO DEFEAT...
THE BEAT...
IS WITH MEAT!
>> A NEW COOK HAS ENTERED THE
KITCHEN.
[ PIG SNORTS, CHICKEN SQUAWKS ]
>> Steven: I HAVE TO WIN!
>> LET'S MEAT IT!
PREPARE YOUR MEATS!
SHAKE IT!
TENDERIZE!
>> [ SLURPING ]
[ CHICKEN SQUAWKS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> PLAYER 1 WINS!
YOU'RE TOAST, PLAYER 2.
[ BEEPING ]
EAT IT UP!
[ CHICKEN SQUAWKS ]
A PLAYER 2 BARBECUE!
>> Steven: AW, NO!
MY LAST SHOT!
[ BEEPING ]
>> LET'S MEAT IT!
RACK THOSE RIBS!
SPICE IT UP!
THRILL IS IN THE GRILL.
YOU'RE TOASTED.
>> Steven: THIS...IS...
IT!
[ CHICKEN SQUAWKS ]
[ GROANS ]
>> PLAYER 1 WINS!
YOU'RE TOAST, PLAYER 2.
>> Steven: I CAN'T DO IT!
GARNET, SNAP OUT OF IT!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP PLAYING THIS
[GRUNTS] HORRIBLE GA-A-A-ME!
[ METAL GROANING ]
[ STRAINING ]
AAH!
[ YELLS ]
[ CONTINUES YELLING ]
[ GROANING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Steven: GARNET!
>> Garnet: YOU WON.
>> HUH? HUH?!
IT WAS YOU!
YOU'VE BEEN BREAKIN' MY GAMES!
[ WHOOSH ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
PEARL! AMETHYST!
>> Steven: I CAN HELP, TOO!
>> OH, NO! NO, NO!
DON'T YOU GO FLIPPITY-FLOPPIN'
OUT OF HERE!
>> Steven: YEAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
I'M WORKING! SEE?
HMM?
[ GASPS ] A QUARTER!
>> NOW YOU'RE COOKIN'!
>> Amethyst: HA! TAKE THAT!
>> Pearl: WOW, AMETHYST, I'M
IMPRESSED.
>> Steven: NOW IT'S YOUR MOVE,
PEARL!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, ARE THE WATER
BALLOONS REALLY NECESSARY?
>> Steven: YEAH!
THIS WAY THE MOVES REALLY
MATTER.
>> Pearl: BUT IT'S CHECKERS.
EVERY SINGLE MOVE MATTERS.
>> Amethyst: IT SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEONE'S BEING A SORE LOSER.
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
I'M NOT A SORE LOSER...
BECAUSE I JUST WON THE GAME.
>> Amethyst: WHAAAA?
HERE IT COMES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
AHH, IT FEELS GOOD TO LOSE.
>> Pearl: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
I CERTAINLY HOPE THAT'S NOT THE
ATTITUDE YOU HAVE DURING BATTLE.
>> Amethyst: YOU'RE NO FUN
ANYMORE.
THIS IS WHY WE NEVER FORM OPAL.
>> Pearl: WE DON'T FORM OPAL
BECAUSE YOU'RE DIFFICULT AND A
MESS.
>> Amethyst: WE DON'T FORM OPAL
BECAUSE YOU'RE UPTIGHT AND --
>> Steven: GUYS!
GUYS!
WHAT IS OPAL?!
>> Amethyst: OH, IT'S THE TWO OF
US MASHED TOGETHER.
>> Pearl: [ SCOFFS ]
IS WATER JUST HYDROGEN AND
OXYGEN "MASHED TOGETHER"?
>> Both: UH...
>> Pearl: ANALOGY WASTED.
LOOK HERE, STEVEN.
WHEN WE SYNCHRONIZE OUR FORMS,
WE CAN COMBINE INTO A POWERFUL
FUSION GEM NAMED OPAL.
>> Amethyst: EXCEPT I DON'T
DANCE LIKE THAT.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
>> Steven: WOW!
THAT'S SO COOL!
BUT TELL ME MORE ABOUT OPAL!
>> Amethyst: WELL, STEVEN, SHE'S
AN ULTRA-POWERFUL, STONE-COLD
BETTY.
THAT PART'S ME.
AND SHE'S, LIKE, KIND OF TALL.
THAT PART'S PEARL.
>> Pearl: WHAT AMETHYST IS
ATTEMPTING TO SAY IS...
OPAL IS AN AMALGAM OF OUR
COMBINED MAGICAL AND PHYSICAL
ATTRIBUTES FUSED INTO A SINGLE
ENTITY.
>> Steven: WOW!
CAN YOU DO IT RIGHT NOW?
COME ON! FORM OPAL!
>> Amethyst: PFFF!
>> Pearl: WE ONLY FORM OPAL WHEN
IT'S ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY.
>> Steven: GARNET'S BACK!
OOH! OOH!
DID YOU BRING ME ANYTHING?
WHOA!
A ROCK!
THANKS, GARNET!
>> Pearl: SO, WAS YOUR MISSION A
SUCCESS?
>> Garnet: I'VE LOCATED THE
GEODE BEETLES OF HEAVEN AND
EARTH.
WE SHOULD SPLIT UP TO RETRIEVE
THEM.
>> Amethyst: WELL, I'M GOING
WITH NOT PEARL.
>> Pearl: THAT'S PERFECT BECAUSE
I DON'T WANT TO GO WITH
GRAMMATICALLY INCORRECT PEOPLE
ANYWAY.
>> Steven: IS HER TALKING ABOUT
ME?
>> Garnet: YOU THREE GO
TOGETHER.
I GO ALONE.
>> Both: WHAT? WHY?
>> Garnet: THE EARTH BEETLE IS
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE BOILING
LAVA LAKE, AND ONLY I CAN SWIM
IN LAVA.
YOU'LL FIND THE HEAVEN BEETLE AT
THE TOP OF THE SKY SPIRE.
IT'S SAFER.
>> Amethyst: YOU MEAN BORING-ER.
>> Pearl: YOU MEAN "MORE
BORING."
>> Amethyst: SO YOU AGREE WITH
ME.
>> Pearl: [ SCOFFS ]
COME ON, YOU TWO.
LET'S GO.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, BE SURE TO
KEEP THE HARMONY.
>> Steven: NO PROBLEM.
TODAY'S GONNA BE ALL ABOUT
HA-A-A-A-RMO-O-O-O-O-NY!
UGH!
WHOA!
IS THIS WHERE THE HEAVEN BEETLE
LIVES?
>> Pearl: APPARENTLY.
>> Amethyst: ALL THE WAY AT THE
TOP.
>> Steven: SO, WHEN YOU FUSE, DO
YOU TURN INTO A GIANT GIANT
WOMAN OR JUST A REGULAR-SIZED
GIANT WOMAN?
>> Amethyst: UGH.
>> Steven: DOES ONE OF YOU
CONTROL THE RIGHT ARM AND THE
OTHER CONTROL THE LEFT ARM?
>> Pearl: COME ON, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WAIT!
THESE ARE EXTREMELY IMPORTANT
QUESTIONS.
WHEW!
[ PANTING ]
THERE SURE ARE A LOT OF STAIRS.
HOW ABOUT YOU FORM OPAL AND GIVE
ME A PIGGYBACK RIDE?
>> Both: NO!
>> Steven: WHAT ABOUT IF YOU EAT
A HOT DOG?
WHOSE STOMACH DOES IT GO INTO,
OR DO YOU SHARE THE SAME
STOMACH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT WOULD BE GROSS.
[ RUSTLING ]
[ GASPS ] LOOK OUT!
IT'S A MAGICAL GOAT GUARDIAN!
QUICK! YOU HAVE TO FORM OPAL!
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO DEFEAT IT!
HURRY BEFORE IT KILLS US ALL!
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ]
STEVEN, WE ONLY FUSE FOR
DEADLY SITUATIONS.
DOES THIS LOOK LIKE A DEADLY
SITUATION?
>> [ CHOMPS ]
>> Pearl: OW! HEY!
BAD MOUNTAIN GOAT!
>> [ BLEATS ]
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: DARN IT.
AW, I'M NEVER GONNA GET TO SEE
OPAL.
[ SIGHS ]
♪ ALL I WANNA DO IS SEE YOU TURN
INTO A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA BE IS SOMEONE WHO
GETS TO SEE A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO IS HELP YOU
TURN INTO A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA BE IS SOMEONE WHO
GETS TO SEE A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ OH, I KNOW IT'LL BE GREAT
AND I JUST CAN'T WAIT ♪
♪ TO SEE THE PERSON YOU ARE
TOGETHER ♪
♪ IF YOU GIVE IT A CHANCE,
YOU COULD DO A HUGE DANCE ♪
♪ BECAUSE YOU ARE A GIANT
WOMAN ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT EVEN LIKE BEING
TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DON'T,
IT WON'T BE FOREVER ♪
♪ BUT IF IT WERE ME, I'D REALLY
WANT TO BE A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ A GIANT WOMAN ♪
♪ ALL I WANNA DO IS SEE YOU TURN
INTO A GIANT WOMAN ♪
>> [ BLEATS ]
>> Steven: OOH!
>> Steven: WAIT UP, STEVEN JR.!
>> Pearl: WAIT!
STEVEN, I'M NOT SURE YOU CAN
MAKE THOSE JUMPS.
>> Steven: OH!
YOU SHOULD FUSE INTO OPAL, AND
THEN LAY ACROSS THE ROCKS LIKE A
BRIDGE!
>> Pearl: WE DON'T NEED OPAL TO
GET ACROSS.
>> Steven: CAN YOU DO IT ANYWAY?
PLEASE?
IT WOULD BE EASIER, WOULDN'T IT?
>> Amethyst: NOT AS EASY AS
THIS!
>> Steven: WAAAAHHHHH!
OOOOH!
OOH.
WOW, AMETHYST.
THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD IDEA!
>> Amethyst: I KNOW.
I'M FULL OF 'EM.
>> Pearl: [ GROANS ]
>> Steven: AW, COME ON, PEARL!
IT'S SAFE!
JUST LOOK!
[ LAUGHS ]
AAH!
>> Pearl: AAH!
>> Steven: AAAAH!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: THAT WAS SO GREAT HOW
YOU WORKED TOGETHER.
WHY DON'T YOU DO THAT ALL THE
TIME?
[ PANTING ]
I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS ANYMORE!
HEY, LOOK AT THAT!
IT'S A TINY TEMPLE!
>> Pearl: IT'S JUST WHERE GARNET
SAID IT WOULD BE.
THE HEAVEN BEETLE SHOULD BE
INSIDE.
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
CHECK IT OUT!
IT'S EVEN GOT A LITTLE BEETLE
BEDROOM AND LITTLE BEETLE
BONGOS AND A LITTLE BEETLE BABY
BOOK.
>> Pearl: BUT WHERE'S THE
BEETLE?
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
THE HEAVEN BEETLE WOULDN'T
LEAVE, WOULD IT?
OH, IT COULD BE ANYWHERE!
>> Amethyst: UH, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD FREAK OUT SOME MORE.
THAT'S REALLY GONNA HELP US FIND
IT.
>> Pearl: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOUR
ATTITUDE, AMETHYST.
AND NOW YOU'RE JUST SLOUCHING
OVER HERE DOING NOTHING!
>> Amethyst: HEY!
IT'S NOT MY FAULT THE BEETLE
ISN'T THERE!
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO MAKE THINGS
WORSE BY SQUAWKING AT ME?
>> Pearl: I DON'T SQUAWK!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YOU'RE
SQUAWKING AND COMMENTING ON MY
POSTURE!
>> [ BLEATS ]
>> Steven: HEY! CUT IT OUT!
YOU'RE SCARING STEVEN JR.!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> [ SQUAWKS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] MY SON.
>> [ SCREECHES ]
>> Steven: AAAH!
>> Amethyst: IN HERE, GUYS!
>> Pearl: IT SWALLOWED MY SPEAR!
>> Steven: GUYS, THIS IS GREAT!
NOW'S THE PERFECT TIME FOR YOU
TWO TO FORM OPAL!
>> [ SCREECHES ]
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Pearl: OH, BROTHER.
AAH!
>> Amethyst: UGH!
SO, YOU WANNA TRY THAT AGAIN
WITH LESS HITTING ME IN THE FACE
THIS TIME?
>> Pearl: WELL, IT WOULD HAVE
WORKED IF YOUR MOVEMENTS WEREN'T
SO ERRATIC AND FORMLESS.
>> Amethyst: SO, IT WAS ALL MY
FAULT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU TOTALLY WEREN'T EVEN TRYING
TO SYNC WITH MY DANCING.
YOU SHOULD KNOW HOW I DANCE BY
NOW!
>> Steven: STOP!
COME ON, GUYS!
PLEASE STOP FIGHTING!
IF YOU CAN'T GET ALONG WITH EACH
OTHER, I MIGHT NEVER GET TO SEE
YOUR AWESOME FUSION POWER!
>> [ SCREECHES ]
>> Steven: AND I MIGHT GET EATEN
BY A GIANT BIRD!
[ GASPS ]
>> [ GULPS ]
>> Both: STEVEN!
>> Steven: UNH!
AAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
>> [ BLEATS ]
>> Steven: STEVEN JR.!
HOW CAN YOU EAT AT A TIME LIKE
THIS?
[ GASPS ]
HEY, IS THAT THE HEAVEN BEETLE?
LET ME SEE IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY!
BE A GOOD GOAT AND GIVE ME THE
MAGIC BUG!
[ RUMBLING ]
AAH!
I GOT IT!
>> [ BLEATS ]
>> Steven: NO! B-BAD GOAT!
YOU'RE NO SON OF MINE!
AAAH!
[ PANTING ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
STEVEN JR.!
OOOH!
OPAL?
AAAAAH!
>> HUP!
>> Steven: AAAAAH!
>> STAY LOW.
[ WHIRRING ]
>> Steven: UH...
DO YOU...KNOW WHO I AM?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
♪ ALL YOU WANNA DO IS SEE ME
TURN INTO ♪
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
A GIANT WOMAN.
WE'RE BACK!
>> Garnet: THE HEAVEN BEETLE.
>> [ GASPS ] I DON'T HAVE IT.
[ GROANING ]
>> Both: UNH!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, YOU GOT
DISTRACTED!
>> Amethyst: HEY!
YOU WERE THE ONE GETTING CARRIED
AWAY WITH ALL THOSE FANCY
BACKFLIPS!
>> Steven: WAIT A SEC.
I'VE GOT THE BEETLE!
>> Garnet: GOOD JOB, STEVEN.
I ALSO SEE YOU HELPED YOUR
TEAMMATES FUSE.
>> Steven: AND ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS GET EATEN BY A BIRD.
>> Garnet: NICE WORK.
YOU'LL BE GREAT AT FUSING ONE
DAY.
>> Steven: YEAH.
WAIT. I CAN DO THAT, TOO?!