>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: OKAY, EVERYONE.
I THINK WE ALL KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
I'M SURE YOU KNEW THIS DAY
WAS COMING SOONER OR LATER.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR CONCERN, BUT
THAT LANGUAGE WAS INAPPROPRIATE.
I'M A CRYSTAL GEM.
I'M A BIG BOY NOW.
AND I GOT TO STOP SAYING STUFF
LIKE, "I'M A BIG BOY NOW."
LOOK, I'M SURE THIS IS TOUGH,
BUT LET'S ALL BE POSITIVE
ABOUT THIS.
MAN, I GUESS I CAN'T BE IN
THE NINJA SQUAD ANYMORE.
GET OUT OF MY LIFE, NINJA SQUAD!
YEAH! NEW NINJA SQUAD!
MM. THAT'S EVERYTHING FOR NOW.
HMM?
OH.
MASTER OF CEREMONIES BEAR BEAR.
I GUESS I SHOULD GET RID OF YOU,
TOO?
NAH.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN I'LL NEED
A COOL DEEJAY FOR A FUN PARTY,
RIGHT?
WHO-O-O-O-AH!
UH.
GARNET!
>> Garnet: GOOD MORNING TO YOU,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: BOY, I SURE AM LUCKY
YOU SHOWED UP WHEN YOU DID.
>> Garnet: LUCK'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
>> Steven: WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> Garnet: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> Steven: NO, SERIOUSLY.
HOW DO YOU ALWAYS KNOW WHERE
TO BE?
>> Garnet: MM.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN HANDLE
THAT INFORMATION.
>> Steven: ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
SOMETHING COOL ABOUT YOURSELF?
>> Garnet: NOPE.
>> Steven: AW, COME ON.
I'M A -- LARGE...MAN NOW.
>> Garnet: WELL...
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THAT
I HAVE A SORT OF FUTURE VISION.
[ ZING! ]
I'M ABLE TO SEE POSSIBLE
OUTCOMES TO MOST SITUATIONS,
WHICH COMES IN HANDY SINCE YOU
SEEM TO ATTRACT A LOT OF DANGER.
>> Steven: WELL, DANGER IS MY
MIDDLE NAME.
>> Garnet: THAT'S A LIE.
YOUR MIDDLE NAME IS CUTIE PIE.
>> Steven: HAAA!
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> OON-DOHNG HAH JAH! CHA!
HANA DOOL, DOOL DOOL.
SEHT DOOL, NEHT DOOL.
DUH-SUHT DOOL.
YUH-SUHT DOOL.
IL-GOHB DOOL, YUH-DUHLP.
GEH SOHK HAH JAH!
HANA DOOL, DOOL DOOL.
SEHT DOOL, NEHT DOOL.
DUH-SUHT DOOL.
YUH-SUHT DOOL.
IL-GOHB DOOL.
YUH-DUHLP --
[ ZAP! ]
>> Garnet: OKAY, WE'RE DONE.
>> Steven: BUT THE DAY STILL HAS
SO MUCH POTENTIAL.
GARNET, WHAT ARE MY BREAKFAST
POSSIBILITIES?
>> Garnet: WELL, YOU'RE ALREADY
OUTSIDE, SO YOU'LL PROBABLY
GO TO THE BIG DONUT.
>> Steven: WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING.
UM, DO YOU SEE ANY POSSIBLE
FUTURES WHERE YOU, UM, COME
WITH ME AND HAVE A GREAT TIME?
>> Garnet: HMM.
[ MUSICAL WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING RESUMES ]
YES.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] REALLY?!
THEN LET'S GO!
SO, CAN PEARL AND AMETHYST
SEE THE FUTURE, TOO?
>> Garnet: NO ONE CAN SEE
THE FUTURE.
I CAN SEE OPTIONS AND
TRAJECTORIES.
TIME IS LIKE A RIVER THAT SPLITS
INTO CREEKS OR POOLS INTO LAKES
OR CAREENS DOWN WATERFALLS.
I HAVE THE MAP, AND I STEER
THE SHIP.
>> Steven: I...SEE.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
SO, WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF I SAID
HI TO SADIE?
>> Garnet: THE MOST PROBABLE
OUTCOME IS THAT SADIE WILL SAY
HI BACK.
>> Steven: HMM.
HI, SADIE!
>> OH, HI, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
OH, THAT WAS AN EASY ONE.
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF...
I SAID HI TO MY BFF, LARS?
OUR FRIENDSHIP IS DEEP, BUT
COMPLICATED.
SO THE OUTCOME OF THIS
EXPERIMENT IS WAY UNPREDICTABLE.
>> Garnet: I SEE A SINGLE
POTENTIAL FUTURE WHERE LARS
GIVES YOU A HIGH FIVE.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: AND TWO MORE
POTENTIAL FUTURES WHERE YOU
SUFFER THIRD-DEGREE BURNS
ALL OVER YOUR BODY.
>> A HIGH FIVE...FROM LARS!
HI, LARS!
>> UGHH!
>> Steven: OHH!
>> CRIMINY! ARE YOU OKAY?!
THAT COFFEE WAS REALLY HOT!
>> Garnet: I DRINK COFFEE FOR
BREAKFAST.
>> Steven: [ NERVOUS CHUCKLING ]
FUNNY.
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT I WANT.
ANY POSSIBLE FUTURES HERE WHERE
I'M HURT BY THIS?
>> Garnet: HMM.
MM.
TONS.
>> Steven: UH...LIKE...WHAT?
>> Garnet: WELL, FOR STARTERS...
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: ...YOU COULD JUST BE
GOING ON ABOUT YOUR BUSINESS,
EATING YOUR FRY BITS, AND THEN
SUDDENLY YOU CHOKE TO DEATH!
[ PLINK! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
OR YOU GET SO DISTRACTED THAT
YOU FALL DOWN A MANHOLE!
[ SPLASH! ]
[ PLINK ]
YOU COULD GET FOOD POISONING,
OR BE BULLIED BY WASPS.
[ WASPS LAUGHING ]
[ PLINK! ]
AND THAT'S JUST A FEW INSTANCES
OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD.
>> Steven: W-WHAT IF I STAND
PERFECTLY STILL?
>> Garnet: YOU'LL PROBABLY GET
A REALLY BAD SUNBURN.
YEAH.
>> Steven: UH, GARNET, WAIT UP!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ZING! ]
[ SHARK GROWLS ]
[ WATER GURGLING ]
[ PLINK ]
[ ZING! ]
[ BONK! ]
[ PLINK! ]
[ ZING! ]
[ FLYING SAUCER WHIRRING ]
COOKIE CAT! YOU'RE REAL?!
[ ZAP! ]
OH, NOO!
I EVER CONSIDERED THAT YOU
WOULD BE EVIL!
[ PLINK! ]
[ PANTING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Garnet: NICE HELMET.
>> Steven: [ SCOFFS ]
[ Chuckling ] YEAH.
[ Haltingly ] YOU -- YOU NEVER
KNOW WHEN YOU'RE GONNA RIDE
A BIKE.
>> Garnet: AND YOU'RE MAKING
A SANDWICH.
>> Steven: YEAH.
JUST GOT TO PICK UP THE KNIFE
AND...S-SPREAD THE MAYONNAISE.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
PICK UP THE...
[ WHIMPERS ]
THE KNIFE!
[ WHIMPERING ]
PICK UP...
[ HEART BEATING ]
...KNI-I-FE!
AAH!
[ PANTING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
>> Steven: WAIT! WAIT!
I'VE GOT IT.
[ PLOP! ]
>> Garnet: THAT WILL KILL YOU
FASTER.
>> Steven: NOT FUNNY!
>> Garnet: OH.
>> Amethyst: NICE NOGGIN,
STEVEN.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ PANTING ]
HUH!
>> Pearl: WE'RE READY, GARNET.
>> Steven: WAIT.
YOU'RE GOING ON A MISSION?
HOLD ON! DON'T LEAVE ME!
AT LEAST TELL ME WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN WITH MY LUNCH!
DO I CHOKE ON A PICKLE?
>> Garnet: MM, YOU DON'T CHOKE
ON A PICKLE.
>> Steven: THAT MEANS SOMETHING
ELSE HAPPENS WITH THE PICKLE!
>> Pearl: GARNET!
SHOULDN'T WE BE GOING?
>> Garnet: STEVEN, I CAN'T BE
WITH YOU ALL THE TIME.
JUST TRUST ME WHEN I SAY THAT
YOU ARE IN CONTROL.
DO NOT GO ON THE ROOF.
NO MATTER WHAT.
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
>> Steven: [ WHIMPERS ]
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY HAPPEN
TO ME ON THE ROOF?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAH!
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
UGH.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OKAY. CALM DOWN.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GET
A SNACK.
[ GASPS ]
BUT WHAT IF -- [ ZAP! ]
OOH!
[ PLINK! ]
UGH!
HOW COME YOU GUYS ARE BACK?!
>> WE'RE MADE OF MAGIC.
>> YEAH! MAGIC!
[ PLINK! ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> Steven: AAAAH!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAH!
UGH!
MASTER OF CEREMONIES BEAR BEAR.
[ Thinking ] I'M A BIG BOY NOW!
BIG BOY NOW!
BOY NOW!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
A CRYSTAL GEM.
A CRYSTAL GEM!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAAAAAH!
UGH!
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OKAY. I'M HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO TO ME,
FUTURE?
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
GET OFF THE ROOF!
>> Steven: NO!
IF SOMETHING IS GOING TO HAPPEN
TO ME, JUST LET IT HAPPEN.
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> Steven: NO, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
EVERYTHING I DO SHOVES ME
VIOLENTLY TOWARDS THE END!
THE MORE I KNOW, THE MORE I KNOW
THAT I DON'T KNOW!
I CAN'T LIVE LIKE THIS!
WHY DID YOU TELL ME ABOUT
FUTURE VISION?!
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME
ON THE ROOF?!
>> Garnet: THIS.
>> Steven: W-WHAT?
>> Garnet: I KNEW YOU MIGHT DO
THIS IF I TOLD YOU ABOUT MY
POWER.
I SAW THIS, AND I TOLD YOU,
ANYWAY.
>> Steven: BUT...WHY?
>> Garnet: I TOOK A RISK AT YOUR
EXPENSE.
THERE WAS A CHANCE YOU'D
UNDERSTAND THIS, AND WE'D BE
CLOSER.
STEVEN, I SEE SO MANY THINGS
THAT CAN HURT YOU.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE LET ONE
OF THEM BE ME.
THERE ARE MILLIONS OF
POSSIBILITIES FOR THE FUTURE,
BUT IT'S UP TO YOU TO CHOOSE
WHICH BECOMES REALITY.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
YOU CHOOSE YOUR OWN FUTURE.
>> Steven: I DO UNDERSTAND.
I --
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
WHAT AM I DOING?
I GUESS I CAN'T REALLY SEE
A FUTURE FOR MYSELF UP HERE.
[ SIGHS ]
MM.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I'LL WATCH OUT FOR MYSELF
FROM NOW ON.
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ ZAP! ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> Garnet: OH, NOTHING
IMPORTANT.
>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ BIRDS SQUAWKING ]
>> Steven: WHOA. HOW ARE THEY
GONNA GET OUT OF THIS ONE?
OH, THAT'S HOW.
[ WHIRRING ]
YOU'RE BACK!
HEY, IT'S THOSE THINGS FROM THE
GALAXY WARP.
WHY'D YOU BRING THEM HOME?
>> Pearl: WE CAN'T HAVE THEM
REACTIVATING AND FIXING THE
HOMEWORLD WARP.
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN, CHECK
THIS OUT!
KABLOOSH!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, PLEASE!
THIS IS SERIOUS!
WE NEED TO UNDERSTAND THESE
THINGS, NOT SQUASH THEM.
IF HOMEWORLD GEMS ARE TRYING TO
RETURN TO EARTH...
THEY HAVE TO BE STOPPED!
>> Garnet: PEARL, CALM DOWN.
WE'RE STILL CUT OFF.
THE EARTH IS SAFE.
>> Steven: SAFE FROM WHAT?
WHAT DO THE HOMEWORLD GEMS WANT
TO DO?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, A VERY LONG
TIME AGO, GEMS TRIED TO DO
SOMETHING...VERY BAD.
IT WAS SOMETHING THAT WOULD HAVE
DAMAGED THE EARTH.
SOME GEMS, LIKE YOUR MOTHER,
GARNET, AND MYSELF FELT THAT
THIS WAS UNFAIR TO THE LIFE THAT
ALREADY EXISTED HERE, AND SO WE
SWORE TO NEVER LET THE EARTH BE
USED FOR THEIR...PURPOSES, EVEN
IF IT MEANT...
[ GROANS ]
EVEN IF IT MEANT WE COULD NEVER
GO HOME.
>> Garnet: WE CHOSE EARTH.
>> Steven: WAIT A SEC.
SO THAT MEANS...
WE'RE JUST LIKE THE
NO HOME BOYS!
>> Pearl: THE WHA?
>> Steven: THE NO HOME BOYS!
IT'S A BOOK SERIES ABOUT THESE
BOYS WHO HAVE NO HOME.
SO THEY TRAVEL AROUND THE
COUNTRY, LIVING IN BOXCARS, AND
RIDING RIVER RAFTS, SOLVING
MYSTERIES!
THEY HAD A SUCCESSFUL RUN, UNTIL
THE DISASTROUS GRAPHIC-NOVEL
ADAPTATION.
BUT MY FAVORITE STORY IS THIS
CLASSIC ONE WHERE THE
NO HOME BOYS ARE CHASED ACROSS
THE COUNTRYSIDE BY A MYSTERIOUS
PURSUER, WHICH TURNS OUT TO BE
THE VERY FEAR RESTING WITHIN
THEMSELVES.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WE ARE NOT
LIKE THE NO HOME BOYS.
WE ARE LITERALLY STANDING IN
YOUR HOME RIGHT NOW.
>> Steven: AW, I WISH I WAS A
NO HOME BOY.
NO PAST, NO FUTURE, JUST THE
OPEN ROAD.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, SOUNDS LIKE
FUN.
LET'S DO IT.
>> Steven: REALLY?!
>> Amethyst: YEAH. LET'S RUN!
>> Steven: ♪ IT'S TIME TO GET
MOVIN' ♪
♪ TIME FOR US TO HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ THERE'S NO TIME TO HANG
AROUND ♪
♪ OUR ADVENTURE'S JUST BEGUN ♪
♪ WE'LL BE THINKING 'BOUT OUR
FRIENDS AS WE CHASE THE SETTING
SUN ♪
>> Both: ♪ BUT WE'RE LEAVING
THEM BEHIND, WE'RE ON THE RUN ♪
>> Steven: [ WHISTLING ]
[ DINGING ]
♪ WE'RE ON THE RUN ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ I DON'T CARE
ABOUT WHAT ALL THE OTHERS SAY ♪
♪ BUT I GUESS THERE ARE SOME
THINGS THAT WILL JUST NEVER GO
AWAY ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD SAY THAT
THERE'S NO BETTER PLACE THAN
HOME ♪
>> Both: ♪ BUT HOME'S A PLACE
THAT I HAVE NEVER KNOWN ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY WE'RE ON THE RUN ♪
[ TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS ]
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
AAH! AAH!
THE -- THE RACCOON IS BACK!
[ PANTING ]
UM, AMETHYST?
CAN I HAVE SOME OF YOUR FOOD?
>> Amethyst: [ CHOMPING ]
OH, UH, SORRY, DUDE.
>> Steven: MY BINDLE COULDN'T
FIT ENOUGH FOOD FOR ME AND A
RACCOON.
>> Amethyst: WHY DIDN'T YOU
BRING YOUR BACKPACK?
>> Steven: IT WOULDN'T FIT IN MY
BINDLE?
MAYBE I CAN JUST SLEEP THIS
HUNGER OFF.
JUST LIKE THE NO HOME BOYS.
YOU KNOW, I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN
MISLED ABOUT HAY.
IT ALWAYS LOOKS SO SOFT IN THOSE
ILLUSTRATIONS, BUT IT'S ACTUALLY
REALLY SCRATCHY.
[ BANGING ]
AMETHYST, I WANT TO GO HOME NOW.
AMETHYST?
I'M DONE PRETENDING TO BE A
NO HOME BOY.
>> Amethyst: NOT ME.
>> Steven: I'M SURE GARNET AND
PEARL ARE WORRIED SICK ABOUT US,
WONDERING WHEN WE'RE COMING
HOME.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S NOT MY
>> Steven: BUT -- OH, THAT'S
RIGHT.
YOU'RE FROM HOMEWORLD.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S NOT MY HOME,
EITHER!
>> Steven: THEN WHERE ARE YOU
FROM?
>> Amethyst: I'LL SHOW YOU.
[ ANIMAL SQUAWKING ]
HERE WE ARE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
WELCOME TO THE KINDERGARTEN!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> Steven: UH...IT'S GREAT!
>> Amethyst: SURE IS!
[ CHUCKLES ] COME ON!
>> Steven: WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> Amethyst: IT'S KIND OF WHERE
I'M FROM.
>> Steven: BUT I THOUGHT GEMS
WERE FROM SPACE?
>> Amethyst: PEARL AND GARNET
ARE, BUT I WAS MADE HERE ON
EARTH, LIKE YOU.
[ GASPS ]
CHECK IT OUT!
[ Laughing ] OH, MAN.
I MISSED THIS GUY.
AWW! IT'S MY CLIMBING ROCK.
>> Steven: UH, HELLO!
>> Amethyst: AND OVER THERE --
THAT'S THE SITTING ROCK.
AND THAT WAS THE ONE ROCK THAT I
KICKED INTO TWO ROCKS!
>> Steven: UH, HOW LONG DID YOU
LIVE HERE?
>> Amethyst: FOR A WHILE, I
GUESS, UM, AT LEAST UNTIL I MET
YOUR MOM AND THE OTHERS.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> Amethyst: EH, IT'S JUST SOME
OLD GEM JUNK FROM A LONG TIME
AGO.
IT'S PROBABLY BUSTED BY NOW.
HEY, STEVEN. LOOK.
[ CHUCKLES ]
HERE'S THE HOLE I CAME OUT OF!
>> Steven: HANG ON. WHAT?
>> Amethyst: IT'S MY HOLE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
LOOK -- IT'S ME-SIZED.
[ SIGHS ]
STILL GOT THAT GOOD HOLE SMELL.
>> Steven: YOU CAME OUT OF THIS
HOLE?
>> Amethyst: THIS IS WHERE I WAS
MADE, DUDE.
ONE DAY, JUST...
[ POP! ]
...RIGHT OUT OF THIS HOLE.
>> Steven: SO, WHAT ABOUT THE
OTHER HOLES?
[ WHIRRING ]
>> Pearl: THERE YOU ARE!
>> Amethyst: GREAT.
HERE COMES THE FUN POLICE.
>> Pearl: GARNET SAID YOU'D BE
HERE, BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO
BELIEVE IT.
AMETHYST, WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
BRINGING STEVEN TO A
KINDERGARTEN!?
>> Amethyst: I DON'T KNOW.
WE WERE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> Steven: PEARL?
WAS AMETHYST REALLY MADE HERE?
>> Pearl: HOW MUCH DID YOU TELL
HIM?
>> Amethyst: WHAT?
YOU MEAN ABOUT THE BAD THING?
HOW THIS BAD PLACE IS WHERE BAD
GEMS CAME TO GROW MORE BAD GEMS?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT?
>> Steven: THEY GREW OTHER GEMS
HERE?
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, HE'S NOT
READY!
>> Amethyst: OH, BUT DON'T
WORRY, STEVEN.
EVERYTHING'S JUST FINE NOW.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST.
>> Amethyst: IT ALL WORKED OUT.
WE WON!
>> Pearl: STOP.
>> Amethyst: AND WE SHUT THIS
PLACE DOWN SO THE EARTH WOULD BE
SAFE FROM PARASITES LIKE ME!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, THAT'S
ENOUGH!
>> Steven: PEARL?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, I'M SORRY.
I NEVER WANTED YOU TO SEE THIS
HORRIBLE PLACE.
>> Amethyst: THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST LEAVE!
ADMIT IT -- I'M JUST AN
EMBARRASSMENT TO YOU!
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
[ GASPS ] WAIT!
AAAH!
>> Pearl: I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
YOU.
>> Amethyst: I WOULDN'T WANT TO
FIGHT ME NEITHER.
>> Steven: YOU GUYS, STOP IT!
>> Amethyst: STAY OUT OF IT!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, STOP THIS!
YOU CAN'T BEAT ME.
>> Amethyst: I DON'T CARE!
AAAAAH!
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU STAND
THERE AND REMIND ME OF
EVERYTHING I HATE ABOUT MYSELF!
>> Pearl: [ WHIMPERS ]
>> Amethyst: I NEVER ASKED FOR
IT TO BE THIS WAY.
[ SNIFFLES ]
I NEVER ASKED TO BE MADE!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST.
>> Steven: AMETHYST, PLEASE, NO
MORE!
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET, BUT I CAN'T
BEAR TO WATCH YOU TWO HURT EACH
OTHER.
[ CREAKING, RATTLING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
AMETHYST!
AMETHYST, AMETHYST! AMETHYST!
[ CRASHING ]
AMETHYST!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
[ GRUNTS ]
AMETHYST.
>> Amethyst: GO AWAY.
I'M BAD, AND YOU SHOULDN'T BE
AROUND ME.
>> Steven: WHAT?
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT ANY OF
THIS REALLY MEANS, BUT I --
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YOU DON'T,
'CAUSE IF YOU DID, YOU WOULDN'T
BE TALKING TO ME.
>> Steven: PEARL, GET IN HERE.
YOU GOT TO HELP ME.
>> Pearl: BUT...
>> Steven: YOU HAVE TO TALK TO
HER.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST?
AMETHYST, I-I HAD NO IDEA YOU'VE
BEEN UPSET ABOUT THIS.
>> Amethyst: WHAT?!
YOU HAD NO IDEA?!
HO! THIS IS LIKE MY ENTIRE
EXISTENCE!
YOU WANT TO PRETEND THAT NONE OF
THIS EVER HAPPENED.
YOU THINK I'M JUST A BIG
MISTAKE!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
NO, NO.
AMETHYST, YOU'RE NOT THE
MISTAKE.
YOU'RE JUST THE BY-PRODUCT OF
A...BIG MISTAKE.
NO, THAT'S NOT -- I...
I JUST NEVER THOUGHT OF THIS AS
YOU.
NONE OF THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
YOU DIDN'T BUILD THIS PLACE.
I-I'M SORRY, AMETHYST.
I HOPE YOU CAN FORGIVE ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE GOOD THING THAT
CAME OUT OF THIS MESS.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU WERE PROUD
OF THAT.
>> Steven: PHEW!
CRYSTAL GEMS FOREVER!
NOW LET'S GO HOME SO STEVEN CAN
SLEEP IN A BED.