>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
WHAT? WHY NOT?
>> STEVEN, I TOLD YOU I CAN'T
HANG OUT TODAY.
I HAVE TENNIS PRACTICE.
AND THEN MOM WANTS TO GO OUT FOR
A FAMILY DINNER.
BUT SHE SAID I COULD HANG OUT
ALL DAY TOMORROW AND I CAN COME
OVER ALL THE TIME NOW THAT IT'S
SUMMER VACATION.
>> Steven: WHAT'S SUMMER
VACATION?
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN SCHOOL GETS
OUT FOR THE SUMMER?
>> Steven: I'VE NEVER BEEN TO
THIS -- HOW DO YOU SAY? --
SCHOOL.
HOW DOES IT WORK?
>> IT'S A PLACE WHERE YOU GO TO
LEARN.
IT'S FULL OF DESKS,
CHALKBOARDS...
>> Steven: HMM.
>> ...BOOKS, MAPS.
>> Steven: I SEE.
YEP, IT'S ALL COMING TOGETHER.
>> Pearl: SO, HOW DO WE BEGIN
OUR "SCHOOL"?
>> Steven: UH...I...
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS EVERYTHING CONNIE TOLD
ME.
WHY DO I NEVER ASK FOLLOW-UP
QUESTIONS?!
WHO WILL TEACH LITTLE STEVIE
NOW?!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
TEACH YOU?!
STEVEN, IF ONLY I HAD KNOWN
THAT'S WHAT YOU REALLY WANTED.
TWOOOW!
HAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
WE FOUND THIS GEM-POWERED MIRROR
AT THE GALAXY WARP.
IT CAN CAPTURE AND DISPLAY ANY
EVENT IT'S WITNESSED IN ALL OF
GEM HISTORY.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: IT'LL OFFER YOU
EVERYTHING YOU'VE EVER WANTED TO
KNOW ABOUT YOUR FELLOW GEMS AND
OUR CULTURE.
>> Steven: I MUST BE INCREDIBLY
IMPORTANT TO GEM CULTURE.
>> Pearl: [ SCOFFS ]
IT'S JUST YOU IN THERE.
IT HASN'T EVEN BEEN ACTIVATED.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
SHOW US THE GALAXY WARP.
OH, COME ON!
>> Steven: WHOA! [ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: I KNOW YOU'VE SEEN IT.
[ SIGHS ]
IT IS IN PRETTY ROUGH SHAPE.
IT MUST FINALLY BE BROKEN.
[ SIGHS ] WHAT A SHAME.
>> Steven: DOESN'T SEEM BROKEN
TO ME.
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ] OH, WELL.
I GUESS THAT'S THE END OF OUR
SCHOOL.
>> Steven: WHOA. WHA...
SO YOU COULD SAY...SCHOOL'S OUT
FOR SUMMER?
>> Pearl: YES. GOOD, STEVEN.
THERE ARE MANY WAYS TO SAY THE
SAME THING.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
SCHOOL'S OUT!
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
>> Pearl: HMM.
THE ASYMMETRY OF THIS PILE IS
REALLY STARTING TO BOTHER ME.
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
SCHOOL'S OUT!
HAPPY SUMMER VACATION, STEVEN.
HAPPY SUMMER VACATION,
BEACH CITY!
[ Chuckling ] YEAH!
>> Both: HEY!
>> ER, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING
YOU LITTLE...
STEVEN!
>> Steven: SORRY!
I'M JUST SO EXCITED FOR SUMMER.
ARE YOU EXCITED FOR SUMMER?
I'M SO EXCITED FOR SUMMER!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
UH, I THINK I'M AS EXCITED AS I
CAN GET ABOUT SETTING UP EXTRA
SEATING FOR THE SUMMER RUSH.
BUT LARS HAS BIG PLANS.
>> YOU BET I DO -- ALL THOSE
OUT-OF-TOWN SUMMER BABES
TRAVELING AWAY FROM HOME WITHOUT
THEIR BOYFRIENDS, IF YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
>> Steven: NOPE.
>> MAYBE I'LL GET A FEW NUMBERS.
MAYBE I'LL EVEN...CALL ONE.
>> HA!
WELL, YEAH, MAYBE I'LL MEET A
NEW FRIEND.
>> Steven: THAT'S A GREAT
IDEA -- A SPECIAL NEW FRIEND TO
HAVE FUN ON THE BEACH WITH IN
THE SUMMER.
MAYBE IF I KEEP USING THE MIRROR
TO GUIDE ME, I'LL WALK BACKWARDS
INTO MY OWN BEACH-SUMMER-FUN
BUDDY!
>> NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME, I'LL BE
ON THE ARM OF A HOT WOMAN'S.
>> YOU CAN STOP TALKING ABOUT IT
NOW.
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
♪ WO WO WO WO ♪
♪ WO WO HEE-HEE ♪
>> MAYOR DEWEY.
>> ER, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
YOU LITTLE...
>> Steven: HUH?
>> MAYOR DEWEY.
>> Steven: NOOOOO!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
>> CAR WASH KID, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?!
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW.
WHY WERE YOU DRIVING DOWN THE
BOARDWALK?
>> I'M THE MAYOR -- I'M NOT
GONNA WALK ANYWHERE.
NOW, GO GET RUN OVER SOMEWHERE
ELSE.
I'M LATE FOR A SPEECH.
MAYOR DEWEY. MAYOR DEWEY.
>> Steven: WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
[ WHIR! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU WORK!
THIS IS SO COOL!
WHAT'S IT LIKE BEING A MIRROR?
[ WHIR! ]
YOU WORK!
SO YOU CAN REPEAT STUFF?
[ Chuckling ] YEAH!
>> HELLO, BEACH CITY,
MY FRIENDS!
IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE TO
CELEBRATE THE COMING SEASON.
A WARM SUMMER BREEZE WAFTS
THROUGH THE AIR.
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
PBHT!
[ SPECTATORS SNICKER ]
>> WE ALL LOOK FORWARD TO THE
SOUNDS OF THE SUMMER SEASON...
>> Steven: PBHT!
>> ...THE SMELLS OF THE BUSY
BOARDWALK...
>> Steven: PBHT!
>> ...THE HOT, WET OCEAN WIND...
>> ...THE TIME TO TAKE THAT
PRESSURE THAT'S BUILT UP ALL
YEAR AND JUST LET IT OUT.
>> Steven: PBHT!
[ LAUGHTER ]
WOW, YOU PICKED THAT UP FAST.
PBHT!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU GOT A LOT OF MILEAGE OUT OF
THAT JOKE.
YOU'RE PRETTY FUNNY FOR A
MIRROR.
[ Chuckling ] I'M NOT A MIRROR.
YOU'RE PRETTY FUNNY FOR A --
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YOU MADE SOMETHING NEW!
SAY SOMETHING ELSE!
>> STEVEN...
>> Steven: IS...
>> A NEW FRIEND.
>> Steven: REALLY?
[ Chuckling ] YEAH!
YOU'RE MY FRIEND, TOO.
[ LAUGHS ]
I GOT TO GO TELL THE GEMS.
NOOOOO!
DON'T BE SHY. THEY'LL LOVE YOU.
[ Echoing ] NOOOOO!
[ CHUCKLES ] DON'T WORRY.
THEY'RE A GOOD AUDIENCE.
GUYS!
WAIT TILL YOU SEE...
>> Amethyst: YO! STEE-MAN!
>> Pearl: HELLO, STEVEN.
>> Garnet: HOWDY. BANG.
>> Amethyst: WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING HILARIOUS?
[ SHING! ]
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SYMMETRICAL MEANS BOTH SIDES
HAVE TO BE THE SAME!
[ Grunting ] OH, GOD.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: M.C. BEAR BEAR!
OKAY, THAT'S GREAT.
ANYWAY, I FIXED THE MIRROR!
>> Pearl: EXCELLENT WORK,
STEVEN!
>> Steven: YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
IT'S LIKE A PERSON.
>> Pearl: WAIT. WHAT?
>> Steven: SAY HEY.
LITTLE BUDDY.
UH...EXCUSE US.
COME ON.
YOU WANT TO COME OUT, DON'T YOU?
YOU HAVE SO MUCH TO SAY AND
FUNNY NOISES TO SHARE FROM
ACROSS THE AGES.
ARE WE NOT BEACH-SUMMER-FUN
BUDDIES?
[ WHIR! ]
PBHT!
[ LAUGHS ]
JUST COULDN'T HELP YOURSELF,
HUH?
[ WHIR! ]
JUST FOR YOU...
>> STEVEN!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: IT'S TALKING TO HIM?
IT SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
I-IT SHOULD ONLY BE FOLLOWING
ORDERS.
>> Amethyst: GARNET, DO
SOMETHING.
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
NOOOOO!
>> Garnet: YOU SHOULD JUST GIVE
US BACK THE MIRROR.
IT WILL BE SAFER WHERE WE CAN
WATCH IT.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, LET'S BUBBLE
IT.
>> Steven: NOOOOO!
[ Echoing ] NOOOOO!
WHA...
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
DON'T MAKE ME HAVE TO TAKE IT
FROM YOU.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
IT DOESN'T WANT TO GO WITH YOU.
DON'T YOU HEAR IT SCREAMING?
>> Garnet: STEVEN, IT'S JUST A
MIRROR, A TOOL.
IT CAN'T WANT ANYTHING.
>> Steven: [ Echoing ] NOOOOO!
[ Echoing ] NOOOOO! NOOOOO!
NOOOOO!
[ GROANS ]
IT WANTS TO BE WITH ME!
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
AAH! AAH! I'M SORRY!
>> Garnet: THAT LITTLE BOY IS IN
BIG TROUBLE.
>> Pearl: GARNET, WAIT!
I'M SURE HE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT HE WAS DOING!
>> Garnet: FAN OUT.
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SIGHS ] WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHAT'S THEIR PROBLEM WITH YOU?
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY SOMETHING?
[ WARBLE! ]
>> AWAY FROM HOME.
>> LET...
>> Steven: ME...
>> Garnet: OUT!
>> Steven: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: COME ON!
I WANT TO HELP YOU!
WHAT CAN I DO?
[ WHOOSHING, WARBLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
AH!
[ GASPS ] WHA...
>> [ SIGHS ]
THANK YOU.
YOU DIDN'T -- OHH.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU ACTUALLY TALKED TO ME.
YOU HELPED ME!
IT'S STEVEN, RIGHT?
>> Steven: [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
MM.
>> I'M LAPIS -- LAPIS LAZULI.
ARE YOU REALLY A CRYSTAL GEM?
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> BUT YOU SET ME FREE.
>> Steven: BUT...WHA...
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHA...
WAIT!
>> [ Sternly ] YOU...
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> YOU THREE KNEW I WAS IN
THERE, AND YOU DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING.
DID YOU EVEN WONDER WHO I USED
TO BE?!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, RUN!
>> Steven: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M LAPIS LAZULI, AND YOU
CAN'T KEEP ME TRAPPED HERE
ANYMORE!
>> Steven: HUH?
>> THEY'RE NOT GONNA LET US
LEAVE.
>> Steven: LEAVE?
>> STEVEN, COME WITH ME.
>> Steven: WHERE?
>> HOME.
>> Steven: B-B-BUT -- B-BUT I,
UH...
>> FINE.
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> DON'T TRUST THEM, STEVEN.
GOODBYE.
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Garnet: [ COUGHING, GAGGING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN! ARE YOU OKAY?!
>> Steven: YEAH. I'M FINE.
SO, THAT WAS ANOTHER GEM?
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ] YES.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, YOU'RE
GROUNDED.
>> Steven: I'M GROUNDED?
>> Pearl: YES, YOU'RE GROUNDED.
>> Garnet: YOU DISOBEYED AN
ORDER.
>> Amethyst: NOW WE'RE GONNA
BURY YOU TILL YOU'VE LEARNED
YOUR LESSON.
>> Steven: AAH!
THAT'S NOT HOW GROUNDING WORKS!
[ DOOR OPENS ]
DAD?
>> [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UH, YOU GUYS BETTER COME CHECK
THIS OUT.
>> W-W-WHA?
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
>> WAIT.
>> WHAT THE...
>> WHERE DID IT GO?
>> WHOA!
>> Steven: THE OCEAN!
>> HUH?
>> HEY, IT'S THOSE MAGICAL
LADIES!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> Garnet: THE OCEAN IS GONE,
OBVIOUSLY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW IT'S JUST A DESERT.
NO ONE WANTS TO TAKE A VACATION
TO...DESERT CITY!
AW, WE'RE GONNA LOSE ALL OUR
SUMMER BUSINESS!
>> AND ALL THE BEACH BABES. AW!
>> WHO'S GONNA BUY MY FRIES?
>> AND MY PIZZA!
>> WHO'S GONNA HAVE FUN AT
FUNLAND?
>> AS MAYOR, I DEMAND YOU
EXPLAIN THIS IMMEDIATELY!
>> Garnet: IT WAS LAPIS LAZULI.
>> Steven: LAPIS LAZULI?
>> Pearl: SHE'S THE GEM YOU
RELEASED FROM THE MIRROR.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
>> THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
>> HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
>> Steven: BUT SHE'S A GEM, JUST
LIKE US.
>> Pearl: THERE'S A LOT YOU
DON'T KNOW ABOUT GEMS, STEVEN.
HOW COULD I HAVE KNOWN THE GEM
CONTAINED IN THAT MIRROR WOULD
BE SO POWERFUL?
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING, STEVEN?
>> Steven: I'M LEAVING TO FIX
WHAT I DID TO OUR HOME.
I WAS THE ONE WHO SET LAPIS FREE
FROM THE MIRROR.
NOW IT'S MY FAULT THE OCEAN'S
GONE.
I'M GONNA BRING THE OCEAN BACK
OR GET REALLY THIRSTY TRYING.
>> WAIT UP, KIDDO.
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
>> I WANT TO HELP, TOO.
ALSO, I FEEL WEIRD BEING IN YOUR
HOUSE IF YOU'RE NOT HERE.
>> [ ROARS ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
>> Pearl: CLEARLY, WE'RE COMING,
TOO.
>> Garnet: YOU'RE UNGROUNDED,
BY THE WAY.
>> Amethyst: WHOO-HOO!
ROAD TRIP!
>> [ SOBBING ]
>> HOW ABOUT SOME TUNES?
THIS WAS ONE OF ROSE'S
FAVORITES.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, GARNET?
[ BOTH SNORING ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: I CAN'T BELIEVE LAPIS
WOULD DO THIS.
GEMS SHOULDN'T FIGHT EACH OTHER.
>> Pearl: WE'RE ALWAYS FIGHTING
GEMS, ACTUALLY.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
WHAT?!
>> Pearl: OH, HOW DO I PUT THIS?
ALL GEMS AREN'T NECESSARILY...
GOOD.
>> Amethyst: ALL THOSE MONSTERS
WE FIGHT USED TO BE JUST LIKE
US!
RIGHT, PEARL?
>> Pearl: YES.
BUT THEY'VE BECOME CORRUPTED AND
BROKEN.
WE HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF THEM,
SUBDUE THEM, CONTAIN THEM.
IT'S THE BEST WE CAN DO FOR THEM
FOR NOW.
IF WE DON'T, THEN...
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> THAT'S SOME MAGICAL DESTINY
STUFF, RIGHT THERE.
>> GUYS, I JUST HAD THE BEST
IDEA FOR AN ALBUM COVER.
>> Garnet: THIS IS IT.
LAPIS LAZULI IS HERE.
>> Pearl: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DOES SHE WANT WITH THE
OCEAN?
>> WHOA. LOOK AT ALL THIS.
IT'S -- IT'S JUST LIKE A GIANT
AQUARIUM.
>> [ Echoing ] YOU SHOULDN'T BE
HERE!
>> Garnet: SHE SENSED US.
>> Steven: LAPIS LAZULI, IT'S
ME, STEVEN!
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
>> GO AWAY BEFORE I MAKE YOU.
>> Steven: BUT WE'RE
BEACH-SUMMER-FUN BUDDIES!
>> N-O-O-O-O-O!
[ BOTH GASP ]
YOU'RE ONE OF THEM -- ONE OF
THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
>> Pearl: [ GROWLS ]
>> Garnet: EASY.
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE'RE ALL GEMS, RIGHT?
JUST LET US HELP YOU.
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> Steven: WE'RE NOT LEAVING,
LAPIS -- NOT UNTIL YOU GIVE US
BACK OUR OCEAN!
AAH!
>> I SAID, "LEAVE ME ALONE!"
>> Pearl: GREG, KIDS, YOU STAY
BEHIND US.
WE'LL HANDLE THIS.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> Amethyst: RUH-OH.
>> Garnet: STAND TOGETHER.
DON'T LET THEM SEPARATE US.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: GARNET!
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
[ JOINTS CRACK ]
>> Amethyst: AW, COME ON!
AAH!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL, AS LONG AS WE'RE PLAYING
FAIR...
[ SCREAMS ]
>> Pearl: [ LAUGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
I HATE FIGHTING ME.
>> [ ROARING ]
>> COME ON, LION!
>> Steven: YOU CAN TAKE ME!
>> OH, NO, NOT THE VAN!
>> Steven: REVENGE!
>> REVENGE!
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
>> KIDS!
>> [ GROANS ]
>> Steven: [ MUFFLED SCREAM ]
[ BOTH COUGHING ]
CONNIE?
>> IS THIS A NORMAL MAGICAL
MISSION FOR YOU?
'CAUSE I'M NOT SO SURE HOW
COMFORTABLE I AM WITH YOU GOING
ON THESE ANYMO-O-O-RE!
>> Steven: DAD!
>> [ COUGHING ]
>> Steven: DAD! DAD!
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> [ Groaning ] OH, I THINK MY
LEG'S BROKEN.
SEE?
THIS IS WHY WE WEAR SEATBELTS,
KIDS.
>> Steven: LAPIS, I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
I SAID, "I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT"!
[ WARBLING ]
>> Amethyst: HMM?
MM.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
>> STEVEN?
>> Steven: LAPIS, I'M COMING UP
TO SEE YOU.
SO PLEASE DON'T DROWN ME.
>> WAIT, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
LAPIS?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
STEVEN?
>> Steven: WHAT? I --
NO! WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THIS THING, THE OCEAN,
THIS IS CRAZY.
CAN'T WE WORK THIS OUT?
WE GEMS SHOULD BE FRIENDS.
WHOA!
>> DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING,
STEVEN?
YOUR FRIENDS, THEY DON'T REALLY
CARE ABOUT OTHER GEMS.
ALL THEY CARE ABOUT IS THE
EARTH.
BUT I NEVER BELIEVED IN THIS
PLACE.
>> Steven: WHAT?
>> I JUST WANT TO GO HOME.
>> Steven: I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
HOME CAN BE.
BUT THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
YOU TOOK THE OCEAN AWAY, AND THE
OCEAN IS AN IMPORTANT PART OF MY
HOME.
>> I'M ONLY USING THE OCEAN
BECAUSE MY GEM IS CRACKED.
IF I JUST STRETCH IT FAR
ENOUGH...
[ SCOFFS ]
THIS IS NEVER GOING TO WORK.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
I CAN FIX YOUR GEM!
I HAVE HEALING POWERS!
>> WAIT, YOU HAVE HEALING
POWERS?
>> Steven: I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> OH, WHAT SHOULD I...
>> Steven: OH, UH, SORRY.
THIS MIGHT BE A LITTLE WEIRD.
>> WHAT?
>> Steven: [ SLURPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> [ SHUDDERS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> THANK YOU, STEVEN.
>> Steven: NO PROB, BOB.
>> IT'S LAPIS.
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> OKAY. BYE.
>> Steven: OH!
[ GASPING ]
>> Garnet: THE WHOLE TOWER'S
COMING DOWN.
>> WHAT ABOUT STEVEN?
>> Steven: AAH!
WHOA-AAH!
>> GRAB MY HAND!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
>> GOTCHA.
>> STEVEN!
>> [ CRYING ]
HUH?
>> YES! BABE CITY, HERE WE COME!
WHOA!
>> Amethyst: THAT'S HOW YOU DO
IT.
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Pearl: WELL, WHAT'S THAT
THING YOU ALWAYS SAY ABOUT THE
PORK CHOPS AND THE HOT DOGS?
>> LOOK!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Amethyst: MM.
>> [ BLOWS NOSE ]
>> Garnet: SO, LAPIS MADE IT OFF
PLANET.
>> Pearl: WHAT DOES THIS MEAN
FOR US?
>> Garnet: WE WAIT AND SEE.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> Steven: SEE YOU, LAPIS.
WHEREVER YOU ARE.