>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> ♪ I BAIT MY HOOK WITH
SELF-PITY ♪
♪ SOMEONE TELL ME THAT I'M
PRETTY ♪
♪ FISHING FOR COMPLIMENTS ♪
>> Steven: [ GIGGLING ]
CANNONBALL!
AMETHYST, DID YOU SEE?
I THINK THAT WAS MY BEST ONE!
>> Amethyst: EH.
YOU NEED TO PUT MORE "BALL" IN
YOUR CANNON.
>> Steven: IS THAT GONNA HURT?
>> Amethyst: NOT IF YOU DO IT
LIKE...THIS!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
THAT WAS AWESOME!
I WANT TO JUMP IN SOME MORE
PUDDLES.
>> Amethyst: OKAY.
YOU CAN TRY THIS ONE...
OR THAT ONE.
>> Steven: WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
>> Amethyst: WHOA, STEVEN! WAIT!
>> Steven: UNH!
>> Amethyst: ONLY GARNET IS
ALLOWED IN THERE.
LET'S DO SOMETHING LESS
DANGEROUS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUMP OFF THAT?
>> Steven: WHOA.
HOW DO YOU EVEN STACK YOUR STUFF
THAT HIGH?
>> Amethyst: IT'S A TALENT.
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Amethyst: DO IT!
>> Steven: AMETHYST, I HOPE
YOU'RE READY, 'CAUSE HERE I...
G-O-O-O-- UNH!
AAAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
AM I IN PEARL'S ROOM?
>> Amethyst: HA! THAT WAS CRAZY!
HUH?
WHAT IS SHE DOING WITH A
ROSE QUARTZ BUBBLE?
>> Steven: MY MOM BUBBLED THAT?
>> Amethyst: GARNET'S GONNA BE
SO MA--
[ MUFFLED ]
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> Pearl: AH.
HMM. HMM?
MM-HMM.
MM...
>> Amethyst: BUSTED!
>> Pearl: WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN
HERE?!
>> Amethyst: WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN HERE?!
>> Pearl: I...JUST WANTED TO SEE
HOW THE SHARDS ARE REACTING TO
ROSE'S BUBBLE.
AND IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
>> Amethyst: I THINK IT'S
GARNET'S BUSINESS.
>> Steven: OHHHH!
>> Pearl: DON'T TELL HER.
>> Amethyst: HOW ARE YOU GONNA
STOP ME?
UGH!
>> Pearl: AAH! AMETHYST!
>> Steven: GUYS, STOP FIGHTING!
>> Pearl: HEATHEN!
>> Amethyst: [ HISSES ]
>> Steven: HERE.
LET'S JUST PUT IT BACK...
>> Pearl: STEVEN, BE CAREFUL
WITH THAT!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, GIVE IT TO
ME!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: UH...
AAH! AAH! AAAAH!
WE GOT TO GET GARNET.
>> Amethyst: NO!
NO WAY!
WE JUST FREED A BUNCH OF
MINDLESS GEM CHUNKS, OKAY?!
THEY'RE GONNA CRAWL WHO KNOWS
WHERE, ALL OVER THE TEMPLE!
WHEN GARNET FINDS OUT, WE'RE
DEAD!
>> Pearl: SHE'S NOT GOING TO
FIND OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO CATCH THEM -- ALL
OF THEM.
>> Amethyst: YOU'RE RIGHT.
EVERY SINGLE ONE -- BACK IN A
BUBBLE AND BACK IN THE BASEMENT!
>> Pearl: LIKE NOTHING EVER
HAPPENED.
>> Steven: AND THEN WE TELL
GARNET?
>> Both: NO!
>> Pearl: THIS HAS TO STAY A
SECRET.
OKAY?
>> Steven: OUR SECRET...
TOGETHER?
[ GASPS ]
IF WE'VE GOT A SECRET, WE HAVE
TO DO THIS RIGHT, WHICH MEANS WE
GOT TO COME UP WITH A NAME FOR
OUR SECRET-KEEPING TEAM --
SOMETHING COOL, LIKE...
THE SECRET TEAM!
>> Pearl: UH...
>> Steven: AND A SECRET TEAM
NEEDS MEMBERSHIP CARDS THAT WE
CAN SHOW OFF TO OTHER PEOPLE!
HERE.
>> Pearl: FISH-STEW PIZZA?
>> Amethyst: EH, WHAT'S A
"V.I.PIZZA"?
>> Steven: WELL, IF YOU COLLECT
ENOUGH OF THEM, YOU CAN GET A
FREE PIZZA.
BUT NOW THEY'RE THE OFFICIAL
CARD OF...THE SECRET TEAM!
>> Pearl: GREAT, STEVEN.
COME ON.
WE'RE DOING THIS.
>> Amethyst: HM!
>> Steven: SECRET TEAM, MOVE
OUT!
UNH! AAH!
AAAAAAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Amethyst: [ GIGGLES ]
>> Pearl: OKAY.
>> Amethyst: THAT LOOKS LIKE
ALL OF THEM.
>> Steven: YEAH! SECRET TEAM!
>> Pearl: HMM. ARE YOU SURE WE
DIDN'T MISS ANY?
>> Amethyst: NO WAY!
WE TOTALLY NAILED THIS.
>> Steven: YEAH!
>> Pearl: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
IF YOU'RE SURE THIS IS ALL OF
THEM, THEN WE JUST NEED TO SEAL
IT IN A ROSE-QUARTZ BUBBLE.
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, THIS IS
ALL YOU!
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
>> Steven: YEAH. I CAN DO IT.
>> Pearl: OF COURSE YOU CAN!
YOU'RE PART OF THE SECRET CLUB.
>> Steven: SECRET "TEAM."
>> Pearl: AH, YES.
SECRET TEAM.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, THAT THING.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ] G-GARNET!
>> Amethyst: DID SHE SEE YOU?
>> Steven: I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Pearl: THEN WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
CONGRATULATIONS, US.
>> Amethyst: AWW, YES.
WE'RE OFF THE HOOK.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT!
SO, WHAT'S NEXT?
>> Amethyst: NOTHING'S "NEXT."
THE MISSION IS OVER.
>> Pearl: NOW EVERYTHING GOES
BACK TO NORMAL, AND WE NEVER
SPEAK OF THIS AGAIN.
>> Steven: BUT WHAT ABOUT...
SECRET TEAM?
>> HEY, STEVEN!
WHAT'LL IT BE?
>> Steven: GIVE ME...
THE BITS.
WE WERE THE BEST, FRYMAN.
>> WHO WAS THE BEST?
>> Steven: I CAN'T TELL YOU!
[ SIGHS ]
HOW COME THE BEST THING'S IN
LIFE ARE THINGS YOU CAN'T TELL
OTHER PEOPLE BECAUSE YOU'D GET
IN BIG TROUBLE?
>> STEVEN, ARE YOU IN A GANG?
>> Steven: NOT THESE DAYS.
BUT MAYBE I CAN BE AGAIN.
>> THAT KID KEEPS GETTING
WEIRDER.
>> I LIKE YOUR HAT!
>> Steven: I KNOW YOU MUST BE
WONDERING WHY I BROUGHT YOU ALL
HERE.
IT'S 'CAUSE I'M GETTIN' THE TEAM
BACK TOGETHER!
SO, HERE'S THE GIG.
I LEFT MY SPECIAL HAT AT THE
BIG DONUT.
>> Pearl: I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
WEAR THIS.
>> Steven: BUT NOW IT'S CLOSED
FOR THE DAY.
SO THE MISSION IS, WE BREAK IN
AND GET IT BACK.
AND BAM!
THE SECRET TEAM IS BACK ON TOP!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN,
SECRET TEAM IS OVER.
>> Pearl: SECRET TEAM?
WH-WHAT'S THAT?!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
>> Steven: AW, COME ON!
WE HAD SO MUCH FUN TOGETHER!
GETTING ALONG, SNEAKING
AROUND --
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THAT WAS NOT
ABOUT FUN.
THAT WAS ABOUT FIXING OUR
TERRIBLE MISTAKE.
>> Amethyst: UH, YOUR TERRIBLE
MISTAKE.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD THAT
BUBBLE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> Pearl: IT NEVER WOULD'VE
POPPED IF YOU HADN'T INVADED MY
PERSONAL SPACE!
>> Steven: AW, COME ON.
TEAM, TEAM!
>> Amethyst: FINE.
YOU CAN HAVE ALL THE PERSONAL
SPACE YOU WANT, 'CAUSE I NEVER
WANT TO BE ON A TEAM WITH YOU
AGAIN!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: GOOD!
I DON'T WANT TO BE ON A TEAM
WITH YOU, EITHER!
>> Amethyst: FINE!
>> Pearl: FINE!
>> Steven: GUYS! COME ON!
[ DOOR OPENS, BELL JINGLES ]
>> Garnet: I'M HERE.
>> Steven: I HAVE SOMETHING I
WANT TO TELL YOU.
>> Garnet: PIZZA.
>> Steven: NO!
I...NEED TO COME CLEAN.
PEARL AND AMETHYST POPPED A
BUBBLE.
WE MADE A SECRET TEAM TO COVER
IT UP 'CAUSE THEY DIDN'T WANT
YOU TO KNOW.
>> Garnet: AND NOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
>> Steven: NOT REALLY.
I JUST WANT SECRET TEAM AGAIN.
>> Garnet: I SEE.
I KNOW HOW TO HANDLE THINGS WITH
THEM.
WE'LL HAVE TO FORM OUR OWN
SECRET TEAM TO DO IT.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YOU MEAN LIKE...
A SUPER SECRET TEAM?
>> Garnet: PIZZA DAUGHTER.
I'LL TAKE ONE "PIZZA POSSE"
CARD.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
GARNET!
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THE DEAL?
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHAT'S THIS ALL
ABOUT, GARNET?
>> Garnet: I KNOW ALL ABOUT THE
GEM SHARDS!
>> Pearl: UH...
>> Steven: IT -- IT WAS ME!
I'M THE ONE WHO POPPED THE
BUBBLE!
ALL BY MYSELF.
>> Pearl: STEVEN...
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU!
>> Garnet: [ SIGHS ]
IF NO ONE HAS ANYTHING ELSE TO
SAY, AND EVERYONE ELSE IS
INNOCENT, STEVEN, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO PUNISH YOU.
>> Steven: NO!
NOT PUNISHMENT!
[ SIGHS DRAMATICALLY ]
>> Garnet: COME WITH ME, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
GARNET!
>> Steven: OH, NO!
WE MUST HAVE MISSED A SHARD!
>> Amethyst: UNH!
UNH!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: WAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
HUH?
>> Pearl: AAH!
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: UNH!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, SHAPE-SHIFT!
GET SMALL OR...SOMETHING!
>> Amethyst: I CAN'T!
I'M FREAKING OUT!
YOU DO IT!
>> Pearl: I CAN'T CONCENTRA--
AAH! UNH!
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT!
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE HAD THAT
BUBBLE!
>> Amethyst: IT WOULDN'T HAVE
POPPED IF IT WASN'T FOR ME!
>> Steven: WE SHOULD'VE TOLD
GARNET!
WE SHOULD'VE TOLD HER RIGHT
AWAY!
I KNEW SECRET TEAM WAS WRONG!
I JUST --
I WANTED TO SEE YOU GUYS ACTING
LIKE FRIENDS!
[ GASPS ]
GARNET?
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> Amethyst: HUH?
>> Garnet: SO, YOU TWO CAN'T GET
ALONG UNLESS YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO KILL YOU.
STEVEN, I KNOW YOU WANTED TO
HELP THEM.
YOU WANTED TO PROTECT THEM, EVEN
FROM ME.
THEY MADE YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAD
TO TAKE THEIR SIDE.
BUT THERE ARE NO SIDES, BECAUSE
WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME TEAM --
THE CRYSTAL GEMS!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BETWEEN THE FOUR OF US...
WE COULD'VE HAD A FREE PIZZA.
>> Pearl: ARE YOU SURE IT'S
HERE?
>> Garnet: IT WAS.
>> Pearl: DO YOU THINK IT SWAM
AWAY?
>> Garnet: WE'LL HAVE TO LOOK.
>> Steven: WHOA.
>> Amethyst: COME ON!
IT'S TIME TO GO.
>> Steven: AWW. ALREADY?
WAIT, WAIT.
CAN I WARP US BACK?
>> Pearl: ALL RIGHT.
>> Steven: YES!
HMMMMM...
...MMMM!
[ GASPS ] I DID IT!
I'M THE WARP MASTER!
>> Pearl: YOU DID GREAT.
>> Garnet: GOOD JOB.
>> Amethyst: ST-E-E-E-EVEN!
>> Steven: WAAAAAAH!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, THAT'S NOT
FUNNY!
>> Garnet: IT WAS A LITTLE
FUNNY.
>> Pearl: REGARDLESS, WE NEED
TO WARP BACK OUT.
>> Steven: CAN I WARP US THERE?
>> Garnet: WE'RE GOING
UNDERWATER.
>> Pearl: AND YOU DO NEED AIR TO
BREATHE.
>> Steven: THEN CAN I TELL ALL
MY FRIENDS I'M THE WARP MASTER?
>> Pearl: I GUESS, BUT --
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ PANTING ]
I'M THE WARP MASTER!
>> THAT'S NICE, STEVEN.
>> [ GRUMBLES ]
STEVEN...
>> YOU WANT A DOUGHNUT?
>> Steven: CHOCOLATE JELLY,
PLEASE.
>> YEE-OH!
WAAH!
>> WHA-- HUH?
SADIE?!
I, LIKE, JUST GOT TO SLEEP!
NOW I HAVE TO START ALL OVER!
>> THEN DON'T SLEEP AT THE
COUNTER!
I'M TRYING TO WORK!
>> WHY DON'T YOU NOT WORK AT THE
COUNTER WHEN I'M TRYING TO
SLEEP?!
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS DOING THIS!
>> Steven: SOMETHING'S HAVING A
BAD EFFECT ON THEIR RELATIONSHIP
AND THEIR CUSTOMER SERVICE.
>> AND YOU COULD GET FIRED!
>> WHO CARES?
I'M SICK OF THIS PLACE!
I WANT TO GO SOMEWHERE NEW.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
THAT'S IT!
I'M THE WARP MASTER!
>> YEAH, STEVEN, I KNOW.
>> Steven: I CAN TAKE US ON
VACATION -- SOMEWHERE WARM AND
BEAUTIFUL AND MAGICAL FOR JUST
THE TWO OF YOU.
AND ME!
>> IT COULD BE WORTH A TRY.
>> Steven: WE'RE HERE!
COME ON. THIS WAY!
>> THIS IS WAY TOO WEIRD.
I'M GOING HOME.
>> Steven: NO, NO! FOLLOW ME!
YOU GOT TO SEE IT.
>> COME ON, LARS.
GIVE IT A CHANCE.
>> UGH! FINE.
BUT IF IT BLOWS, I'M OUT OF
HERE.
>> Steven: WELCOME TO PARADISE!
>> OH, STEVEN, IT'S BEAUTIFUL
HERE.
>> IT'S A BEACH.
WE LIVE ON A BEACH!
>> Steven: IT'S A MAGICAL BEACH!
>> IS THAT WHY MY PHONE HAS NO
RECEPTION?
WHY WERE YOU EVEN HERE?
>> Steven: WE CAME HERE TO LOOK
FOR A DANGEROUS GEM CREATURE
THAT WE NEVER FOUND.
>> YEP. I'M GONE.
>> HUH? LARS!
WAIT! LARS, THIS COULD ACTUALLY
BE KIND OF FUN!
>> IF I'M GOING TO BE BORED OUT
OF MY MIND AND POSSIBLY DIE, I'M
GONNA GO TO WORK AND GET PAID
FOR IT.
OKAY. WHERE IS IT?
>> Steven: WHAT?
>> THE TELEPORTER THING!
WHERE IS IT?!
>> OH, IT -- IT WOULDN'T
DISAPPEAR, WOULD IT?
>> Steven: NO, NO, NO.
WELL, MAYBE.
>> WHAT?!
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY!
THE GEMS'LL COME SAVE US WHEN
THEY SEE I'M MISSING...
EVENTUALLY.
>> STEVEN, HOW COULD YOU DO
THIS?!
WE'RE STRANDED!
>> CALM DOWN!
IS THIS THE WORST PLACE TO BE
STUCK IN?
>> UGH! YOU CALM DOWN.
I'M GONNA FIND BETTER RECEPTION.
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S AMAZING,
STEVEN.
>> [ GRUMBLES ] NOTHING!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] GUYS, CHECK
IT OUT!
I FOUND THESE ROCKS THAT LOOK
LIKE PILLOWS!
>> HEH. GOOD JOB, STEVEN.
>> MY ROCK'S TOO CLOSE TO THOSE
OTHER ROCKS.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANS ]
>> Steven: SADIE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING WRONG.
>> TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> Steven: YOU WERE GONNA LOVE
IT HERE SO MUCH.
YOU'D NEVER WANT TO LEAVE.
>> DON'T WORRY.
LARS IS JUST A TOUGH NUT.
HE CAN'T KEEP UP THIS SCHTICK
FOREVER.
>> I COULD DO WITHOUT THE AUDIO
COMMENTARY!
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
GOOD NIGHT, SADIE.
>> NIGHT, STEVEN.
AAH!
UH! HUH! WAAH!
>> Steven: ANY LATE LUNCH, EARLY
DINNER YET?
>> UH, NO LUCK.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> Steven: MMM...
NO.
BUT I CAN SEE WHY.
MY BAIT IS TOO ADORABLE TO EAT!
EVERYTHING ON THIS ISLAND HAS
SUCH A BRIGHT, HAPPY SMILE.
>> UGH!
NO SIGNAL OVER HERE, EITHER.
>> HEY! UH, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HELP OUT IF YOU WANT TO EAT!
GRR!
[ SQUISHING ]
>> Steven: SADIE!
WE'RE GONNA LIVE!
>> I CATCH, YOU COOK!
>> YOU AIN'T THE BOSS OF ME.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> WHATEVER.
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOKS DONE TO ME.
OOH!
WHO'S FIRST?
>> Steven: ME, ME, ME!
IT KEEPS LOOKING AT ME.
>> MAYBE IT KNOWS IT'S YOUR
FAULT FOR GETTING US LOST.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
>> MMM.
MMM, LARS, THIS IS REALLY GOOD!
>> HMM?
>> YOU CAN REALLY COOK!
>> HEH!
FIRE -- NATURE'S MICROWAVE.
>> [ GIGGLES ]
[ BOTH CHUCKLING ]
>> Steven: COULD THIS NIGHT GET
ANY BETTER?!
[ GUITAR STRUMS ]
♪ ISN'T THIS SUCH ♪
♪ A BEAUTIFUL NIGHT? ♪
♪ WHOA-OH ♪
♪ WE'RE UNDERNEATH A THOUSAND
SHINING STARS ♪
♪ ISN'T IT NICE TO FIND YOURSELF
SOMEWHERE DIFFERENT? ♪
♪ WHOA-OH ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET YOURSELF
JUST BE WHEREVER YOU ARE? ♪
♪ LOOK AT THIS PLACE ♪
♪ LOOK AT YOUR FACES ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU LOOK LIKE
THIS BEFORE ♪
♪ ISN'T IT NICE TO FIND YOURSELF
SOMEWHERE DIFFERENT? ♪
♪ WHOA-OH ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET YOURSELF
JUST BE WHEREVER YOU ARE? ♪
♪ LOOK AT THIS PLACE ♪
♪ LOOK AT YOUR FACES ♪
♪ THEY'RE SHINING LIKE A
THOUSAND SHINING STARS ♪
♪ ISN'T IT NICE TO FIND YOURSELF
SOMEWHERE DIFFERENT? ♪
♪ WHOA-OH ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET YOURSELF
JUST BE WHEREVER YOU ARE? ♪
JUST BE SOMEWHERE DIFFERENT? ♪
♪ WHOA-OH ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET YOURSELF
JUST BE WHOEVER YOU ARE? ♪
>> DID YOU SEE WHERE LARS WENT?
>> Steven: MM-MNH-MNH.
>> HELLO?
COME ON! COME ON!
DUMB PIECE OF JUNK.
NO BARS...
NO BARS!
YAAH!
>> DID THAT HELP?
>> NO!
IT'S JUST...
WHAT IF I NEVER GET BACK HOME?
>> OH!
YOU'RE JUST REALLY HOMESICK.
>> DUH! WHAT'D YOU THINK?!
>> NO, IT'S OKAY.
>> [ CRYING ]
>> WE'RE OKAY!
STEVEN SAID THE GEMS COULD BE
COMING FOR US ANY DAY.
AND, YOU KNOW, UNTIL THEN, I GOT
YOUR BACK.
>> SADIE...
DO YOU EVER GET LONELY...
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE AROUND PEOPLE?
>> Steven: ♪ WHY DON'T YOU LET
YOURSELF JUST BE-- ♪
>> Both: STEVEN!
>> HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
WATCHING US?!
>> DON'T YOU KNOW WHAT PRIVACY
IS?!
>> Steven: PEOPLE WALK IN AND
OUT OF MY ROOM ALL THE TIME.
>> UGH!
I'M GONNA GO START ON THE FIRE.
>> HEY! YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO!
WE'RE KIND OF ON OUR OWN
SCHEDULE HERE!
[ RUMBLING, GRUNTING ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
>> WHAT THE HECK?!
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: IT'S A...GEM?
[ CREATURE GROWLING, ROARS ]
AAH!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
UGH!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE!
>> STEVEN!
WHAT WAS THAT THING?!
>> Steven: IT MUST BE WHAT THE
GEMS WERE LOOKING FOR!
IT NEVER LEFT THE ISLAND AT ALL!
IT'S INVISIBLE.
>> A BIG INVISIBLE THING IS
AFTER US?!
I -- I -- I WANT TO GO HOME!
I WANNA GO HOME!
[ CRYING ]
>> Steven: AAH!
>> THIS WAY!
>> OKAY!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> Steven: IT'S THE WARP PAD!
>> LARS, COME ON! LET'S GO HOME!
>> YOU KNEW!
>> Steven: UH, GUYS?
>> IT'S HER FAULT WE'VE BEEN
TRAPPED HERE!
>> Steven: WHA-A-A-A-A-A-A-AT?!
>> LOOK, I PANICKED!
I HID THE WARP PAD!
YOU WERE JUST GONNA LEAVE, BUT I
KNEW HOW MUCH YOU REALLY NEEDED
THIS!
WHY DON'T YOU EVER LET ME HELP
YOU?!
>> HELP ME?
ARE YOU INSANE?!
YOU TRAPPED ME ON AN ISLAND SO
YOU COULD COME ON TO ME!
>> AAAAH!
>> OW!
>> YOU KISSED ME ON THE MOUTH!
>> NO, I DIDN'T!
>> Steven: GUYS, I WANT TO BE
MAD, TOO, BUT CAN WE DO IT ON
THE WARP PAD?!
>> WAAAAAH!
>> LARS!
OH, GOSH.
>> [ GROANING ]
[ THUDS ]
AAH!
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> [ GRUNTS ]
RAAH!
[ CREATURE ROARS ]
YAH!
UNH!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
SADIE!
USE YOUR FISH-MURDERING SKILLS!
>> [ GRUNTING ]
[ GROWLS ]
>> UNH! OHH!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> Steven: GO, SADIE!
>> [ SHOUTING ]
[ MOANING ]
>> Steven: OH. OH, I GOT THIS!
THE GEMS ARE GONNA BE SO
IMPRESSED.
WE CAPTURED A GEM ALL BY
OURSELVES!
SADIE, YOU WERE AMAZING!
>> YEAH, THAT WAS REALLY GREAT
HOW YOU, UH...S-SAVED ME.
>> DON'T READ INTO IT.
>> Steven: WE SHOULD DO THIS
AGAIN SOMETIME.