>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: THIS PLACE IS EVEN
BIGGER AND MORE WEAPONY THAN I
REMEMBER.
>> Pearl: THIS WAS THE SITE OF A
HISTORIC BATTLE.
EVERY WEAPON HERE WAS LEFT BY A
GEM OVER 5,000 YEARS AGO.
I DON'T LIKE TO DISTURB IT, BUT
GARNET SAID WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
THESE LYING AROUND.
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU
MIGHT NEED ONE OF THESE.
>> Steven: I NEED ONE OF THOSE
ALL THE TIME!
>> Pearl: WHY DON'T YOU LOOK FOR
ONE THAT'S MORE...YOU?
>> Steven: OKAY!
LION, COME HELP ME LOOK!
AWW, COME ON!
>> Pearl: YOU REALLY NEED TO
TRAIN THAT THING BETTER.
>> Steven: OH, WE'VE BEEN MAKING
PROGRESS.
NOW HE LOOKS AT ME WHEN I SAY
HIS NAME!
LION!
LION! HEY, LION!
UH, SOMETIMES.
>> Pearl: WHAT'S HE GOT NOW?
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S THE SCABBARD FOR ROSE'S
SWORD!
GRR! GIMME!
GIMME!
SHOO. SHOO.
>> [ SNORTS ]
>> Steven: MOM FOUGHT HERE?
>> Pearl: THAT'S RIGHT, AND I
FOUGHT ALONGSIDE HER.
>> Amethyst: MAN, I WISH I
COULD HAVE SEEN IT.
>> Garnet: NO, YOU DON'T.
COUNTLESS GEMS WERE BROKEN HERE.
IT WAS A MAELSTROM OF
DESTRUCTION AND DEATH.
>> Pearl: BUT WE WON!
YOUR MOTHER LED US TO GLORIOUS
VICTORY.
THE ODDS WERE AGAINST US, AND
OUR HEARTS WERE UNCERTAIN, BUT
WE CHOSE TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE
ROSE, AND HERE WE MADE OUR STAND
AGAINST OUR HOMEWORLD!
[ WARBLE! ]
>> Amethyst: THIS IS GREAT!
MY ROOM'S BEEN NEEDING ANOTHER
PILE!
>> Garnet: AMETHYST, HELP ME
WITH THIS AX.
>> Pearl: OH, IT'S BEEN AGES.
>> Amethyst: TURN IT CLOCKWISE!
NO, YOUR OTHER CLOCKWISE!
>> Pearl: WH-WHAT IS IT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: WHAT WAS MOM LIKE?
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: SHE WAS COURAGEOUS AND
BRILLIANT AND...
BEAUTIFUL.
SOMETIMES YOU LOOK SO MUCH LIKE
HER.
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> Garnet: YOU MEAN "PULL."
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YEAH, PULL.
SURE. YAH!
>> Pearl: HEY, STEVEN...
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HOLD ON TO
THIS.
>> Steven: WHOA! THANKS, PEARL!
IF ANYTHING TRIES TO EAT ME,
I'LL BOP 'EM WITH THIS!
>> Pearl: THAT'S JUST THE
SCABBARD, STEVEN.
IT HELD YOUR MOTHER'S SWORD.
NOTHING ELSE COULD FIT SO
PERFECTLY INSIDE.
FOR ALL THIS TIME, IT'S BEEN
INCOMPLETE.
>> Steven: WELL, LET'S
COMPLETE IT.
WHERE'S THE SWORD?
>> Amethyst: THAT'S IT!
YEAH-AH! HA! YOU GOT IT!
[ BLAM! ]
>> Pearl: CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET?
>> Steven: A SECRET?!
>> Pearl: SHH!
IT'S A SECRET, EVEN TO GARNET
AND AMETHYST.
ROSE HAD A PLACE THAT SHE KEPT
HIDDEN FROM ALL BUT ME.
[ GASPS ]
BUT YOU HAVE HER GEM.
THAT PLACE IS YOURS NOW, AND I
CAN SHOW IT TO YOU.
>> Steven: UH, OKAY.
>> Pearl: NOW, IT'S JUST A
3-HOUR HIKE THAT WAY, FOLLOWED
BY A VERTICAL CLIMB AT
90 DEGREES.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
>> Pearl: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I WAS YOUR MOTHER'S SOLE
CONFIDANT.
FOR THE WORDS SHE COULD SHARE
WITH NO ONE ELSE, I WAS THERE TO
LISTEN.
>> Steven: WHY'D SHE KEEP SO
MANY SECRETS?
>> Pearl: SHE HAD TO, STEVEN!
IT'S THE MARK OF A GREAT
LEADER -- KNOWING JUST WHAT TO
KEEP HIDDEN FROM EVERYONE YOU'RE
TRYING TO PROTECT --
EVERYONE EXCEPT ME.
HA HA!
WELCOME TO ROSE'S SECRET ARMORY.
>> Steven: WHOA!
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE!
>> Pearl: WHAT?
UH, YOU MUST BE THINKING OF
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
I'M THE ONLY OTHER CRYSTAL GEM
WHO'S EVER WITNESSED THE
ARMORY'S MAGNIFICENCE BEFORE
NOW.
>> Steven: NUH-UNH!
LION SHOWED ME.
>> Pearl: THE LION?!
>> Steven: YEAH!
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF GREAT STUFF
HIDDEN IN HERE.
>> Pearl: I KNOW!
THAT'S WHY I BROUGHT YOU HERE!
NOW LET ME SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN
ACCESS THE ARTILLERY.
>> Steven: THAT'S OKAY.
I CAN DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
WHAM!
OH, RIGHT.
UGH!
WE GOT SOME...AXES!
>> Pearl: THE AXES OF AGES?
>> Steven: OOH!
WE GOT SPIKY CHAIN LADY AND HER
METAL DEALIES.
>> Pearl: THE HERETIC'S ANGUISH!
>> Steven: WE GOT A --
OOH-OOH! -- 3-PACK OF LASER
LIGHT CANNONS!
>> Pearl: THE QUARTIZINE TRIO!
>> Steven: BOOP!
AND...A WHOLE LOT OF THESE ARMOR
GUYS!
>> Pearl: THE ARMOR OF THE
FALLEN!
>> Steven: WHAT WERE WE LOOKING
FOR?
>> Pearl: HER SWORD!
YOUR MOTHER'S SWORD!
IT'S A STRAIGHT-BLADED SABER
THAT'S PINK WITH A RED HANDLE.
THERE ARE VINES ETCHED IN THE
GUARD THAT CONNECT TO A
ROSE-SHAPED POMMEL.
>> Steven: OHH!
I KNOW WHERE THAT IS!
>> Pearl: HUH?
>> Steven: ♪ DA-DA DA-DA DA-DA
DA-DA DA-DA DA-DA DA-DA
DA-DA DA ♪
♪ HERE IT IS! ♪
>> Pearl: ROSE'S SWORD --
HOW DID IT GET IN THERE?
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW, BUT
THERE'S A TON OF STUFF IN THERE.
I KEEP STUFF IN HIM, TOO.
HUH!
HUP!
[ LAUGHING ]
TA-DA!
>> Pearl: BUT...HOW?
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
DOES LION HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH ROSE?
>> Amethyst: OHH! OF COURSE!
THAT'S WHY HE'S PINK!
>> Garnet: IT'S A LITTLE
OBVIOUS.
>> Pearl: BUT ROSE DIDN'T HAVE A
LION.
>> Steven: IT SEEMS LIKE HER
STUFF IN THERE.
>> Pearl: NO! ROSE DIDN'T HAVE A
LION, BECAUSE IF ROSE HAD A
LION, I WOULD HAVE KNOWN
ABOUT IT!
>> Garnet: ROSE KEPT MANY THINGS
SECRET, EVEN FROM US.
>> Pearl: BUT NOT FROM ME!
I WAS THE ONE SHE TOLD
EVERYTHING!
>> Amethyst: YO, YOU'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONE WHO MISSES HER!
>> Pearl: YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL!
NONE OF YOU HAD WHAT WE HAD!
>> Steven: SHE PROBABLY JUST
WANTED TO PROTECT YOU, LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE.
>> Pearl: WHAT DO YOU KNOW?!
YOU'VE NEVER EVEN MET HER!
[ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: HUP!
>> Pearl: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Amethyst: FINE! GO!
GO CRY ABOUT IT!
>> Steven: WHERE'D SHE GO?
>> Amethyst: WHO CARES?
I HATE IT WHEN SHE GETS LIKE
THIS!
>> Steven: GARNET?
IS SHE OKAY?
WELL, I'M GONNA GO FIND HER.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE SHE WENT?
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Steven: I'M GOING TO ASSUME
THAT MEANS YOU DO.
UGH! LET'S GO FIND PEARL!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Garnet: GOOD LUCK.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> Steven: PEARL?!
>> Pearl: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Steven: HUH? HMM!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: PEARL! WAIT FOR ME!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UGH! UGH!
GET THAT THING AWAY FROM ME!
>> Steven: YOU BETTER SIT THIS
ONE OUT, LION.
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HUH-UGH!
[ GRUNTING ]
OKAY!
I HAD A TALK WITH LION!
HE'S GONNA -- UGH! --
CHILL OUT HERE!
UGH! WE'RE ALONE NOW --
NICE AND PRIVATE!
HUH-UGH! HUH-UGH! HUH-UGH!
UH, GOOD IDEA!
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE TOP!
HUH-UGH! HUH-UGH!
HUH! UGH! HUH-HUH-UGH!
TH-THIS IS REALLY HARD TO DO IN
SANDALS!
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Pearl: GO AWAY!
>> Steven: PEARL!
DID I -- DID I DO SOMETHING
WRONG?!
YOU GOT TO TELL ME!
HUH-UGH!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: AAAAAAAAAAH!
UGH! UGH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTING ]
UGH-HUH!
PEARL!
PEARL, YOU HAVE TO TELL ME
WHAT'S WRONG.
>> Pearl: SOMETIMES...
YOU EVEN SOUND LIKE HER.
DO YOU REMEMBER THIS PLACE?
DO YOU HAVE ANY OF HER MEMORIES?
WE WERE RIGHT HERE, OVER 5,000
YEARS AGO.
[ TING! ]
>> PEARL...
>> Pearl: YES?
>> ...I'M GOING TO STAY AND
FIGHT FOR THIS PLANET.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS WITH
ME.
>> Pearl: BUT I WANT TO!
>> I KNOW YOU DO.
PLEASE, PLEASE UNDERSTAND --
IF WE LOSE, WE'LL BE KILLED, AND
IF WE WIN, WE CAN NEVER GO HOME.
>> Pearl: WHY WOULD I EVER WANT
TO GO HOME IF YOU'RE HERE?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
MY PEARL.
>> Pearl: YOU'RE WONDERFUL.
[ TING! ]
EVERYTHING I EVER DID,
I DID FOR HER.
NOW SHE'S GONE...
BUT I'M STILL HERE.
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF SHE CAN
SEE ME THROUGH YOUR EYES.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT WOULD SHE THINK OF ME NOW?
>> Steven: WELL, I THINK YOU'RE
PRETTY GREAT.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ GUITAR PLAYING ]
>> Steven: WHOO!
THAT SOUNDED GREAT!
>> AW, THANKS.
I'M THINKING ABOUT CALLING IT
"WATER WITCH."
>> Steven: COOL!
>> AND CHECK THIS OUT.
I CAN ADD SOME VOCAL DISTORTION,
TOO.
[ Distorted ] STEVEN, YOUR DAD'S
A ROBOT NOW.
AND NOW THAT I'M A ROBOT, THINGS
WILL BE BETTER AND COLDER.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME FOR BEING AN
AMAZING MACHINE.
>> Steven: I CAN'T STAY MAD AT
MY ROBO DAD!
WHERE'S ALL THIS AWESOME ENERGY
COMING FROM?
>> ACTUALLY, I WAS INSPIRED TO
MAKE SOME NEW SONGS AFTER THE
OCEAN GOT SUCKED UP INTO SPACE A
WHILE BACK.
I EVEN DREW UP SOME FREAKY ALBUM
ARTWORK.
>> Steven: IT LOOKS LIKE...
LAPIS LAZULI.
>> EASY WITH THE TENDER TOUCHES.
DON'T WANT IT TO GET ALL
SMUDGED.
HERE, PLUG THIS UP AND HELP YOUR
OLD MAN WORK OUT THIS WITCHY
JAM.
>> Steven: YEAH!
L-E-E-ET'S JAM!
[ GUITAR STRUMS QUIETLY ]
UH...
WHERE MY JAMS AT?
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S PLUGGED
IN.
>> Steven: AHA!
BOOP!
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO!
L-E-E-ET'S JAM!
[ GUITAR STRUMS QUIETLY ]
UH...
HMM.
JAM!
MM. J-A-A-A-AM!
>> OH! SORRY.
THAT'S JUST THE TV.
SEE?
YOU PLUGGED INTO THE VIDEO JACK.
WE'RE MAKING AUDIO HERE.
DON'T YOU KNOW?
VIDEO KILLED THE AUDIO STAR.
>> Steven: I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
YOU LEAVE THE DETAILS TO ME.
WHEN YOU'RE A ONE-MAN BAND, YOU
GOT TO KNOW HOW TO DO IT ALL --
LYRICS, GRAPHIC DESIGN, FORUM
MODERATION.
[ SPEAKER HUMS ]
BUT FOR ME IT WAS ALL ABOUT THE
AUDIO!
>> Steven: WHAT A LOVELY POEM.
>> OKAY!
WE NEED A CATCHY HOOK --
SOMETHING LIKE...
♪ WELL, SHE'S A RIPTIDE QUEEN ♪
AND SHE'S SUPER-MEAN ♪
>> Steven: WHOA. HOLD THE PHONE.
NOW GIVE THE PHONE TO ME.
LAPIS WAS NOT MEAN.
SHE WAS JUST TRYING TO GET HOME.
HOW ABOUT THIS INSTEAD?
♪ SHE WAS TRAPPED IN A MIRROR ♪
♪ AND IT COULDN'T BE CLEARER ♪
♪ SHE WANTED TO LEAVE THIS
PLACE ♪
♪ AND GET HERSELF BACK IN
SPACE ♪
♪ AND, DAD, YOU MIGHT THINK
SHE'S A CRIMINAL ♪
♪ BUT HER FRIENDSHIP COMES
THROUGH SUBLIMINAL ♪
♪ LAPIS LAZULI ♪
♪ YOU FLED INTO THE BOTTOM OF
THE SEA ♪
♪ LAPIS LAZULI ♪
¿♪ YOU WERE SO MAD, BUT THEN YOU
CAME AROUND TO ME ♪
[ ENERGY HUMMING ]
UH, WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?!
>> MUST BE SOME KIND OF WEIRD
FEEDBACK.
HMM...
IT'S NOT US.
I THINK IT'S COMING FROM THE
TEMPLE.
>> Steven: LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
>> UH, YOU GO ON AHEAD.
IF THIS IS A GEM THING, I DON'T
WANT TO GET IN THE WAY.
PLUS, I GOT TO EAT THE REST OF
THIS PIZZA.
>> Steven: GOOD THINKING!
I'LL BE BACK.
[ PANTING ]
OW! WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
>> Pearl: IT'S THE WAILING
STONE!
>> Amethyst: MAKE IT STOP!
>> Pearl: IT JUST ACTIVATED ON
ITS OWN!
>> Amethyst: IT WON'T SHUT OFF!
UGH!
[ LOUD HUMMING STOPS ]
[ HUMMING RESUMES ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> Pearl: STAND BACK!
[ HUMMING SOFTENS ]
HUH?
IT WORKED!
NOW WE CAN --
[ HUMMING INTENSIFIES ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> Steven: UNH!
BWAAAAAAAAH!
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ HUMMING RESUMES ]
[ HUMMING SOFTENS ]
>> Garnet: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT THING HAS LAIN DORMANT
SINCE WE FOUND IT.
>> Pearl: I HAVEN'T HEARD A
WAILING STONE ACTIVATE SINCE WE
USED THEM FOR THE REBELLION.
AND I'VE NEVER HEARD IT SOUND
LIKE THAT!
>> Garnet: SOMEONE IS TRYING TO
SEND US A MESSAGE.
>> Pearl: BUT WHO?
WE'VE ROUNDED UP ALL THE WAILING
STONES ON EARTH, AND WE'RE NOT
SENDING THIS SIGNAL TO
OURSELVES!
UNLESS...
AMETHYST, IS THIS A PRANK?!
>> Amethyst: NO WAY!
I WANT IT TO STOP!
I DON'T LIKE IT!
>> Garnet: IF IT'S NOT COMING
FROM EARTH, THEN A GEM MUST BE
SENDING THIS MESSAGE FROM SPACE.
>> Steven: IS THAT...WHAT SOME
GEMS SOUND LIKE?
>> Pearl: NO, NO.
WE SHOULD BE HEARING A VOICE.
MAYBE THIS SIGNAL IS TOO
ADVANCED FOR THE WAILING STONE
TO PROCESS.
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN THE DISTORTED
AUDIO.
>> Steven: AUDIO?
MY DADDIO KNOWS AUDIO!
>> Amethyst: EH, YOU MEAN GREG?
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> Pearl: I DON'T KNOW.
>> Garnet: DON'T WHINE.
LET'S TRY IT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
YOU NEED HELP WITH SOUND STUFF?
YOU'VE COME TO THE RIGHT GUY!
AHA!
THE LUBITZ CARDIOID CONDENSER
680!
IT'S GOT WARM TONES WITHOUT TOO
MUCH TOP-END.
>> Amethyst: UH, PLUS IT'S GOT A
BIG HONKIN' SPONGE THING.
>> I KNOW! ISN'T IT AWESOME?
[ LOUD HUMMING RESUMES ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ HUMMING SOFTENS ]
NOW I'M GONNA ADD SOME REVERB
AND SOME LOW-OCTAVE EFFECTS.
I'M ALSO ADDING SOME FUZZ,
'CAUSE WHO COULDN'T USE MORE
FUZZ?
NOW, IF I DIRECTLY INPUT THE
WAILING STONE AND RUN IT THROUGH
A FLANGER, WE MIGHT GET WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
>> Pearl: FLANGERS ASIDE, DO YOU
REALLY THINK A SIGNAL LIKE THIS
IS COMPATIBLE WITH YOUR ANALOG
DEVICES?
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY, DAD.
[ Distorted ] IT'LL WORK!
>> WELL, HERE GOES NOTHIN'.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> Amethyst: THIS IS EVEN WORSE!
>> I'M SORRY!
>> Steven: DAD, YOU CAN DO IT!
YOU'RE THE AUDIO DADDIO!
>> YEAH!
[ HUMMING SOFTENS ]
>> Amethyst: [ GROANS, SIGHS ]
>> Steven: IT -- IT SOUNDS
LIKE...
MUSIC.
>> YEAH!
THAT'S REAL NICE.
YES!
WHOO-HOO!
>> Pearl: BUT IT'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE MUSIC.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A MESSAGE.
>> OKAY, HOLD ON.
I GOT THIS.
[ HUMMING WARBLES ]
IT'S...CHANGING!
>> Steven: IT ALMOST SOUNDS LIKE
A VOICE.
>> ALMOST GOT IT!
[ WARBLING INTENSIFIES ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
AAH!
UGH!
OH, GREAT.
>> Pearl: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHERE'S THE SIGNAL?
>> UH, LOOKS LIKE THE VAN
BATTERY COULDN'T HANDLE ALL
THIS.
>> Pearl: I HAD A FEELING THIS
WOULDN'T WORK.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY GREG'S
EQUIPMENT CAN INTERFACE WITH OUR
ANCIENT GEM TECHNOLOGY.
>> Steven: AW, COME ON, PEARL!
YOU CAN'T BE READY TO GIVE UP
YET!
>> LOOK, WE JUST GOT TO KEEP
TRYING.
SURE, WE DON'T HAVE THE LATEST
AND GREATEST "GEM TECH" BUT...
[ HUMMING INTENSIFIES, SOFTENS ]
>> Garnet: IT'S OKAY, GREG.
YOU TRIED.
BACK TO THE TEMPLE.
WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING ELSE OUT.
>> Pearl: WHAT A WASTE OF TIME.
>> Amethyst: SEE YA LATER,
GREGORY.
>> Steven: AW, COME ON, Y'ALL!
HUP! OOF!
>> [ SIGHS ]
I REALLY BLEW IT, HUH?
>> Steven: AW, DAD...
>> ♪ I COULD HAVE TAMED YOU ♪
♪ I COULD HAVE SHOWN ♪
♪ THAT I COULD DEPOSE YOU
FROM YOUR LOUD THRONE ♪
♪ BUT IN THE END,
I WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH ♪
♪ I JUST SHOWED THE GEMS
THAT I AIN'T GOT THE STUFF ♪
♪ OH-OH, WAILING STONE ♪
♪ I TRIED SO HARD TO FLY ♪
♪ BUT I WAS THROWN ♪
♪ OH-OH, WAILING STONE ♪
♪ I GOT TO TELL THE GEMS
'CAUSE THEY SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ HAVE A LITTLE, HAVE A LITTLE ♪
♪ HAVE A LITTLE FAITH IN ME ♪
♪ I JUST WANTED TO HELP ♪
♪ YOU KNOW, I HAVE A LITTLE ♪
♪ HAVE A LITTLE ♪
♪ HAVE A LITTLE EXPERTISE ♪
♪ I KNOW IT'S NOT MUCH ♪
♪ BUT IF IT COULD COME IN
HANDY ♪
♪ I'D WANT TO BE THERE ♪
♪ I THINK SO HIGHLY OF YOU ♪
♪ IT JUST ISN'T FAIR ♪
♪ THAT YOU HAVE SO LITTLE
FAITH ♪
>> EH. THAT'S A "B" SIDE.
>> Steven: DAD, I HATE SEEING
YOU LIKE THIS.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING ELSE
WE CAN TRY.
>> EH, I DON'T KNOW, STEVEN.
I MEAN, SOUND AND STUFF LIKE
THIS?
THIS STUFF'S MY WHOLE WORLD.
AND IF I CAN'T FIGURE THIS OUT,
THEN...MAYBE IT ISN'T EVEN
SOUND.
>> Steven: BUT, DAD, IF IT ISN'T
SOUND, THEN...WHAT ELSE COULD IT
BE?
HMM...
[ GASPS ]
WAIT.
WH-A-A-A-AT?
D-A-A-A-A-AD!
>> I'M NOT THAT FAR AWAY FROM
YOU, BUDDY.
>> Steven: WHAT IF IT'S...
>> UH, SOME OTHER THING I'M NOT
GOOD AT?
MAGIC...
EYEBALLS?
OH, MY DAYS! IT'S VIDEO!
>> Steven: WE HAVE TO TELL THE
GEMS!
VIDE-O-O-O-O!
>> HEY! SLOW DOWN!
[ SOFT HUMMING ]
I JUST WANT TO HELP!
HAVE SOME FAITH IN --
>> Amethyst: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
WE OVER HERE.
>> I KNOW MY AUDIO EQUIPMENT
SEEMS LIKE A PILE OF EARTH JUNK
TO Y'ALL, BUT I --
>> Garnet: GREG, IT'S OKAY.
>> NO, IT'S NOT!
YOU GUYS DON'T GIVE UP ON
ANYTHING -- EXCEPT FOR ME!
COME ON!
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN MAKE IT ANY
WORSE!
>> Pearl: GO FOR IT, GARNET.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
OKAY, AMETHYST, TRY IT NOW.
>> Amethyst: NEVER STARTED A CAR
WITH A KEY BEFORE.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ GIGGLES ]
THAT'S WAY EASIER!
>> Pearl: THE BATTERY'S READY
TO GO.
>> Steven: THE WAILING STONE'S
READY!
>> READY WITH THE VIDEO CORD,
STEVEN?
>> Steven: READY!
[ SPEAKERS WARBLING ]
>> Pearl: IS THAT IT?
>> JUST A SECOND...
[ WARBLING OSCILLATES ]
>> Steven: I -- I HEAR
SOMETHING.
>> COME ON...
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: LAPIS?
>> I DID IT!
>> Pearl: I CAN'T BELIEVE MY
FLIPPING EYES!
>> Garnet: EVERYONE, LISTEN UP!
>> I HOPE YOU'RE ABLE TO HEAR
THIS.
THERE'S A GEM THAT'S LOOKING FOR
YOU.
SHE EVEN KNEW YOUR NAME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW --
I DIDN'T TELL HER, I SWEAR!
SHE'S ON HER WAY TO EARTH.
AND SHE'S NOT ALONE!
STEVEN, HOME WORLD...
IT'S NOT THE WAY IT USED TO BE.
EVERYTHING HERE IS SO ADVANCED!
I CAN'T EVEN UNDERSTAND IT!
THERE'S NO WAY ANYTHING ON EARTH
CAN STAND UP TO IT!
PLEASE DON'T PUT UP A FIGHT!
IT WILL ONLY LEAD TO
DEVASTATION!
>> Pearl: IT'S PERIDOT.
SHE MUST BE TALKING ABOUT
PERIDOT.
>> Amethyst: SHE'S COMING FOR
US!
>> Steven: LAPIS...
SHE SOUNDS SO UNHAPPY.
>> Amethyst: THIS IS SERIOUSLY
BAD NEWS!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
>> Garnet: WHEW!
>> Together: WHA?
>> Garnet: WE DID IT.
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
>> Garnet: WE GOT THE MESSAGE.
>> Amethyst: BUT --
>> Garnet: IT'S GOT.
THANK YOU, GREG.
WE WOULD NOT HAVE RECEIVED THIS
MESSAGE WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
>> YOU -- YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Steven: MY DAD IS...
[ Distorted ] THE BEST!
>> OH, MY GOSH!
STEVEN'S A ROBOT! HELP!
I CAN'T RELATE TO MY ROBOT SON!
>> Steven: [ Distorted ] MY MIND
IS THE INTERNET.
I KNOW EVERY CONTINUITY MISTAKE
EVER MADE ON TELEVISION.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]