♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
Peridot:
STUPID BROKEN WARP.
FIRST THE COMMUNICATION HUB.
[ GRUNTS ]
NOW THIS IS BUSTED AGAIN.
THESE CRYSTAL GEMS ARE A MENACE.
OH, AHA!
LOOK! I WAS RIGHT!
MY PLAN WORKED PERFECTLY.
GOOD MORNING.
WHAT?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
I WAS HERE?
WE FOUND A SECRET WAY
TO TRACK YOU
AND WE'LL NEVER TELL YOU
HOW EVEN IF YOU ASK NICELY.
NYEH!
PERIDOT!
WE'RE HERE TO --
AND YOU'LL NEVER GET AWAY
WITH THIS!
DON'T YOU GEMS HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO THAN ANNOY ME?
NOPE.
WE'RE GONNA --
PREPARE TO BE ANNOYED.
[ GROANS ]
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
THIS PLANET
HAS AN EXPIRATION DATE,
AND I'M NOT GONNA STICK AROUND
TO FIND OUT WHEN!
WHA?
UH...
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S IT.
I'M TAKING HER OUT.
PEARL, WAIT!
HA!
SORRY.
BUT YOU'RE GOING THE WRONG WAY!
[ GRUNTS ]
GET HER!
[ GROANS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU MISSED.
PEARL!
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
AH, DOESN'T ANYTHING WORK ON
THIS CRUDDY PLANET?
I DO!
HUH?
OW!
AMETHYST, CATCH!
DESTROY!
AAH!
I GOT HER! I GOT HER!
I GOT HER!
[ GRUNTS ]
PEARL!
OH, GET OFF ME!
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
[ WHIMPERS ]
WOW.
THIS IS JUST SAD.
I ALMOST FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
NYEH!
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
I MEAN, I HOPE HER WEEKEND
IS NOT SO GREAT.
OKAY, I REALIZE
THAT WAS A BIT OF A FIASCO.
BUT THERE'S A SILVER LINING
TO THIS.
NOW WE KNOW FOR SURE THAT WE CAN
TRACK HER EVERY MOVEMENT.
WHENEVER SHE USES
THE WARP SYSTEM,
HER ESCAPE POD WILL INSTANTLY
DETECT EXACTLY WHERE SHE IS.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
UNTIL WE CATCH HER,
AND WHEN WE DO, WE'LL BE ABLE
TO CLOSE THIS CHAPTER
AND FINALLY MOVE ON,
RIGHT?
[ GROANS ]
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING
THAT MAYBE THE TWO OF YOU
MIGHT NEED
TO TALK ABOUT?
IT'S PERIDOT.
SHE'S USING THE WARPS
RIGHT NOW.
LOOK.
THIS IS WHERE SHE IS.
WE GOT HER FOR SURE
THIS TIME.
IF SHE THINKS
SHE'S GOT THE UPPER HAND,
THEN SHE HAS ANOTHER THING
COMING, AND THAT'S US.
WELL, AT LEAST PEARL'S
OPTIMISTIC.
IT WON'T HELP.
SHE COULD HAND PERIDOT OVER
ON A SILVER PLATTER,
BUT IT WON'T MAKE UP
FOR THE STUNT SHE PULLED
TO GET GARNET
TO FUSE WITH HER.
Garnet:
STEVEN, LET'S GO.
Steven: WHOA.
HA!
SHE'S DESPERATE.
LOOK AT THIS.
SHE'S CORNERED HERSELF IN THERE.
HMM.
WE'VE GOT HER
JUST WHERE WE WANT HER.
WHAT IS --
EXCELLENT QUESTION,
STEVEN.
WHAT WE SEE BEFORE US
IS AN ANCIENT INTERPLANETARY
GEM VESSEL.
HOMEWORLD GEMS USED THESE SHIPS
TO TRAVEL ACROSS THE COSMOS
AND LAND HERE ON EARTH
BEFORE THE WARP PADS WERE BUILT.
BUT THESE SHIPS LANDED HERE
SO LONG AGO
THAT THERE'S NO WAY
THEY CAN BE FUNCTIONAL.
PERIDOT'S
RUNNING OUT OF OPTIONS.
PEARL,
WE CAN'T WASTE TIME.
LET'S FOCUS ON THE TASK
AT --
AH, YES.
THE TASK AT HAND.
NO MORE DODDLING.
LET'S GO GET PERIDOT!
IT'S MORE LIKE A GREENHOUSE
THAN A SPACESHIP.
LOOKS LIKE EARTH WON
THIS BATTLE.
[ WARBLES ]
OH.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU GEMS REALLY ARE
AS DULL AS DIRT.
YOU'RE THE DULL ONE IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN FLY THIS WRECK.
WHAT?
CAN YOU SPEAK LOUDER?
SOME OF THESE COMMUNICATORS
ARE GUNKED UP.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
PEARL SAYS
YOU'RE THE DULL ONE
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN FLY
THIS WRECK.
[ Echoing ] FLY THIS WRECK.
[ LAUGHS ]
FLY?
I'M NOT USING THIS VESSEL
TO FLY.
I'M USING IT TO TRAP YOU!
[ ALL GASP ]
ISN'T THIS NICE?
NO MORE CRYSTAL GEMS
RUNNING AROUND,
MESSING WITH MY PLANS,
DESTROYING MY THINGS.
LOOKS LIKE I'VE GOT YOU
JUST WHERE I WANT YOU.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE SO
EASILY OUTSMARTED, YOU CLODS?!
NO.
HEY, UH...
THIS IS AMETHYST.
I DON'T APPRECIATE
BEING CALLED A CLOD, YOU CLO--
ENOUGH TALK.
PREPARE YOURSELVES
FOR ANNIHILATION!
HYAH!
HYAH.
AHA! IT WORKS.
YES!
DIE! DIE! DIE! DIE! DIE! DIE!
HEY, GUYS, OVER HERE.
THIS WAY.
YOU'RE ON FIRE,
STEVEN!
THAT'S THREE SHIELDS
IN ONE DAY.
NOT TOO SHABBY!
MOVE!
AAH!
Peridot: SPIKES!
HOW DO YOU LIKE MY SPIKES?!
PERIDOT!
PEARL, DON'T JUST --
[ GROANS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU IDIOT.
[ GROANS ]
AAH! AAH! AAH! AAH! AAH!
[ PANTING ]
PEARL, STOP.
THAT ISN'T HELPING.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I WALKED US
RIGHT INTO PERIDOT'S TRAP.
THIS IS ALL MY...FAULT?
[ RUMBLING ]
HUH?
AAH!
[ Straining ]
I GOT YOU, STEVEN.
THANKS, AMETHYST.
[ GASPS ]
GARNET AND PEARL.
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
WE'RE FINE.
[ GASPS ]
CRUD.
[ DISTANT GRUNTING ]
WE'VE GOT
TO GET THEM OUT.
AMETHYST,
WHAT SHOULD WE --
Pearl: GARNET, I'M SORRY.
WAIT A SEC.
THINGS WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO TURN
OUT THIS WAY.
[ GRUNTS ]
WE'LL GET OUT OF HERE SOMEHOW.
[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
I REALLY WANTED TO CATCH PERIDOT
TO MAKE UP FOR WHAT I DID.
I WANTED TO PROVE TO YOU
THAT --
THAT EVERYTHING COULD GO BACK
TO NORMAL.
CATCHING PERIDOT WON'T MAKE
THINGS GO BACK TO NORMAL.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT PERIDOT.
HEY,
THEY'RE ACTUALLY TALKING.
NOW THEY CAN FINALLY
WORK THINGS OUT.
[ RUMBLING ]
NOT IF THEY GET CRUSHED!
PLEASE TELL ME!
HOW CAN I MAKE YOU
FORGIVE ME?!
YOU CAN'T.
YOU LIED TO ME.
YOU NEED TO LEARN THAT THERE ARE
CONSEQUENCES TO YOUR ACTIONS.
I'M SORRY.
I...I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
YOUR EXCUSES.
BUT IT'S TRUE.
NO MATTER HOW HARD I TRY TO BE
STRONG LIKE YOU,
I'M JUST A PEARL.
I'M USELESS ON MY OWN.
I NEED SOMEONE
TO TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
[ RUMBLING STOPS ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
WHEN WE FUSE, I CAN FEEL
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE YOU.
CONFIDENT AND SECURE
AND COMPLETE.
YOU'RE PERFECT.
YOU'RE
THE PERFECT RELATIONSHIP.
YOU'RE ALWAYS TOGETHER.
I JUST --
I WANTED TO BE A PART OF THAT.
YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT AS STRONG
AS YOU THINK.
I-I FELL APART OVER THIS.
RUBY AND SAPPHIRE
WERE IN TURMOIL OVER
HOW YOU DECEIVED ME.
I CAME UNDONE.
WHOA.
THAT REALLY HAPPENED?
HMM.
IT'S NOT EASY
BEING IN CONTROL.
I HAVE WEAKNESSES, TOO,
BUT I CHOOSE NOT TO LET THEM
CONSUME ME.
I STRUGGLE TO STAY STRONG
BECAUSE I KNOW THE IMPACT
I HAVE ON EVERYONE.
PLEASE UNDERSTAND, PEARL,
YOU HAVE AN IMPACT, TOO.
THERE ARE TIMES WHEN I LOOK UP
TO YOU FOR STRENGTH.
YOU ARE YOUR OWN GEM.
YOU CONTROL YOUR DESTINY.
NOT ME,
NOT ROSE, NOT STEVEN.
BUT YOU MUST CHOOSE TO BE STRONG
SO WE CAN MOVE FORWARD,
SO I CAN TRUST YOU AGAIN.
I UNDERSTAND.
I CAN'T GIVE UP ANYMORE.
GOOD.
[ GRUNTS ]
PEARL, THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
OUT OF THIS.
ONLY IF YOU'RE OKAY
WITH IT.
MM.
Both: AAH!
WHAT DO WE DO?!
[ GROANS ]
STUPID BUTTON HERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ANYTHING IS --
AAH!
BLAST THIS OLD GEM TECH!
WHERE DID THEY GO?
WHY ISN'T ANYTHING WORKING?!
AAH!
SURRENDER, PERIDOT.
YOU HAVE NOWHERE TO RUN.
THE CRYSTAL GEMS
ARE GONNA GET YOU.
YOU REALLY THINK
THIS IS THE END?
[ LAUGHS ]
THIS -- THIS IS ONLY
THE BEGINNING...
OF MY ESCAPE.
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL,
I'D LOVE TO STICK AROUND
AND WATCH ANOTHER ONE OF YOUR
PATHETIC ATTEMPTS TO CAPTURE ME,
BUT I GUESS
I'M JUST TOO SMART
FOR THE LIKES OF YOU LUMPY,
CLUMPY CLODS.
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT THE?
I CAUGHT A PERIDOT.
HEY, GET YOUR TOUCH STUMPS
OFF ME, YOU STEVEN.
HEY!
YEAH, STEVEN!
DON'T LET HER GO.
[ GROANS ]
LET GO OF ME!
YOU -- YOU PERSISTENT, LITTLE
WHATEVER EXACTLY YOU ARE!
PERIDOT,
YOUR FLIGHT'S BEEN CANCELED.
NO!
[ GROANS ]
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS,
CRYSTAL GEMS.
I'LL GET YOU BACK.
JUST YOU WA-A-A-IT!
PEARL?
IT'S OKAY, STEVEN.
NEXT TIME,
WE'LL GET THE REST OF HER.
RIGHT, GARNET?
IT'S A GOOD STEP FORWARD.
[ LAUGHS ]
FOOT JOKE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GROANS ]
FINALLY.
♪ YOU ♪
♪ ARE LIKE YOU ♪
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
WELL, TIME TO ASSUME
MY SECRET IDENTITY.
SAME TIME NEXT WEEK
FOR SWORD TRAINING?
YEAH. IT'S A SHAME
I CAN'T PRACTICE MORE AT HOME.
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
HUP!
MAY I?
[ GASPS ]
HERE-ETH.
YOU CAN BORROW-ETH
MY MOTHER'S SWORD...ETH.
STEVEN, THAT'S SO NICE,
IF GRAMMATICALLY INCORRECT.
BUT THOU CAN'T JUST GIVEST ME
THINE MOTHER'S SWORD.
WHY NOT-ETH?
BECAUSE IT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT-ETH.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
YOU SHOULD HAVE-ETH IT.
YOU CAN HAVE ALL WEEK
TO PRACTICE-ETH WITH IT-ETH.
[ LAUGHS ]
PbbhhTHANK YOU.
WE GOT TO BE READY IF WE HAVE TO
FIGHT MALACHITE OR PERIDOT
OR THOSE CREEPY
GEM-FUSION EXPERIMENTS.
I'LL MAKE SURE
NOTHING HAPPENS TO IT.
[ GARAGE DOOR WHIRRING ]
THAT'S THE GARAGE DOOR.
MOM'S HOME.
WE HAVE TO HIDE
THE SWORD.
THERE'S NO WAY MOM WOULD LET ME
HAVE THIS IN THE HOUSE.
LION? LION?
HE WALKED OFF.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?!
[ DOOR CLOSES,
VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING ]
HI, MOM. JUST FINISHING
MY 6:00 VIOLIN PRACTICE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE FINISHED
FIVE MINUTES AGO.
YOU'RE LATE
FOR YOUR 7:00 STUDY HOUR.
HELLO, STEVEN.
HI, DR. MAHESHWAREN.
HOW ARE YOU?
SITTING!
[ SHUDDERS ]
[ SIGHS ]
I HAD A ROUGH DAY
AT WORK,
AND I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
FOR ANY MORE SURPRISES.
WHAT HAPPENED AT WORK?
THERE WAS A REALLY STRANGE CASE
AT THE HOSPITAL TODAY --
STRAIGHT OUT
OF A NIGHTMARE.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
THE RULES OF DOCTOR-PATIENT
CONFIDENTIALITY
KEEP ME FROM SHARING
THE GRAPHIC DETAILS, BUT --
HANG ON A MOMENT.
WHEN DID WE GET A COAT RACK?
OH, NO.
A SWORD?!
CONNIE,
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?!
IT'S --
I FOUND IT.
I JUST FOUND IT
OUTSIDE,
AND I WANTED TO SHOW IT
TO STEVEN.
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY
THINK THIS IS OKAY?
IT'S --
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY CHILDREN
I SEE EVERY DAY IN THE HOSPITAL
WHO'VE CUT THEIR FACES OFF
PLAYING WITH SWORDS?
I --
NONE!
BECAUSE THEY ALL HAVE
PARENTS WHO LOVE THEM
AND WHO DON'T LET THEM PLAY
AROUND WITH DEADLY WEAPONS
LIKE SOME KIND
OF GANG MEMBER!
NO PLAYING WITH SWORDS
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
THIS IS DR. MAHESHWAREN.
YES, CALM DOWN, STRAUMBURG.
ANOTHER ONE?
IS SHE
GONNA GIVE IT BACK?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL --
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
I'LL HAVE A TALK
WITH YOUR FATHER
TO CALCULATE
JUST HOW GROUNDED YOU ARE.
AND WE'RE USING
THE ABACUS.
I HATE THAT ABACUS.
STEVEN, I'M SO SORRY.
SHE TOOK YOUR MOTHER'S SWORD.
MAYBE WE CAN GET HER
TO CHANGE HER MIND.
SHE NEVER, EVER
CHANGES HER MIND.
WE'VE GOT TO GET
THAT SWORD BACK OURSELVES.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
WHOA!
UGH.
WE CAN'T
BRING LION INSIDE.
I'D FEEL REALLY BAD
IF MY MOM CONFISCATED HIM, TOO.
OH, IT'S NO PROBLEM.
HE CAN STAY OUT HERE.
LOOK -- I FINALLY FOUND A WAY
TO GET HIM TO DO WHAT I WANT.
[ CHOMP! ]
[ GROWLING SOFTLY ]
HE DIDN'T EVEN TAKE
THE PLASTIC OFF.
WHAT AN ANIMAL.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
OKAY, SERIOUS.
YEAH. SERIOUS.
THIS WAY.
AH, YOU MEAN
THE SUPER SCARY WAY.
THEY TURN THE LIGHTS DOWN
AFTER DINNER.
[ WHEEZING ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ HINGES CREAK, DOORS SLAM ]
Man: DR. WEST
AIN'T GONNA LIKE IT.
Woman: WELL,
DR. WEST ISN'T HERE.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE EVILLY ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
YES, YES, I JUST GOT HERE.
MM-HMM. MM-HMM.
[ WHEEZING ]
WHERE DID YOU SAY
YOU FOUND THEM?
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD?
I'M NOT SURE JUST YET.
I HAVEN'T HAD A LOOK FOR MYSELF.
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A CAR ACCIDENT.
YOU DIDN'T FIND AN I.D.?
LISTEN,
I'LL CALL YOU BACK
WHEN, OR IF,
I HAVE AN ANSWER FOR YOU.
GOODBYE.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
OKAY, NOW.
[ WHEEZES ]
WHAT'S SHE DOING?
SHE'S PROBABLY CHECKING
THEIR VITALS.
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN
TO A HOSPITAL BEFORE?
NO.
OH. LUCKY.
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN, LOOK.
HMM.
[ GROANS ]
[ WHEEZING ]
HMM.
NO HEARTBEAT.
UGH.
CHEAP HOSPITAL BUDGETS.
[ SCREECHES ]
[ WHEEZING ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
[ WHEEZING ]
[ WHEEZING STOPS ]
[ BOTH SIGH ]
CONNIE!
OH, NO!
HOW DID YOU EVEN --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH THIS?!
I MADE A RULE --
NO SWORDS
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES.
BUT, MOM!
WE WILL FINISH
THIS CONVERSATION AT HOME.
[ CLATTERING IN DISTANCE ]
[ HEAVY FOOTSTEPS ]
SIR? MA'AM? DR. WEST?
[ SIGHS ] HE CAN'T
TAKE A DAY OFF, CAN HE?
[ GROWLS ]
YOU?
IT'S MY OTHER PATIENT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT OF BED?
WHY AREN'T YOU WITH
DR. STRAUMBURG?
[ GROWLS ]
THAT'S NOT A PATIENT.
[ ROARS ]
AAH!
[ ROARING, SCREECHING ]
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
BUT I AM GOING TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
[ GROWLING ]
CONNIE, I THINK THAT'S
ONE OF THE GEM MUTANTS.
WHAT? ARE YOU SURE?
PRETTY SURE
AT THIS POINT.
MOM, I REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY NEED THAT SWORD.
CONNIE, NO.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
[ POUNDING ]
NOW IS THE PERFECT TIME,
MOM!
CONNIE,
WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU?
YOU KNOW I NEVER GO BACK
ON A RULE, YOUNG LADY.
THERE HAVE TO BE
SOME EXCEPTIONS.
I'M NOT
SOME RULE-DRIVEN ROBOT.
[ SCREECHING ]
AAH!
CONNIE!
MOM!
I'LL SAVE YOU!
HERE!
KEEP YOUR HANDS
OFF MY CONNIE!
THESE PATIENTS
ARE BEYOND REASON.
MOM, IF YOU WOULD JUST GO BACK
ON YOUR RULE THIS ONE TIME...
[ SCREECHES ]
AAH!
I JUST NEED TO HELP STEVEN
TO GET US OUT OF HERE!
MOTHER KNOWS BEST!
[ SCREECHING ]
STEVEN, COME ON!
[ SCREECHING CONTINUES ]
OH, NO.
WE'RE TRAPPED.
WE DON'T HAVE TO BE.
[ SCREECHING CONTINUES ]
REALLY, MOM,
I KNOW HOW TO DO THIS.
NO, YOU DON'T.
UGH! YES, SHE DOES.
SHE'S BEEN TRAINING.
SHE WASN'T PLAYING AROUND
WITH THAT SWORD.
SHE WAS TAKING CLASSES,
LEARNING HOW TO USE IT RIGHT.
EVEN THOUGH
SHE'S ALWAYS STUDYING
OR PRACTICING TENNIS
OR DOING HER HOMEWORK,
SHE STILL WORKS REALLY HARD
TO BE A GOOD SWORD FIGHTER.
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I KNOW MY DAUGHTER.
I KNOW WHAT SHE'S DOING
EVERY SECOND OF THE DAY --
ALL HER ACTIVITIES,
ALL HER INTERNETS.
I KNOW SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT
SOME SWORD-FIGHTING HOOLIGAN.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME
AT ALL!
YOU STILL HAVEN'T EVEN NOTICED
MY GLASSES.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR GLASSES?
THEY DON'T HAVE LENSES
ANYMORE.
I HAVEN'T NEEDED ACTUAL GLASSES
FOR ALMOST A YEAR.
WHAT? YOUR EYESIGHT
JUST MAGICALLY GOT BETTER?
YES!
I'VE BEEN DEALING
WITH MAGIC AND MONSTERS
AND THINGS LIKE THESE
SINCE I MET STEVEN.
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU TO BELIEVE
I KNOW WHAT TO DO HERE.
BUT YOU --
UGH!
THERE'S NO TIME FOR THIS.
READY?
DROP THE BUBBLE.
[ SCREECHING ]
HA!
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHOOSH ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
SO THAT'S WHY
IT HAD NO PULSE.
GEM EXPERIMENTS.
THIS IS WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN DOING?
TRAINING TO FIGHT
THESE...THINGS?
AAH!
SORRY,
DR. MAHESHWAREN.
THAT'S MY LION.
MOM, I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT LYING TO YOU.
IT STARTED OFF
AS A TINY SECRET,
AND THEN IT FELT LIKE
IF I DIDN'T HIDE IT,
YOU WOULDN'T LET ME SEE STEVEN
EVER AGAIN.
IS THAT HOW YOU FEEL?
ARE WE TOO CONTROLLING?
MAYBE.
I JUST WANTED TO BE
A GOOD MOTHER.
I-I JUST WANTED
TO PROTECT YOU.
I CAN PROTECT MYSELF NOW.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY.
WE'LL PULL BACK
ON THE RULES,
AND I'LL TRY TO KEEP
AN OPEN MIND
ABOUT THIS AND THAT
AND...HIM.
IT SCARES ME
THAT YOU CAN'T TALK TO ME.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN YOUR LIFE.
I NEED TO STEP IN
WHEN YOU'RE IN OVER YOUR HEAD.
WILL YOU JUST PROMISE ME
YOU'LL STOP ALL THIS LYING?
THAT'S A RULE.
I LOVE YOU, HONEY.
I LOVE YOU TOO, MOM.
♪ I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I MIGHT BE BAD ♪
♪ NOW I'M SURE THAT IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I THINK
YOU'RE SO GOOD ♪
♪ AND I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU ♪