♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
[ CHATTER ]
HERE YOU AREZ,
MY LARZ!
UH, I'LL JUST LEAVE IT HERE
FOR YOU.
[ DOOR CHIME PLAYS ]
SADIE, MY LADY!
I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD HANG
ONE OF THESE BEACH-A-PALOOZA
FLYERS IN --
[ POP MUSIC PLAYING ]
SADIE? SADIE!
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
♪ I CAN'T HELP IT
IF I MAKE A SCENE ♪
♪ STEPPING OUT
OF MY HOT-PINK LIMOUSINE ♪
♪ I'M TURNING HEADS,
AND I'M STOPPING TRAFFIC ♪
♪ WHEN I POSE, THEY SCREAM,
AND WHEN I JOKE, THEY LAUGH ♪
♪ I'VE GOT A PAIR OF EYES
THAT THEY'RE GETTING LOST IN ♪
♪ THEY'RE HYPNOTIZED
BY MY WAY OF WALKING ♪
♪ I GOT THEM DAZZLED
LIKE A STAGE MAGICIAN ♪
♪ WHEN I POINT, THEY LOOK,
AND WHEN I TALK, THEY LISTEN ♪
♪ WELL,
EVERYBODY NEEDS A FRIEND ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT YOU
AND YOU AND YOU ♪
♪ SO MANY,
I CAN'T EVEN NAME THEM ♪
♪ CAN YOU BLAME ME? ♪
♪ I'M TOO FAMOUS ♪
YEAH! WHOO-HOO!
♪ HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
I'M A STAR? ♪
YEAH! THAT WAS AMAZING!
OOH-HOO-HOO!
AWESOME!
WHA? NO, HEH.
I WAS JUST -- I WASN'T --
♪ HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
I'VE MADE -- ♪
HEH. MM.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD SING.
NOBODY DOES.
SO, UM, DO YOU NEED SOMETHING?
OH!
I'M JUST GOING AROUND
HELPING MR. SMILEY
HAND OUT FLIERS
FOR BEACH-A-PALOOZA THIS YEAR.
[ GASPS ]
YOU SHOULD SIGN UP!
EHH, WHY?
EHH...BECAUSE YOUR VOICE
IS BEAUTIFUL!
AW, ANYBODY'D SOUND FINE
SINGING ALONG WITH THAT SONG.
IT'S SO CHEESY AND DUMB
AND -- AND CATCHY.
AND...I KNOW
EVERY SINGLE WORD.
PERFECT!
NOW YOU JUST NEED
A ROUTINE.
I CAN HELP YOU
PUT ONE TOGETHER.
AW, REALLY?
YOU THINK PEOPLE
WOULD WANT TO HEAR ME SING?
OF COURSE THEY WOULD!
YOU'RE GREAT!
BESIDES, EVERYONE IN TOWN
IS DOING SOMETHING!
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YEAH!
WHO CARES,
RIGHT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT AM I AFRAID OF?
TH-THIS COULD BE FUN!
[ DOOR OPENS ]
YOUR HOUSE
IS SO COOL.
JUST DOWN HERE.
WHOA!
YOU SLEEP
IN A BASEMENT?
I LIKE TO THINK OF IT
LIKE A BUNKER.
[ GASPS ]
ARE THESE ALL YOURS?
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE NOT
REALLY MY THING.
YOU CAN HAVE ONE
IF YOU WANT.
EHHHHH, I DON'T WANT
TO BREAK UP A FAMILY.
SO,
NOW WE HAVE THE CD.
I GUESS
I CAN PRACTICE SINGING.
FIRST, WE GOT TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA WEAR.
DOES IT MATTER?
EVER SINCE MY ACT
TWO YEARS AGO,
THERE'S BEEN A RULE THAT
YOU'VE GOT TO WEAR CLOTHES.
[ GIGGLES ]
WELL, I WASN'T PLANNING
TO GO IN MY UNDERWEAR.
HOW ABOUT
SOMETHING FLASHY?
AND SPARKLY.
O-OR WAIT, WHAT DO YOU THINK
SHOULD BE YOUR GIMMICK?
WHOA.
NO, NO, NO.
NO GIMMICKS.
THE SINGING'S ALREADY A STRETCH.
WELL,
MAYBE...THIS?
OR MAYBE EVEN --
THAT ONE'S PRETTY!
EH, I THINK
IT'S A LITTLE MUCH.
I'LL JUST DO
SOMETHING COMFORTABLE.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S THAT?!
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
WE'LL DO THIS
ANOTHER TIME!
[ FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE ]
HEY, SADIE!
HI, MOM.
YOU'RE HOME EARLY.
I JUST HAD TO RUSH HOME
TO SHOW YOU THIS!
LOOK AT THIS LITTLE GUY
I GOT FOR YOU!
AIN'T HE THE CUTEST?
OH. THANKS MOM.
SADIE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HANGING OUT WITH GREG'S BOY?
BARB, I KNEW
YOU DELIVERED MAIL,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU DELIVERED SADIE!
YEAH,
MY MOM'S THE MAILMAN.
THAT SHE IS!
BEST DANG MAILMAN, WOMAN,
OR ANIMAL ON THE FORCE!
[ LAUGHS ]
AT LEAST UNTIL THEY CATCH ME
TAKING FROM THE "LOST MAIL" BIN!
[ CHUCKLES ]
BUT THAT'S BETWEEN US,
HEH?
SO, STEVEN, WHAT ARE YOUR
INTENTIONS WITH MY DAUGHTER?
WE'RE PLANNING A STAGE SHOW
FOR BEACH-A-PAWOOZA.
BEACH-A-PAWOOZA!
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ SIGHS ]
I'M GOING TO SING A SONG
FOR BEACH-A-PALOOZA.
WHAT?!
OH, OH, OH OH!
SADIE,
YOU'RE GONNA SING?!
YEAH.
THEN COME ON!
WE HAVE TO
START PLANNING NOW!
STEVEN,
HELP ME FIND AN OUTFIT!
OKAY!
UH, YOU KNOW, I COULD PROBABLY
DO THIS BY MYSELF.
IT'S NO TROUBLE.
WE'D LOVE TO HELP YA OUT!
RIGHT, STEVEN?
RIGHT!
OH, LOOK!
IT'S YOUR OLD
BALLET OUTFIT!
YOU'RE A BALLERINA?
WHEN I WAS LIKE 10.
OH,
IT'S YOUR SWIMSUIT!
SHE USED TO BE
A COMPETITIVE SWIMMER!
FOR LIKE A MONTH.
WHEN I WAS 11.
BARB,
WHAT'S THIS?
OH!
LOOK, LOOK!
REMEMBER WHEN I USED TO DRIVE
YOU TO YOUR SOFTBALL GAMES?
I REMEMBER WHEN YOU PUNCHED
THE UMPIRE.
THAT'S WHAT HE GETS
FOR TRYING TO CHEAT MY DAUGHTER
OUT OF
A DOUBLE!
AND THEN I WASN'T REALLY ALLOWED
IN THE LEAGUE ANYMORE.
THEM'S THE BREAKS!
SO WHAT HAVE YOU GOT PLANNED
SO FAR FOR YOUR SHOW?
NOTHING,
I GUESS.
WELL,
DON'T YOU WORRY!
ME AND STEVEN WILL FIGURE OUT
YOUR SHOW FOR YOU!
WE'LL MAKE SURE THE WORLD
WILL HEAR YOUR VOICE!
WELL, LET'S JUST TRY
TO KEEP IT SIMPLE?
WHAT WAS THAT?
♪ I CAN'T HELP IT
IF I MAKE A SCENE ♪
♪ STEPPING OUT
OF MY HOT-PINK LIMOUSINE ♪
♪ I'M TURNING HEADS,
AND I'M STOPPING TRAFFIC ♪
♪ WHEN I POSE, THEY SCREAM,
AND WHEN I JOKE, THEY LAUGH ♪
♪ I'VE GOT A PAIR OF EYES
THAT THEY'RE GETTING LOST IN ♪
♪ THEY'RE HYPNOTIZED
BY THE WAY I'M WALKING ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THEM DAZZLED
LIKE A STAGE MAGICIAN ♪
♪ WHEN I POINT, THEY LOOK,
AND WHEN I TALK, THEY LISTEN ♪
♪ WELL,
EVERYBODY NEEDS A FRIEND ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT YOU
AND YOU AND YOU ♪
♪ SO MANY,
I CAN'T EVEN NAME THEM ♪
♪ CAN YOU BLAME ME? ♪
♪ I'M TOO FAMOUS ♪
I THINK
WE DID AN EXCELLENT JOB!
WE JUST NEED TO TELL MR. SMILEY
TO ADD HER NAME TO THE FLIER.
OH, MAYBE DON'T PUT MY NAME
ON IT.
YEAH!
WHAT IF SHE WAS A SURPRISE?!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
SHE'LL BE
A MYSTERY FINAL ACT!
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
Mr. Smiley:
THANK YOU, BEACH-A-PALOOZA!
YOU KNOW THIS NEXT ACT FROM
THEIR DAY JOB, DELIVERING PIZZA!
BUT TONIGHT,
THEY'RE DELIVERING JOKES!
THAT WAS A JOKE.
LET ME HEAR
A BIG ROUND OF APPLAUSE
FOR KIKI
AND HER VENTRILOQUIST DUMMY!
KIKI, THAT RUDE MR. SMILEY
JUST CALLED ME A DUMMY!
THAT'S JUST OUR ACT,
GUNGA!
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW THEM
YOUR JOKES?
HOW DOES A PIZZA
TIE ITS SHOES?
HOW?
WITH A GARLIC KNOT!
[ RIM SHOT, LAUGHTER ]
[ LAUGHS ] ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE'RE GETTING CLOSER
TO TONIGHT'S MYSTERY GUEST.
EVEN I DON'T KNOW WHO IT IS,
AND I'M THE HOST!
BUT FIRST,
RONALDO FRYMAN WITH A LECTURE
ON "ROCK PEOPLE:
IDENTIFICATION AND DEFENSE."
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THE FLIERS
REALLY WORKED!
THE WHOLE TOWN IS HERE!
PLUS SOME!
OH,
MY SADIE!
SUCH A BIG STAR!
NEVER EVEN WENT TO THE PROM
AND LOOK AT YA NOW!
AM I ON YET?
SADIE MILLER!
YOU'RE
THE MYSTERY GUEST?
I NEVER EVEN WOULD'VE
RECOGNIZED YOU!
OH!
HI, MR. SMILEY.
UH, UM. MM.
HOW, UH,
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M FINE,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE HERE
HAS A CASE
OF THE SHOWBIZ SHAKES.
YOU KNOW WHAT AN OLD FRIEND
OF MINE TOLD ME ONCE?
A LITTLE SMILE
NEVER HURT ANYBODY.
NNNNNNN.                NNNNNNN.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
AWWWW,
LOOKIN GOOD!
THANK YOU!            THANK YOU!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ SIGHS ]
GAH-AH.
MORE SPARKLES!
YES, SIR!
Mr. Smiley:
NEXT UP, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR MAILMAN AND "MIME!"
[ LAUGHS ] JAMIE!
[ PIANO PLAYING ]
OH,
IT'S A BOX.
HE'S -- HE'S --
HE'S DOING A BOX.
[ GASPS ] UH-OH.
NO MORE GLITTER.
I'LL HAVE TO RUN AND GET THE
EMERGENCY SUPPLY FROM THE CAR.
GUARD MY GIRL,
STEVEN.
[ GASPS ]
SADIE, COME BACK HERE!
[ MAN COUGHING ]
I CAN'T WAIT
FOR THIS MYSTERY ACT!
YOU THINK
IT'S A JUGGLER?
MAYBE THEY'LL JUGGLE
SOMETHING SHARP.
I'M GONNA HAVE MY PHONE READY
IN CASE SOMEONE GETS HURT.
[ GASPS ]
SADIE!
UH!
I-I CAN'T BREATHE!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GULPING ]
OKAY, OKAY,
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA COME BACK
AND LET ME WORK ON YOU,
THEN LET'S WORK ON THE ROUTINE.
OKAY,
JUST LET ME --
OH, NO!
YOU RUINED
MY LIPSTICK!
NEVER FEAR!
STEVEN'S HERE!
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
SADIE,
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
RAH! BECAUSE!
YOU'RE JUST AS BAD
AS MY MOM!
WHAT?!
PLEASE, MOM,
DON'T MAKE ME DO THIS.
MAKE YOU?
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO SING!
YEAH!
I DID! I DID!
JUST LIKE
I SAY LOTS OF THINGS!
LIKE, "HEY, MOM,
SWIMMING LOOKS FUN!"
THEN BAM!
SUDDENLY, I'M ANCHORING
A 400-METER RELAY
FOR THE
BEACH CITY SEALS!
"HEY, MOM, I THOUGHT SIGNING UP
FOR SOFTBALL WOULD BE NICE!"
SIX BIRTHDAYS LATER,
I'M STILL GETTING NOTHING BUT
KNEEPADS AND BATTING HELMETS!
"HEY, MOM, I WANT TO SING
IN THIS YEAR'S BEACH-A-PALOOZA,"
AND WHAT DO I GET?
THIS!
I JUST THOUGHT FOR ONCE,
I'D GET TO DO THINGS MY WAY,
BUT YOU CAME IN AND TOOK OVER
EVERYTHING, LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
I JUST WANTED EVERYONE TO KNOW
HOW TALENTED MY DAUGHTER IS.
THIS IS NOT
YOUR DAUGHTER.
I'M SORRY.
I --
Mr. Smiley: NEXT UP, THE ONE
YOU'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR.
THE ONE! THE ONLY!
MYSTERY GUEST!
AAAH!
HOW DID I LET THIS HAPPEN?
I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS!
YOU NEVER DID.
I-IT WAS ALWAYS ME.
[ POP MUSIC PLAYS ]
GIVE IT UP FOR...
LOOKS LIKE YOU CALLED IT,
GUNGA.
THAT "MYSTERY GUEST" BIT
HAD STEVEN WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
♪ I CAN'T HELP IT
IF I MAKE A SCENE ♪
♪ STEPPING OUT
OF MY HOT-PINK LIMOUSINE ♪
♪ I'M TURNING HEADS,
AND I'M STOPPING TRAFFIC ♪
♪ WHEN I POSE, THEY SCREAM,
AND WHEN I JOKE, THEY LAUGH ♪
♪ I'VE GOT A PAIR OF EYES
THAT THEY'RE GETTING LOST IN ♪
♪ THEY'RE HYPNOTIZED
BY MY WAY OF WALKING ♪
♪ I'VE GOT THEM DAZZLED
LIKE A STAGE MAGICIAN ♪
♪ WHEN I POINT, THEY LOOK,
AND WHEN I TALK, THEY LISTEN ♪
♪ WELL,
EVERYBODY NEEDS A FRIEND ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT YOU
AND YOU AND YOU ♪
♪ SO MANY,
I CAN'T EVEN NAME THEM ♪
♪ CAN YOU BLAME ME? ♪
♪ I'M TOO FAMOUS ♪
♪ HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
I'M A STAR? ♪
♪ I'M COMING INTO VIEW
AS THE WORLD IS TURNING ♪
♪ HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
I MADE IT THIS FAR? ♪
♪ NOW EVERYONE
CAN SEE ME BURNING ♪
♪ I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I MIGHT BE BAD ♪
♪ NOW I'M SURE THAT IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I THINK YOU'RE SO GOOD,
AND I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU ♪
[ SPITS ]
AHH.
GOOD NIGHT, HAPPY BEAR.
GOOD NIGHT, SAD BUNNY.
GOOD NIGHT, PLAYFUL KITTY.
GOOD NIGHT, OMINOUS TRIANGLE
AT THE FOOT OF MY BED.
[ SIGHS ] WHATEVER.
[ MUFFLED SCREAM ]
AH!
LET ME GO!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
ENOUGH OF THIS.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU WANT
FROM ME?
I WANT TO GET OFF
THIS LOUSY GEM-FORSAKEN PLANET.
HUH? AH!
YOU HAVE TO FIX THIS.
WAIT, WHAT?
YOU'RE MY LAST CHANCE.
I'VE GOT NO FLASK ROBONOIDS.
I'VE GOT NO FOOT.
I'VE GOT NO RESPONSE
FROM YELLOW DIAMOND.
[ INHALES DEEPLY,
EXHALES ]
I KNOW YOU FIXED
LAZULI'S GEM.
WHATEVER YOU DID, YOU'VE GOT
TO DO IT TO THE HOMEWORLD WARP.
OR ELSE!
UH, OKAY.
JUST -- JUST GIVE ME A SECOND.
MY MOUTH GETS REALLY DRY
WHEN I'M SCARED.
HERE GOES.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
IT DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK.
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
IT HAS TO WORK!
I'M REALLY SORRY.
[ LAUGHING ]
THIS WAS IT.
THIS WAS MY LAST SHOT.
[ GASPS ]
I'M GONNA DIE HERE.
OHHH.
HEY, HEY, COME ON.
EARTH ISN'T THAT BAD.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT EARTH IS LIKE.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
LIKE ANYTHING SOON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[ WARBLES ]
[ GROANS ]
THERE HE IS.
GUYS!
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, YOU'RE OKAY!
PERIDOT!
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE?
GEMS, MOVE!
YAH!
HA!
NOT THIS TIME.
WHOA!
[ GASPS ]
[ COUGHS, GROANS ]
WAIT, WAIT.
YOU -- YOU NEED ME.
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS ABOUT THE --
RRAH!
WHAT ON EARTH?
UGH, SICK.
THERE'S BITS OF HER ALL OVER.
NOPE.
SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
AND NOW SHE'S
IN THE TEMPLE.
SO, THESE WEREN'T
ACTUALLY PART OF HER BODY?
UH, WHOOPS.
GARNET, SHE WAS TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING.
THOSE ARE JUST THE DESPERATE
LIES OF A GEM WHO'S BEEN CAUGHT.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT HER ANYMORE.
COME ON, STEVEN.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
THIS IS FINALLY OVER.
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
I'M BACK TO KIDNAP YOU!
WHAT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S BEEN LONG ENOUGH THAT
WE CAN JOKE ABOUT IT, RIGHT?
IT'S ONLY BEEN
LIKE AN HOUR.
SO, EW, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH HER FOOT?
THINK IT'S LUCKY?
NOT FOR PERIDOT.
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL,
GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
UM...AMETHYST?
YEAH?
UH...DO YOU THINK...
NO, IT'S OKAY.
NEVER MIND.
OKAY, WEIRDO.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, I'LL BE
IN MY ROOM EATING GARBAGE.
OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
WHY WERE YOU SO SCARED?
WHAT WERE YOU GOING TO SAY?
NOW YOU'RE DEEP IN THE TEMPLE IN
A BUBBLE AND WE'LL NEVER KNOW.
IF I COULD JUST TALK TO YOU
FOR ONE MORE SECOND...
[ GASPS ]
[ WARBLES ]
ROOM,
I NEED TO TALK TO PERIDOT.
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS ABOUT THE --
THE WHAT?!
UGH. NO, NO, NO.
ROOM,
I NEED TO GO TO THE BASEMENT.
THE REAL BASEMENT.
I KNOW THERE'S A WAY DOWN
FROM HERE.
THANK YOU!
WHOO! YEAH! WHOO-HOO!
TRIPLE 550 DELUXE
WITH NO CHEESE!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ Strained ] YEP.
PERFECT LANDING.
HMM...
[ GASPS ]
THERE WE GO.
[ GRUNTING ]
GOTCHA!
WHOA!
...THE CLUSTER,
YOU INSUFFERABLE, HALF-FORMED,
TRAITOR MEGACLODS!
OH, MY GOSH!
YOU'RE SO CUTE!
MY LIMB ENHANCERS!
WHERE ARE MY LIMB ENHANCERS?!
AWW! YOU'RE LIKE
AN ANGRY LITTLE SLICE OF PIE.
STOP TALKING.
I DEMAND TO KNOW WHAT
THIS PLACE IS AND WHERE I --
OH, MY STARS.
YOU'RE GOING TO HARVEST ME?
NO.
I-I MEAN...
OW! THAT HURT!
IT DID?
YEAH. A LOT.
OW!
YES!
FEEL MY UNBRIDLED RAGE!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
HEY!
HEY, HEY.
WHAT'S THAT
ON YOUR SHIRT?
WHAT'S A SHIRT?
OW!
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S IT!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
WHY ARE YOU ACTING
LIKE THIS?
YOU SMASHED ME
INTO A LIMBLESS CLOUD!
YOU TRAPPED ME
IN YOUR BUBBLE DUNGEON!
AND YOU CALLED ME CUTE!
NYAH!
I DIDN'T POOF YOU.
I FREED YOU.
WHY WOULD YOU MAKE
SUCH A MISCALCULATION?
BACK AT THE WARP PAD,
WHAT WERE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
WHY DO WE NEED YOU?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
WHAT DO I KNOW?
EVERYTHING THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT THE CLUSTER, YOU PEBBLE.
CLUSTER?
WAIT, PEBBLE?
MY MISSION,
THE REASON WHY I'M ON THIS
SAD ROCK IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I WAS TO CHECK PROGRESS
ON THE CLUSTER.
JUST IN AND OUT
BEFORE IT HATCHES.
I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO GET STUCK HERE.
BUT NOW IT'S GOING TO EMERGE
AND NOTHING CAN STOP IT,
AND WE'LL ALL BE SHATTERED!
OKAY, OKAY.
WAIT, SLOW DOWN.
NOW, FROM THE TOP.
EMERGING,
HATCHING CLUSTERS.
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
YES.
YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
WHAT'S YOUR SHIRT?
THESE ARE
MY BANANA PAJAMAS.
OW!
WAIT, DON'T RUN AWAY!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
NYAH!
[ LAUGHING ]
STOP!
THEY'RE GONNA SEE YOU!
FREEDOM IS MINE!
WAIT!
LOOK, OVER THERE!
ANOTHER PLANET TO BETRAY!
[ CHOMPS ]
RETREAT!
OH, NO YOU DON'T!
EEP!
HEY.
AAAH!
AAH!
GET HER!
YOU MAY HAVE WON
THE WAR,
BUT THE BATTLE ISN'T OVER,
CRYSTAL CLODS!
[ LAUGHS ]
SHOULD WE TELL HER
THAT'S THE BATHROOM?
EH.
HMM.
SEEMS I DISCOVERED SOME
SORT OF ARCHAIC THINK CHAMBER.
ROOMY, WITH A FRESH HINT
OF EARTH CITRUS.
A PERFECT CROSSROADS
FOR MY ESCAPE.
IT'S LOCKED.
PERIDOT,
OPEN THE DOOR.
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
UH, IF YOU'RE TRYING TO
FLUSH YOURSELF DOWN THE TOILET,
IT WON'T WORK.
TRUST ME.
I'VE TRIED.
HOW DID SHE GET OUT?
WE BUBBLED HER.
MAYBE WE NEEDED
A BIGGER BUBBLE.
MY BUBBLES ARE FINE.
I DID IT.
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN,
WHY WOULD YOU DO SUCH A THING?
BECAUSE SHE KNOWS SOMETHING,
SOMETHING THAT'S MADE HER
SCARED.
DUH. HOMEGIRL KNOWS WE'RE GONNA
BEAT HER INTO A GREEN PANCAKE.
NO, NOT 'CAUSE OF US.
'CAUSE OF SOMETHING CALLED
"THE CLUSTER."
CLUSTER?
THAT'S NEW.
WHAT ELSE
DID SHE TELL YOU?
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
THAT'S RIGHT, YOU DIRT BOMBS.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S COMING.
OH!
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING
THESE GAMES.
IF WE CAN'T FIGHT HER,
THEN FINE.
WE'LL TALK.
PERIDOT!
WHOA!
ALL RIGHT,
NO MORE FIGHTING.
LET'S JUST HAVE
A CIVIL CONVERSATION.
AS IF I'D NEGOTIATE WITH YOU,
FILTHY WAR MACHINE!
OKAY,
LET'S KICK HER BUTT.
WAIT!
Peridot:
YEAH, DESTROY ME AGAIN.
AND HAVE FUN TRYING TO TALK
TO ME WHEN I'M IN A BUBBLE.
[ GRUNTS ]
I REALLY HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
IF SHE HAS INFORMATION, SHE'S
MORE VALUABLE TO US LIKE THIS.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
TRICKY.
[ SHOWER RUNS ]
Peridot:
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT!
YOU HAVE TO TURN THE KNOB
THE OTHER WAY FOR COLD.
WAIT, SO WE'RE JUST GONNA
LET HER LIVE IN MY BATHROOM?
WELL, YES.
WHAT OTHER OPTION DO WE HAVE?
KEEP HER OUTSIDE
ON A LEASH?
[ LAUGHS ]
HMM.
BUT I NEED TO USE
THE BATHROOM.
RIGHT NOW?
YEAH, KINDA.
JUST GO IN THE OCEAN, BRO.
PSSSH!
LIKE A FISH.
WHAT'S WITH YOU GUYS
AND MAKING ME PEE OUTSIDE?
WELL,
I HAVE FUN DOING IT.
OH, BUT EVEN IF WE DO GET HER
TO COME OUT OF THE BATHROOM...
SHE'S NEVER GONNA
TALK TO US.
[ YAWNS ]
Garnet: LOOKS LIKE THERE'S NOT
MUCH ELSE WE CAN DO RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE HER IN...
PERIDOT, CAN I COME IN?
I NEED TO GET READY FOR THE DAY.
Peridot: NO.
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
Garnet: IF IT HAS ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE EXPERIMENT
SHE WAS CONDUCTING
IN THE KINDERGARTEN, THEN VERY.
WHAT A GREAT SOUVENIR OF THAT
OTHER TIME YOU ASSAULTED ME.
OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
I CAN TAKE IT BACK.
NO, IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO HAVE THE REST?
UH, SORRY.
WE LOST THEM.
WELL,
WE KIND OF THREW THEM AWAY.
CAN YOU PASS ME THAT?
IS THIS A WEAPON?
ONLY FOR CAVITIES.
HMM.
THANKS.
IS THAT A WEAPON?
NO.
THAT'S A COMB I NEVER USE.
IS THAT A WEAPON?
HMM? OH, WELL, I GUESS IF
YOU GET IT WET AND ROLL IT UP.
AAH!
LOOK,
I KNOW YOU'RE SCARED,
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO HURT YOU.
AND WHATEVER'S GOING ON,
WHATEVER THE CLUSTER IS,
I WANT TO HELP.
I DOUBT
YOU CAN HELP ME.
BUT I...
APPRECIATE THE OFFER.
NOW, DO YOU MIND MOVING?
I HAVE TO USE THAT.
FOR WHAT?
♪ I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I MIGHT BE BAD ♪
♪ NOW I'M SURE OF IT,
IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I THINK YOU'RE SO GOOD,
AND I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU ♪