♪♪
-(bagpipes playing)
-(Scrooge groaning)
(Flintheart groaning)
(intensified angry groaning)
Are we going
to the store, or...
Quiet. I'm in the middle
of a Vision Beast
battle of wills.
So, it's
a staring contest?
It's not just
a staring contest!
It's a-- (gasps)
Nice try, McDuck,
but your family bickering
will never get me
to look away, never!
It's a staring contest.
Excuse me, this area
of the Duckburg
Billionaires' Club
is only for
our elite members,
the crème de la crème,
the finest ducks in Duckburg!
(gasps) Is that--?
Yup.
Old guys, nice clubhouse
you've got here.
Got a real "I'm so rich
I don't care how I look"
quality about it.
-Rich peeps! I'm tagging us.
-(phone clicks)
I'm sorry,
who are you?
Seriously?
Mark Beaks?
Founder and CEO
of Waddle?
Soon-to-be newest addition
to the of the Duckburg
Billionaires' Club, come on!
-Meh!
-And creator
of the newest tech innovation,
Project Tahdah!
It's everything you think it is
and nothing you're expecting.
I'll flip you my Peep deets
so you can follow my updates.
I don't understand
half those words.
Whoa, weird.
I wouldn't have thought
you successful guys
would be so behind
the times.
Allow me to take you
to the future.
(bagpipe remix playing)
Remix!
Pew! Pew pew pew pew!
Pew a-roo!
Wait for it.
Wait for it!
(beat drops)
Ohh!
That was Mark Beaks!
He's right in there!
Oh, man, I'm almost breathing
the same air as him.
(sniffing)
Oh, ingenuity.
Come on,
like I couldn't be
a young, influential
business guy?
(sighing laugh)
What?
Oh. Oh!
You were serious?
It's just you're more
the crazy,
irresponsible, fun guy
than the serious,
brilliant, successful guy.
You don't know!
At least I'm not the guy
who just reads about people
who do stuff guy.
I could be a bigger deal
than Beaks in three years, tops!
(crashing, clinks)
I'll pay for that
in three years.
I am very sorry.
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck blur ♪
♪ Might solve a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Duck Tales
Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do,
bad and good luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks
behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do,
just grab onto some Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do,
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
nor cottontails ♪
♪ They're Duck Tales
Whoo-ooh ♪
(heavy door opens)
MARK: Keep making
dat money, y'all!
See you in $2 million
and counting!
Stuck up old money-duddies.
Don't even have
a social media presence.
Mr. Beaks, I'm Dewey,
future astronaut president--
Can you sign this?
You're my hero and a genius!
Genius? You two, I like
how much you like me!
That shows real smarts!
Come by the offices
and I'll hook you up
with a tour.
Maybe even
an after-school job?
Pew pew pew
pew pew pew pew!
Pew! Pew pew-pew!
-You mean it?!
-Sure. Why not.
Amazing sauce.
I'll text you.
Internship
starts mañana!
Ach... (grumbling)
What, did you
say something?
I was just grumbling.
Well, do it louder.
Then it's not grumbling!
Gah, I hate this music.
We've got to do something
about New Guy.
I never had Lou's Pie.
No, New Guy!
Oh, agreed!
Let's get rid of him!
Great. Now I want pie!
(ding)
Wait, no!
Hah! See you
tomorrow, Flinty.
(grunts)
HUEY: Let's see.
Can Do Attitude, check.
Professional posture... check.
Completed checklist, check.
Wow, I can't believe
we get to be interns
at Waddle for Mark Beaks!
Yeah, I'm mostly doing it
to show off this bad boy.
-What is that?
-Oh, this?
It's my super serious
business briefcase.
"What brilliant
business secrets
is he hiding
in there?"
Who knows?!
You can't open
the lock, can you?
Nope.
Welcome to Waddle,
where imagination
and innovation
get married
and have babies!
(beeps)
Digital high-five app,
so you never get
left hanging,
or, you know,
have to touch anyone.
Come, roll with Beaks.
Here are
the high-impact trampolines,
the low-impact trampolines,
and, of course,
the no-impact trampolines.
Those are fun.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Slides are the new stairs.
Ha! That's actually
pretty cool!
If, by cool, you mean
statistically proven
to increase
employee productivity.
Huh! This guy.
Oh, before you ask,
yeah, it's all
made of candy.
You're welcome.
Ooh, wow!
Who knew work
could be so awesome?
Mark Beaks did. Blamo!
He talks the way
I want to live!
Here are your official
Waddle trainee beanies.
Congratulations, weenies!
Oh, P.S., there's only space
for one intern,
so one of you is going home
by the end of the day.
Cool? Cool. Beaks out!
One internship?!
Well, hehe, you didn't
really want it anyway,
so I'll just tell
Mr. Beaks to give it to me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Sliding my way to billions?
Licking
other people's stuff?
It's everything I never knew
I always wanted!
I am in!
This is about more
than just goofing around.
Whee!
You're doing it wrong.
This is supposed to be
efficient, not fun.
(unenthused) Whee.
Ha! I'm about to be
a billionaire!
And when Scrooge tries
to follow me online,
I'll block him.
Man, you are killing it
today, Beaks!
GUARD (muffled): Sir,
you can't go in there!
(blows landing, groaning)
Stop right there!
Ooh, neat!
-(beeps)
-(groans)
Mr. Beaks, allow me
to introduce myself.
Falcon Graves, professional
corporate saboteur and--
Professional is right, man!
That suit game is on point.
(sighs) As I was saying,
unfortunately for you,
I've been hired to steal
your coveted Project Tahdah.
-(phone clicks)
-What are you doing?
I'm just updating
my status to "hostage."
Feel like this could be huge
for my online presence.
Oh, uh, were you not done
with your speech?
Get me to Research
& Development.
Hey, let him go. Aah!
Immediately.
[techno music playing]
Turn that nonsense off!
I already tried.
It's impossible.
[beeps]
Well, how was I supposed
to know the "On" button
and the "Off" button
were the same button?
Did you sleep here
last night?
Don't be ridiculous.
Who can sleep when you're
plotting against a nemesis?
That cocky Mark Beaks
may be the only man I hate
as much as you!
I know the feeling.
So now I propose
we get rid of him.
Do we really need
a slideshow?
Ha! Sweet, naive Scroogy.
Leave the devious planning
to the professionals.
You're in
my world now, McDuck.
Yeah, all right.
Show me what you've got.
No, you're actually
on my side of the room.
Ooh, task lists!
This is a place of dreams!
Oh, I don't know, Dewey,
this looks like
a whole bunch of boring
business-guy tasks.
You're not really equipped
to handle them, so...
And lose this internship
to you? No way!
This place
has free snow cones!
Free snow cones!
(beeps)
(phone ringing)
Thank you for calling Waddle.
Please hold.
Please hold. Please hold.
-Waddle.
-DEWEY: Yup, yeah, no.
I totally get it.
I hate talking
on the phone, too,
so that's why
I kick my feet up,
I'm leaning back...
Who are you talking to?
Oh, uh...
Business-man-ning-ton-son?
-(dial tone)
-Oh, you just missed him!
Okay. One sandwich cut
diagonally with no crusts,
no pickles, but yes
to pickles on the side,
so you can decide
which pickles to use.
I got pizza!
Everybody loves pizza!
(chanting) New guy! New guy!
But I'm also
the new guy...
There's the high-impact
trampolines,
the low-impact trampolines...
Mr. Beaks, is the tour
really necessary?
Listen, Graves,
if we're gonna keep
this hostage stuff on the DL,
I gotta act natural.
(louder) And naturally,
I give tours
of my awesome company!
Must I wear the hat?
You bet. All trainees
gotta wear the hat,
and you are
a trainee, right?
Boop!
Complimentary snow cone?
Oops, you dropped it.
Here's another.
How 'bout blueberry?
Ah, good call, that one
stains your mouth forever.
-Look, see? Ahh...
-You do realize
you're in quite a lot
of danger right now.
I know! I'm gonna be
trending online for days!
Hostage selfie!
Backup phones.
(groans)
Excuse me, Mr. Beaks.
I just tagged
us together. 'Sup?
Mr. Beaks, here's
my completed, color-coded,
and categorized checklist.
I even made
some categories for--
I ordered
everybody pizza.
So who would you say
is in the lead
for the internship?
Oh, uh,
I guess you're tied.
-(techno music plays)
-Oh, mandatory dance break!
Whoo-whoo!
Pew pew! Chicka-pew!
And, lo, he shall pay
for his arrogance
as his world
crumbles around him
and Beaks will rue the day
he heard the name
Flintheart Glomgold!
-(thunder crashing)
-(maniacal laughter)
(startles)
Oh, and Scrooge McDuck,
I guess.
(yawns)
Ooh, are you finished?
What? Every evil plot starts
with a "Declaration
of Hatred" speech.
Oh, you have
so much to learn.
Great. Now, can we talk
about the actual plan?
I thought you'd never ask!
I asked
several hours ago!
Behold.
Our scheme to destroy Beaks
begins with an invitation
to a Billionaires' Convention
on a yacht.
We'll tell him we're going,
but then we won't show!
First slam!
Seems unnecessary,
especially the part
about the yacht.
Emotionally devastated,
Beaks will seek solace
and drown his sorrows
at the buffet.
A yacht and a buffet
for one person?
I'm not paying for that.
Fine. We'll use
my yacht.
Now, distracted
by delicious shrimp,
Beaks won't realize he's being
sailed into an active volcano,
where it'll get so hot
he'll jump
into the yacht's pool,
which, unbeknownst to him,
will be filled with sharks!
Where did
the sharks come from?
I've got a great shark guy.
Beaks will be so terrified
by the sharks,
he'll forget
he's in a volcano
and jump blindly
into the lava!
All while we watch
from a bridge above.
Wait, wait, I though
we wanted to boot him
out of our club,
not kill him!
Although you have tried
to kill me countless times,
which usually ends up
being more annoying
than deadly.
That's right,
I'm a genius.
Now, pay attention,
'cause this is where
it gets complicated.
Ooh...
♪♪
Listen, I got
your most important task yet.
Getting my 2:15 artisanal
cold-pressed coffee.
Now, I want
almond-infused foam,
not almonds in my foam.
Infused foam,
understood?
Coffee
with stuff, got it!
You don't even know
where it is!
-[both] Come on, come on...
-HUEY: Almost there.
Here's another
XL Waddle T-shirt,
a bunch of Waddle yo-yos,
and a Waddle jetpack.
(whispers) Don't try it.
It's super broken.
(panting) Beaks,
coffee! Winner!
Oh, I-- ahem.
I'm sorry, why am I getting
my 2:15 coffee at 2:14?
I didn't get an email
about it moving up.
-Hello.
-Just take the coffee!
I didn't become
an almost-billionaire
by having coffee
at random times of the day
like some commoner!
There's an order to things,
my order, and I--
Mr. Beaks, I have
your 2:15 coffee
at exactly 2:15.
Ooh, yummy!
Man, things got real
for a second
back there, right?
How is this
not very real?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
one sec.
Kid, what's your name?
Huey, sir.
Ooh, don't love it.
How about brand-new Waddle
intern Huey!
Ha-ha!
Achieve dream. Check.
(huffs) Now, can we finally
get to Project Tahdah?
Whoa, is that
an ironically fancy briefcase
in my super-chill
work environment?
Uh... yes.
What's going on in there,
like, brilliant
business secrets?
You know it!
Very chill.
Oh, I like how you roll!
You are my new Vice President
of Fancy Business.
Intern, you report
to him now. Boom.
Beaks out!
-What?!
-Yes!
Faked it,
maked it!
I didn't even know this was
my life's dream until today.
But-- but-- how did I win
and still lose?
I worked so hard
and had so many
completed checklists.
Do you need me
to get a briefcase?
'Cause I can go get one
and then become
the Vice President
of Being Chill!
'Cause I'm chill.
I'm straight chilling.
Like a villain, even!
Oh, no, Huey's broken.
Or I could be Chief Manager
of Being Broken!
'Cause anyone
can just be anything!
Look at me, everybody,
now I'm the Duke
of Making a Mess!
(growling)
Watch out for the Duke!
Mr. Beaks,
is everything okay?
Uh, this again.
(cracks knuckles)
(blows landing, grunting)
Oh, I missed that last punch.
Could you prop him back up
and do it again?
No more games.
You're all my captives now.
You, Vice President,
take me to Project Tahdah!
Yes, of course. Sure.
Um...
Seriously?
It's that way.
Of course it's that way.
Sorry, it's my first day,
but, eh, let's go this way.
Huh!
Welcome to the cutting edge
of the latest technology.
See that in the air?
What is that?
It's called magic!
Open the vault!
-Now!
-Ugh, fine! I'll
(imitating Graves) "finally
take you to Project Tahdah."
Blech! Ugh.
-(beeping)
-(tumblers clicking)
Menacing man,
small children,
prepare yourselves
for my greatest invention.
(whirring)
What? Nothing?
Everything you think it is,
and nothing you're expecting!
You got
the nothing part right.
So, Project Tahdah
is a hoax?
Tahdah!
I build hype
for a fake product,
everyone invests
in my company,
kablam, I'm a billionaire!
This is ridiculous.
I'm calling my employer.
-(dialing)
-(ringing)
Go for Beaks.
(growls)
You've got to be kidding me!
Why would you hire me to steal
something that doesn't exist?
So he gets to say
Project Tahdah was stolen,
but he still keeps
the money!
See? Fancy Business
gets it.
Why actually put in
the hard work
of inventing something
when I can just tell
everybody I did?
Fake it till you
make it, right?
(chimes)
And become a billionaire!
Ba-bam!
Just crossed the mark.
Aw, count them zeroes!
One, two, three,
four, five--
Bah, I'm bored.
You get it.
And it's all thanks
to you, bud.
Get over here,
Selfington!
(growls)
I can't believe
I looked up to you.
You and your whole company
are as fake as Project Tahdah.
Maybe, but the money
and the buzz
are very, very real.
I just got
so many followers!
-Pah!
-Gravesy, there's a helicopter
waiting for you
on the roof.
You know what?
Keep the beanie.
I do not like being lied to!
Oh, this is fun.
Where we going?
To the roof...
So I can toss you off it!
Oh! Mwah, mwah, mwah.
Who loves being a pawn
in my twisted evil plots?
You! Yes, you do!
Why on earth should
we ever need this?
Well, how else is Beaks
going to know
he's at the Annual
Carrot Festival?!
You clearly didn't
understand the plan.
Let's start
from the beginning.
-Behold, our--
-No!
"Backstabbing Scrooge,
version 3..."
What's this?
Oh, i-it's nothing.
This whole thing
is a trap for me, isn't it?
What?! No...
Of course not.
Your new best friend
would never...
No, stay right there.
Uh, heh, thank goodness
you moved at the last minute,
or you would've been
destroyed by the axe.
How long have you
been planning that one?
More than six months?
I don't want to say.
I can't believe
I wasted a whole day
obsessing over someone
I don't like,
and it nearly
got me killed!
Who am I, you? Ugh!
Have fun
with your new nemesis.
I'm gonna go beat you both
by actually being
a better billionaire.
(techno music plays)
BEAKS (narrating): "Help.
Project Tahdah was stolen
and now I'm going
to be tossed off the roof."
Oh, should I add a sad face,
or is that too much?
(growls)
Oh, ground.
Dude, not cool!
-That's my last backup phone!
-Yes!
(exclamations
from Beaks and Graves)
We've gotta save Beaks.
Right? I mean,
he's the worst,
but it's
the right thing to do.
Why? I'm sure
your biggest,
favorite friend
will just fake
his way through it
like everything else.
Okay, first off,
that's not what BFF stands for.
And secondly, guys like him,
guys like me,
we have to put on
a show and fake it
because smart guys like you
are so good at making it.
We don't need this.
What we need
is a checklist.
In fact, here's a checklist
for how to get through this.
One, get a plan.
Two, ask Huey for a plan.
Three, do you have
a plan yet?
'Cause honestly I don't know
how checklists work!
I got it.
HUEY: Hey, Graves,
over here!
DEWEY: Wha?!
This is dumb.
I hate this plan.
Ha-ha, I win!
Oh, gross!
Your dumb fingerprints
smudged my screen.
(huffs)
Now, go be Dewey.
Aaah!
Take this!
And all of these!
(grunting)
Time out!
We have to take off
these stupid hats.
It's humiliating.
Tight end!
Nyah!
Dewey, whatever you do,
do not tell Graves
what's in the briefcase!
What is in the briefcase?
Oh, this briefcase?
Just a bunch of fancy business
secrets, very hush-hush.
You see the lock?
Give me that.
What's the code?
-Try 1111.
-No.
-Mmkay, 2222?
Right,
of course not. 3333.
Oh, now you're
just guessing.
Have you tried
the factory default?
Of course I have--
Oh...kay.
(slowed-down scream)
Doink. Ah.
Oh, that's it, I'm done!
And I'm untagging myself
from all those photos!
(laughs) That's
gotta be $20 million!
Where did you get
a briefcase full of money?
Next to the suit of armor
in the Billionaires' Club.
That place needs
better security.
'Sup over here?
Uh, we saved your life.
Right. Hey, so obviously
I have to fire you guys
because you know the secret
of Project Tahdah,
and if you tell anybody
I'll just say you're lying
because you're mad I
fired you. Cool? Cool-cool.
"My face looks
like a butt."
And... sent.
Seriously, that's
your big plan?
Who even cares
about what--
It already has 1,000 likes!
What? No! No!
I can't delete it now!
Give it back!
(opera aria plays)
(slowed-down scream)
Hah! Me and my phone
are fine!
(laughs) We totally crushed
that fall!
Aw, man!
Letter for billionaire
Mark Beaks.
Aha, that's me!
Oh, an invite
to a Billionaires' Convention
on a yacht.
Awesometown,
population Beaks.
I still get to be
a Duckburg billionaire.
And everything
that comes with it.
Get the sharks ready.
-(thunder crashing)
-(maniacal laughter)