Alice: 'Twas a single day left
before Hearth's Warming Eve.
Every pony was busy!
So much to achieve.
They hustled and bustled,
their heads were a-spin
And it's here that our
Holiday story begins.
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
Is almost here ♪
♪ There's so much left to do ♪
♪ Still need to shop
for all my friends ♪
♪ But what to get, no clue! ♪
♪ This one is nice
and that's so cute ♪
♪ Although, that's
pretty too ♪
♪ Why do I make all these
gifts each year? ♪
♪ I doubt I'll make
it through ♪
♪ One more day ♪
♪ Before the cheer ♪
♪ Shop Bake Box
Wrap Bow Repeat ♪
♪ One last chance ♪
♪ Before the Holiday's here ♪
♪ Box Wrap Bow Again! ♪
♪ One more day to make
the Holiday great ♪
♪ One more day before
we celebrate ♪
♪ One day and
then it's here ♪
♪ One more chance to bring
back Holiday Cheer ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
Is almost here ♪
♪ A day for us to share ♪
♪ Friends and Family
all together ♪
♪ Pies, Apples and a Pear ♪
♪ Together family plots
the work. There's so
much to prepare ♪
♪ With all the planning
we still have to do, ♪
♪ We've got no time to spare ♪
♪ One more day ♪
♪ Before the cheer ♪
♪ Stuff Box Wrap
Card Bow Repeat ♪
♪ One last chance ♪
♪ Before the Holiday's here ♪
♪ Stir Pour Bake Again! ♪
♪ One more day to make
the Holiday bright ♪
♪ One more day and I
can sleep at night. ♪
♪ The family's almost here! ♪
♪ One more chance to bring
back Holiday cheer! ♪
♪ Before the fun
there's preparations ♪
♪ just around the corner
Shopping, cooking ♪
♪ decorations and
complications ♪
♪ It's all worth it
in the end ♪
♪ spreading joy to
all your friends! ♪
♪ Even when it never ever
ever seems to end. Aaah! ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve
is getting close ♪
♪ We're not prepared, I fear. ♪
♪ Twilight? You
should take a break. ♪
♪ No time for rest,
that much is clear! ♪
♪ I made a list and
checked it twice ♪
♪ There's LOTS to do on here. ♪
♪ Oh, if I can't get
everything done, ♪
♪ I'll have to wait and
celebrate next year. ♪
♪ One more day ♪
♪ Before the cheer ♪
♪ Shop Cake Box
Wrap Bow Repeat ♪
♪ One last chance ♪
♪ before the Holiday's here, ♪
♪ Box Wrap Bow Again! ♪
♪ One more day to make
the Holiday great ♪
♪ One more day until we
celebrate ♪
♪ Please oh please make
it really really great ♪
♪ One more gift try to
hurry don't be late ♪
♪ Box Wrap Bow Repeat
Gotta concentrate! ♪
♪ Just one more day
until we all celebrate! ♪
Gah. Do we want to know why you're
wrapping up everypony in town?
Not wrapping paper.
A to-do list.
Two of these. Three of those...
Maybe ten of those.
Just in case.
Twilight, darling,
are you all right?
Sure! Just grabbing
a few things.
Do I need this? No. That's
silly. I need EIGHT!
Hey y'all! What's
everypony...? Oh.
Traditional
holiday meltdown?
Uh huh.
Hey, Twilight.
How's your day?
I got way behind
grading midterms.
And Cadance and Shining
Armor are coming here
with Flurry Heart for
Hearth's Warming Eve.
And I haven't
started decorating
and I don't know what
to get any of you, and--
Stop. Take a breath...
Now let it out slow.
Now, I think I have an
idea that might help.
What if we change up how
we give gifts this year
and do a Hearth's
Warmin' Helper?
What's a Hearth's
Warming Helper?
Whenever the whole Apple
Family got together,
there were just so many of us,
it didn't make sense
to buy everypony gifts.
So we'd put our
names in a hat...
Oooo! A game of
chance! Tell me more.
Then we'd pull a name,
but keep it a secret!
A dash of mystery.
Good. Good.
Instead of buyin'
everypony a present,
you just get one for the pony
you picked from the hat!
Wait. So instead of
lots of presents,
I only buy one of
you a present?
WHAT KIND OF GAME
IS THIS?
Well, it would
save time.
And you could get the pony you
pick something really nice...
Ahem.
The less shopping
the better! In!
Will that help, Twilight?
I WAS stressed
about shopping..
[groan] Fine. I will only
buy one present
for my secret Hearth's
Warming Helper buddy.
We just need to put
everypony's name
in this here hat.
Y'all ready?
No peekin'!
SO. Excited. Ah!
Too excited!
I don't want to
give anything away!
Whee!
When will the gift
exchange occur?
How about.. Twilight's
castle tomorrow night?
Hearth's Warming Eve!
That's perfect! Pinkie and
I can spend the evening
with y'all and the next
morning with our families!
And thanks to
all of you,
I should be ready to
celebrate by then!
Oh, this is so exciting!
Uh... Um, Applejack? Is it against
the rules to trade names?
Like if I had a better
idea for somepony special?
I mean, specific?
If you can figure out who
has the pony you want,
and they're OK with tradin',
I guess it's fine.
Great! So uh...
who do you-
I don't have Rarity.
What? That's
not who I--
Uh-huh.
Hey, Twilight!
Whatcha plannin' to
get your secret pony?
Not sure. I'm getting
the castle ready
for my family first.
Then I'll shop.
Maybe something
sparkly? Fashionable?
No. Those aren't really the
kind of things my pony likes.
Oh. Well, gotta
go! Wish me luck!
With shopping..?
Well, yeah! If every pony's
only getting one gift,
we have a ton of responsibility
to make sure it's
extra special good!
I.. didn't think
of it that way.
The present I get
for Pinkie Pie
should make or
break her holiday!
I can't just go shopping and
hope to find something nice.
This needs forethought,
planning, research!
I'll decorate later.
Knowing Pinkie, she probably
already has a perfect idea
what to get her pony!
I have no idea what
to get my pony!
There's a pile of
presents right there.
Pick one and you're done.
Those were for when I was
getting all of my friends
matching harmony
Hearth's Warming hats!
Now it's just Twilight!
I can't give one pony
a matching present
with nothing to match it!
I need something
special for only her!
I've got it.
I don't think Twilight likes
rocks as much as you do, Maud.
Don't rock it till you try it.
Thanks for the vote
of confidence, Gummy,
but this is the biggest
holiday challenge
I've ever faced!
Uh, this one's for you.
Hey! This is the biggest
holiday challenge
I've ever faced! HOW
EXCITING IS THAT?
Am I up for the challenge? I
know I'm good at gift-giving.
But am I the best
at gift giving?
Who would say they're
the best at gift giving?
That's ridiculous.
Uh-
Marble, you're a genius!
Yaks would say they're
the best at gift giving!
If anypony knows what
to do, it's them.
I gotta go to Yakyakistan!
Thanks, these Pie sister
talks are the best!
Pinkie!
I don't have Rarity!
Woah!
Oh! Heh. How's your
shopping going, Spike?
Uh. Fine.
Which pony did you get?
I...can't remember?
I've got Applejack, darling.
She's going to
adore her present.
There's a brilliant
designer in Manehattan,
Fedora Felt, who makes
the most marvelous hats!
I asked for a new take on
western chic that would be
the envy of every
farmpony in Equestria.
That's a great gift, Rarity.
I hope I can find something for
my pony as special as you are...
She is. Uh, bye!
OK, what about
your favorite food?
Oh, I couldn't
pick just one.
What if it hurt the
other foods' feelings?
Right.... But there's
gotta be something
you really really like!
I really really like...
everything! Why do you ask?
Just...getting gift ideas.
For my pony. Who isn't you.
So... is there anything
you don't like?
Hm. Not liking things.
Grrr.
I hope that helped!
Hey, Fluttershy.
Thinking of getting that for
your Hearth's Warming helper?
Mm-hm. She loves
shiny things.
I wish I knew what my
secret pony wanted.
She's so hard to shop for...
Oh, no. Maybe I could help.
Unless you don't want to-
Rainbow Dash.
Oh! I was just talking to
Rainbow Dash about things we-
Great idea! We
SHOULD trade ponies!
Wait. Trade?
Well, Applejack said it's
not against the rules.
And you know what Rainbow
Dash likes, so it's perfect!
[gasp] Rarity? What. A.
Surprise! Thanks!
There you are. I
need your help!
Do you want to
trade names too?
What? No.
I just need help figurin'
out what to get Spike.
Phew!
Candle. Great. Whatever.
Fluttershy shopping done.
Oh! You can't honestly be serious?
Ghost candle!
A candle is what you buy
when you have no idea
what to get somepony.
Ugh. What do you
want, Discord?
Fluttershy told me about this
hearth-whatever-it's-called.
I may not be invited,
but I wanted to make sure
she gets a quality gift.
I tried asking her
what she likes,
but she likes everything!
Well, she says that...
But her REAL friends know
what she actually likes.
I've known her a lot
longer than you have.
Then you must surely
know that lit candles
around adorably flammable
animals make her nervous.
Don't you?
Fine. I'll get her
something else..
Perhaps I'll
tag along.
To steer you in the
right direction.
Whoa!
I can't wait to give
Rarity her gift.
It'll be just as
special and beautiful
and amazing as she is!
Just imagine when she
opens it and sees...
Uh... sees...
I have no idea
what to get her!
I come to the Rainbow Falls
Hearth's Warming craft
fair every year.
They have perfect
presents for anypony!
Hopefully anydragon too.
Wanna split up? Meet
back here in an hour?
Sure.
Oh, no! There's
only a few left!
Fillies and gentlecolts!
We want you all to
have the best holiday
your bits can buy!
But there are only a
limited number left!
Limited number of what?
Why, you don't know about
Holly the Hearthwarmer?
You seem like somepony
looking for a gift
for a very
special friend!
I am!
A friend who wouldn't want to
miss out on the must-have gift
everypony is talking about?
She certainly wouldn't
want to miss out on that!
A truly awesome friend who
deserves something 20% cooler
than any other gift out there?
That sounds just like her!
Well, look no
further. This. Is. It!
Oh, oh! How much does it cost?
How much do you have?
Yojan! Is that good angle
for optimal smashing?
Guess who!
Yojan!?
No, silly!
Yngvild!? Tormund!? Grunhorn!
Nopety nope and nien
and nyet! It's me!
Aw, Prince Rutherford knew
it pink pony all along.
Yaks best at guessing!
Yaks best at everything!
That's why I'm here!
Sorry to interrupt Snilldar
Fest, but I need help.
Can you tell me where
to find... BEST GIFT EVER?
Not here. Follow this way.
Prince Rutherford about to
tell honorary yak friend
something very top secret.
Honorary yak friend listening!
Yaks best at all
things except one!
Yaks not best at giving gifts.
[gasp] What!?
I know! It hard
to believe.
How am I gonna figure
out how to get Twilight
the best Hearth's
Warming gift ever!?
Oh, no worry,
honorary yak.
Prince Rutherford
keep secret map
in perfectly
organized files.
Best gift givers
up northern pass,
where sky shimmers
and glows.
There, secret gift
giver grove.
Only yak princes and
pink honorary yak know.
My lips are sealed!
TIME FOR MY TOP-SECRET
QUEST TO THE GIFT GIVERS!
Oh, hi Rarity! How
can I help you?
I expected a package today,
and I was wondering
where that might be.
Oh, OK. Uh, let's
check. Name?
Uh, Rarity?
Hm.
Oh! Here we go.
Your package was delivered
to Sweet Apple Acres.
What!? It was supposed
to be delivered
to Rarity's Boutique!
Um, OK but now the
package was for Applejack,
and she is at
Sweet Apple Acres.
Yes, it's FOR Applejack,
but I will be delivering it.
That's my job.
It's a gift for
Applejack from.. me.
[gasp] What if she opens it!?
It shouldn't go to
Sweet Apple Acres!
Oh! Wait. It went to Sweet
Acorn Orchard instead.
[giggle] Oh! That's a relief!
WHY is that a relief?
Because Applejack's not
in Sweet Acorn Orchard.
Do you want me to get the
package and deliver it to her?
No! [ahem] May I
have the address
for Sweet Acorn Orchard?
I think I'll just collect
the package myself.
Are you sure? Cause
I would be happy to--
You have helped
so much already.
Break time!
Shopping for Rarity.
No problem.
She likes lots of stuff. I just
need something extra special.
Brand new top of the
line sewing equipment?
A priceless rhinestone necklace?
A sculpture of Rarity
made from smaller
sculptures of Rarity?
[gasp] Oh! Wow! Awesome!
Shopping for Rarity.
Slight problem.
She likes lots of stuff. But
nothing is special enough!
Oh, goodness, no.
Even worse.
Oh, come on! Fluttershy
would love a spa day!
Really?
Love the stress of deciding
which treatment to get?
Love worrying that she's
not relaxing enough?
Or relaxing too much?
And what about all those sweet
animals she's left alone?
So much to worry about
and all because of you!
She's Fluttershy!
Everything makes her worry!
Now you sound like
somepony who knows her!
Well, if you're such an
expert on Fluttershy,
what did YOU get her?
Oh, and you honestly
expect me to tell you
what I got Fluttershy so
that you can one up me?
Well, I have half a mind to
stop helping you entirely!
Good! Please stop helping
me! I'm begging you!
Well, I suppose I
could tell you
what my back-up
present was.
Great. Still helping...
It would have made
a lovely addition
to her animal sanctuary.
But you'd have to be the
fastest pony in Equestria
to even have a chance of-
Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
You're talking to the
fastest pony in Equestria!
If there's some fast
animal out there
Fluttershy would love, I'm
the one who can get it.
Oh, I just don't know...
I'm calling it! Dibs!
If you insist.
The ideal gift for Pinkie
Pie needs to be a) unique,
b) specific to her personality
and c) food-based.
What is a unique food?
Cupcakes? Nah. Cookies? Nope.
Pies? Pastries?
Pudding? [gasp] Wait! PUDDING!
After defeating the windigos,
the Earth Pony, Pegasi
and Unicorn nations
prepared the first Hearth's
Warming meal together.
Chancellor Puddinghead made
a pudding so delicious,
legends were written about it!
This is it! Unique.
Totally Pinkie!
The most incredible
dessert ever!
Where's the recipe!?
I've narrowed down my
choices for Spike to
fire-dancin' sticks or
a Power Ponies comic.
Un-enchanted. I think.
Aaah! What
is that!?
Holly the Hearth's Warmer
doll. Isn't she sweet?
"I love being an expensive toy!"
Ugh. Why'd you think THAT was a
good gift for Rainbow Dash?
It's the must-have gift of the
season! And in short supply!
Short supply, huh? How
much did that set ya back?
All my bits.
All my bits! Can I borrow
some for the train ride home?
Something about this
here doll seems fishy,
and I ain't just talking about
the smell of that plastic.
Where'd you get it?
Flim and Flam!
What are those two Hearth's
Warmin' hooligans up to now?
Uh, is this Sweet
Acorn Orchard?
It is. But we've never had
nopony like you visit before.
Uh, Rarity. A pleasure.
I'm actually here
about a package
that was recently
deliv-
Oh, that was
from you?
Oh! So it did arrive. Ha
ha! If I could just-
We don't know how
to thank you!
Thank me?
I was just saying to
Butternut I wished we knew
who our Hearth's
Warming miracle was.
Oak Nut and I couldn't
believe it when we opened it!
Pistachio said right
away whoever sent it
just "got him".
Says when he put it on,
he could feel his destiny!
As an.. acorn farmer?
Uh! A farmer?
Filly, please.
This is a Fedora
Felt original!
Look at this bold stitching!
These daring textures!
It's a whole new
take on western chic!
There is no way I would
wear it in the grove.
We don't know where he
got his fashion sense.
Far as we know,
a hat's a hat.
Except when
it's art.
Thank you, Rarity.
Rarity? THE
Rarity!?
Mm hm.
You have to stay for lunch. I
won't take no for an answer!
Uh.. I... would be delighted!
The recipe for Chancellor
Puddinghead's magical pudding
was filed under magical
spells, not recipes.
Only took four hours
to figure that out.
Let's see. Nutmeg,
sugarplums, gingerbread, candy canes...
Warning: to avoid untold
culinary devastation,
each ingredient must be
measured with exact care.
Ha ha! Book! Have ya met me!?
Happy Hearth's
Warming!
But... you're early!
Your scroll said you
were coming tomorrow!
The scroll we
sent yesterday..?
Yesterday! Right.
Welcome!
Eh, what are you doing?
Decorations not up, frazzled
mane, determined look.
I've seen this before...
What are you obsessing
about this time, Twily?
Nothing!
So decorations
aren't up because..?
Er. I thought it would
be more fun
if we all decorated
it together!
Oh! That sounds wonderful. We
can start decorating right--
After I finish one
quick errand.
Just a few ingredients.
Nothing to obsess about here!
Make yourselves at home.
Be right back! Promise!
She's definitely freaking
out about something.
Oh yeah.
By Blitzen's beard! It
took ya long enough!
Woah! [slam]
Are you sure you were
expecting me? My name is--
Pinkie Pie, I know.
Cause I know everything.
Alice: Oh, don't be silly!
You only know what's
already happened.
But you don't know
what she's about to ask!
Both: What am I about to ask?
How did you know I
was gonna say that?
Will you two stop
showing off?
She doesn't have all
Hearth's Warming!
Who are you reindeer?
Aurora.
Bori!
Alice!
The gift givers of the grove!
Oooo! And you can help me get
Twilight the best gift ever?
Mmhmm!
What about those matching
hats? They were so cute!
-Well, that was--
--Before she had to get just
one gift for Twilight.
Try to keep up, Aurora.
I'm gonna get that box Pinkie
is gonna say she likes.
Aurora remembers gifts
that have already happened.
Alice knows the gifts
that are going to happen.
I... just stay in the moment
and keep the two
of them in line.
Speaking of. I believe we
have a request for a gift?
The best gift is more
precious than gold,
but it cannot be sold.
When it breaks, it's not ended,
for quickly it's mended.
It can never be bought,
yet is easily sought.
Ah! Here we go.
Oooo. I like that box!
Told ya!
The perfect gift. WOW!
I don't get it.
You will...
We said.. no refunds!
Ahem!
Oh. You.
What are y'all doin'
with these dolls
and that
ridiculous getup?
Don't you have a
resort to run?
It's off-season. Besides,
we're planning an expansion.
And expansions cost bits.
Flim and Flam's
Fro Yo Flume ride!
That sounds fu-
It ain't no excuse for sellin'
cheap dolls to ponies.
We're just giving
ponies what they want!
Shopping for the perfect
gift is stressful.
Oh, that's true.
You want to get something
that really stands out.
I do!
And when you tell your friend
you got them the hottest gift
in Rainbow Falls,
what'll they say?
Woo hoo?
"The more you spend,
the more your friend knows you love them!"
Oh. Right. They really are
good at selling things.
You may not like it.
But technically, we're
not doing anything wrong.
Ponies are desperate
for the right gift.
And who are you to tell
them this isn't it?
If ponies get tired of
Holly after a few days...
...or she falls apart,
who really got hurt?
Nopony!
Don't let the curtain
hit ya on the way out.
Of course Rainbow Dash
wouldn't want this.
I'm so mad I
could just kick...
Convincin' ponies
to buy that doll
ain't in the
holiday spirit.
But Flim and Flam
have a point.
We can't tell
ponies what to buy.
But maybe we
can show 'em!
Could you TRY to
make less noise?
Of course!
Move silently;
blend into the shadows.
The winterchilla will
never hear us coming.
Winter...chilla?
Small, adorable,
fuzzy and fast.
But they're so rare, there's
no telling where they...
Oh, there's one
right there!
Now, if you're
going to get it,
I think the first
move is to be--
Be super-fast?
Making a gift is way more
personal than buying it.
Rarity loves things that
take time and effort.
I'm sure this one will
be the one that works.
[yawn] I just... need to
stay focused and...
Have a wonderful holiday and
remember, no refunds! Next?
And what are YOU doing here?
Same as everypony else!
I want a hearthwarmer!
In fact, I want three!
Seriously?
After I saw my friend here with
hers, I knew I had to buy some!
For my granny, my brother
AND my little sister!
Yeah yeah, great story. Next!
But Applejack! Your granny,
your brother and your sister.
They are all so different!
How can the same doll be the
right gift for all of them?
Oh. Well, that might be true.
But Fluttershy, this is THE
must-have gift of the season.
Just because it's
must-have for one pony
doesn't mean it's must-have
for everypony. Does it?
That's true!
I guess I need to
put more thought
into gettin' the right
gift for each pony.
Can I return these?
No refunds!
Oh. Uh...you want 'em?
I'm gonna go pick out gifts
that are just as special
as the ponies they're for.
I... think I'm going to go
do some more shopping too.
Now hang on a moment!
Wait! Come back!
We'll give you
a great deal!
Buy one get one free!?
Ah. The sweet sounds
of the season.
It's a shame you gotta leave.
Oh, you've been so generous,
but I must get home
for a previous engagement.
I'll be keeping an
eye on you, Pistachio.
I've a feeling you've got
quite the future in fashion!
Rarity! Rarity! I
love my parents,
but.. they don't understand
that we just had lunch
with one of the most famous
ponies in Equestria.
Oh.. I don't know about
"most famous".
Ha ha!
I know you didn't send
a Fedora Felt original
to some nopony you've never
met from nowhere, Equestria.
I'm sure this is actually
for somepony special
so.. if you want it
back, I get it.
The hat is indeed for
somepony very special.
And I couldn't bear to
see him part with it.
[gasp] Oh, thank Celestia, because I
did not want to give this up! Heh.
But if I hear you call
yourself a nopony again,
you shan't be my guest for
fashion week in Manehattan.
Sorry, Applejack...
Puttin' those two
in their places
makes me all warm
and fuzzy inside.
Ooh. But we never got gifts
for Spike or Rainbow Dash.
And it's already
Hearth's Warming Eve.
It probably ain't what
they're expectin',
but.. we still got these.
Yay?
Don't do that.
Flurry loved sledding!
Too bad her aunt
wasn't there.
Oooh!
There! Ingredients
measured exactly!
Now, what were you saying?
Hi! Remember us?
We came all the way
from the Crystal Empire for
some quality family time?
OK. I did get a
little stressed
about Hearth's
Warming this year.
What? You? Never!
So my friends decided
we should do a
Hearth's Warming helper
and give one pony a
present to save time!
What?
Let me guess. You got super
worried about making sure
the present was perfect
and went all Twily-nanas,
didn't you?
I wasn't Twily-nanas!
OK fine. A little
Twily-nanas.
Twilight, we know
you get overwhelmed.
You should have just told
us! We could've helped!
The good news is, Pinkie's
present is almost done!
Then it's just
friends and family
and a calm quiet
Hearth's Warming Eve!
Good-bye. Enjoy your exclusive
pony-only holiday gathering!
I'll just be home spending
quality time with.. myself.
Ugh..
I wouldn't have this little
fella without you so...
If you wanna join, Fluttershy
would love having you.
And.. I wouldn't totally hate it...
Great! Awesome! In
that case... Oh, look!
Sunset! It's officially
Hearth's Warming Eve!
What is it doing!?
Oh uh, did I forget to
mention that the winterchilla
transforms into a winterzilla
when the sun sets?
How did everypony's
shopping go?
-Well..
-Um..
-Yeah....
Spike: Coming!
Ha ha...
Did you get attacked
by a party?
I fell asleep. On
somepony's present.
RUN! The pudding is coming!
Run! The winterzilla
is coming!
What IS that!?
Magic pudding! What is THAT!?
A winterchilla!
They turn into
winterZILLAS after dark!
Does everypony know
this except me!?
Ah!
You like the sparkly?
Just follow it this way!
Is this HONESTLY the best
plan we can come up with!?
Can't you do something!?
I did! This is
Fluttershy's gift!
What!?
A LITTLE HELP, PLEASE!
I've got this!
Which one of us
can fly, darling?
Wah!
Your mom sure
is something...
You're not so
bad yourself...
No, no, no! Not that
sparkly. This one!
Uh, I'm OK if he doesn't
want to chase me anymore.
How we gonna get
rid of this thing?
Oh, for Scorpan's sake.
Hello! If only one of you
had a way with animals?
Oh, my.
Uh. Ahem. Excuse me.
This is supposed to be the
happiest time of year!
So if this is how
you plan on behaving,
you can march yourself right
back to where you came from!
Oh. Your family is gone for the
holidays and you're all alone?
I'm so sorry. If you calm down,
I'm sure you could join us.
Ah!
Uh, maybe leave the baking
to me next time? Heh heh.
Actually, it's pretty good!
Chancellor
Puddinghead's recipe.
Now that's an
impressive dessert!
It's your Hearth's
Warming present!
Really? That's
so thoughtful!
It took a lot of
research, but I--
Maybe focus on the
task at hoof, Twily?
Right! The recipe
needed to be exact.
I think Flurry Heart
added something
while I wasn't looking,
but I have no idea
what to add to adjust it.
A teaspoon of nutmeg?
Three sugarplums? Extra-
gingerbread? Four
more candy canes?
How do YOU know
the recipe?
I don't get it.
You will.
Happy Hearth's Warming,
Twilight!
I'm your Hearth's-Warming
helper!
A bit reindeer-
ex-machina, but...
Two thumbs way up. Whoooo!
Sorry for failing as a
Hearth's Warming helper, Pinkie.
What!? With no
pudding disaster,
my gift with the
exact ingredients
wouldn't have made any sense!
This way it was perfect!
At least Twilight
has something to show
for her effort.
I ordered you a fabulous
farm hat, Applejack.
Alas, it decided it
belonged to somepony else.
Pop said sometimes the
hat chooses the pony
when he gave me this.
Hopefully my gift inspired
whoever's wearin' it
to be the best farmer ever.
Ah. Ooo. Something like that.
We're really sorry
about your gifts.
We got a bit distracted with
Flim and Flam's shenanigans.
"Commercialism is the
greatest gift of all."
They're better than my gift.
[groan] Sorry about the winterzilla.
Oh, he's a big
sweetheart.
And he ended up
being really helpful!
It was actually kind
of nice to be the pony
who saved the day for once.
Oh really? You
mean a giant beast
that only Fluttershy
could tame,
making her the hero of
Hearth's Warming Eve
was a great gift?
Imagine that...
You mean you tricked me into
putting my friend in danger
on purpose so you...
Let's just say it
was from.. both of us.
I guess Hearth's Warmin' helper
was kind of a disaster.
I don't know. Ponyville
always seems to have way more
exciting holidays than
the Crystal Empire.
There's one gift left.
But.. I messed up too.
Your present's only
kinda finished, Rarity.
But I guess it's
better than nothing.
♪ I wanted to get you
something oh so rare. ♪
♪ A gift to show I care ♪
♪ but nothing can compare ♪
♪ to you that's easy to see. ♪
♪ But I got stressed ♪
♪ and overthought ♪
♪ until the day was shot ♪
♪ and it was all for naught. ♪
♪ But now it's clear to me ♪
♪ I'm not gifted at gifting ♪
♪ It's really pretty sad ♪
♪ I tried to show I care ♪
♪ But it turned out bad ♪
♪ I'm not gifted at gifting ♪
♪ So all that's left to say ♪
♪ Is that I really
hope my gifting ♪
♪ Didn't ruin your holiday. ♪
Oh, Spike. A song
is a lovely present!
I wanted to get you
the best gift ever.
I just couldn't figure
out what it was..
Ooo! Ooo! The gift givers told
me that! Um. What was it..
The best gift is more
precious than gold
but it cannot be sold.
When it breaks, it's not ended
for quickly it's mended
it can never be bought
yet is easily sought.
What's so funny?
It's a riddle. And the
answer is, friendship!
♪ The most magical gift
That I can recall ♪
♪ It could have been big or
small. Or even nothing at all ♪
♪ It doesn't matter you see
If it's from my friends ♪
♪ On whom I depend
no matter what you spend ♪
♪ it will be perfect to me. ♪
♪ The true gift of gifting
is what it means inside ♪
♪ we can show we care
spreading love far and wide ♪
♪ the true gift of gifting
is totally free ♪
♪ and you're the best
there is at giving it ♪
♪ with the friendship
that you give to me. ♪
♪ We've all been
friends forever ♪
♪ And look how far
we've come, ♪
♪ how far
♪ the holiday brings us
closer now its time for fun. ♪
♪ It's now begun. ♪
♪ The greatest gift you
give to me is more
precious than gold. ♪
♪ Ahh-ahh-ahh! ♪
♪ Never-ending and
always mended ♪
♪ and it can't be
bought or sold! ♪
♪ The true gift of gifting
is what it means inside, ♪
♪ We can show we care
spreading love far and wide. ♪
♪ The true gift of
gifting is totally free! ♪
♪ And you're the best
there is at giving it ♪
♪ with the friendship
that you gift to me! ♪
And so it worked out!
And a lesson was learned
there's no need to obsess.
Gift giving is simple
as long as you recall....
Friendship is the
best gift of all!