Try again, Twi.
You can do it.
Phew!
This spell's a toughie.
But I feel lucky this time.
One, two...
- Hi!
Pinkie, why'd you do that?!
'Cause hugs are funeriffic!
Especially when you throw one
around a friend.
Whatcha doin'?
Trying to turn that apple
into an orange!
But you kind of threw her aim off.
Whee!
What a cute orange birdie!
Do me next, Twilight!
Do me! Do me!
Ooh! Rarity, wanna see Twilight
turn me into an orange?
It's gonna be funna-fun-fun!
As fun as creating an
haute-couture ensemble
that I just finished making?
Delightful, no?
This is terrible!
I admit it's perhaps not
my finest work, but I--
You had total, awesome, amazing fun,
and I missed out on it?!
Wait.
What if there's more awesome,
amazing fun with friends
happening somewhere
in Ponyville right now
that I'm missing out on too?!
We weren't gonna turn her
into an orange. I swear!
Hey, Rainbow Dash.
Whatcha doin'?
This punk cloud got so heavy,
it's making fog.
Figure I'll thin this bad boy out
so it floats back up.
Ooh! Fun!
Gotta go!
Thanks, Pinkie?
Hey, Applejack.
That looks like fun.
Can I join you?
Whee!
Next time, I'll pull you.
Fluttershy!
There...
There... you...
There... you... are...
doing...
doing... anything...
doing... anything... fun?
Not especially.
Oh, good.
Fun is hard!
Season 3 | Episode 3
Too Many Pinkie Pies
Subbed and Synced by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@Gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
Feeling better, Pinkie?
Abso-tutely-lutely!
Thanks for letting me rest in
your butterfly grove
while I get
my Pinkie strength back.
What are friends for?
That's just the thing!
I've got so many wonderful friends
having fun in every last corner of Ponyville
I can't figure out how
to keep up with it all.
It's driving me even more
coco-loco than usual!
I can promise to not do anything
fun at all if that would help.
You are such a good friend.
There you are, Pinkie.
Been looking everywhere for you, girl.
- Hey, Pinkie.
Got something fun planned this afternoon.
Thought you might wanna know about it.
Well, I'll be an apple crisp.
I'm here for the same reason!
This is perfect!
Everyone will now
bring their fun to me.
This will solve everything!
Why didn't I think of that?
Actually, what I meant is
after I'm done whipping up today's weather,
I'll be chilling by the lake
catching some rays.
- Wanna hang?
- I am so there!
And my family's having a barn raising
this afternoon at Sweet Apple Acres.
And I'm also so there!
Whee! Whee!
But that's when I'll be
at the swimming hole.
Oh, well.
Doesn't matter.
Whichever one you choose
is okay with me.
Me too.
Choose?
One... two...
Pinkie!
What in the wide-wide world
of Equestria are you doing now?
Timing myself
galloping back and forth
between the swimming hole
and Sweet Apple Acres.
I'm trying to cut down my time
so Rainbow Dash dives off the swing,
I can get to Sweet Apple Acres
to help with the barn raising,
and then be back in time
to see Rainbow Dash hit the water
after doing a double flip.
If I can cut my time by only 20 minutes,
I'm good.
Oh, Pinkie.
I'm afraid no matter
how hard you try,
the only way to
pull something like that off
is if there's more of you
to go around.
That's it, Twilight!
The legend of the Mirror Pool!
The legend of the who-what now?
Pinkie!
I'm familiar with loads of legends,
and I never heard of--
Does this mean practice is over?
Of course not.
Back to work.
Seems like hardly
anypony's been here in ages.
I hope I'm remembering the rhymes right
from my nana Pinkie story.
Where the brambles are thickest,
there you will find... huh...
a pond beyond
the most twisted of vines.
Who's there?!
I heard a voice!
Oh.
It was me.
Ouch! Oh!
Stop scratching me up, brambles!
The Mirror Pool!
Oh, and there's that voice again.
Ah, Pinkie.
You have got to stop
talking to yourself.
Starting... now.
And into her own reflection she stared,
huh... yearning for one
whose reflection she shared
and solemnly sweared not to be scared
at the prospect of being doubly mared!
Whee-hee!
Wow. The legend is true.
It really worked!
Okay, wait, I promised
not to talk to myself anymore.
I should say something to her.
Or... would that still be
talking to myself?
Excuse me, me?
Can I have word with you?
Uh, I mean, me?
Listen, I can see you're having lots of fun,
but--
Fun!
Did somebody say 'fun'?
Where?
- I did, over here.
I thought someone said
something about fun.
Where is it? Over here?
Over here?
I don't see it.
Where is it? Where is it?
Oh, calm yourself.
There's loads of fun to be had
in Ponyville with my girls.
Trot on over back to Ponyville with me,
and I'll tell ya all about them.
And then there's Rarity.
She's the one with all
the fancy clothes and ribbons and stuff.
I'm thinking she can make us all
matching t-shirts that say 'team Pinkie' and--
Is this Ponyville?
Where's the fun? Where's the fun?
Uh, well, let's see.
Applejack's having a barn raising at--
It's thataway!
Wait!
Come back!
Don't forget to meet me back here
to tell me everything about everything.
Like I was there myself.
Because I'm you and...
and you're me, and--
Oh my gosh!
This is the greatest plan ever!!
Now, off to double my fun!
Let's rock this pool, ponies!
Coming in, Dashy?
The water's great.
It's totally wet and everything.
I don't know.
Cloud busting was tougher work
than usual, today.
I'm kind of exhausted.
That's fine.
You relax.
At least we'll still be together.
Glad you made it, Pinkie.
I thought you maybe went
to Applejack's, instead.
- I did.
-Oh. The Barn up yet?
I have no idea.
But I thought you said
you were just at Applejack's.
Actually, I'm probably still
on my way there now!
Whee!
Oh, Pinkie Pie.
I'm so glad you wandered by.
I know I promised
not to have any fun today, but
I couldn't help myself.
All of my critter friends wanted a picnic,
and I couldn't disappoint them.
Come join us.
We have plenty of hay juice
and marmalade to go around.
Don't we, critters?
Wait!
That sounds super fun!
But Applejohn sounds super fun too!
And-- and-- I can't do one
without missing out on the other!
Who's Applejohn?
Two fun things at once!
But which-- which--
Can't decide!
Trouble breathing!
Walls closing in!
Walls?
But we're outside.
Goodness.
Was it something I said?
Yes!
So, you see, that's how I'm able
to have fun in two places at once.
Duplicates of you, huh?
Yeah, sure, Pinkie.
Look, I was just gearing up
to catch some Z's. So uh...
Gotcha!
I'll have the rest of my fun very quietly.
How'd you do that?
Just trying to show a little consideration
for my sleepy friend.
Ooh! Ooh!
Gotta run!
Looks like I'm trying to
get my attention.
- Excuse me.
- And me.
Ooh! Ooh!
Tell me all about it.
Did they pull the walls of the barn up
slooow... or fast?
Maybe slow to medium-fast?
Somewhere in that range?
Ooh!
Did you get ice cream?
What kinds did they have?
Banana brickle?
I didn't make it!
I was on my way there,
and then Fluttershutter--
Fluttershy.
Yeah! Her! She offered
something else fun for me to do.
A picnic!
With cute little animals.
How could you say no to that?
That's what I'm saying!
Then I would have missed the super fun thing
with Applesauce!
Applejack.
So I didn't do
anything fun at all!
Oh, my poor, poor me.
There, there.
Tell me what.
We just need a couple more Pinkie Pies.
- Easy-peasy.
- Really?
Come on.
Would I lie to me?
And solemnly sweared
not to be scared
at the prospect of being
doubly mared.
Look!
A double me!
I think you mean
a double-double me?
Plus another double-double me,
which makes two double-double me's,
or a double-double-double me,
if you will.
Did somebody say 'fun'?
Where? Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun!
Now Applejack, Rainbow Dash
and Fluttershy are covered
plus one extra Pinkie Pie in case
we get an extra invite from somepony else.
Perfect!
Okay, let's go!
And solemnly sweared
not to be scared,
at the prospect of being doubly mared!
Okay, good enough.
Pinkie Pies, moving out--
...not to be scared,
at the prospect of being doubly mared!
What in the name of pink?!
Knock it off!
To Ponyville, everyone!
Follow me!
Yes, it's fun there.
Okay, between the bunch of us,
we should have every nook and cranny of fun
in Ponyville covered, at all times.
An unprecedented
and massive undertaking!
But first,
a pop quiz on the names I taught you!
Applejack!
Fluttershy!
Pinkie Pie!
Excellent!
Okay,
let's get on with this, folks.
Fan out on three.
One--
Eh, good enough.
What the--
Wow! Pinkie Pie wasn't kidding
about the duplicates!
Except now there's triplicates...
and quadruplicates!
Dash is gonna love this!
If I push her around on this floaty thing,
it'll be fun, and relaxing!
Uh oh...
No more Pinkies!
I can't take it!
Gosh, uh...
I wonder what fun they're having raising
the barn at Applejack's right now!
Maybe I'd better go check!
Oh, phew!
Looks like I haven't missed a thing!
I wanna know right now
where all you Pinkies came from
so I can find out who's responsible for
y'all ruinin' our barn raisin'!
Uh, you look pretty busy right now,
so...
maybe we should talk a little later?
Y'all come back here and clean up
after yourselves this instant!
Oh no, what have I done,
what have I done?!
My poor friends...
Okay, everypony,
please, calm down!
Calm down?!
I have just had a Pinkie hurricane
raging through my shop!
And they trashed our critter picnic!
Please, everypony, hang on
while I try to figure something out!
Come on, Spike.
I've gotta try to remember
the name of that legend she mentioned.
Ah, here it is!
"The legend of the Mirror Pond".
It describes a spell I can use to send
them back where they came from!
That's perfect, let's go!
But there's a catch.
If I can't figure out which one's the real Pinkie,
I might send her back by mistake!
Well, we'll just have to figure out
who the real one is then.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Does anypony here know how we can tell
the real Pinkie from all the rest of them?
Twilight! I have to talk to you,
I need your help!
Excuse me, whoever you are,
but I'm not talking to any of you Pinkies
unless you're the real Pinkie.
Oh, but, I am the real Pinkie!
No you're not,
I'm the real Pinkie!
- No, I'm the real Pinkie!
How in tarnation are we supposed
to tell which is the real Pinkie?
I have no idea.
Me either.
We've all got the same adorable tails,
we've all got the same adorable manes,
we've all got the same adorable hooves!
Which one of us is the real Pinkie?!
I haven't the slightest clue!
And if I can't tell us apart...
who can?
Ugh, this is hopeless!
Maybe that one's the real Pinkie.
Please. The real Pinkie Pie never sat
that long in one place for her whole life!
I'm gonna go ask.
Of course she's gonna say
she's the real Pinkie! They all do!
You're wasting your time.
So, lemme guess.
You're the real Pinkie Pie.
Heck if I know!
Could be any one of us,
if you ask me.
And if I said I was the real Pinkie,
you wouldn't even believe me anyway.
So just leave me alone.
I've got some important poking around
with my hoof to do.
Oh Spike, how're we gonna do this?
I can't risk sending the real Pinkie
back into the pond!
I miss the real Pinkie.
I bet she misses you too.
Bet she'd do just about anything
to get to be with her friends again.
Hey, hey!
What if you gave them a test?
Pick something really hard for a Pinkie to do,
something not fun at all!
Any Pinkie that can't do it
goes back into the pond.
But whoever wants to stay the most,
that must be the real Pinkie!
You know, that's not a bad idea.
This is great! If I pass,
I get to be with my friends again!
But what if I don't pass?
What if I'm not the real Pinkie Pie?!
Stupid magic mirror water!
This is all your fault!
And mine.
Hey, Twilight!
I've been looking all over for you ponies.
What are you all doing here?
Fluttershy spoke
with the woodland critters,
and they've agreed to take us into their
home 'til the Pinkie storm dies down.
You guys, we're gonna fix this.
And I know exactly how.
Are we gonna lose our real Pinkie Pie?
I don't think so.
Now come along.
I've already got Applejack and her family
rounding up all the Pinkies.
Hyah, Pinkies, hyah!
Ooh, they wanna play chase!
This is fun, too!
Oh, give it a rest.
Welcome, Pinkies, welcome.
Please have a seat and
make yourselves comfortable.
Okay, I suppose you can't be
comfortable staying in one place,
but have a seat anyway.
Sit down!
Better. Now, I suppose
you're all wondering
why I've gathered you
all here today.
For fun?
No, just the opposite, actually.
Wait up,
I got one more!
I found this one poking at the ground
with her hoof and drawing frowny faces.
Have her come sit with the others.
Pinkies, you've been brought here
to take a test.
Don't worry, it's a simple test.
About as simple as they come.
And whoever passes gets to stay.
Curtain, please.
The test will be watching paint dry!
On your mark, get set, go!
Whoa, this is so exciting!
Okay, maybe not that exciting.
Oh, hey, look at the birdie!
Watch me bounce
and touch the ceiling!
Is that... is that a frog
crossed with an orange?
- Cool!
- Where?
Look what I can do
with my hooves!
Betcha can't make a face
crazier than...
this!
I can't take it any more!
Somepony's making balloon animals!
What? Where?
Pinkie,
you can look away now.
- I passed?
- You passed.
You're the only Pinkie
who kept staring at the wall.
I had to, I just had to.
I couldn't leave my friends,
I just couldn't.
But I guess sometimes
I will have to choose between them.
I knew you'd be up to the challenge.
I'm me! I'm me!
I'm meeee!!
Or am I?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I am.
Dear Princess Celestia,
it's great to have fun,
but it's even greater
to have great friends.
And having lots of friends means that
you sometimes have to make choices
as to who you spend your time with.
But that's okay,
because good friends
will always give you
lots of opportunities to have fun.
So even if you're missing out,
it's never for long.
Respectfully yours,
Pinkie Pie.
Hi Pinkie Pie,
we were thinking
we should go out and celebrate.
You up for some wheelbarrow races?
Or I could take everypony
on a cloud ride!
I could throw a party with punch
and zesty cucumber sandwiches! Ooh!
You wanna know exactly
what I feel like doing right now?
That looks like fun.