♪♪
[snoring]
Let's go through
this one more time.
We've been over it, like,
a million times, Twilight.
We found all six
keys, defeated Tirek,
and got this sweet castle.
End of story.
Yes, but why?
I don't know, Sugarcube.
Maybe it's just
your new house,
and there ain't nothin'
more to it than that.
I must say, speaking
strictly on aesthetics,
there really doesn't
need to be more to it.
It's all simply divine!
I agree with Twilight.
And Rarity and Applejack and
Rainbow Dash and Pinkie Pie.
Oh. And probably Spike.
As princess, I've been chosen to
spread the Magic of Friendship
across Equestria.
So why would the
Tree of Harmony
want us to sit in a
castle in Ponyville?
It doesn't make any sense.
♪ [chimes] ♪
[zapping]
[rumbling]
[yawn]
Is that new?
I like it.
YayPonies HoH Subtitles.
♪♪
This is incredible!
It's got all of Equestria!
Hi, Mom and Dad!
[crash]
[giggle]
♪♪
But if this is Ponyville...
...why are our Cutie
Marks over there?
I don't know.
But it seems like the
map wants us to find out.
The Tree, the chest, this
castle...and now the map.
How can we not follow it?
You know what?
There's a ton of room
for dangerous adventure
along that route.
Count me in.
Aw shoot, I reckon
you're right.
Well, I was planning on
organizing my baking sheets,
but OK!
[sigh] Very well.
Um, maybe I'll just
stay here with Spike.
Spike: Awesome!
Me and Big Mac have a huge
weekend ahead of us
talkin' hoofball and
trading hoofball cards
and arguing about
hoofball stats!
On second thought, maybe
I'd better go with them.
In case they need me.
Looks like it's time
for a road trip.
Well? Suit yourself.
But he's got a Hock
Fetlock rookie card
I plan to sweet talk right
into these hot little claws.
♪♪
[chugging engine]
[tracks rattling]
♪♪
That's it! That's the
place on the map!
Right! Let's get down
there and find the spa.
Wait. We don't know why
the map sent us here.
We shouldn't just walk right
in. It could be dangerous.
Yesss!
Stay behind me, everypony.
I'm on it.
Careful, Pinkie!
♪♪
[crash]
[scraping]
Rainbow: This is
where the map sent us?
It looks like the most
boring place in Equestria!
Applejack: That's just
an ordinary village
full of ordinary pony folk.
It could certainly use
a few more architectural
flourishes...or any
architectural flourishes.
I think it's lovely.
I don't like it.
I don't like it one bit.
I know smiles.
And those smiles?
They're just not right.
Twilight: Forget the smiles;
look at the Cutie Marks!
OK, that's weird.
♪♪
Twilight: An entire village
with the same Cutie Mark?
How can that be?
I bet there's some sort of
horrific monster behind it!
What makes you say that?
'Cause fighting a horrific
monster would be super awesome!
I reckon we oughta
just head into town
and talk to some locals.
Find out what's goin' on.
Great idea, AJ! Let's go.
Those smiles are bad news!
♪♪
Welcome!
This must be the most
pleasant place in Equestria!
Welcome!
[giggle]
Ugh. Thanks a lot, map.
Welcome!
Pardon my forwardness,
but are you an alicorn?
That there's the
Princess of Friendship!
Well, you've certainly come to
the right place for friendship.
What brings you to town?
We're not
entirely sure.
I see.
Well, all are welcome here
in our little village.
My name is Double Diamond
and this is Party Favor.
Howdy, Double Diamond.
I'm Applejack, and this here's
Pinkie Pie, Fluttershy, Rarity,
Rainbow Dash, and
Twilight Sparkle.
And you all have your
own unique Cutie Marks.
If you don't mind,
has there been any sort
of trouble here lately?
Why, I don't think
Trouble?
we've ever had trouble
in our little village.
It's true.
You'll see.
Perhaps you'd care to speak to
our founder, Starlight Glimmer.
I wish everypony in Equestria
was as friendly as
these ponies are.
I've got my eye on them.
Something's rotten in...whatever
the name of this village is
that we're in right now.
[knock knock]
Starlight?
We have some new visitors!
Be ready to fight.
We don't know what's gonna
come through that door.
Welcome!
I'm so pleased to
have you here.
[groan]
This is Applejack, Fluttershy,
Pinkie Pie, Rarity,
Rainbow Dash, and
Twilight Sparkle.
Forgive my bluntness,
but I'm assuming it's
Princess Twilight Sparkle?
We don't get many
alicorns around here.
Yes. But Twilight is fine.
So! How did you hear
of our little village?
It's kind of a long story.
Let's just say we
found it on a map.
Technically it's a
tree-chest-castle-map.
Well, however you found us,
we're happy to have you.
We're happy to have anypony
who wants to experience
true friendship for
the first time.
Say what?
Oh, indeed.
That's what's so unique
about our village, you see.
Around here, we don't
flaunt our special talents
because we don't have any
special talents to flaunt.
Is that why you all
have those Cutie Marks?
Perhaps it would be
easier to understand
if I gave you a tour
of the village.
♪ [military drum beat] ♪
Heads High ponies!
Marching proud!
All together now,
every one of you!
No pony left behind!
♪ Life is so grand in our town ♪
♪ We're always
filled with cheer ♪
♪ We never have to look around ♪
♪ To know that we're all here ♪
♪ In our town! ♪
♪ In our town ♪
♪ We don't have to wait ♪
♪ To find out that our destiny ♪
♪ Is just to emulate! ♪
Let's see those
big happy smiles!
♪ Life is a smile in our town ♪
♪ Our cutie marks the same ♪
♪ Because we do not separate ♪
♪ Ourselves by
more than name ♪
♪ In our town! In our town ♪
♪ We dare not compete ♪
♪ Winning only breeds
the worst ♪
♪ Ego-filled conceit ♪
You see, now everypony wins!
♪♪
♪ Life is a joy in our town
We're all equal here ♪
♪ No-one is superior
And no-one shakes in fear ♪
♪ In our town! In our town ♪
♪ We work as a team ♪
♪ You can't have a nightmare
If you never dream ♪
♪♪
♪ Other ponies argue
Do you ever wonder why? ♪
♪ When you think your
talent's special ♪
♪ You don't see eye to eye ♪
♪ There's just too
many differences ♪
♪ That lead to disarray ♪
♪ But when you learn
to act as one ♪
♪ It's like a holiday ♪
♪ In our town In our town ♪
♪ We don't complicate ♪
♪ When you learn to simplify ♪
♪ Life is oh so great ♪
♪ Join in our utopia ♪
♪ Come out of the dark ♪
♪ Banded by equality
By our cutie mark! ♪
♪♪
[laugh]
You're kidding, right?
Give up our Cutie Marks?
No way!
Fluttershy: Rainbow Dash,
don't be so rude!
I don't think we
should judge them.
They all seem perfectly
happy with their choice.
Don't believe their
smiles, Fluttershy.
I'm sorry, I guess we're just a
little confused by all of this.
We have no judgments
here in our village.
Each of us was
confused once as well,
blinded by the false
promise of our Cutie Marks.
Whoa whoa whoa!
Is she for real?
When we were sent
to this village,
we assumed it was to help
in some way, but...well,
it doesn't seem like
you need any help.
Have you considered perhaps that
you might have been sent here
so we could help you?
After all, nopony has
ever come to our village
and wanted to leave.
Why should you be any different?
But that is entirely
your choice.
Please, enjoy our little
corner of Equestria.
We're all quite fond of it.
No doubt you will be as well.
Double Diamond, please
help our guests
with whatever they
might need.
Of course.
Well, this will certainly
provide a boost
to our little community.
When the rest of Equestria sees
that a princess gave up
her Cutie Mark to join us,
they'll finally understand what
we're trying to accomplish.
Welcome!
A Cutie Mark is
a representation
of a pony's unique
talents and skills.
How is it possible to--
[gasp] What in the name
of Equestria is THAT?
Welcome!
Care to sample
some local fashion?
We've got cloaks this month!
[gag]
Perhaps another time,
good sir, thank you.
No wonder nopony's
wearing anything.
Really, girls, they may do
things a bit differently
than we're used to, but that's
no reason to be rude!
No, the reason to be rude
is that they all
keep staring at us.
Need something?
Uh, no, we're good.
Fluttershy's right.
If we're going to
get to the bottom
of why the map sent us here,
we'll need the
help of these ponies.
I think we ran off to
the end of Equestria
before we even knew
what that map was!
If we were at the
end of Equestria,
we'd be sitting on
a big A!
Hee Hee! Get it?
Oh please, Miss Pie, this is
hardly the time for jokes.
We've come all this
way and for what?
Maybe you're right,
but we're here now.
And it sure feels like
something's wrong.
That and two bits'll
get you a cup of cider.
Is this a bad time?
We shouldn't be
bickering like this
in front of our
new friends.
Really, Applejack, you're
almost as bad as Rainbow Dash!
Don't drag me
into this.
Is your friendship ending?
Are you crazy?
We'd never let a disagreement
get in the way of food!
OK, well. My
name is Sugar Belle.
What can I bring you?
We have...
muffins.
Then I guess we'll
take six muffins.
Make that twelve.
What? I'm hungry.
Come on, girls, we've
got to stick together.
It doesn't matter what happened
before; we're here now.
I guess you're right.
And the sooner we figure out
why, the sooner we can go home.
Forgive me for
overhearing,
but just a moment ago
you were disagreeing.
And now it sounds
like you're agreeing.
Uh-huh.
Well, you had such
differing opinions.
And Cutie Marks.
We have differing opinions
all the time, darling.
But you look like
you're friends.
We are friends.
A simple disagreement
wouldn't change that.
I'm sorry, I'm just having
a hard time understanding.
Different talents lead
to different opinions,
which lead to
bitterness and misery.
So, why aren't you
bitter and--
Peh!
Blech!
Mmm...good!
It's all right, I know
I'm not a very good baker.
At least, I'm not any
better than anypony else
in the village.
Well, I hope you enjoy
our little village!
Come inside before you go.
Meet me downstairs.
OK, that was weird, too.
Let's all sit here and eat
these muffins and act normal.
I think we're being watched.
Ya think?
No, not like that.
I mean somepony here doesn't
want us talking to Sugar Belle.
I got an idea.
But you gotta eat all
them muffins, Pinkie.
Me? Why me?
You got a stronger
stomach than any of us
and that filly in there
might be our best chance
at findin' out what in the
hay is goin' on around here.
Applejack: I can't believe you
ate all our muffins, Pinkie Pie!
We'd best go inside
and get some more!
Nice work, Pinkie.
I've accidentally eaten
cardboard tastier than that.
Hello? Sugar Belle?
Sugar Belle: Thank
you for coming.
Why did want us
to come down here?
So nopony could see
what's about to happen.
♪ [eerie] ♪
Are you really the
Princess of Friendship?
Do you know Princess Celestia?
I love your Cutie Mark!
How can you be friends with
different Cutie Marks?
Don't you end up
hating each other?
Oh, look at this one!
This one's great too!
I'd love to have my
special talent back,
even just for a day...make
something besides those
disgusting muffins.
So what's stopping you?
Go get your Cutie
Marks back.
Daydreaming is one
thing, but you mean...
actually having
it put back on?
That seems extreme.
I'm not sure Starlight
would like that.
She wants us all to be
happy in our sameness.
How do you take somepony's
Cutie Mark, anyway?
The Cutie Unmarking is
a beautiful experience.
Starlight uses the
Staff of Sameness
to magically take them away
and replace them with these.
But nopony should keep
you from your Cutie Mark.
It represents such an
essential part of who you are!
Oh, we're not kept from them.
They're in the vault,
up in the caves.
We can visit them any time
we like to remind us
of the heartache of a life
with special talents.
Can we visit this cave?
I'm delighted you're interested
in our Cutie Mark vault!
We hope someday every pony in
Equestria will make a pilgrimage
here to our little village
to have theirs removed, too,
And our message of ...[continues]
This must be the
reason we're here.
Pilgrimaging?
No, helping those ponies
get their Cutie Marks back.
Oh. Are you sure, Twilight?
Maybe they missed
them a little,
but even they didn't
seem all that unhappy.
Then why did they want
to meet us in secret?
And why did they ask us
not to tell Starlight
who told us about the vault?
Something's not right.
Just through here!
Behold!
Our Cutie Mark vault.
Twilight: I've never seen
anything like it!
And here is the
Staff of Sameness.
It was one of the great
mage Meadowbrook's
nine enchanted items.
We are incredibly
fortunate to have it here.
This is the tool that allows
us to free ourselves
from our Marks.
I'm curious; how did the
subject of the vault come up?
Oh, some ponies
were telling us
how much they missed
their Cutie Marks and--
Pinkie!
Oops.
Starlight: Were they!
Well, it seems you inspire
all sorts of free thinking,
don't you?
We certainly didn't intend to
cause any disruptions
to your charming
little--
Good.
Let's just make sure
of that, shall we?
It's a trap!
♪♪
[groans]
Oh, I don't blame you for what
you tried to do here today.
You've spent your whole
lives thinking those Marks
are a good thing.
Give them back!
Well! Now you can spend the rest
of your lives here with us.
And we'll teach you just
how much better life can be
without your Cutie Marks.
♪♪