[galloping hooves]
Greetings, Tantabus. I am ready.
Do your worst.
[grunts]
Princess Luna's turning into
Nightmare Moon...again!
[evil laugh]
Yeah? Well, we've got
the cure for that!
[crashing]
♪ [dramatic] ♪
[whoosh]
[evil laugh cut short]
Wait! What is it doing?
NO! It's gone!
[grunts of pain]
[happy squeals]
[gasping]
What?
My dream ended happily?
That cannot happen!
Hearing impaired subtitles by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Pinkie Pie: Ooh!
This is amazing!
[noisy yawn]
Yeah, Rarity, thanks
for setting all this up.
A grooming day for our pets
really was a great idea.
[cat yowls]
Oh my! Oh I'm sorry!
I didn't get my normal
beauty sleep last night.
[hiss]
You know, [yawn] I didn't
sleep well either.
[agreeing murmurs]
[upbeat] I'm totally beat, too!
[bark]
All right, Winona,
time fer yer brushin'.
[yelp of pain]
[splash]
Whoops. I guess I'm too plumb
tuckered out to do this right.
[yawn]
I even went to bed
early last night.
But then I had a
really scary nightmare.
All: Me too!
Uh, only, you know, I didn't
think mine was THAT scary.
Well, mine sure was. There was
this blue smoke monster and-
What?
I dreamt about a blue
smoke thingy too!
Me too!
So what? Probably
just a coincidence.
That's an awfully
big coincidence.
Huh. I wonder why I didn't
have that nightmare.
I slept great!
So then what could have given
us all the same nightmare?
I don't know. But I
do know who might.
Spike, could you send a
scroll to Princess Luna?
Sure.
All set!
Dear Princess Luna. Last night,
my friends and I all dreamt
of a creature made
of blue smoke.
I'm sure you're very busy, but
[yawn]
when you have the chance,
please let me know if you have
any idea what it could mean.
Yours, [yawn] Princess
Twilight Sparkle.
You can leave out the yawns.
[whoosh]
[crash]
Which of you saw the creature of
blue smoke in your nightmare?
Wow! That was fast!
We all did.
Not me!
Ugh! We know!
So you've encountered
the smoke monster, too?
The Tantubus is a
creature of my nightmares!
It escaped from my
slumbers yesterday.
But, how did it get into ours?
The Tantabus is like a parasite.
My dreams must no
longer be enough for it.
Now it seeks others
to infect and corrupt.
It must have learned of you six
from seeing you in my dream.
Whoa whoa whoa! So what
you're saying is...
You dreamt about all
of them and not me?
So Smokey gave us bad
dreams. No biggie.
I saw that the Tantabus
had grown more powerful,
but I did not realize that
power was enough to enable it
to escape my dreams.
If its power grows,
it could very well
find a way to escape
into the real world.
It could turn all of Equestria
into a living nightmare!
OK, OK, OK! I take it back. That
does sound bad! Really bad!
Twilight: We've
prepared everything
exactly as you requested.
Good. As you six slumber here,
I will pursue the creature
into whichever of your
dreams it infests.
Ooh! It'll be like a
princess sleepover!
Speaking of Princesses, aren't
you going to ask Celestia
for her help as well?
There is nothing
my sister can do.
She has no power in
the realm of sleep.
Only I can move
from dream to dream.
I am afraid no pony
can help me tonight.
Even us?
Especially you.
You have all suffered
so much because of me.
You need only slumber
while I hunt the
Tantabus in your dreams.
I know you said no pony
can help, but I'm no pony.
I'm going to stay up and watch
over you guys just in case.
Oh, thank you, Spike.
One good thing about not
sleeping well last night:
shouldn't be too hard
to fall asleep now!
Are you kidding?
This is so exciting,
I don't know how
I'm ever going to -
[snoring]
Oh my! This is simply divine!
How avant-garde!
Forget avant-garde. I should
have said, "en-garde!"
[squeals]
It is here!
[sob]
You were such a
pretty little chiffon!
What kind of monster
would do this?
The Tantabus.
Then let's stop it!
No! Please! I don't want you to
suffer any more because of me.
I will catch it!
It has jumped into
another dream!
I am sorry, but if
I am to stop it,
I must follow it
where you cannot.
Go!
[crash]
I shall be able to
handle things here!
[gulp]
I hope.
♪ La la la la ! ♪
[giggle]
♪ La la la la la! ♪
I followed the Tantabus
here. Now I need only find--
Sorry! Can't help it. An
idea pops into my head and--
[gasp]
Oooh! Cake!
[splat]
[growl]
Eww! Cake!
[whoosh]
No!
Sorry!
Who wants ice cream?
Hmmm. It's so nice to
be the pet for once.
[shriek]
N-n-nice, giant, evil Angel?
[panicked yelp]
Whew! Oh, thank you, Princess!
[slam]
[chomping]
[sigh]
Now, this is what I call
an incredible dream!
I can see the Tantabus has
already turned your slumbers
into a nightmare!
What are you talking about?
This is my favorite dream!
[Smack]
♪ We are such happy flowers! ♪
♪ We will now sing for hours! ♪
♪ Aren't we unbearably cute? ♪
♪ Watch me solo on jazz flute! ♪
♪♪
[screams in horror]
Huh?
[gasp]
Luna!
[grunts]
[shuddering yelps]
What happened? Are you guys OK?
That...that was terrible!
I...I never want to have
that nightmare again!
[shudder]
Me either!
But Luna caught it? Didn't she?
I am so sorry, my
friends. I failed.
It will be back to infect your
dreams the next time you sleep.
Oh, no!
Yeah, I reckon I could
live without seeing
that thing ever again.
But you will. Again
and again. Every night.
Until it grows powerful enough
to infect the waking world!
After what I did
as Nightmare Moon,
the fact that I am once again
responsible for harming others
is more than I can bear.
It'll be OK. Everypony
makes mistakes.
As long as none of you
dreamt about another pony,
the Tantabus remains
confined to your dreams.
I still have a chance to catch
it before it's too late!
Whew! That's good to hear.
Although after you left,
I did happen to dream
I was eating a giant ice
cream cone with all of Ponyville
while taking a test
we hadn't studied for.
See, what did I tell ya?
Everypony makes mistakes!
But that means the Tantabus
could be turning every dream
in Ponyville into a nightmare!
It is far worse than that.
Infecting all those dreams
gives it more and more power.
Soon it will be able to
escape into the real world
and infect Equestria with
its nightmare plague!
Then you must let us help you
stop it before that happens!
But how? The Tantabus
was able to escape Luna
when it only had SIX
dreams it could get to.
It is true. With so
many dreams to hide in,
I do not know how
I can catch it.
Hmmm. What if everypony in
Ponyville were having one dream?
I can create shared dreams, yes.
But for so many ponies at once?
I have never done
anything like that.
The amount of power
it would take...
Fluttershy: Well, it is
worth a try. Isn't it?
Of course. I will do
anything to end this.
Including accept your help.
I cannot allow the Tantabus to
escape into the real world.
All of you must now
go back to sleep.
And hope that I can
create such a dream...
[snoring]
[whoosh]
Derpy: Meow?
[gasp] Princess Luna did it!
Big Mac! Boy, I'm glad to
see something familiar!
Eeyup.
Princess Luna: Ponies!
Princess Luna!
There is no time for
bowing, my friends.
There is something coming!
Something terrible.
No! It is already here!
[roar]
[screams]
I am so sorry. I brought this
upon you. But I will end it now!
[zaps]
[roar]
[screams]
Princess! What's wrong?
[straining]
It is taking all my strength
just to hold this
massive dream together!
You will have to stop it!
I truly wish I did not
have to ask this of you.
Then you're in luck.
Yeah! We're already on it!
[frightened squeals]
Please, I'll pay you anything!
[roar]
Ya-wah!
I got ya!
[panicked cries]
[grunts]
[chomp]
[wails]
Oh, no!
Big Mac! You can do anything
in a dream, remember?
[whinny]
E-wheeeeeee.
C'mon! If that Tantabus
thing turns any more
of this dream against us,
we'll be too busy saving
ponies to catch it
and it'll grow powerful enough
to escape into the real world!
How are we even gonna know
when it's able to escape?
Oh, I think we'll know.
Hurry, my friends!
What the--?
Please! We need your help, too!
Fluttershy's right! We've
all got to work together
to stop it from escaping!
But how can we help? No pony
in Ponyville has your magic.
Or your speed.
That's true!
In Ponyville.
But this here isn't
Ponyville! It's a dream!
Eeyup!
And not just any.
This is YOUR dream.
Anything you can do in your
dreams, you can do now!
Well, if you're gonna dream,
might as well dream big, right?
He-ya!
Derpy: MEOW!
[cheers]
♪♪
It's working!
But it's not enough.
Then do more! This
is a dream, remember?
♪♪
I cannot hold this
dream together much longer.
Equestria will
fall because of me!
[growl]
Am I crazy or did it
just get even bigger
after Luna said that?
I think it's feeding off
your guilt, Princess Luna!
If that is so, then perhaps that
is how it grew strong enough
to escape in the first place!
Say what now?
I created the Tantabus
to give myself the same
nightmare every night.
To punish myself for the evil
I caused as Nightmare Moon.
But why would you do that?
To make sure I
never forgave myself
for how much Equestria
suffered because of me.
But it seems I have
not learned my lesson,
for now I have only
made you suffer more!
[roar]
But that means you might just be
the key to stopping all this!
Yeah! If it gets strong
because you feel bad
about what you did
as Nightmare Moon,
then you just gotta stop
feeling bad for what you did!
How can I forgive myself? I am
no better now than I was then!
My creation is about to turn the
world into a living nightmare!
But look at what YOU'RE doing!
Nightmare Moon would
have wanted the Tantabus
to turn Equestria
into a nightmare.
You're doing everything
you can to stop it!
Don't you see?
That proves you're not the same
pony you were then!
Everypony who knows you
knows that Nightmare Moon
is in the past.
We all trust you, Luna.
Do you trust us enough
to believe we're right?
I do!
[growl]
[moan]
[ding]
Thank you. Thank you all!
[rooster crows]
[gasp]
Luna did it!
She sure did! Only, I'm not
exactly sure WHAT she did.
Luna created the Tantabus
to punish herself.
The worse she felt,
the more power it had.
But once she finally
forgave herself
for what Nightmare Moon did...
Poof!
Shhh!
Huh. Wonder what she's
dreaming about now?