You look nervous. There's
no reason to be nervous.
Nothing to worry about.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Twilight, tell those butterflies
in your tummy to "beat it!"
Making new friends
is always fun!
Oh!
They're probably just
as nervous as you are.
You've been planning
this shindig for weeks.
You know everything about these
fellers. It's gonna be dandy.
You're right. Remember,
Equestria and Yakyakistan
haven't opened their borders
for hundreds of moons.
In fact, Yakyakistan is so far
north of the Crystal Mountains,
nopony's even BEEN there.
Imagine the look on
Princess Celestia's face
when she finds out we made
friends with a Yak Prince!
Ha ha!
I'm calm. I'm calm.
PONIES! GREETINGS, PONIES!
Prince Rutherford, Your Majesty,
on behalf of all of us, I
welcome you to Equestria.
Me honored. Yaks hope
for great friendship
between Ponies and Yaks.
Friends for a thousand moons!
You must be hungry
after your long journey.
We've prepared a banquet
of traditional yak foods.
IF THINGS NOT
PERFECT, YAKS GET MAD!
YAKS ALWAYS GET MAD
WHEN THINGS NOT PERFECT!
THIS NO TASTE LIKE YAK FOOD!
FAKE PONY FOOD MAKE YAKS MAD!
Is it OK to be nervous now?
Regular subtitles by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Them yaks sure have a
funny way of saying howdy.
They're different, that's all.
Very different.
I think they broke my record
for Most Stuff Broken
in Under a Minute.
I mean, they even
broke the trophy.
All we have to do is show them
how great it can be
to have friends before
Princess Celestia arrives for
the friendship party tonight.
Now, who read the seven-volume
cross-indexed history
of Yakyakistan I recommended?
I - I had a thing.
I did! I did! Did you know
they live so far North
of the Crystal Empire that
it's cold all the time?
Yaks have yak fur
to keep them warm!
Pretty sure that's what fur's
always for, Pinkie Pie.
I KNOW! YAKS ARE SO COOL!
Pinkie Pie, can you
show them around town?
I know you have to plan
the friendship party too,
but it would really help
make them feel welcome.
Don't worry. They'll be
in good hooves with me.
Remember, we want to make sure
Equestria feels like home.
That means doing
everything we can
to make this place
feel like Yakyakistan.
No problem!
Good. Let's get out there
and make some new friends.
We know y'all are noble warriors
who avoid the
so-called finer things,
so me and my family'd be honored
if you rested here in the
barn during your visit.
Applejack and I made hay beds
like you're used to
back in Yakyakistan.
HM. THIS PERFECT.
You can snooze
here all afternoon
cause you're gonna need a lot
of energy for my party tonight.
That wasn't so hard.
WAIT!
THIS NOT YAK HAY!
Well, we didn't have actual
hay from Yakyakistan,
but we tried our best to
make it just like yours--
NOT PERFECT! YAKS DESTROY!
Pinkie Pie, what do we do?
And now, for your
entertainment pleasure,
presenting, "Animals,
Yakyakistan Style."
ANIMALS CUTE!
OH. Thank goodness.
WAIT. THESE ANTLERS A LIE!
THESE NOT YAKYAKISTAN ANIMALS!
YAKS SMASH!
OK, well, there's still other
things we can do...I think.
Yes, these are some of my
favorite materials, very rare,
imported from the Crystal Empire
to match your Northern
sensibilities.
I hope you'll find them...
delicious.
This no taste like yak fabric!
YAKS DESTROY!
Everything's gonna be fine;
you just make it
up to them somehow.
Listen up! Tell your faces
to hold onto their frowns,
cause they're about to
get turned upside down.
HOLD YOUR FROWN, FACE!
Hit it, Rainbow Dash!
Just like Yakyakistan
snow, right?
Because snow is snow, no
matter where it comes from.
THIS NOT YAK SNOW!
Seriously?
You know? It's going OK.
Satisfactory, I'd say.
It could be better.
It's not very good.
It's a disaster!
Pinkie Pie. Tonight's
Yakyakistan-theme party
is more important than ever.
You'll make them forget all
about this afternoon, right?
Because if it's not perfect,
they're going to
smash everything,
and I'm not sure how much more
smashing this visit can take!
I definitely will,
I think... maybe?
You're the best gosh-darn
party planner in Equestria.
You'll show 'em a good time.
You can do it.
We have absolute confidence in
your abilities, Pinkie Pie.
It's going to be my most
happy-tacular party ever...
I hope!
Why are your eyes
darting around like that?
It's what I do when I'm not
nervous! Hahahahahahaha!
Pinkie Pie, I don't know
what we'd do without you.
Me either! GOTTA GO!
Gummy! What am I gonna do?
I have all this amazing
stuff planned for the party
but they're going to hate it!
There's no way to make Equestria
feel like Yakyakistan.
They're just too sensitive.
Even Fluttershy made
them mad. FLUTTERSHY!
Oh, I need a new idea,
and I need it now.
How am I supposed to make this
party feel like Yakyakistan
without actually going there
and bringing something back?
Gummy, you're a genius!
And this is Sugarcube Corner.
They're working hard to make you
a traditional Yakyakistan cake.
VANILLA EXTRACT
BALANCE VERY TRICKY!
Do you mind, um, waiting
here for one moment?
How's tonight's party coming?
I'm doing what I can, but it's
really up to you at this point.
Pinkie? Where are you?
Did you find her?
Angel and I searched
the forest, but...
Aerial recon turned
up nothing, either.
I searched the farm inside
and out. No Pinkie Pie.
But I did find a set of
Granny Smith's dentures
under the house. So...not
a complete loss.
She's simply vanished!
But the party, it's all we have
left. What are we going to do?
"Don't worry. I'll be back
in time for the party.
Love, Pinkie Pie."
If Pinkie Pie says she'll be
back in time for the party,
she'll be back.
We have to trust her. Right?
No reason to FREAK OUT.
Don't worry, Twilight.
When it comes to parties,
I think she knows
what she's doing.
You're right, let's just focus
on keeping the yaks happy
till she's back.
Piece of cake.
The cake!
One bite and you'll
be transported
right back to
Yakyakistan. Ha ha!
I hope.
PONIES TOO HEAVY ON
VANILLA EXTRACT! BWAR!
We've never needed
a party so badly.
Next stop, Crystal Empire!
And so my quest begins.
I know what you're thinking:
"Why go to Yakyakistan
alone, Pinkie Pie?"
Because I'm the party planner.
This burden falls on my
rump, and my rump alone.
If I want a great party,
I gotta climb the mountains
North of the Crystal Empire,
find Yakyakistan, and come
back with something authentic.
Know what I mean?
Did we go the wrong way?
Where's all the snow?
Please tell me this is
magical sand-colored snow!
Pthew! Nope! Sand.
Definitely sand.
Dodge City. End of
the line, I'm afraid.
All trains had to stop. Sheep
decided to sit on the tracks.
CURSE YOU, SHEEP!
Thanks for your help, Conductor.
Cherry Jubilee!
Pinkie Pie? I reckoned
I eyeballed you
crossin' my way right now.
How ARE you? You look
amazing! I need help!
I'm dandy as a daffodil
and fit as a floribunda.
What can I do ya for?
Have you heard of Yakyakistan?
Do you have ANY idea
how I could get there?
Mark your calender, missy,
cause this right
here's your lucky day.
I'm headin' north to the Crystal
Empire myself for a delivery.
I oughta warn you, though. Me
and the boys are powerful tired
cause we was up all
night countin' cherries.
Hey there! Wake up!
Counting cherries? How many?
Four hundred and
seventeen thousand,
two hundred and
thirty-four. YEE-HAW!
Whoa!
And so my quest resumes.
As I stare across
the endless desert,
I tell myself I will soon
triumphantly enter the homeland
of our noble guests
and return with a prize
to make the best party
they've ever seen.
You know what I mean?
Cherry?
RAVINE! RAVINE!
WAKE UP!
STOP!
Whoa! I was dreamin'
about a ravine.
RAVINE!
That's what I said!
MUSIC BEAUTIFUL! MUCH SOUL!
Phew.
When Twilight told me to
stall, I mean,entertain you,
I thought "there's
NO way I could--"
Huh?
Spike!
PIANO PLAY ITSELF?
MUSIC A LIE! BWAR!
WE DEMAND PARTY! PARTY
NOW, OR YAKS NO FRIENDS!
No! Just a little longer!
NO MORE LONGER! WE LEAVE NOW!
YAKS GO GET TRAIN!
RETURN WITH MORE YAKS!
WE DECLARE WAR!
No Pinkie Pie? What's this?
Heh heh. We panicked and
tried to plan our own party.
It's sorta panic-themed.
The yaks are going
home! This is awful!
I wanted to surprise
Princess Celestia.
Now the only surprise is that I
may have just started a war.
There we were, face to face
with Falling Pony Ravine.
Down! Down! Down! And
then suddenly-- POW!
We were rescued MID-AIR
by the Wonderbolts!
And then they gave me
a ride to Manehattan
where I joined a travelling band
and we played some shows
here and there, got popular,
almost made it big until
creative differences
tore us apart.
And that's when I knew I had
to get back on with my journey
to the Crystal Empire, the
gateway to Yakyakistan!
And so, here I am! It
was a major adventure
that took most of the afternoon.
You know what I mean?
This is it: the northern
boundary of the Crystal Empire.
Beyond lies Yakyakistan.
Nopony who's attempted this
climb has ever returned.
Are you sure you
have to do this?
I do.
Good luck, Pinkie Pie.
How could she be so late to the
party? This isn't like her.
I'm sure she's trying her best.
Pinkie Pie's tougher
than she looks.
I know you're right,
but...I wish she was here.
I put too much pressure on
her. I let everypony down.
And Princess Celestia
will be here any minute
and see that I haven't made new
friends. I've made new enemies.
Hi! My name is Pinkie Pie!
I'm looking for Yakyakistan.
You know: faraway land, lots of
yaks. Maybe you've heard of it?
Whoa, slow down, I can't
understand a word you're saying.
There it is! Yakyakistan!
Noooooooo!
Is everypony all right?
I can't tell if my eyes
are opened or closed.
I think I can
see a little bit.
Nope.
Ooooooooh!
Look at these. Pinkie Pie's made
files for everypony in town.
With exactly what kind
of parties we like.
Pinkie Pie has a Secret Party
Planning Cave! How cool is this?
Twilight Sparkle likes
vanilla ice cream,
red balloons, dancing.
That's right.
But she's afraid
of quesadillas.
No I'm not!
They're just so
cheesy.
No! I'm all the way
back where I started!
Gummy, I was this close
to helping Twilight
befriend the yaks!
Now I've just let
everypony down.
Lookie here.
It's notes for the party
she wants to throw for her
folk's 50th anniversary.
But they ain't nearly that old.
Huh. She's already
plannin' their 100th, too.
And their 500th?
I had no idea she worked
so hard on her parties.
She may be more organized
than you, Twilight.
Let's not get carried away.
I just wish Pinkie Pie were here
so we could tell her how much we
all appreciate her hard work.
Thank you, thank you! I
love you too, all of you!
You're back!
I tried to go to Yakyakistan so
I could bring something back
for my party but at the last
second I made a mistake.
I worked harder on this
party than any party ever,
but I'm still just
a big failure.
Pinkie Pie, you're
not a failure.
What matters is
how hard you tried.
Who else would've gone
all across Equestria
to plan one party?
You know, the trip
was really hard,
but everypony I met along
the way was so helpful.
I just wish the yaks could see
how friendly and wonderful
and great Equestria really is.
I JUST GOT THE BEST
PARTY IDEA EVER!
It's too late. The yaks
left on the last train.
Um, no they didn't.
Trust me, there are a whole
lot of sheep out there.
So, do we walk back
up the slide, or what?
YAKS STUCK HERE? WHY
TRAINS NOT WORK? GRRRR!
I never thought I'd say
this, but THANK YOU, SHEEP!
And now, if it's OK with
you, it's party time.
Wow, Pinkie, this came
together quick, even for you.
What can I say? I'm
good at what I do.
Prince Rutherford,
every time we tried
to make something in Equestria
feel like Yakyakistan,.
we couldn't get it right.
When I got back from my
adventure, I realized something.
We shouldn't try to make
Equestria feel like your home.
We should try to make you
feel at home in Equestria.
And that means showing
you why we love it here,
so you'll love it too.
Pink pony work hard to make yaks
feel at home. Now yaks happy.
No declare war.
Ponies and yaks. Friends?
For a thousand moons?
For a thousand MOONS!
I am very impressed, Princess.
Ha hah. Just doing my
best to spread friendship.
And you did a wonderful job
of it. You and your friends.
Pink Pony? You
understand yaks now.
Aw, come here, you.
Wow, too strong. OK! OK! OK!