♪♪
[birds chirping]
[gasping for air] Twilight?
Can you slow down a bit?
Sorry, Spike. It's just Pinkie
Pie, Rarity and Applejack
are getting back from their
Seaward Shoals boat trip.
And I can't wait to
hear all about it!
It's such a shame Rainbow Dash
and Fluttershy had to miss it
for their Cloudsdale
Flight School reunion.
Maybe the rest of us not going
was for the best anyway.
I know the three of them
were really looking forward
to getting out of their element.
Getting out of their element?
I think they all just
wanted to try something new.
Huh. I guess a boat
trip qualifies as that.
My only worry is
they'll be so excited,
they'll talk over
each other
and I'll miss some
of the details.
Just to be safe, I may
need you to take notes.
Uh, right.
[train chugging]
[steam hisses]
So how was the trip?
Well, at least you don't
have to worry about them
talking over each other.
Hearing impaired subtitles
By YayPonies
Yar har har Pony Piracy and Pirate Pony!
https://yp1.yayponies.eu
♪♪
I don't know what happened
on that boat trip,
but once Rarity, Applejack,
and Pinkie Pie have some tea
and talk it out, I'm sure
everypony will feel better.
[knock at door]
Come on in,
everypony.
Gummy, Opalescence, and
Winona? This is a surprise.
Are Pinkie Pie, Rarity
and Applejack with you?
"Sorry darling, but I must
decline the invitation
to your soirée.
While I'm sure it will be
positively resplendent,
there are certain ponies I'd
rather not associate with
at the moment. Rarity."
Rarity's not coming? Aww.
So I polished my
scales for nothing.
"Sorry I can't make it,
but I'm still a mite upset
about everything that happened
on the boat. Applejack."
"Sorry I can't make
the tea party today,
but there's a small problem
with the guest list.
Plus, I'm right in the middle
of a very important cupcake.
Pinkie."
Come on, Spike. Since our
friends won't come here
and tell us what happened,
we'll just have to go to them.
Right behind you.
[gasp]I am sorry, but
my mane wasn't made
to support marine life.
Ruined. Completely ruined.
I don't know, Rarity.
Maybe you could--
Throw it away? Yes, I agree.
Just another innocent casualty
of that disastrous boat trip.
About that.
Spike and I were wondering
what happened out there.
Please, darling, I don't
know if I'll ever be able
to discuss it. It's
far too painful.
If it's too difficult
to talk about,
we completely understand.
Well, since you
dragged it out of me:
It all started
at the docks.
I knew Applejack and Pinkie
Pie wanted to get out
of their element, so I
thought I would surprise them
with an elegant cruise.
I had brought a small bag with
just a few key essentials.
All right, ponies.
Prepare yourselves for
luxury on the high seas!
That sounds... fun.
The sea air carries a portent
for trouble this day.
T'is a treacherous
and perilous journey
that lies ahead of us.
We sail to adventure
or our very doom.
I have no idea
what you just said,
but your wardrobe is
delightfully seaworthy!
Despite Applejack's
colorful seafarer attitude,
I was still determined
to get my friends
out of their element
by providing them
with all the refinements
of a luxury cruise.
I'd made sure to bring the
most delectable nibbles
for them to enjoy.
Oooh. I brought food, too!
Let's see, I've got cotton
candy, taffy, circus peanuts
and lots of other
super-yummy stuff.
Oooh Pinkie Pie, that all
looks positively delectable,
but you simply must try one
of these cucumber sandwiches.
Dig in!
Hmmm.
Arrgh! Get those off me ship!
[splash]
[bubbling]
Ohh, I'm so sorry.
I had no idea you had such
distaste for cucumbers!
Yar-har-har-har!
Hardy-har-har-har.
Hmmm. That doesn't
sound like Applejack.
Well, hold on, because
it gets even worse.
Pinkie tried to
lighten the mood
with some fun
maritime games.
It's Piñata O'clock! Wanna
give it a whack, Rarity?
Oh, darling, of course!
[thunderclap and whistling wind]
Har-har! Har-har!
I'll be chartin' a
course to the very heart
of that maelstrom.
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Uh, Applejack?
Just a thought,
but maybe we should steer the
ship toward calmer waters.
This be the only
way to Plunder Cove.
[thunder crack]
[crashing waves]
Perhaps if I take a quick
look-see at that map of yours,
I could find us a more
cruise-friendly path.
There'll be no mutiny
aboard me ship!
Look at me! I'm
the captain too!
Clearly Pinkie Pie had caught
Applejack's sea madness.
[squeals and grunts]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Is that all you've
got? Yar-hahah-HAR!
[whoosh]
Then what happened!?
Oh, the boat sank, obviously.
So, Applejack got some
sort of "sea madness"
and caused the
boat to capsize?
After all the effort I put
in to provide her and Pinkie
with the exact luxury
cruise they needed
to get out of
their elements,
that is how
Applejack thanked me.
So, you were stuck out in
the middle of the ocean?
How in Equestria
did you get back?
Spike, darling, you'll
have to forgive me.
I'm far too emotionally
drained to discuss
the matter any further.
Rarity? I don't suppose
there's any chance
you might be uh, exaggerating
things just a little?
Well! I can assure you that
that is exactly what happened.
And if you don't believe
me, you can ask Pinkie Pie.
I am quite certain her
story will be the same.
So, that's what Rarity said
happened on the boat, huh?
We thought there was a
chance she might have [ahem]
embellished the
story just a tad.
So we wanted to hear about
what happened from you.
Did Applejack really
capsize the boat?
Of course not!
That's just silly.
There's no way Applejack
could have sank the boat.
I knew it!
That's a relief.
Because Rarity did!
What?!
It all started on the docks.
I knew Rarity and
Applejack wanted to get
out of their element, so
I figured I'd throw them
the funnest, silliest
boat party ever.
But I guess Rarity
had other ideas.
I thought I overpacked
until I saw Rarity
and her team of
porter ponies.
Prepare yourselves
for a luxury cruise!
A day of opulence,
decadence and extravagance!
[gulls squawking]
That sounds fun.
Ahoy, mateys! Batten
down the hatches, ya'll
'cause this here's gonna be
a boat ride of adventure!
I can live with that.
♪ [military march] ♪
Huh. They just keep coming.
Now you can't throw a silly
boat party without snacks,
so I made sure to pack
the funnest party food
I could find.
Rarity? Would you care
for some cotton candy?
It's freshly spun!
Oh, Pinkie Pie, those all
look simply... well, simple.
But they're obviously
unfit for a luxury cruise.
Now my cucumber sandwiches
on the other hoof...
Try one. Then you'll understand.
Oh, are those
chocolate-chip?
[splash]
[bubbling]
Sorry, cucumber sandwiches
are so ten seconds ago.
Wait, wait, wait. That
doesn't sound like Rarity.
Just wait until you hear
how much more unlike her
she sounds!
I thought I'd lighten
the mood with some
super-fun party boat games.
But Rarity was a
real wet blanket.
It's Piñata Time! Oooh! Wanna
give it a whack, Rarity?
[derisive laughter]
Oh, you were serious.
Well, that's adorable.
I'll give it a go!
That's the spirit. Let's get
this boat party started!
Whoa, doggy!
[thunderclap]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[splash]
[squeals and grunts]
Tug of war? Now we're talking!
Whoever wins gets to
be captain!
[screams and growls]
Or one of us could
just be captain now.
Oh don't worry, dear.
Luxury cruises never sink!
What?!
[whoosh]
And that's why
the boat sinking
was all Rarity's fault.
That seems odd. I mean,
we trust you, of course,
but it's all so
extraordinary.
Oh, it's extraordinary,
all right.
But that's exactly
what happened.
In fact, the only thing
I might have gotten wrong
was that there were
even MORE porter ponies.
But just to be safe, you
should talk to Applejack.
She'll know exactly how many
porter ponies there were.
OK, but if the boat sank,
how did you all get rescued?
Oh, that's easy. We just...
[scream] My muffins!
That's it. We've got to
go talk to Applejack.
Good idea. She'll
straighten this out.
I just really, really want to
know how they made it back.
But yeah, that'd be great, too.
Hold on a tick. Pinkie Pie
says it's Rarity's fault
And Rarity says I
sank the boat?
Well, that's plum crazy.
If you two really want to know
what happened, I'll tell ya.
Y'all know how Pinkie
Pie and Rarity wanted to
get out of their element?
Well, I brought a treasure map
to give 'em a rip-roaring,
seafaring adventure!
But they had other ideas.
La-la-la! Prepare
yourselves for the most
luxurious boat outing
that ever outed a boat!
And more fun than you
can shake a stick at
because I brought a stick!
All right, mateys. But just
y'all wait till you see
the high-seas adventure
I've got planned.
Unfortunately, they
seemed less interested
in a treasure
hunting adventure
and more interested
in snacks.
Oh darling, that food
isn't fit for a pony
of proper breeding, darling
and refinement, darling.
Now my cucumber sandwiches
on the other hoof...
Betcha I can fit
them all in my mouth!
Pinkie, darling, please!
[chomp chomp chomp]
Uh-oooh!
Agh!
[splash]
[bubbling]
Rarity, I--
Well, I never! Humpha!
Me neither! Humpha!
Do you want to say
it or should I?
I'll go.
That sure doesn't sound
like Rarity or Pinkie Pie.
Oh, it gets a sight
worse than that.
It's P.W.T.!
Piñata-whacking time!
Oh, darling, "whacking"
is a base pastime
for common ponies, doesn't
interest me in the least.
Meh.
Hee hee!
Huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[thunderclap]
[whistling wind]
Looks like we need
to change course.
Oooh! Why, this will
make a perfect tablecloth
for my cheese board.
Maybe so, but it's also the
only way to find Thunder Cove!
[giggling]
And Pinkie Pie was
just about as helpful
as a weasel in a hen house.
Captain Pinkie Pie
reporting for map duty!
[squeals]
[splash]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Hold on, everypony!
[whoosh]
Wait, so it was Rarity
and Pinkie's fault?
Yup. And maybe if
they ever apologize,
I'll consider talking
to them again.
If they all blame
each other,
I don't know how we're going
to get them to talk again.
Neither do I,
Spike. Neither do I.
♪♪
There's got to be some way
to fix this. If Applejack,
Pinkie Pie, and Rarity keep
not talking to each other,
they could forget what good
friends they really are.
I just don't get it.
All of their stories
are so different.
We're never going to figure
out what really happened.
Their stories were different,
but they also had
a lot in common.
I guess. They were all on
a ship that sank and...
that's about it.
Not quite.
♪♪
Ah-ha! Not only do I think
I know how the boat sank,
I have a pretty good idea
how to get Rarity, Applejack,
and Pinkie Pie back together!
I hope this plan of yours works.
Winona brought me your note
about a friendship emergency.
How can I help?
Opalescence delivered
your message, Twilight.
What's the emergency?
It's a good thing it was time
for Gummy's bath, or I might
not have seen your note about
the emergency, Twilight.
What's she doing here?
Sorry, but I just
didn't know how else
to get the three of
you here together.
And there really is a
friendship emergency. Yours!
Oh, there's no emergency. I'm
just waiting for an apology.
An apology?
What?
Why would you want
me to apologize,
when it was Rarity's fault?
What are you
talking about?
Applejack clearly
caused the boat to sink!
She stranded us in the
middle of the ocean!
UGH! Will somepony please
tell me how you made it back?
[gurgling]
Well, maybe it wasn't
the middle of the ocean.
[sigh]
Even so, I don't appreciate
being hornswoggled
into coming back here.
On that, at
least we agree.
Yeah.
I know you each have a
different perspective
on how the boat capsized
and blame each other...
but if you come on
the boat with me,
I'll show you what
really happened.
Well, not that I
have any doubt,
but it will feel good for
everypony to see exactly
whose fault it was.
I think we all
know which pony's
about to be proven right.
We sure do!
Like I said, I sure
hope this works.
Heh heh heh.
Whatever you're looking for,
I hope you find it soon.
Don't worry, Spike. I've
got it all under control.
While all of your stories
seemed very different,
they all had something in
common. Cucumber sandwiches!
What in the hay does that
have to do with anything?
[splash]
And why would you waste a
perfectly good hors d'œuvre?
You also mentioned
the bubbling water.
And the swell.
Cucumber just happens
to be the favorite food
of the Tri-horned Bunyip. And
bubbles, followed by a swell
is what happens when they
swim up to the shallows
from deep water!
So, we attracted a tri-horned
whatchamacallit...
With cucumber
sandwiches?
Sounds like a stretch.
Hello, Bunyip, sir.
So that's a...
A Tri-horned Bunyip...
Who's very sorry
he accidentally
knocked over your
boat, right?
Wait; the storm had nothing
to do with the capsizing?
Nope.
All right. Even if our friend
the Bunyip is responsible
for sinking the boat,
that still doesn't excuse
a certain pony's behavior.
Me!? How about you
and Pinkie Pie?
Pfft! Wha-?! How- ME?--
Twilight: I think I can
explain that too.
Each one of you spent so
much time trying to come up
with the perfect way
to get the others
out of their element,
that you didn't notice
your friends were
doing the same thing.
Wait a minute. You brought all
those games and things for us?
Of course! I figured the boat
trip was the perfect time
to do things that
were silly and fun.
And I was just trying
to give the two of you
the elegant cruise I
thought you deserved.
And I just wanted to give you
two a high seas adventure,
since that'd be something
new and different for y'all.
OOOOHHHHHHH.
That is so sweet.
You must have gone
through so much trouble.
Well, not half as much
trouble as you did
making all that fancy food.
And bringing all those games.
I guess this just teaches us
that even longtime friends
need to work at communication.
Well, there's something
I'd like to communicate
to you all right now.
You girls are the best friends
a pony could ever have.
Oh, let's never
fight again!
Agreed.
You've got it!
[growl]
All right, you big
softy. Bring it in.
Come on, Bunyip,
sir. You've got it!
♪♪
One thing's for sure, Spike.
There's nothing like a
luxurious adventure boat party
to get you out of your element.
Spike: You said it!