♪♪
Applejack: The map
is sending us WHERE?!
Fluttershy: Las Pegasus?
But Las Pegasus is a
wild vacation spot.
It's just one big party!
All those lights and sounds,
not to mention the crowds!
Oh! Just the thought
of it is overwhelming.
I know Las Pegasus doesn't seem
like either of your cups of tea,
but I have total faith you
wouldn't have been called
unless you were the perfect
ponies for the job.
Probably not as
bad as we think.
It can't just be
a loud obnoxious party
all the time... right?
Uh, Applejack. It isn't
as bad as we thought.
PARTY ALL NIGHT! WHOO-HOO!
You're right.
It's worse!
♪ [big band swing] ♪
Hearing impaired subtitles
By YayPonies
\_o<
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
[loud music and chatter]
[gasp]
Do you think the map could
be on the fritz again?
I mean, this place seems a
lot more suited to Pinkie Pie
or even Rainbow Dash.
If Twilight trusts
the map then so do I.
All we have to do is solve
our friendship problem
and get back home.
Of course, we have
to find it first.
And make sure to experience
our signature show:
Poné Fantastique!
Trust me when I say you've
never seen anything like it!
Unparalleled acrobatics,
unique animal antics!
Your only regret will be that
you didn't see it sooner!
And like everything at
this amazing, incredible,
"I can't believe it
even exists" hotel,
Poné Fantastique is
brought to you by the
Chairpony of Kindness,
Gladmane himself!
[swoons and shouts]
Wow. This Gladmane
sure seems impressive.
[southern gentleman voice] Well,
uh, it is a little embarrassin'.
But the crowds seem to
like it, uh-huh-huh.
Mr. Gladmane?
Just Gladmane'll do.
And it's a pleasure
to meet actual cohorts
of the Princess
of Friendship!
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much.
You know who we are?
I'm what you might call a
friendship connoisseur,
so naturally I'm familiar
with the friends of the great
Twilight Sparkle!
Applejack, Fluttershy,
it's an honor to have
you here, uh-huh-huh.
I have to admit you're
not the type of pony
I expected to find
in Las Pegasus.
[laugh]
My guests may be looking for
lights, music, and parties,
but working hard
and making friends
is how I turned this hotel
into what it is today.
And how I plan to make it
even bigger. Uh-huh-huh.
Uh, excuse me one second.
Wise ponies may say the folks
that come here are customers,
but I can't help
but thinkin'
of each and every
one of you as friends.
That's why there's a three-for-
one special on apple fritters
in the cafe for the next
hour. Enjoy! Uh-huh-huh.
[excited shouts]
Would you two like to
take a tour of the place?
I'm just about to
do my rounds
and check on my
friends who work here.
We do have a friendship
problem to find.
Lead the way, Mr. Gladmane.
Just Gladmane,
now, you hear?
AH! Gladmane! You're just in
time to see my newest move!
New moves or not, I'm glad
to have a star like you
working for me,
I'll-tell-you-what.
Oh, don't make me
blush. Now watch this!
♪♪
Stellar, ah-huh-huh!
[French accent] Hon-hon, Monsieur
Gladmane himself is here.
Let's run through
the whole routine!
Now, don't make a
fuss for ol' me.
I'm just gonna keep on giving
a tour to my new friends,
Applejack and Fluttershy.
Hi.
Howdy.
If this pony
calls you friend,
you're welcome
backstage anytime.
I owe him my
entire career.
Oh shucks. Well, let's leave
the artists to their work.
Doesn't look like there's any
friendship problems here.
I've never seen a pink
prairie dog before.
I like the folks
that come here
to have a unique
experience, uh-huh-huh.
[German accent] And
we love him for it.
With Gladmane's help,
we've been able to take care
of all these little guys.
Now this place is
overwhelming in a good way.
Oh, glad you like it.
[ahem] Fluttershy?
Hmm? Oh, um. Coming.
There doesn't seem
to be anything wrong
around here at all.
I figured looking for
a friendship problem
in Las Pegasus would be like
trying to find a needle
in a stack of needles,
but everypony seems to be
getting along just fine.
Ladies and gentleponies,
despite what my
competition might say,
I know you've come to this
fair city to be entertained,
and I assure you
there is nothing more
entertaining than the
astounding acrobatics in
Gladmane's Poné Fantastique!
Oh, I suppose that might be true
if it weren't for the existence,
and far superiorly
entertaining presence,
of the show-stopping
exotic animal act
that Poné Fantastique includes!
Those voices
sound familiar.
They sure do.
Flim and Flam.
Why, I won't even dignify that
assertion with a response,
except to say that if you were
to consider buying your tickets
from me, I might consider
offering them to you
at a substantial discount.
I have always thought
you get what you pay for
and in my humble opinion,
these tickets are a
value at twice the price!
Don't let this price-gouging
charlatan take you for a ride!
[gasp] Charlatan!?
How dare you?!
Ha! How dare I?
Yes, how dare you.
I call them
like I see them
[mumbled arguing]
Well, they certainly don't
seem to be getting along.
[gasp] You don't suppose we've
been brought here to help them?
Absolutely not!
[arguing]
I know you and the rest
of the Apple Family
have had your issues with
Flim and Flam in the past,
but they're definitely
having trouble
and solving a friendship
problem is important,
no matter who's
having it.
Well, of course
that's true.
For anypony but them!
I'm sorry you had to see
that. I don't know why,
but those two've been fightin'
ever since they got here.
I thought giving them
these jobs might help,
but I guess it just
made matters worse.
Trust me; I know
those ponies
and you're better off
with them apart.
The two of them together
will cheat the hooves
right out from under you.
I suppose you're right.
Flim's such a showpony
and Flam has such a
head for business.
Why, if they ever
did work together,
they'd be runnin' this
place in two shakes.
Speaking of which, I
better get back to work.
Y'all enjoy your
stay now, ya hear?
I'm pretty sure we should
help Flim and Flam.
And I'm pretty sure there's
another friendship problem here
and I'm gonna search this resort
top to bottom till I find it.
[sigh]
I hope you didn't travel
all the way from Ponyville
to try to get me to reconcile
with my no-account brother!
Brother? I don't believe
I have one of those.
Oh, I already know
what he thinks of me,
all show and
no substance.
Well, if he's so smart,
he should have no trouble
becoming a big
success on his own!
Why, he's the greatest salespony
that ever lived, of course!
Just ask him; he'll
tell you all about it!
I'm sure you could work
out your differences
if you just sat down and
talked to each other.
I'm never speaking
to that pony again!
[sigh]
[loud music and
rattling machines]
NO! You are
ruining my show!
It isn't just your show
and I'm improving it!
You don't pull a rabbit
out of a hat on a trapeze!
That's the point!
To give the audience
something they've never seen
before: acrobatic magic!
♪ TA DA. ♪
It's called "blending
genres" and it's AWESOME!
Shouldn't somepony do something?
Ha! They've been doing this
since they started working here.
Too bad, really. If they ever
stopped shouting at each other,
we could take the show on tour.
They'd be way more successful
than staying at Gladmane's.
Now, that sounds like a
real friendship problem!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Stop! What are
you doing?
It's supposed to be a
Pink Prairie Dog Pyramid.
It's alliterative!
You said a tower! Why do you
keep changing everything?!
I'm not changing anything.
You said pyramid!
ARGHHH! You are
driving me crazy!
I thought you
two got along.
We used to.
But we just can't seem to
agree on anything anymore.
We used to perform
all over Equestria,
but if we can't
agree on a new act,
we might as well stay
at Gladmane's forever.
[knock knock]
Two friendship problems in the
same theater? Now we're talking!
If you count Flim and Flam,
that's three big friendship
problems all in the same place.
Well, I don't
count Flim and Flam
since those two not being
friends isn't a problem.
It certainly isn't
for Gladmane.
It sounds like he's better
off with them fighting.
Actually, the other
ponies' problems
seem to be good
for Gladmane too.
Both the trapeze show and the
animal act would be better off
if they left, but everypony is
so busy arguing that they can't.
Do you think he knows?
I don't know. But I'm starting
to think we should find out.
Of course, Gladmane wants
everypony to get along!
He's the nicest, most
genuine pony I've ever met.
Did the director
put you up to this?
[whispering noises]
I tell you, if Gladmane
is your friend,
you are welcome backstage,
but if you are speaking
of him poorly, you leave!
Gladmane is the
kindest, most gentle...
...most compassionate
pony I've ever known.
My problem is with him!
I just can't figure it.
The only pony who benefits from
all this feudin' is Gladmane,
but by all accounts
he's the best friend
any of these
ponies have.
Well, Bernard, that adorable
bunny from the acrobat's hat,
claims that every morning,
Gladmane tells the director
that the star wants
control of the show.
And every afternoon
tells the star
that the director wants to get
rid of her. But neither is true.
And the Flying Prairinos,
the Pink Prairie Dog family,
say Gladmane keeps
changing their act
to make each trainer think
the other is doing it.
So, all his talk
about friendship
is just a load of
apple sauce.
He's gettin' them all to fight
with each other on purpose!
But how can we get everypony to
believe that's what he's doing?
There must be a way to trick
him into telling the truth.
Gee, if only
there was a pony
who knew how to
trick a trickster.
[shouted argument]
Or maybe, a pair
of ponies.
[sigh]. Fine. I guess bringing
Flim and Flam back together
might be why we're
here. Maybe.
Sorry if I don't take the word
of some pony off the street.
Even if that street
is in Ponyville.
But Gladmane is behind so many
other friendship problems,
how can you be sure he
isn't the cause of yours?
Because the only problem I
have is standing right there.
Same here, buster.
Do either of you even know
what you're fighting over?
Gladmane let me know
that ex-brother of mine
thinks I'm just a mouthpiece
without a single good idea.
Gladmane assured me this
former, fraternal foal here
thinks I couldn't sell
heat lamps to yaks.
Sounds to me like neither
of you said those things.
Why'd you believe Gladmane
when he said you did?
Why would he lie?
Because he's afraid that
the two of you together
could move in and
take over his resort.
And if I'm telling
you he said it,
you know it's the
absolute truth because...
You never lie!
Oh, brother of mine, I think
it's time for a little payback.
The "Canterlot Two-step?"
We don't have the chickens. How
about the "Baltimare Flare"?
Uh, my flare isn't
what it used to be.
[Gladmane over loudspeaker]
Listen here, y'all.
If you're a friend of
mine, you're entitled
to a free night's stay.
And everypony here's a
friend of mine! Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Are you thinking
what I am?
The "High
Roller Hustle"!
The what now?
Trust us, when we're done,
there won't be a pony in town
who doesn't know the
Applejackiest truth
about Gladmane.
That is, assuming you
two are willing to help.
What size gown
do you wear?
[excited murmurs]
What's all the fuss, now?
It's the grand-matriarch of the
Rich family, Impossibly Rich.
She's one of the wealthiest
ponies in Equestria.
Well, why didn't
somepony tell me?
You know how I like to give
VIP guests my personal touch.
Well, she's not
exactly a guest.
Word is she's planning
a resort of her own.
I think she's here to
scout the competition.
Oh, really?
And with her bits, she could
take over the whole strip,
hire away anypony
she wants.
[snarl]
Not me, of course.
I love it here.
My good-for-nothing
brother on the other hoof.
Pfft. Impossibly Rich! What
an honor it is to have you
at my humble
five-hoof resort!
I'm sure Flam has
done an excellent job
showing you around,
but nothing could beat
a personalized tour from The
Mane himself! Ah-huh-huh?
[whispering]
You'll have to excuse Ms.
Rich, she saves the energy
other ponies spend talking
out loud and uses it
to make more money.
[whispers]
She'd love a personal tour,
say, in uh, about an hour?
Well, that sounds
right pleasant.
And if you can break
away for a moment, Flam,
I'd love to see you in my
office so I can get ready.
Are all of you sure
this is a good idea?
Abso-tively!
Gladmane is one fish
that's hooked but good.
I sure hope you two
know what you're doing.
Oh don't you worry.
When it comes to throwing
ponies off their game...
...no two ponies do
it better than us.
I can't argue with that.
Hey there boss, Impossibly
Rich is just about ready
for that tour. So what did
you wanna see me about?
Actually, there's something
I want you to see.
The grand plan: Every hotel on
the strip as amazin' as this one
and every one of them mine.
[admiring whistle]
And all it'll take is a little
salesponyship. Like this.
Hey there, friends, ah-huh-huh!
If you think my
resort is fantastic,
wait till you see
Poné Fantastique.
Tickets are on sale now.
Two for the price of one.
Thank you. Thank
you very much.
Now I know Impossibly
Rich has probably
made you a tempting offer
to come work for her.
Well, now that
you mention it...
And as your friend, I'd
never tell you what to do,
but no pony is gonna stand
in the way of my plans,
no matter how rich she is.
And I sure wouldn't want you
to end up on the losing side.
Think you might
consider staying here?
Yeah.
Well, all right, then.
They're coming!
And last, but not least, Ms.
Rich, the jewel in my crown.
[whispers]
Impossibly wants you to
know she's very impressed.
But doesn't think
you can keep a resort
of this calibre
going for long.
Oh, and why is that?
[whispers]
Because you've got the best
talent in the industry.
What stops them from just
leaving to join any competitor?
[laugh] Well, you see,
I have a trick for that,
I must confess, ah-huh-huh.
And it all has to do with
how I handle my employees.
And how is that?
Well... LIKE FRIENDS, of course!
And I treat every
one of my employees
with the kindness
they deserve!
Oh. That's it?
THAT'S your secret?
There's nothing else?
Nope. Just friendship.
But you know all about
friendship, don't you...
FLUTTERSHY?
You knew the whole time?
Never try to con a con-pony!
Uh-huh-huh! [mocking laughter]
I'd have thought you'd
hit the road by now.
Whether we were able
to fool you or not,
you can't just go on keeping
ponies from getting along.
It's just mean!
Now maybe it is, but it's
a meanness that works,
unlike your pathetic
little ploy.
I practically invented
the "High Roller Hustle."
But I suppose I
should be impressed.
You're the only ponies to
ever figure out the secret
to my success.
It takes a lot of work
keepin' everypony fightin',
but as long as I keep 'em
convinced I'm their only friend,
all of Las Pegasus will be mine.
Oh, you can't trick a confession
out of a pony like me.
I am always one step ahead.
Well, you better
check your hooves.
Because... you've just
stepped in a confession.
Oh no. Oh no. Wait, wait.
Did that sound OK?
Never better!
Flim and Flam told us
you'd see right through
the fake rich pony bit.
And that once you did,
you wouldn't be able to
resist gloating about it.
This was all part of the plan.
Oh now, now friends! Listen
I can explain everything!
I think you've done
enough of that.
Darling?
Oh! I cannot believe we let him
almost ruin our friendship.
And our act. Good luck
finding another one.
Wait! No! Y'all COME BACK!
C'mon I'm gonna be ruined!
This is Gladmane, y'all!
C'mon you can't do this!
Gladmane has left
the building!
[crash]
I guess the map wasn't
on the fritz after all.
If it weren't for your
history with Flim and Flam,
you never would have be
so determined to find
somepony else to help
and we never would have found
out what Gladmane was doing.
And if it weren't for you
wanting to show even those
two con ponies kindness,
we never would have been
able to trick the trickster.
It must've felt pretty
nice to finally put
all your connivin' and
cheatin' skills to good use.
In fact, we like to think of it
as a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
Emphasis on the "once."
What do you mean?
While this establishment
undergoes a slight change
in management, my brother
and I want to assure you
that it remains the pinnacle
of Las Pegasus entertainment.
Which is why we invite
each and every one of you
to experience the wonder of
the Poné Fantastique Theater
at half the normal
cost of admission.
And, while you're appreciating
this historic venue,
totally devoid of
performers of any kind,
we invite you to use the wonder
of your own imaginations
to fill the space at
no additional charge!
[excited chatter]
Applejack: FLIM AND FLAM!!