Well, that's the last
of it, Filthy Rich.
Just Rich, please. And on behalf
of Rich's Barnyard Bargains,
thanks for another season's
shipment of Zap Apple Jam.
Our pleasure. See
ya next time!
Uh, Apple Bloom? Did you pack up
the cider into the same crates
as the Zap Apple Jam?
Sure did! Now that
I'm getting older,
I want to prove I can handle
more responsibility on the farm.
But the crates aren't marked.
You kept track of what when
into which crate, right?
Oh. Um... Yep. I totally
kept track of everything.
Good. Because we wouldn't want
Filthy Rich to get a shipment
of cider when he's supposed
to get Zap Apple Jam.
You know how Granny
feels about selling cider
anywhere but
on the farm.
Are you sure he
got the right crates?
Sure, I'm sure!
Now why don't you and Big
Mac head on out to the house
and let me finish up here!
If you gave Rich the Zap Apple
Jam, then what's this here?
Um... Extra?
Nnope!
Regular subtitles
By YayPonies
#APPLEJACK2016 - MAKE CIDER ALCOHOLIC AGAIN!
https://yp1.yayponies.eu
Granny knows I wasn't trying
to make off with a shipment
of cider, right? Because
I would never do that.
Don't worry. We know
exactly whose fault it was.
Now, why in tarnation would
you lie to me, Apple Bloom?
I was kinda hoping I could fix
it before anypony found out.
Telling lies won't fix
anything. Trust me, I know.
What could you
possibly know about it?
You've never told a
lie in your whole life.
What's so funny?
Oh, sugar cube, your
big sister lied so much
when she was a filly, the whole
family ended up in the hospital.
WHAT?!
Eeyup.
You might as well
tell her the whole story.
It might even do
her some good.
When Applejack and Big Mac
were just a wee bit older
than you are now, they
both kept squabblin' over
who would run
the farm better.
All I'm sayin' is that you
may have plenty of brawn,
but I'm the one with the
ideas on how to run things
better around here.
Applejack, Applejack,
Applejack.
Ideas are all
well and good,
but you can't plow
a field with them.
I don't know how many
times I've told you that.
Too many!
You two horned toads better stop
jabberin' and get to workin'!
Yeah they'd better! I
need you to go to town.
The apple blight's been awful
and if we don't get more spray,
cider season'll be shorter
than a dwarf crab-apple tree.
Like I was just telling
cousin Braeburn last week;
now there's a pony who knows how
to put his back into a problem.
Oh hi there, Filthy Rich!
Just Rich, please.
And I'd like you to meet
my fiancée, Spoiled Milk.
Honey, this is
Applejack and Big Mac,
the two hardest-working
ponies at Sweet Apple Acres.
You work on a farm?
How... quaint.
Oh ho now,
dear, be nice.
Sweet Apple Acres
makes Zap Apple Jam.
It's one of Dad's
best-sellers.
You mean one of
your best-sellers.
My amazing husband-to-be
is running the
Rich family business now. Did
you know that? Well, now you do.
Don't mind Spoiled Milk.
She's just proud of me.
But she's right; I'm in
charge of the store now
and I'm just bursting
with ideas I wanna try.
Like what?
Well, how about this? Cider
season's around the corner.
Why not let me
sell it for you?
That is an
interesting idea.
Well, maybe it's interesting
and maybe it ain't,
but it's definitely
not a new idea.
Granny Smith told us your
grandpa, Stinkin' Rich,
used to ask her every year
if he could sell our cider
in your store, and Granny
told him every year
about the tradition of
everypony in Ponyville
lining up out at
Sweet Apple Acres.
So, start a new tradition!
Someday one of you'll
take over the farm
just like I've taken
over the store.
I'm guessing it'll be the
one with the best ideas.
Well, now, as I've said
many a time before,
ideas are all well and good,
but you can't plow a field--
You know what? How about
we give you three barrels
of cider early, and
if it sells well,
we'll make a deal
for the rest.
Oh, hey now! Perfect!
Come on, honey. I've got
to get everything ready.
Hoo-wee, I tell ya, if the
future means me running
Sweet Apple Acres and you
being quiet, I can't wait!
I just can't believe you'd
make a deal with Filthy Rich
without even talking to Granny.
Aw, Granny will love the
idea and then she'll decide
that I'm the one who should
take over the farm. You'll see.
See what?
Applejack here had another
one of her "big ideas,"
and I think we all know my
position on ideas, you...
...can't plow a
field with them.
Eey... Right.
Big idea, huh?
Actually, more of
an opportunity.
You see, we ran into
Filthy Rich in town.
Did you know he's running
the family store now?
And what does this
here "opportunity"
mean for Sweet
Apple Acres?
Well, since cider season is
almost here, he or, I mean,
I thought it'd be a good idea to
give him a few barrels of cider
to sell at the store
before the season starts.
Oh, is that all?
Absolutely not!
Hmmm.
But Granny, why can't we sell
a few barrels of cider early
to Filthy Rich? How's it any
different than when you gave
Zap Apple Jam to Filthy's
grandpappy to sell?
Your cider and your jam
ain't the same thing!
Zap Apple Jam jars preserve
the flavor for moons,
but cider starts to spoil
the second it comes
out of the press.
That is why every cider season,
all of Ponyville lines up
at Sweet Apple Acres and first
come is first served. Hmm!
I get what you're
saying, Granny,
but couldn't you make an
exception just this once?
I sorta promised.
Meh-eh. Besides, cider-makin'
is iffy business.
And we're probably not gonna
have a lot this year anyway,
what with all the blight.
I'm sorry, Applejack, but
you'll have to un-promise.
Oh!
I hate to say I told
you so, Applejack, but--
You and I both know you
don't hate to say anything.
Well, I've always thought
that the most important thing
a pony can do is say
exactly what's on his mind
to anypony who'll listen
so everypony everywhere
always knows everything
you're thinking and...
And you don't ever have to
listen to anypony else.
What?
Exactly.
Well, if it ain't my
new business partner!
Um, about the
cider, Rich...
Take a look at what I did last
night after we made our deal.
Woo! Pretty great, huh?
The thing is, I don't
think I can get you any.
What?! But I did all
this work on your say-so.
We shook hooves and
everything.
Well, you see, at
Sweet Apple Acres,
we've always been about quality
and while your basic jam jar'll-
Plus it's been a tough
harvest this year,
what with all the
blight.
Sounds to me like you're
trying to make excuses.
Whenever Granddad dealt with
Granny Smith, she kept her word.
If you can't do that,
then maybe our families
should stop doing business
together. Altogether!
Now, now, the thing is, Rich,
it ain't really up to us.
You see, Granny's--
--sick!
Wait. Granny's
sick? I had no idea!
Eey... Yeah, nopony did.
What Big Mac means is we've
been trying to keep it quiet.
We don't want people
to make rash decisions
about doing business
with Sweet Apple Acres
just because we're a little
short-hooved at the moment.
Oh my! Of course, of
course. I am so sorry.
Please let me know if
there's anything I can do.
Much appreciated. But
right now, we only ask
for your understanding
during this difficult time.
Mm hm.
Big Mac: You were supposed to
tell Rich the simple truth,
but instead you made things
worse with a giant lie!
Well, what was I supposed
to do? You heard Rich.
If I told him the truth, he
was gonna stop doing business
with us altogether.
Yeah, but that's
only because--
--I forgot to ask if we
had any oat crumbles
for this delicious-looking
salad, Granny!
I'll go take a look.
--that was only because you made
promises you couldn't keep,
but there's gotta be a
better way out of this mess
than by making up some story
about Granny being sick!
Well, it worked, didn't it?
Sorry to drop by unannounced.
We just wanted to come by to
wish Granny a speedy recovery.
Look, sis, our good friend Mr.
Rich and his fiancée are here.
Oh, and they brought
flowers. For Granny.
On account of she's sick, like
you said. Ain't that sweet?
Uh, excuse me one second!
What in tarnation?!
Oh, I'm sorry, Granny.
I didn't see you there.
You came blasting in so fast,
t'weren't possible
to see nothin'!
Can you go out to the barn?
I, uh, I think we might
have left a blight sprayer
in the orchard.
Are you outta your apple-pickin'
mind? It's suppertime, girl!
I know, but if we
forgot a sprayer,
I'd wanna get it before
dark. You go start counting
and I'll tell Big Mac
we'll be right back, OK?
So from that moment on, I
took to referring to myself
as Big or Large or--
Oh Applejack, your brother
was just explaining
why he always wears his yoke.
Even though we asked him how
your grandmare is doing.
Oh, you know how Big
Mac can get to talking,
especially when he's
upset. And right now,
he's just as worried about
Granny Smith as I am.
Oh dear. Is she doing that bad?
Well, one thing's for sure,
she shouldn't be seeing
anypony right now.
In fact, I'm getting more
upset just thinking about it.
Excuse me!
Oh, what in the frilly
fumidila has gotten into you?!
Sorry, Granny! I just
decided if I helped you,
it would go faster.
Well, you're too late.
All the sprayers are here.
Oh, good. Uh say, Granny,
when did you first fight
the apple blight again?
It was my second year
here in Ponyville
and that was before I had
the rick on the one knee.
...and others say that's how the
trees got to growing so tall,
but to me, it's just
how I got my cutie mark.
But we asked when we could
come back to see Granny!
Big Mac didn't
want to be rude,
but you just can't see Granny
right now because she's...
...got apple blight!
I thought only trees
got the blight.
Yeah, that's
usually the case.
The doctors think it's from
working in the orchard
for so many years.
You see. We had to take
Granny to Ponyville General.
We just got back right
before you showed up.
Oh my, that is terrible!
Eww, it's not
contagious, is it?
Um, I'm sure you'll be
fine, but you should leave,
just in case.
You're right. We're gonna have
to hurry if we want to get there
before visiting hours are over.
That's right. Wait. Get where?
Why, the hospital, of course.
I'm sure we'll see you there!
Telling Filthy Rich that
Granny's in the hospital
just made everything
a hundred times worse!
What are we supposed to do now?
I got it!
...dropped my second best
teeth right in the pig pen
and that was the worst case of
apple blight I've ever seen!
I'd love to hear
more Granny,
but we gotta get to the
hospital right away!
The hospital?
Why, who's sick?
You are, apparently.
What he means is, you're
needed at the hospital.
Whatever for?
It's the apple blight! It's
starting to infect ponies now!
The doctors need an expert
opinion, and nopony knows more
about fighting blight
than Granny Smith!
Well, what in tarnation are
we waiting for? Let's go!
You know, we're supposed
to go in the back.
Uh, to avoid anypony in the
waiting room with the blight.
Oops, I almost forgot!
This is perfect.
Now you don't have to worry
about catching the blight.
If you say so, dearie.
Now you wait right here while
I... check on your presentation.
What in the rotten
rhubarb's going on here?
Fancy meeting you two here!
Well, we told you
we were coming.
Oh, I'm glad we found you
because I can't seem to find
Granny's room, or any
nurses who've even heard
about a pony with
apple blight.
Granny's room. Sure. Just
go down here, take a left,
then a right, go down some
stairs, up a bunch more stairs,
through the cafeteria,
left three more times
and then you're there. Easy as
Granny's apple pie! Heh heh.
Aren't you coming with us?
I'll catch up! I
gotta find Big Mac.
OK, Granny, just wait here
one second and we can go.
Where are you
two going?
Big Mac can't come.
He, uh...
...might be contagious.
Contagious?
All right. Climb up here
and I'll cover you up.
Then I'll bring Rich in,
tell him you're Granny,
but you're not allowed
to take the sheets off.
You moan a few times, he leaves,
and this whole thing is over.
This is spinnin' way out
of control, Applejack!
Now I know you thought selling
cider in Filthy's store
was a good idea, but it
ain't worth lying to him
about Granny being sick and
needin' to go to the hospital,
or fibbin' to Granny about
them wanting her to come here
to talk about the blight, or--
BIG MACINTOSH, PLEASE JUST
LISTEN TO ME FOR ONCE!
This ain't about my ideas!
If Rich finds out
about all the lies,
he'll cut ties with us and
the farm will go under.
Now do you want that to
happen or do you wanna help?
Why can't you be Granny?
You're her size,
and this is all your fault
in the first place!
I would, but if I let
you do the talkin',
you'd just ramble on and on
until we all got caught.
Just lay down, keep still
and promise me you won't say
anything for once in your life.
Eeyup.
Granny!
Granny.
It's about time. What
is going on around here?
Granny, they need you to wait
here. I'll come get you.
There you are! We've
been going in circles
looking for Granny's room!
Well, you're in luck, 'cause
it's, it's right over here
and this time I'll make
sure you don't get lost.
What in the dadgum?
What now?
He-- I mean, "she"
was right here!
Oh no! We gotta go!
Is that
Granny Smith?
Where are they
taking her?
You two, don't lose
that gurney!
Granny, what're you doin'? You
were supposed to stay there!
It was a supply closet!
Oh! Uh, well, OK, come
with me, but be quiet.
You know, save your voice
for the big presentation.
I'm sorry, but you can't get any
closer without a gown and mask.
But-- but-but that's
my brother on there!
Don't worry. This
is our best doctor.
She'll have your brother back
on his hooves in no time.
Now, apple blight is
a serious disease.
Now then? Did she say
"apple blight?"
I think she said
"gasket mites."
And once the trunk
turns red like this,
the only thing to do
is prune the branches.
Oh no! Granny!
Did you say "prune
the branches?"
Well, sure. What
else you gonna do
once the blight
gets this bad?
Everypony just stop!
This is all a big
misunderstanding.
Actually, it's a big lie!
Big Mac?
Granny Smith? What is
going on here, Applejack?
That is a darn
good question.
I'm not sure if I was worried
that nopony was listening
to my ideas or just nervous
that I wouldn't be the one
to end up running the farm,
but I promised
something to Filthy Rich
that I couldn't deliver and I
was too embarrassed to admit it.
So Granny was never sick?
And there ain't no
apple blight in ponies?
Nope!
Those were all lies. And I
thought if you found out,
you'd stop doing
business with the farm,
so I just kept
telling more.
So, she's not a doctor?
Please don't make Granny and
the farm suffer for what I did.
This whole thing is my fault.
That's not
entirely true.
Maybe if I paid more attention
to what you had to say
instead of talking
all the time,
none of this would have
happened in the first place.
I just need to talk
less and listen more...
Especially to you.
Thanks, big brother.
And whether it's me running
Sweet Apple Acres or you,
I know it'll be in good hooves.
Well, that's nice, but I
don't know what in blazes
you two are talking about.
I ain't going anywhere anytime
soon. Pfft! Running the farm.
Not after this
display. Not likely.
And don't you go getting any
ideas about "cutting ties"
with Sweet Apple Acres, or I'm
goin right to your grandpappy.
Get me?
Um... Yes, ma'am.
Now, who here still wants to
hear about the apple blight?
Now when I was a filly...
I can't believe you
told all those lies!
It's not a story I'm
proud of,
but it taught me a lifelong
lesson about being honest.
I hope you learned
something too.
I sure did! I learned that
no pony starts out perfect
and sometimes you gotta
make a few mistakes
to figure out who you are.
Eeyup!
But I think the most
important thing I learned
is who really runs
Sweet Apple Acres...
Granny!
Yer darn tootin'! Now everypony
quit yer lolly-gaggery
and get back to work. Right
after we have a glass of cider!