♪♪
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
Oooo, be careful!
♪♪
[clatter]
Oh!
Are you OK, Angel?
[loud crying]
I told you that entering the
Ponyville Paw-Kour contest
was a dangerous idea.
You just rest here and I'll have
you all fixed up in no time.
♪♪
Oh, dear. I'm all out
of bunny foot braces.
I think we need to pay
a visit to Dr. Fauna.
[whimpering]
♪♪
[grunts]
I was sure that she
would be here today.
Hello? Is anypony there?
Fluttershy? Oh, am
I glad to see you!
I wish I could say the same,
but the door is stuck so,
I um... can't see you.
Ooh. Somebunny hurt his foot!
Let's bandage that up
so he can get back home.
I'd like to keep him overnight,
but as you can see
my place is just
bursting with animals.
I don't think I can take in even
one more critter right now.
[sneeze]
Both: Oh, dear.
♪♪
[animal sounds]
[gasp]
[thud]
You really have your
hooves full here.
This place is like a zoo!
Then again, it's normally
like that but still...
I can't keep up!
Now does my favorite wittle
bunny want a carrot-pop?
[raspberry]
[sigh]
That's OK. I think the goats
ate all of them, anyway.
[burp]
I just can't believe all these
poor little animals are hurt!
What happened?
I'm flummoxed!
Every day, there's more and
more animals on my doorstep.
Most of them just
have minor ailments:
hurt wings, stuffy
noses and such.
But the trouble is, even
after they're all healed up,
I can't seem to get these
comfy critters to leave!
Oh, dear!
They do seem to have made
themselves right at home here.
I wonder why they chose
to flock to my office.
It just doesn't
make sense.
Don't be silly, Dr. Fauna.
You're the best Vet
Pony in Equestria!
At least that's what I've
been telling everypony.
Ah, you did what?
Oh, no! Do you suppose it's
my fault? I'm so sorry;
I didn't mean for
this to happen.
I just know animals feel safe
and happy under your care.
[chirping]
Normally, I don't mind if a
snake wants to slither in
or a raccoon needs a rest. But
now this place is so full,
I have no space to treat
any injured animals!
That is a big problem.
That I'm going to
fix for you!
I already have the
perfect solution
that'll make the critters
happy and give you more space!
Then you'll have all
your ducks in a row.
♪♪
The sooner you fix
it, the better!
I'm on it.
[sob]
I want to thank you all
for rushing right
over when I called.
[angry chittering]
Dr. Fauna needs my help
with a serious problem.
A friendship problem?
No. Her vet clinic is a
bit maybe um... overrun
with adorable critters in
dire need of a safe place
to lay their heads and...
... they don't have
anywhere to go!
Oh, that's just awful.
I know!
Yeah, Dr. Fauna's
always fixin' Winona up
when she ain't
feelin' too fine,
so helpin' her out
is A-OK by me.
Yeah!
[all agreeing]
That's great news because it
means you'll all be helping me
with something special, too.
Something that's been a dream
of mine for a long time.
Oh, goody! Is your dream
to make a bouncy castle
shaped like a
gigantic bundt cake?
Um, no...
not exactly.
Oh, just me then.
So what is it,
Fluttershy? Spill!
My dream is to build a
real animal sanctuary.
A beautiful habitat where every
animal, whether sick...
or scared...
or even just lonely.
Feathered or furry,
scaly or slimy,
every critter would be welcome.
My sanctuary can be the
one place in Equestria
they call home till they feel
ready to take on the world.
[cheering]
Wow, Fluttershy.
I've never heard you speak
with such conviction.
That was exquisite!
Pretty awesome.
Thank you, everypony.
You've all taught me so much
about building my confidence
over the years. It's
because of your friendship
that I finally feel able to make
my dream project a reality.
But I can't build the sanctuary
alone. Will you join me?
Of course! Yeah!
I'm happy to offer my
extra hooves to ya!
But come to think of it,
I actually know a filly
who'd be more help than I
would. She's a friend of mine
from Winona's sheep herdin'
competition: Wrangler.
She's an expert in
animal enclosures.
How lovely!
Ooo! Ooo! Ooo! I
know somepony, too!
Hard Hat is the best
construction pony in Ponyville.
He can build anything you
could ever, ever, ever want!
Hearing you all
mention these experts,
I am reminded that I,
too, have the perfect pony
to help capture the
essence of your vision.
To give it some
style, some flair!
Is it you, Rarity?
No, no. Um I was referring to
the premiere interior designer
of the Canterlot
Elite: Dandy Grandeur.
He helped me when I was setting
up my Canterlot boutique.
I know he'd be thrilled
to work with you!
Wow, everypony!
Thank you.
I can't wait to meet all of
them and hear their ideas.
We're right on
track to building
the most wonderful
sanctuary in Equestria.
♪♪
Thank you,
Rupert!
Ahem. It's wonderful that
you all could join me
to discuss the Ponyville
sanctuary project.
My friends have so
many nice things to say
about each of your talents!
This is a big project,
so I'm happy to have
such experienced ponies
working on it with me.
Rarity has impeccable taste
in design and friends.
So I can't wait to work
with you, you know?
I--I think so.
Yee-haw!
I'm just lookin' forward
to helpin' ya out, ma'am.
And the animals.
Of course.
So, uh... Pinkie Pie said
you drew up some blueprints?
Um, Not exactly; it's
more of a "dream-board."
♪♪
That sure doesn't look
like an animal hospital.
That's because it's
not. It's a sanctuary.
A place that is safe but not
restrictive, cozy but natural.
A place where the animals can
come and go as they please.
[squeaking]
So... can you build it?
[nervous chuckles]
I want the sanctuary to
have an open floor plan.
No walls, more like an enclosure
that melts into the trees,
with a gate in the back.
That way, the animals
can return to the forest
right when they feel ready.
Sneaky! I like it.
You know, I designed
the Ponyville Hospital.
I could do the exact
same thing right here.
I still have the blueprints.
Though it'll take a while
to clear all these trees.
But I don't want to clear the
trees. I want to use them.
Are you sure?
What you're talking about
doesn't really seem
like a cohesive structure. Or
any structure I'm familiar with.
Critters don't live
the same way ponies do.
I know this is unconventional,
but that's because
we're trying to do something
that's never been done before.
And I really believe
it'll work.
[chirping]
All right, then. I'll
see what I can do.
See, Fluttershy?
Whatever you want!
Good.
♪♪
I know she thinks
knows what's best,
but once she sees how
much better it works
with these plans,
she'll thank us.
Which one do you like for
the window treatments?
Loving the print
on those!
Um... not to be rude, but
there must be some mistake.
We have no need for
curtains at the sanctuary.
And why ever not?
Everything is going to look
natural in the animal habitats,
not like it was
made for ponies.
All those shades
of brown and green?
But... they're so
drab. You know?
Ha ha ha ha!
Drab? You're calling the colors
of beautiful trees drab?
Exactly! The "natural"
look is not in right now.
This is better, trust me.
I appreciate your input,
but I just know the animals
would be happiest with
dirt brown pillows
and leaf green accents.
I'll look into it.
Thank you.
When a client has a vision!
[giggle]
Sometimes they need me to
steer them away from it.
Especially if its dirt brown.
And right there we got yer
standard sheep travelin' cage.
Fits two critters,
dependin' on size.
Hmmm.
What is it, sugarcube?
I'm looking for something
less like a cage...
more like a nice hug. Maybe
if we lose that part...
Well, then it
wouldn't be a cage.
Exactly! Ooh!
This is the perfect
base for a little nest.
I'll take a bunch of these.
And anything else the
animals can burrow into.
You sure you don't
want something
more secure for
the critters?
She does have a
point there.
You wouldn't want
a bunny wandering
into the wrong
cave, would ya?
No! No cages. I want to
give the animals the freedom
to come and go. It's the only
way they'll feel comfortable.
Well, she's the boss!
♪♪
[hammering]
[gasp]
Hey! What do you
think, Fluttershy?
I told you we'd be fast!
Almost finished with
the building already!
The color just pops,
you know?
Quite roomy inside,
really. And very safe!
Don't keep us
waiting, Fluttershy!
Do you love it or
do you love it?
I.. I...
I don't love it. This is
not going to work at all!
A giraffe can't fit
through this door.
With these curtains
blocking the light,
how are the birds going
to sing in the sunshine?
And this is the
opposite of a nice hug!
I know you all
worked hard,
but none of you did
anything I asked for.
That's not true! We used the
trees just like you asked.
And that curtain
fabric is organic!
It's got
"natural" fibers.
And I added pillows
inside my cages!
That should count as
feelin' like a hug.
I may not know much
about construction,
or interior design,
or wrangling...
but I am an expert at one
thing: the care of animals.
And what animals need is
a sanctuary, not this!
Maybe your vision wasn't all it
was cracked up to be, you know?
My vision isn't
the problem here.
I told you all
exactly what I wanted
and none of you
listened to me!
So while I appreciate
your efforts,
I no longer require
your services.
♪♪
Hello! The animals have been
so excited for the sanctuary,
they couldn't wait any longer.
Can we take a look inside?
Oh, um actually,
it's uh, not ready and--
[gasp]
[bonk]
♪♪
[rip]
[woodpecker pecking]
[bleat]
[slam]
[growl]
[crash]
Oh, no! Ahhh!
[clang]
[whines]
[creaking]
[crash]
[gasp]
♪♪
Oh, I'm so sorry,
Fluttershy.
No, I'm the one who
should be sorry.
This didn't go at all
like I had imagined.
♪♪
Sleep tight, little one.
It's going to be
OK, I promise.
[squeak squeak]
Now, now. Everymouse has
got to wait their turn.
I'm so sorry. I thought I'd
have a beautiful sanctuary
for you all to stay
in by now,
but I put my trust
in the wrong ponies.
It's OK, Fluttershy, I
know you did your best.
But we can make this work
here. It'll be a bit... tight,
but with your help,
we'll have these patients back
on their paws in no time.
Even without a sanctuary.
No!
I won't give up!
These animals need me
and I'm going to solve
this once and for all.
If this little lady can
crawl all the way here
from Western Equestria, I
can find a way to build her
a safe place to rest!
[noisy excitement]
[laughter]
Oops, everyone
back to sleep now.
Thanks for coming,
everypony. As you know,
building the sanctuary
didn't go quite as planned.
I know, right? Who'd
have guessed
that Hard Hat wouldn't
build whatever you want?
I never would have
invited Dandy to help
if I thought he'd
act in such a manner.
And Wrangler sure made
a fool outta me, too.
I'm sorry, Fluttershy.
It's OK. You were all
just trying to help.
But I know that letting all the
experts go was the right call.
So what are you going
to do now?
Try again.
I'm going to re-build
the sanctuary...
and do it my way this time.
Awesome!
That's the spirit!
You show 'em!
How about putting an
awesome flying course
for the birds right there?
And a carrot-cake
stand here!
A library cave?
Everypony, STOP!
I appreciate you
sharing your thoughts,
but I need everypony
to respect mine.
Other ponies may be
experts in their fields,
but animals are my
field of expertise.
And if I say this
is what I want...
Then this is what
needs to happen!
For the animals,
of course.
Wow, we should call
you Flutterbold now!
[laughter]
To get things back on
track, I called in a favor
from an old friend.
He'll be here any minute.
I thought you said
no more "experts."
This is one expert I know I can
trust to put the animals first.
Plus there's nopony
better at building.
[knocking at door]
Heh heh. I heard somepony
needs construction help
for them critters.
Big Daddy McColt!
We met each other back when the
map called me and Fluttershy
to the Smokey Mountains!
And he certainly knows his stuff
when it comes to buildings
and caring for animals.
Well, shucks, let's not stand
around talkin' about it.
Let's build us
a sanctuary!
[excited agreement]
♪ [bluegrass music] ♪
♪♪
Are you ready?
Oh, I'm more excited than
a beaver in a log pile!
OK. You can open your eyes!
Welcome to Sweetfeather
Sanctuary!
A safe and cozy retreat
for every creature.
♪♪
Oh, Fluttershy.
This is amazing!
Now you should have plenty
of room at the clinic
because once you've treated
them, they can recover here!
With my help, of course.
It's OK, Lola. We all
move at our own pace.
♪♪
Sometimes all we need to do
is believe in our dreams!
And when we finally
reach our goal...
... we'll know that it was worth
what it took to get there.
Because the view will be even
better than you imagined.
♪♪