[grunting and groaning]
Scootaloo, is this
such a... good idea?
What are you talking about?
This is the best
idea I've ever had!
It's just--
--You wanna come. But
we talked about this.
Non-Pegasus ponies fall
through the clouds.
Right, but--
I think we're good.
We are?
Scootaloo, I know you
have to go to Cloudsdale
to finish your report;
I'm just wondering
if this is the best
way to get there.
It'll be fine. Besides,
how else could I get there?
A Pegasus chariot.
A flock of birds!
A hot air balloon.
Huh, those do seem a lot safer.
Maybe I should try
to find another--
--WAAAAYY!
♪♪
WOOHOO!
[grunt]
Nailed it.
[mower stops]
Little ma'am, are
you all right?
[shake]
[gasp]
♪♪
You're-- you're-- you're
Rainbow Dash's dad!
♪♪
Ah yes. Bow Hothoof
at your service.
[long shriek]
[long shriek continues]
Uh, honey, something's
going on out here!
[long shriek continues]
[shriek stops]
[higher shriek]
Oh, heavens to Celestia,
what's wrong with her?!
I don't know, but you
just made it worse.
[higher shriek continues]
Sorry, it's just, you're
RAINBOW DASH'S PARENTS!
[long scream]
She's doing it again!
[shriek continues]
Oh, dearie, please.
You might shatter my Princess
Celestia commemorative plates!
Agh!
[scream continues]
[shatter]
[scream stops]
I'm so sorry. I just... I
can't believe I'm meeting you.
My name's Scootaloo and
I'm doing a school report
on your daughter.
Our Rainbow Dash?
The report's on an
inspirational pony in my life.
And no pony inspires
me more than she does!
I'm putting together this
scrapbook for my report.
I'm her biggest fan!
Little trotter, what
you say is impossible...
because nopony is a bigger fan
of our Rainbow Dash THAN US!
Whoa. You always
wear that shirt?
Actually it's er.. laundry day,
but pretty great, right?
Yeah!
My name's Windy Whistles
and I just have to say
that it is a total
blast to meet somepony
that loves Rainbow
Dash as much as we do!
What can we help
you with?
Well, I know all about Rainbow
Dash's time in Ponyville,
but I don't know anything
about her life before that.
Well, you came to
the right place.
[camera snap]
[delighted gasp]
Windy: Here you go. Rainbow
Dash's favorite meal.
A pasta and potato
sandwich on sourdough!
She just LOVES to carbo load!
I can't believe I'm eating
Rainbow Dash's favorite food,
made by Rainbow Dash's mom,
while sitting in Rainbow
Dash's childhood kitchen!!
This is the greatest
day of my life!
[chomp]
[munching]
Mm! Mmmmm!
I think it's time for
a tour of the house.
OK!
Our little Dashie was an early
learner and so rambunctious.
The combination was...
EXCITING!
[camera snap]
Woah.
♪♪
Is that her room?
[scream]
Rainbow Dash's linen closet!
Her carpet!
Her inspirational poster!
"When the going gets tough,
the tough don't notice
because they have hard shells."
That's so Rainbow Dash.
[camera snap]
Woohoo!
Scootaloo, want to see
something really cool?
[curtains open]
[door opens]
♪ [angelic choir] ♪
[gasp]
♪♪
[door closes/angel choir ends]
I.. uhh.. installed the
sound effects myself.
[door opens/closes]
[choir starts/ends]
Pretty great, huh?
So great!
And look at this.
She was wearing it when
she spoke her first words.
So cool!
[camera snap]
And this broken lantern is from
when she first learned to fly.
[camera snap]
And this bitten apple is from
when she grew her first tooth.
So many memories...
[camera snap]
You're so lucky to
have all of these.
Well, I may have a
ton of Dash-mentos,
but I don't have
any of those
Rainbow Dash saves Ponyville
headlines like you.
[gasp!] Tradesies?
Dealsies!
[bump]
So where's all the
Wonderbolt stuff?
You mean.. Rainbow Dash's
personal collection
of Wonderbolt memorabilia?
No, I mean where's all the
stuff about Rainbow Dash
getting accepted into
the Wonderbolt Academy
and then getting
chosen as a Wonderbolt.
Wait, you don't know that
your daughter's a Wonderbolt?
And I got to tell you!
[huge gasp!]
Oh, wow, you should see
your faces right now!
[camera snap]
See that's what your
faces look like.
♪♪
Our daughter's a WONDERBOLT?!
♪ [angel choir] ♪
[door closes]
Great timing.
Great door.
I just... it's unbelievable!
You two were kind enough to show
me the Rainbow Dash you know;
now please, allow me to show
you the Rainbow Dash I know.
♪♪
Let's make some thunder!
I was born to
make thunder!
♪♪
[thunderclap]
[shouting]
We've got turbulence!
How? Where's it
coming from?
[shouting]
There!
[encouraging shouts]
Oh, no.
OK, which pony
broke protocol
and invited guests to
our training exercises?
I guess they're
with me.
Agh!
Mom, Dad,
so ..good to see you.
Oh, honey it's so
great to see you, too!
And WOW! You were so
amazing up there
with all of that flying!
Er.. How did you know
I was here?
Scootaloo filled us
in on everything.
You modest pony, you.
[camera snap]
I can't believe I'm
documenting the moment
your parents first saw
you as a Wonderbolt!
And these must be your
Wonderbolt friends.
Hello team! I'm Windy Whistles,
the mom of the best
Wonderbolt ever! Yeah!
Just kidding.. you guys
were great, too. Go team!
Mom....
[laugh]
Hello Ma'am, nice
to meet you.
Nice to meet you, as well and
love those goggles! Love 'em!
You know I have
goggles, too,
but they're mostly just for
swimming. Oh and bath time.
Mom, please! They don't want
to hear about your bath time.
I can't believe it. My
daughter, a Wonderbolt!
So proud!
Dad, hold it together!
We're in public.
I know, I know, but it's just...
you had a goal and
...you achieved it!
[blubbering]
[camera snap]
All right Wonderbolts,
let's hit the showers
and give Rainbow Dash some
time to spend with her family.
OK, yeah. Great practice.
I'll uh, catch up with
you guys in a minute.
Sir. You really
raised a great flyer.
Oh, no... tears
welling up again!
Dad.....
[blubbering]
[camera snap]
Could you give us a sec?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, you should
have warned me
that you were
bringing my parents,
or talked to Twilight or
something. Not just shown up!
Why?
It's just, my parents and I
have a delicate relationship.
I love them very much
and we're really close,
but there's a reason I didn't
tell them I'm a Wonderbolt!
They can be a little
bit... embarrassing.
Huh...? Really?
Yeah, really.
And now you've invited a whole
lot of crazy into my life!
What's wrong with
a little support?
♪♪
Bow and Windy, I'd
like you to meet
Apple Bloom and
Sweetie Belle.
Hi!
Hello!
Greetings, small ponies.
Are you excited to
see Rainbow Dash?
Oh, my, YES!
And to think we never bothered
to come to a Wonderbolt event!
We said if Rainbow Dash
isn't a Wonderbolt,
then what's the
point? But now she is!
And she earned it!
Did you know it all
started when she won a spot
in the coveted
Wonderbolt Academy,
training under Spitfire!
I didn't know that!
How wonderful!
But then she had some
heavy competition,
especially against another
Pegasus named Lightning Dust.
Oh, no...
But of course, Rainbow
Dash proved to be the best
and later made it into
the Wonderbolt Reserves!
Hooray again!
But.. a jealous ex-Wonderbolt,
Wind Rider, was worried
that Rainbow Dash might
break his speed record
and so he framed her for
a crime she didn't commit.
Oh, no!
But thanks to Rarity, Rainbow
Dash proved her innocence
and became a back-up Wonderbolt.
Until Fire Streak retired
and she became an
official Wonderbolt!
Hooray!
Wow! What a gripping tale.
You really know your
Rainbow Dash history.
You're going to do
great on your report.
Show's about to start!
♪♪
[zoom]
HOO! HOO! HOO! HOO! HOO!
Come on, bolts, LET'S
START THIS THING!
Wonderbolts Spring
Showcase HERE. WE. GOOOO!
Rip it up and tear! it! down!
Then build it back up again
and tear it back down again!
Yeah! Woo!
Yeah! Uhuh! Uhuh!
Go go go! Yes!
GO RAINBOW DASH!
BEST WONDERBOLT EVER!
Woohoo! That's my daughter!
Go Rainbow! Go Dashie!
Go go go go go!
[whoosh]
Woohoo! You go, girl!
Your folks were
definitely loud,
but they weren't that bad.
[explosion]
Whoa, since when did we
add fireworks to the show?
Uh...we didn't.
Atta girl! Woohoo!
Yeah! Go girl! Go go go go!
[explosions and whistling]
Wow.
[excited chatter]
Go RAINBOW DASH!
[rip]
You sign that photo!
Whoo!
♪♪
Cut the ribbon! Cut the ribbon! Cut the ribbon!
Cut the ribbon!
[camera snap]
The camera loves
you! Yeah!
Now let's do the pyramid.
Scootaloo get up
there; you're the top!
You really do got yourself your
very own mega fans! Lucky you.
[groan]
♪♪
[door opens]
You hung that towel!
[bang]
YEAH!
Greatest towel
hanger OF ALL TIME!
TOWEL! TOWEL!
STOP!
This is ridiculous! Mom and Dad,
you are both too supportive!
This is exactly why I didn't
tell you I was a Wonderbolt;
you're just.. TOO MUCH!
Did.. did we do something wrong?
YES! The fireworks,
the cheerleading
and how do you even compare
who is better or worse
at hanging up a towel?!
We're just trying
to be supportive.
Well, I'm tired of it! I've
had enough of you two
being so proud of every
little ridiculous,
insignificant thing I do!
[panting]
I think you should leave.
First of all, great job
yelling at us, sweetie.
No one can make their parents
feel more worthless than you.
Your words were direct,
clear and... so painful.
Is there nothing
you can't do!?
[blubbering]
Why?
Scootaloo, you
don't understand.
I met your parents hoping
to learn more about you,
but I don't like
what I found out.
I'll find somepony else
to do my hero report on.
♪♪
Scootaloo, wait!
I know I wasn't
myself back there
and I shouldn't have
snapped at my parents.
But that's exactly why I didn't
tell them I'm a Wonderbolt.
I don't understand;
they're so proud of you.
[sigh]
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
OK, but you might want
to hold onto your wings
because this could rock
you to your very core.
♪♪
Believe it or not,
there was a time
when I wasn't the
best at everything.
[gasp]
See this picture? It looks
like I won something awesome.
But, actually...
Announcer: And last but not
least, it's time to hand out
our participant stickers.
♪♪
Yeah! Rainbow Dash,
you show them!
Greatest participant ever!
Uh... your parents realize you
didn't win, don't they?
[camera snap]
Granted, I was the youngest pony
in the senior
competitive circuit.
Most other ponies my age
were still in the
junior flappers club.
I thought it was
utterly mortifying
having my parents cheer
me on even when I lost.
But then when I started
to win competitions,
which didn't take
very long, by the way,
things got even worse.
Woo!! Yeah! Go Rainbow!
Go Rainbow! Woohoo!
Yeah, Rainbow Dash! You
show em! That's our girl!
Being the best came
with consequences.
Very loud, very
embarrassing consequences.
[sigh]
You know, some
ponies would dream
of having parents
like that.
Yeah, right, name one.
[sigh]
Me. Growing up, I never thought
I'd be the best at anything
because no pony ever told me.
But your parents told you
over and over again -- look.
Best bath taker ever. Best
carrot eater under three.
Greatest napper of all time!
I am pretty good at napping.
I can fall asleep anywhere.
[snoring]
Huh?
For your entire life,
your parents gave you
the confidence to
believe in yourself.
♪♪
You're right. I was always
so embarrassed by my parents
that I didn't realize their
support actually made me
the awesome, confident,
amazing, awesome
and awesome pony I am!
And I took them for granted!
And you yelled
at them.
Ugh, I gotta make
this right.
I have an idea, but I'm
going to need your help!
That is, if you're willing to
help me after I acted like that.
[camera flash]
Now that's a great picture.
Rainbow Dash learns
the error of her ways.
♪♪
I'm telling you, I just
can't see a thing!
Scootaloo, you are just
so great at blindfolds.
It's true. You must tell me
what kind of knot you used.
A Falconer's knot? Wait
no... a farmer's loop!
What's this
all about, anyhoo?
Rainbow over loudspeaker: Windy
Whistles and Bow Hothoof,
please be seated for a super
private Wonderbolt event.
♪♪
Ahem.
Mom and Dad, welcome to the...
"I love my parents and
I'm sorry that I took them
for granted and I know that
they made me who I am today
so I really want to make
it up to them" event.
♪♪
Enjoy.
Thanks for doing this.
Happy to help!
[whoosh]
Ooooh! Aaaaah!
Oooooh!
[whoosh]
[cheering]
Oooooh!
♪♪
Mom and Dad, I want you to know
that I'm your biggest fan.
♪♪
Oh, honey, thank you. But you
didn't have to do all this.
It's kind of... embarrassing.
Yeah, it is a bit much.
[camera flash]
And that's why Rainbow Dash
is the most inspirational
pony in my life.
[knocking]
Thank you, Scootaloo.
Very well researched,
but a little heavy
on the pictures
and there was a moldy
sandwich in your report.
I'll give you a B.
YEAH! GREATEST
REPORT-GIVER OF ALL TIME!
SCOOT-AL-LOO! SCOOT-AL-LOO!
SCOOT-AL-LOO!
Keep it down! OK, this isn't
a rock and roll concert!
Please!
SCOOT-AL-LOO! SCOOT-AL-LOO!
SCOOT-AL-LOO!