♪♪
Come on, come on! Turn
into a tea cup.
[zap]
No. Tea cup!
No! Tea cup! No!
Starlight, I can't put a
trick that's not working
into my act. How come
it's not working?
It could be because you're
just yelling "tea cup"
and not picturing
it in your mind.
Oh. Yeah, that
could be it.
What does your
tea cup look like?
What shape is
it? What color?
[big breath in]
[zap]
Woo! Starlight, I
did it!
[splat]
[giggle] I did it, I did
it, I did it! [giggle]
Hey!
Tea cup! [giggle] Tea cup!
Tea cup! Tea cup! Tea cup!
Teeeaa Cup! Tea Cup!
Tea Cup! Teeeaa Cup!
You know what you
need? A tea cup!
Oh!
Whoops, I guess I
pictured a tea cup poodle.
Trixie, you ruined
my tea cakes!
I just got excited!
This is the first time I
did a transfiguration spell.
Real magic! C'mon.
Be impressed by me!
"Yay Trixie!
You are so great at magic
and having good hair."
[giggle] Good job, Trix, but
I was baking these to give
to Twilight and the girls for
their friendship retreat.
Pinkie Pie gave me her
recipe and everything.
Oh, you need some snacks
to give to Twilight?
I've got you covered.
♪ [humming] ♪
Problem solved!
[sigh] Not exactly.
Hearing impaired subtitles
By YayPonies
The Legend say the tea cup poodle is still roaming free to this day!
https://yp1.yayponies.no
[train whistle blows]
I am so excited for this
friendship retreat!
I can't remember the last
time we all got to hang out
without having to
save Equestria!
Well, we are awesome,
but technically we weren't the
last ponies to save Equestria.
I was speaking in
a broader sense!
Are you sure you don't
want to come with us?
Yeah, I have three new
comics to get through.
And I promised Trixie
we'd practice more magic.
It might be better if
the castle was empty
if you know what I mean.
Relax. If
anything breaks,
Starlight will just go back
in time and fix it.
[weak laughter]
Kidding!
We'll take good care of the
castle while you're gone.
Have fun on your
friendship retreat!
What in Equestria is a
friendship retreat, anyway?
They're gonna bond, share
laughs and if I know them,
they're gonna
sing a song.
We are gonna have so
much more fun than them.
Shhh!
Twilight, wait! Starlight
has something for you!
Huh?
Here, I, um, brought you snacks.
Oh. How thoughtful. Thanks.
We will... not get
hungry on the train.
It was supposed to be tea
cakes, but it's a long story.
Have a great time.
You, too!
[door closes]
[train
rumbles]
[whistle
blows]
OK Trixie, what kind of spells
did you want to work on next?
Well, every
self-respecting magician
has a disappearing act
so maybe we could
start with that?
Hmm. Nothing just disappears
so that's technically
a teleportation spell and
those are pretty hard.
Maybe we should start
with something smaller.
No no no no. The great
and powerful Trixie
goes big or not at all!
Just tell me how you do it.
Well, I've always found
magic is tied to my emotions.
Whatever I'm feeling
fuels whatever I'm doing
and the stronger I'm feeling,
the stronger the magic.
Right. Like when you were
so upset that Cutie Marks
took away your friend, your
magic was strong enough
to enslave an
entire village.
Yup. Thanks for
bringing that up.
See? I'm already learning!
If anypony is going
to teach me
how to do a
disappearing spell...
Teleportation spell.
Whatever. I'm
complimenting you! And me.
We can do this
cause we're amazing
and magic is
friendship and stuff.
[laughter]
I guess we can
give it a whirl.
Now we just need to find
you something to teleport.
Spike? How bout it?
Ha ha.
Let's pick something, I
don't know, not living.
I mean, it won't be as
impressive, but OK.
Teach away, mini Twilight.
[growl]
Welcome to
Manehattan Escapes!
I'm going to start
with a facial
and then get my
hooves done.
Oh. It's not that
kind of retreat.
Isn't it called
Manehattan Escapes
because it's a deluxe spa
where you can escape
all of your troubles?
Nope. It's because we
get locked in a room
and we have to solve
puzzles and riddles
in order to escape!
The clues will lead you
to a key to get out.
Team building!
[unhappy sighs]
Come on, girls.
This could be fun.
"Could be"? Some of the
brightest minds in Equestria
put together
these puzzles!
I'm just happy to
be with all of you.
Me too! I'm not great
at solving riddles,
but I'm super great at
cheering other ponies on
while they do it. GO
US! Oha oha! Woohoo!
Yes, yes woohoo,
but just so we know,
exactly how long will
we be locked in here?
A group of Griffons set the
record for the fastest escape.
It only took them an hour.
Pssh. Griffons barely
like each other!
We're basically the poster
ponies for amazing friendships
so get your quill ready, bub.
You're gonna have to
write down a new record.
If you master this spell
before the girls get back,
you'd be setting
some kind of record.
Challenge accepted.
OK, what you want to do is
concentrate on the object
that you want to teleport.
Yeah, I'm gonna go...
all the way over here.
Concentrate on teleporting,
got it. Doin' the spell!
No Trix, wait. Not just--
[zap]
[moan]
[thud]
♪ Ta da ♪
[heavy sighing]
Nonononononono!
You made Twilight's
Friendship Map disappear!
Ahem. Teleport.
Really?!
Well, it was behind the apple,
it was bound to happen.
On the plus side, my
magic is getting better.
I made a whole table go poof!
That was pretty impressive.
Trixie, we have to
get that map back.
We'll find it.
No big deal.
Twilight's never going
to trust me to be alone
in this castle again!
What were you thinking?
"Teleport"! Like you told me to!
No! You're supposed to
concentrate on the object!
Not just teleporting!
Well, gee, you probably should
have told me all the steps
before you let me
do the spell.
I TRIED!
I... need a minute.
Hey, are you OK?
I will be, once I cast a
spell to contain my anger
in this bottle.
Wait, what?
Do you see this
storm cloud?
This has never
happened before.
All this magical
energy has to go somewhere
and if I'm not using it
to fight a magical duel
or bend my friends' wills
to obey my every command...
Ha. I remember that.
The point is, I don't know
what my magic's going to do.
So I'm hoping if I
bottle up my anger,
I won't do who-
knows-what to Trixie.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
What choice do I have? I've got
to get that map back
and I don't want
to lose Trixie.
If she knew what I was
thinking right now,
she'd probably never
talk to me again.
OK. You do what
you need to do;
I'll see if I can find the
map somewhere in the castle.
♪♪
Trixie.
Oh, there you are.
For a minute
I didn't think you
were coming back
and that you might be upset
with me for some weird reason.
But then I remembered
you never get mad at me.
Whoo. Nope. Not
mad at all.
So, the map is probably
in the last place
you were thinking
of. Where was that?
Oooh. Great question. I
wish you'd asked it, like,
right after I did the spell.
I don't remember anymore.
No worries. We'll just
take a walk around town.
Maybe that will
jog your memory.
OK, that sounds
fun. Oooh!
Did you remember?
No. But I did think we could
stop for cinnamon nuts
while we're out!
Cinnamon nuts?!
That's a good idea.
Yes! I've been craving
something sweet
since I couldn't have any
tea cakes this morning.
Whoo!
You got this, Starlight.
Woohoo! Go Twilight,
you can do it!
Woohoo!
Hoo-wee! You solved that
triangle-y thing mighty fast.
Does anypony need
a purple jewel?
Ooh! Plum or boysenberry?
Don't both those
fruits mean "purple"?
Yes, but one's a lovely purple
and one's...well...icky.
Just put the gem in! We're
trying to set a record here!
♪♪
Yay, we solved another clue!
Cause our friendship is so true!
Yay us! Woohooo!
Oh, hello Fillies,
how can I help you?
Ooh, are those
cinnamon nuts?
Mmm Yes! I got them
from the cart outside.
They're delicious.
Do you want some?
Have you seen a big
table? Magical map on it?
Sometimes glowing
cutie marks shoot out?
Uhh big ta--No. No.
Why in Equestria would
something like that be in here?
Well, I cast a pretty amazing
spell that transported it
to the last place
I was thinking of.
But I might have been thinking
about how I'd treat myself
to a nice brooch instead.
Ah. Well, no huge table here.
Are you still interested
in that brooch?
Sure!
No!
We don't have
time for this!
Twilight and the girls
are gonna be back soon.
But I'm not upset.
What's our next stop?
♪♪
Nope. I ain't seen it.
Are you sure?
It's really really
important that we find it.
And it might be here because
somepony was craving apples.
I'm still craving them. They'd
go so well with cinnamon nuts!
Them nuts sure
do smell good!
Granny Smith.
Please. The table?
My eyes ain't what
they used to be
but I'd know fer sure if
a big ole table dun appear
out of thin air!
[groan]
[squeaky barking]
Darn. I could've
have sworn it'd be
at the ice cream parlor,
because it was warm
in the castle and I
thought I wanted ice cream.
Ooh! Maybe we should check
out the Crystal Empire
because Twilight's castle
is made out of crystals
so I totally had
crystals on my mind.
OK. We'd better start moving
if we want to make it
to the Crystal Empire.
Are you OK, Starlight?
Because you seem a little...
what's the word? Uck la la.
Nope. I am great.
Did your saddle
bag just glow?
No.
Gimmee.
Give it here.
No. Don't
CINNAMON NUTS!
I've had a hankerin'
for these all day!
Me too, ever since that
Trixie came by with them.
[crash]
[smash]
♪♪
Um. Why are they
looking at me like that?
♪♪
Whoa!
You ruined my
tea cakes!
What?!
You just had to give Twilight
those smelly pretzels.
Were they your pretzels?
I don't understand.
YOU DON'T PAY ATTENTION WHEN
I'M TRYING TO TEACH YOU!
Starlight, can you
help me? Please!
Twilight, can you
help me please?
I've seen those
symbols over here!
You can do it!
Almost there!
I've got the key!
This is it! I'm
so impressed.
I'm not! I knew
we were the best!
You're the worst!
That seems harsh.
Aaah! Starlight!
I don't know what's
happening! Starlight! Help!
I'm glad Twilight
isn't here to see this.
I wish that Starlight was here
to see how strong
friendships can be
when we trust each
other and work together!
You've all taught
me so much.
♪ Friendship used to make
me so queasy queasy ♪
♪ But you made it all
so easy easy. ♪
♪ Now, I don't have to
say what I'm thinkin' ♪
♪ You already know
without even blinkin' ♪
♪ You girls are the
apple of my eye. ♪
♪ The race that
doesn't end in a tie! ♪
♪ You are the funnel
cake at my fair! ♪
♪ The warm hug of
a fuzzy bear! ♪
♪ Best friends until
the end of time. ♪
♪ We'll have each other's backs
and let our true selves shine. ♪
♪ And that's because
everything we need ♪
♪ is all right here when
we're with our team. ♪
Starlight!
A spark of magic
could be very helpful
right about now!
I can't!
♪ I simply can't imagine
there'd be a day ♪
♪ Where I wouldn't want
to be walkin' your way. ♪
♪ Whatever new problems
there may be may be ♪
♪ Our friendship is always
the door with a key. ♪
♪ You are the jewels in
my friendship crown. ♪
♪ The sparks that make
my world go round. ♪
♪ We bring the best
out that's our goal. ♪
♪ There's no telling
how far we'll go. ♪
♪ Best friends, until
the end of time. ♪
♪ We'll have each other's backs
and let our true selves shine. ♪
♪ And that's because everything
we need is all right here ♪
♪ when we're with our team. ♪
That was lovely.
But um, you know
the game isn't over
until you turn that key.
AHH!
Did we do it?
So close. You missed the
griffon record by two seconds.
Probably shouldn't
have sung that song.
AWW NUTS!
AHHHHHHH!
Nuts!
[crash]
YOU JUST DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO DO!
Starlight!
And you don't always have
to bring up my dark past!
I didn't know you had
one, Granny Smith!
I just can't believe you
sometimes! You make me so MAD!
I barely even know you!
I don't understand why
you're all so mad at me!
They're not. I am.
[whoosh]
You are?
[sigh] I'm really...
mad at you.
You lost Twilight's
map table;
you make jokes like
it's no big deal.
It's like you
don't even care
you could get me in
a lot of trouble.
If we can't find
that table,
Twilight's never going
to trust me again.
And the worst part is
you didn't even
say you were sorry!
I... I'm sorry. I had no
idea you felt that way.
Yeah. I do.
[poof]
But to be fair, I don't know
how you could have known.
I did a spell. I
bottled up my anger,
but when the bottle broke,
it infected these three.
I'm really sorry; I used magic
so I wouldn't use magic.
I should have guessed
that would backfire.
Oh, that's all right.
It was a slow day.
Yeah. I was gonna get
my dentures cleaned
before y'all showed up.
Oh, no. My nut cart!
[smash]
♪♪
Yay! My nut cart!
Hang on; don't you
work at the spa?
I'm late for my other job!
What, I wear many hats.
Not gonna lie, hearing you
and those random ponies
say all those terrible
things about me wasn't easy.
But I needed to hear it.
Why didn't you just
tell me how you felt?
I didn't want to
lose you as a friend.
Pfft. Come on! It'd take a lot
more than that to lose me.
Our friendship is stronger
than a few angry words.
And a magical
temper tantrum?
Listen, I'd take that
over the boring pony
you were becoming any day.
The Starlight I love is
passionate, lively and yeah,
sometimes angry. Those are
my favorite parts of you.
That and the fact that you
forgive me every time.
[giggle]
I'll forgive you
if you forgive me.
Deal.
I remember what I
was thinking about!
[door jingles]
You're kidding me.
There's more to
it than that.
I was thinking about how
glad I am to have met you
and I remembered
our first meeting:
here at the Ponyville Spa.
And now I just have
to teleport it back.
No no no no noooo!
[crash]
A little to the left.
Now rotate it just a hair.
Hey, girls!
How'd it go?
[crash]
Nothing.
What?
Let's just say I learned
a friendship lesson
while you were gone.
You've barely graduated
and you're already taking
initiative! Oh. So proud.
We learned about team building
and problem solving--
--and when not to sing songs!
We certainly had
a good time,
but I really was looking
forward to a spa day.
And the Ponyville spa
is still open. Anyone?
Twilight: Sounds good to me!
Applejack: I reckon I could use that.
Rainbow Dash: I have a coupon!
We'll meet you there!
Quick. Do you have a spell
that will make the Spa Ponies
forget that the map
table was there?
Haven't you learned anything
about using magic to
solve your problems?
No. If we learn that lesson,
how will we ever have fun?
[laughter]