♪♪
Oh, thank you so
much for helping me
with these flyers, Spike.
I'm so lucky you just happened
to be walking past the boutique.
Er, yeah, right...
just "happened to
be walking past... "
Ha-ha...
♪♪
What'cha got here?
"Lost dog?" "Balloons for sale?"
"Guitar lessons?"
'Cause I found one, I need
some and yes, I am interested.
[wailing]
No, it's a call for submissions.
Fashion contest
I'm organizing.
A showcase for aspiring
young designers.
Oh, wow!
What an awesome idea.
Thank you.
I remember how difficult it
was to break into the fashion
industry when I
was starting out.
That's why the winner
of the contest
will get to debut their line
in the Carousel Boutique!
So selfless.
So generous.
I've also managed to get
esteemed fashion critic
Hoity Toity and iconic fashion
photographer Photo Finish
to come to Ponyville
and judge the show.
And, [chuckle] wait until you hear who
else will be a judge!
Countess Coloratura?
Sassy Saddles?
Spike?
No....
The third judge for the Carousel
Boutique's Couture du Futur
Fashion Contest is
none other than...
Applejack!
What!?
What?
What?!
You already said
that, darling.
I know. But I had
to say it again
because that's how
confused I am.
You want me to judge
a fashion show?
I'm sure Rarity has her
reasons and once we hear them,
all of this will make sense.
I admit, Applejack is
an unorthodox choice.
But that is precisely what
makes her an inspired choice.
See? Now it all...
still doesn't make any sense.
Hoity Toity has expertise
in fabric and stitchwork.
Photo Finish has an artistic
eye for shapes and colors.
But sometimes we designers
forget about practicality!
That's where you come in.
Uh, I think I might be a
little too "practical."
My closet's nothing but
twenty versions of this hat.
Which tells me you're a pony
who knows what she likes.
Besides, a judge
must be honest
and you're the most
honest pony there is.
Ask any pony,
they'll tell you.
Ooh! Let me try!
'Scuse me.
Have you ever
heard of Applejack?
The most honest
pony there is?
Sure have.
See?
So, what do you say?
Well, if I'm bein' honest...
I don't think I'm the
right pony for the job.
Fashion just ain't
my bag of oats.
Aw Booooooo!
I do understand
your hesitation.
But before you say
no, sleep on it?
Sure.
I guess I can do
that for you.
♪♪
Yeah I know, Big Mac!
I was just as surprised
as you are.
I mean, can you imagine
me judgin' a fashion show?
I'd do it!
It sounds like fun getting to
see all those pretty outfits.
Well, you're the exception
in our family, sugar cube.
You know about
that kind of stuff.
I'd be as useful as a burr
knot on a sapling tree.
[grunt]
Although, Rarity did say I just
had to focus on practicality.
She already has
experts for the...
fashion-y stuff.
But I still wouldn't
know what to say.
[crash]
[clatter]
Come on, Apple Bloom, you're
doubling our workload here.
Sorry.
I wanted to wear a
signature hat like yours,
but it's making
it harder to see.
That's because
it's not like mine.
You don't need a fancy
scarf to keep your hat on.
Now you can see.
♪♪
Hyah!
Wow! That is a lot better.
Thanks, Applejack.
Sure thing.
You know what?
I am gonna help
Rarity judge her show.
I think my sensible,
everypony take on fashion
is exactly what the pony
community needs.
Rarity, I thought
about it some more
and if you still need me,
I'd love to be a judge.
Oooo, I just knew
you'd come around!
I, Photo Finish...
have arrived!
As has Hoity Toity.
It's wonderful to see you!
Kiss.
Kiss!
Thank you both so
much for doing this!
[kisses]
We missed you at Miss Pommel's
debut in Manehattan last week.
Miss Pommel is showing?
I thought she was
still making costumes.
You haven't heard?
Everypony who is anypony
is talking about it.
[knock knock]
Oh, my.
They're absolutely stunning.
It sure is great to hear
Miss Pommel is doing so well.
Who is this
who speaks?
Oh, this is Applejack.
Another one of the judges.
So, judge.
What do you think?
Oh, wow...
that is just...
wow.
These are clothes?
The photo is upside-down.
This is...
she looks like a disco ball.
Did..did they have to roll
her down the runway?
Ha ha ha!
I can't believe anypony
would actually wear this!
Am I right?
Oh, my!
I faint!
Ha ha.. uh.. so funny.
Oh, gosh, I didn't
mean to make her faint.
Oh, don't worry
about it, darling.
Happens all the time.
Besides, that dress did look
a bit like a disco ball.
Although, Miss Pommel
is making the point
that no matter what we wear,
it is a costume of
some kind or another.
I have no idea what
you're talkin' about.
And that's OK!
Let's go meet the
designers and help them
get ready for the show!
De-signers!
Welcome!
Today you will work on your
designs and we judges will offer
our guidance and advice as you
prepare for tomorrow's big show!
[chattering]
Lily Lace, tell us
about your inspiration.
You guys.
This morning on my way here?
I heard a bird singing literally
the most beautiful song
I'd ever heard and
I wanted to capture
not so much the
bird's song exactly?
But more like how the wind
carried the bird's song.
Powerful, yet at the same
time fragile and delicate.
Uh.. Huh?
Next up, meet Starstreak.
I'm not interested in
what's already been done,
only what will
exist in the future.
Tomorrow's fashion belongs
to those who hear it coming.
♪♪
I am Inky Rose.
You have a very focused vision.
A strong sense of
what you want is good!
Applejack, you've
been rather quiet.
What do you think?
Well, it's a lot of black.
It's kind of...
depressing.
♪♪
How's this?
Makes a world of difference!
Maybe to fashion
experts like you,
but to ponies like
me, it's still black.
And I'm not sure how you wear
singing birds or the future.
♪♪
I don't think they
liked what I had to say.
Ah well, that's why you're here.
Fashion needs a healthy dose
of practicality now and then.
♪♪
[bang]
Are you puttin' holes
in the clothes...
on purpose?
It's to create a
distressed look.
More like an "old
and tattered" look.
When a pony's old
clothes get holes in 'em,
they don't want to go to the
store to buy new clothes...
with holes in 'em.
OK, yes, not a very
practical choice.
Fashionable, but
not practical.
♪♪
Simply stunning!
Sure it looks pretty, but
that's a lot of fabric.
With the way it drags behind,
it'll be covered in
dirt in no time.
Thank goodness I'm here.
Otherwise we'd've had holes
in clothes and dirty dresses.
[whine]
♪♪
But of course, no look is complete
without mane and make-up!
So er.. when are you
gonna do her mane?
Uh! It's already been done!
You know what?
I think we've given the
designers enough guidance
for today.
Let's.. uh.. let them
finish their work.
Can't wait to see what ya'll
do for the big show tomorrow!
[indignant chatter]
[nervous giggle]
[door closes]
♪♪
Hey, Applejack!
On your way home?
How'd the first day
of the contest go?
Great!
At first, I didn't
think I'd be much help,
but thank goodness I signed on!
Without me, they'd be doin' all
kinds of crazy fashiony things!
♪ [out of tune strum] ♪
Hey, Rarity.
Applejack says the
contest is going great!
Good thing she's
there, huh?
Yes. Of course.
Some of her thoughts
are tough to swallow,
but hopefully her candor
will help the designers
achieve the best
designs possible.
You seem a
little stressed.
Wanna try?
Music is very relaxing!
Sure.
♪ [solo rock guitar] ♪
Ah, much better.
♪♪
I can meet my goals!
Today is a fresh start!
Good morning, everypony!
Time for final adjustments
before the show!
If buttons could convey
sadness, you've done it.
To me, they convey
waking up an hour early
just to button them all!
And that's if you could
reach most of 'em.
♪♪
Is this better?
There ya go.
Now when it's cold, you just
slide it on ya and you're set.
Like a poncho.
Umm. "Poncho?"
♪♪
I attached each
feather individually, haha.
It took me for literally ever.
Oh, you used hoof-crossed
double-over stitches!
They're perfect!
Who cares if it's
stitched perfectly?
You don't need
feathers on your head.
[shakes]
[outraged cries]
My little sister tried to add
some flair to her hat
and guess what it got her?
An extra hour of work pickin'
apples off the ground.
♪♪
A good start, but.. it needs more.
No...
Yes!
I'd go with this one.
No! This one!
[Applejack laughing]
Something is funny?
What? Oh, no.
It's just...
I mean, those belts
look the same.
That one completely
changes the look.
This one compliments it.
You're kidding, right?
Is everything OK?
They're having a heated
debate about those two belts.
Oooh, both good choices.
No! There is no choice!
They're the exact same belt!
This is so silly!
Fashion is ridiculous!
[gasp]
You don't mean that.
I do.
I'm sorry but that's
my honest opinion.
Well, I never
would have come
if I knew we were
going to be insulted!
We go!
No, please! Come back!
If they're out, I'm out too.
I didn't get into
fashion to design boring,
utilitarian clothes.
I want to create
elegance and drama?
And this is lit'rally
the opposite of...
I mean, I can't even...
Yeah, no.
[sobbing]
What?
I was just bein' honest!
[grunts]
Stop everything!
There is no show!
Take it all down!
Rarity, what's going on?
Is everything OK?
No!
It is the opposite of OK.
The judges have quit; the
designers have dropped out;
the show is cancelled!
All my good
intentions, squashed!
[sobbing]
And it's all Applejack's fault!
Why are you mad at me?
I was just sayin'
what I thought.
And isn't that why you
wanted me to be a judge?
For my honesty?
Of course.
But you said fashion
is ridiculous!
But it's my opinion!
And I'm not gonna lie!
Oh!
[angrily] Come with me!
[knock knock]
[door opens]
[chews] [swallows]
Oh, heh heh, Rarity!
What a nice surprise!
Hello Strawberry Sunrise,
this is Applejack.
I was wondering if you could
tell her how you feel
about apples?
Don't like 'em!
What? Why?
They're crunchy, they're
sweet, they're delicious.
They're not strawberries.
[munching]
You're right.
Apples are better
than strawberries.
Only if by "better" you mean
"better at being disgusting."
You'd better apologize!
Oh, I'm sorry...
that you actually bite
into those tasteless,
mealy, worm-filled things.
Oh..
[door slam]
What!?
[growl]
Applejack!
Why are you so angry?
It's just Strawberry's
honest opinion.
What's wrong with that?
Well, that's fine if
she doesn't like 'em,
but if she knew how hard we
work to make our apples perfect,
maybe she wouldn't be so
mean about it--Oooooh.
Oh, boy.
Mmm-hmm.
Doesn't feel so good, does it?
No.
No, it does not at all.
I am so sorry, Rarity.
I got so carried away
with bein' honest,
I guess I didn't think about
how I was makin' others feel.
I'm a real rotten apple.
I appreciate that, Applejack.
That means a lot.
I just wish you'd realized it
before you ruined
the fashion show!
♪♪
I need to get some of these.
It's the only way to travel.
What are you doing!?
Canterlot is that way..
Yep, but you're not goin'
back to Canterlot yet.
♪♪
Hey!
What is she...
I don't know.
Run!
♪♪
Listen, y'all.
I thought I was
just bein' honest
when I said all those things,
but somepony helped me realize
I was actually bein' hurtful.
So for that, I apologize.
So, you don't think
fashion is ridiculous?
Well... I... still don't
understand it,
but I appreciate how much
it means to y'all
and how much hard
work you put into it.
I also know this contest
is important to Rarity.
So what do you say?
♪♪
I'd hate to have come
all this way here
and not see what
you can do.
If they're judging, we're in.
Under one condition.
Literally.
Anything.
Untie us.
♪♪
Show's back on, fellas!
[groan]
♪♪
Ah!
[crash]
[laughter]
♪♪
Uh uh.
Uh huh!
♪♪
... and then Applejack found me
and told me to distract you
for an hour but the hour's up!
Ta da!
B-b-but... how?
They were all leaving...
This was all coming down.
You can thank Applejack.
She lit'rally did
it all by herself.
I don't think that word means
what you think it means.
But I did bust my tail because I
know how much this means to you.
Ohh!
Thank you, Applejack.
We start now!
♪♪
First up, Lily Lace!
Starstreak!
♪♪
Inky Rose!
And now it's time to vote.
I am drawn to the beauty
and drama of fashion
and no pony does drama
better than Lily Lace!
So I vote for her.
It means soooo much to me,
I literally can't even...
Simplicity is the
keynote of true elegance.
That is why I vote
for Inky Rose.
You've made me so.. happy?
Fashion is the art!
I, Photo Finish,
vote for Starstreak!
Wonderful to hear, darling.
Well, it all comes
down to you, Applejack.
Pinkie Pie: Can you believe it!?
After everything
that's happened,
Applejack is the
deciding vote!
Ah! This is so exciting!
Well, Applejack?
Uh, uh...
Lily Lace's clothes go here,
Inky Rose's will go there
and Starstreak's there.
Sorry, but I couldn't
pick just one.
They all did great
and in my opinion,
they all deserve to win.
And I agree.
I told you your perspective
would be beneficial.
Is.. this one of your
new designs, Rarity?
It's, uh...
the form is reminiscent of...
I mean, it conjures
up images of...
Well, uh..I mean...
Oh, that?
No, I totally
messed that one up.
It's ghastly.
Horrid.
Absolutely terrible!
Oh, thank goodness.
Cause in my honest
opinion, it's awful.
[hearty laughter]
Rarity: When you're right,
you're right!