So in closing, earning a
rockterate in rock studies
from the Equestrian
Institute of Rockology
is no easy feat. I am proud
of each and every one of you.
Uh, each of... No.
Just you actually.
Go Maud! Woo-hoo!
NUMBER ONE! NUMBER ONE!
Fillies and Gentlecolts...
And is that
Magnesium-rich Basalt?
It is my honor to present our
vale-rock-torian, Maud Pie.
Excuse me. "Doctor Pie."
Doctor Pie! DOCTOR PIE!
Rock-ter Pie?!
I'm Maud.
YEAH YOU ARE! BRILLIANT
SPEECH! ENCORE! ENCORE!
There's more, Pinkie.
I'm Maud...
... Pie, thank you.
YOU ARE SO WELCOME!
BRILLIANT SPEECH!
ENCORE! ENCORE! ENCORE!
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee....
You're moving
to Ponyville!
We'll live together
and get bunk beds
and I'll make us fuzzy
slippers that say
"Best Sister
Friends Forever,"
although I probably can't fit
all those words on a slipper
so maybe just "B.S.F.F."
but we don't have
to decide right now
because we'll be together
all the time since
when it comes to Ponyville,
THE DOCTOR IS IN!
Slow down, Pinkie Pie.
You're moving to Ponyville!
I'm not definitely
moving to Ponyville.
Of course you are,
silly. You said--
"There's nothing left to study
back home on the rock farm,
so I might move
to Ponyville."
I'm also considering
Ghastly Gorge.
Hahahahaha classic Maud sense of
humor. You should do stand-up!
I do, but that
wasn't a joke.
GHASTLY GORGE?! That terrible
awful no-fun all-alone canyon
in the middle of nowhere?!
There, or Ponyville.
But Ponyville is
so "eeeee!"
And Ghastly Gorge
is so... "Urghhh."
It's a rock-based
decision.
But what about
B.S.F.F.'s?
That's why I'm giving
Ponyville a chance.
So all I have to do is prove
Ponyville has better rocks
than Ghastly Gorge?
Challenge accepted.
We'll drop your stuff
off at my place and then
hold onto your world cause
it's about. To. Get. ROCKED!
OK.
Ghastly Gorge may have "rocks,"
but our Gem Cave ROCKS!
Ahhhhh? Ahhhhhhhhh? OH!
And look, you never
know who you'll see!
Maud, darling, it's
lovely to see you again.
Congratulations on
your rockterate.
What are you doing now?
Talking to you.
Ah, right. Hahahaha...
Well, if your trained eye
happens to see a
chartreuse gem,
I'm desperate
to find one.
I found one.
Oh, you're an
absolute darling!
This will surely make
my gown stand out
at Countess Coloratura's
album release party.
Do you know how
rare this is?
Just another day
in Ponyville!
That's actually a
really common gem.
Huh?
These are all
really common gems.
They are?!
I mean, come on!
Of course they are.
That's why I didn't bring
you here to impress you.
I wanted to make sure
you had a chance to...
say hello to your
ol' pal... Spike.
Hello, Spike.
Way to go, Maud; cross
that off the to-do list,
you know what I'm
sayin'? Check.
Now let's get moving cause I'm
about to show you something
that'll make you
yell: "ALL RIGHT!"
All right.
See?! Ha ha!
Ta-da! It's a castle...
MADE OF ROCKS!
Whaaaat? Did I just
blow your mind?
I think I just
blew your mind.
A lot of structures are
made from rocks, Pinkie.
They're a very stable
building material.
But this place
grew out of nowhere
after a magical key-filled
gem followed a rainbow
and buried itself
in the ground!
I mean HAVE YOU EVER
SEEN ROCKS LIKE THIS?
Yes.
NO YOU HAVEN'T!
We literally just saw hundreds
of them in the gem cave.
But-- but-- OH LOOK
AT THOSE ROCKS!
Those are sting-bush
seed pods.
So they are. But...
LOOK AT THAT ROCK!
It's even got four smaller
rocks around it like legs!
That's a tortoise.
WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON, TANK!?
WAIT A MINUTE! WHAT'S THAT?
It's a rock shaped
like Lyra Heartstrings!
TOTAL ROCK!
I guess you won't be moving
to Ponyville after all.
Those rocks at Ghastly Gorge
don't know how lucky
they are to have you.
Actually, rocks
aren't the only reason
I'm considering Ponyville.
You said it's a
rock-based decision.
I'm obviously passionate
about exotic rocks.
But I've always
studied them... alone.
I could handle some
less exciting rocks
if it meant I'd have somepony
to talk to besides Boulder.
Are you saying you
want... A FRIEND?!
I wouldn't mind one.
[gasp]! Maudileena Daisy
Pie, this'll be easy!
What are you looking
for in a friend?
Gimme six qualities
assigning each one
a numerical importance rating
between one and seven,
seven being essential
and one being "mehhhhhh?"
It isn't hard to
meet somepony I like.
It's finding
somepony who gets me.
I get you.
You're my sister.
It's different.
Maud. You are THE BEST.
You never know when the
lightning of friendship
will strike! Somepony could
come barrelling through
that door at this very moment
and become your best friend!
You know I really thought
somepony was going
to come barrelling
through that--
My fault--totally my
fault. Are you OK?
I should have been watching
where I was going.
You look really familiar...
have we met before?
Yes.
I knew it--!
WHAT?!
Don't tell me,
ummmmmmmmm...
Yeah, see I was really
hoping you'd tell me
while I pretended
to remember.
How is this POSSIBLE?! AHH!
I travelled Equestria for my
rockterate dissertation...
Psst! Do you know a
lot about rocks?
Yes.
Have you ever come across some
kind of super-powerful stone
that can store the cutie-mark
magic of, I don't know,
an entire village?
Yup. In the big cave.
Hahahaha..hahah.. Hey, I
got an idea!
Let's not tell anypony that
part where you maybe for sure
accidentally helped Starlight
enslave a town. Hahahaha!
Tell. No. Pony.
It's not like she's
enslaved anypony lately.
Heheheh...
Well, great seeing you again.
I gotta run a few errands...
Sigh.
Offer to help.
What?
OFFER TO HELP!
You want to help?
Do I?
Of course you do! Go!
OK.
They're totally
gonna be best friends
and then Maud will
choose Ponyville
and we'll get to wear
B.S.F.F. Slippers!
Rocks take on
different properties
when interacting with magic.
With the right stone, you
could rule all of Equestria
if you wanted to.
You're messing with me.
Am I?
Hahahaha... so, other than
rocks, what else are you into?
Minerals, plate tectonics, oh
and stand-up comedy of course.
I like kites.
Kites are cool.
Ah!
The trick with an SLK is not
to make the spars too heavy,
but if they're too
light you got no ballast
and then good luck
tacking against the ALI.
I really like kites.
They're starting
to grow on me.
Pizza delivery! Maud and
Starlight, you're here too?
WHOA what a coincidence,
cause I was just, you know,
delivering this
pizza to, um... you!
So how's it going?
Just hangin' out--
Hey, you could use
this time to bond
and talk about feelings!
For example: do you "feel"
like you're becoming friends?
Um. I "feel"... like I don't
want to talk about feelings?
Great, I'll go next.
I feel like I love that you
two are becoming best friends!
I mean your friendship
could be the friendship
that makes Maud
move to Ponyville!
No pressure, Starlight!
Hello? Where'd
you two go?
Sorry about my sister. There's
no half-excited with her.
Oh, I know. But she always
calms down eventually.
Why do you find
rocks so fascinating?
Each one has a different story
to tell. Like Boulder here...
This tells me he's over
two thousand years old.
You don't look a day
over six hundred.
Wow. You can tell
that from a line?
I didn't get
a rocktorate
because I can shred on
guitar like nopony else.
Hahahaha.
Another reason I like rocks...
they don't exclude
you if you're...
different than
other ponies.
They're beautiful and strong,
but they don't judge you or
make you feel "less than"
in any way. I think I'm
starting to like rocks too.
It's hollow?
It's granite. Hollow
granite is highly unusual.
Wow. Have you ever seen
anything like this?
No. And that's
unusual... for me.
There you are! I thought
you went your separate ways
but you can't imagine
how happy I am to find
you both together
and to witness
one of your firsts
as friends!
Your first time discovering
an underground cavern!
I can't wait till you're old
and eating pistachios together
telling your
grandfoals about this.
Oh, no! They're not
bonding! I GOT AN IDEA!
Whoaaaa! I'm tripping on a
rock at this very moment!
And now I'm falling down!
Oh, no!
My accidental clumsiness
has trapped us here,
where you'll be forced to
bond until we're rescued.
Oh, we don't have
to wait for that!
There's got to be
a spell that--
Get us out of
here, boy!
Boulder! That...
was... AWESOME.
No, that was sandstone.
More sand than
stone, apparently.
I'm thinking you wear
these around your necks
at all times so I don't
lose you again, you sillies!
That way I can track your
progress as friends!
Ooh and tomorrow we could
have a FRIENDSHIP BRUNCH!
What's your favorite
kind of omelette-cupcake?
Mine's jalapeño-red velvet!
Uhhhh....
Yeah, um... I don't
know if I can make it.
You'll change your minds when
you smell the yummy food.
Come on!
"Oops."
Tomorrow's brunch is
gonna be the scrunchiest,
brunchiest munchiest
brunch ever!
Yeah. About that...
The problem is, while
you two were alone,
I couldn't get data points on
your friendship probabilities:
were you making Starlight smile?
How was Starlight's
smile to frown ratio?
Anything over five
to one is GREAT!
Oh, and how many times
did YOU smile like this?
Zero times.
Oh, Maud, don't be
so hard on yourself.
You've got the best
friendship maker in Ponyville
on the case. I'll be by
your side the whole time.
Speaking of which, your
bell fell off, silly!
Pinkie Pie, I appreciate what
you're trying to do, but...
But... ?
Never mind.
Don't worry, Maud. When
you see this brunch,
you'll realize everything's
going to be OK.
And then I have amazing
bonding activities planned
for the next seventeen days!
You and Starlight will
be besties in no time!
Goodnight!
Friendship brunch!
Maud's voice: Pinkie Pie.
Thank you for trying so hard
to help me make friends.
But my decision has
to be rock-based.
And Ghastly Gorge
has such great rocks,
I won't even have time for
friends. It's better this way.
Sorry it didn't
work out. Maud.
Maud, wait!
Maud!
Maud.
STARLIGHT, WAKE UP!
Kites!
Huh?
If this is about brunch,
I uhh... you know what?
Jalapeno red velvet omelettes
sound gross; I just can't.
Maud left in the
middle of the night!
Oh, I guess Ghastly
Gorge really does have
the best rocks.
Why couldn't you
two just be friends?
Pinkie Pie... I
like Maud.
You do?
Yeah, she's weird.
Hey!
No, in a good way.
She sees the world in
a totally different way
than anypony I've ever met.
She accepts me for who I am.
She taught me that a
rock is never just a rock
and she can make anything funny!
And we never had to say it
but... we got each other.
You really were
becoming friends?
I think so, but you kinda,
sorta...got in the way.
You're right. Too
harsh. Let's go with:
"You ruined everything
all the time?"
Ngh... that's worse. What
I'm trying to say is...
I-have-to-go!
Ta-da. Friendship
lesson... learned?
Sigh.
Sorry.
Emerald-Jasper. This
must be my lucky day.
Maud tracks!
Hello, Pinkie Pie. I
found Emerald-Jasper.
AHHHH!
Are you OK, Maud? That
eel almost ate you!
What eel?
You didn't need to come.
I'm having a great
time on my own.
I even made a new friend.
Is it a rock?
Yes.
Maud!
I don't belong
in Ponyville.
It only proved I'm
better off all by myself,
like I always have been.
DON'T SAY THAT! It was
all my fault! I-- LOG!
I thought I knew everything
about making friends.
But I didn't even
know my own sister.
I forced you to
do things my way,
but my way isn't your way.
This way.
Exactly.
No, this way.
Maud. I thought you couldn't
make a friend without my help.
But it turns out, you couldn't
make a friend with my help.
I underestimated
you and I'm sorry.
I know you did
it out of love.
You're my Best Sister
Friend Forever.
OH MAUD, I LOVE YOU
BIGGER THAN ALL EQUESTRIA!
And you melt my
heart more easily
than sodium-rich
plagioclase feldspar.
I don't know
what that means,
but please-please-
please -please- PLEASE
give Ponyville
another chance.
But more importantly,
give me another chance...
to leave you alone.
What do you
think, Boulder?
You're back!
Mm hm.
For good... ?
This doesn't mean we need to
start talking about feelings,
does it?
No way.
Maybe after this, we could
decorate my new place.
Totally. Where
is it?!
Well, it's not
in Ponyville...
... more like
Ponyville adjacent.
It's perfect.
YES! MY SISTER'S TOTALLY
STAYING IN PONYVILLE!
I MEAN PONYVILLE
ADJACENT!
Ahh ha ha!
Sorry, sorry, I'm leaving. I
promise. I'm not even here.
EEE, you're wearing
the slippers!
OK, now I'm really
leaving. Bye!
Heh heh. Wrong way.