♪♪
Pinkie Pie: Oh, wow!
Oh, my gosh!
[vroom]
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Sorry, Applejack!
Twilight! Twilight,
where are you?!
I'm in here, Pinkie.
What is it?
You'll never guess
what I just got!
Is everything OK?
We heard a lot of "Oh, my
gosh-in'" and we weren't sure
if it was a good thing
or a bad thing.
A good thing!
"To Pink Pony who lives
with baked goods."
It's from the yaks!
"Yaks cordially invite Pink
Pony to Yikslerbertfest."
"Come. NOW!"
Prince Rutherford is officially
inviting me to Yikslerbertfest
in Yakyakistan!
What is "Yikslerbertfest"?
It's a sacred
Yak holiday.
How did you get Prince
Rutherford to invite you?
I subtly hinted for an
invitation in my letters to him.
May I please come
to Yikslerbertfest?
Pretty please?
Pretty please!
Pretty, pretty, pretty,
pretty, pretty please!
After my seventeenth scroll,
I think he picked up
what I was putting down.
Hee hee hee hee!
[giggles]
[giggling]
You know, we still don't
know a lot about the yaks.
So I think you should definitely
go to Yikslerbertfest, Pinkie.
[agreement]
Fostering friendships
is what ponies do.
I won't let you down.
It's an honor to be the Official
Friendship Ambassador
to the Yaks!
Um, that's not an
official position.
Yet.
You're the Princess
of Friendship!
You can make
it happen!
OK, you got it.
Ahem. You have to
make it OFFICIAL!
[groan]
Right. I hereby
make Pinkie Pie
the Official Friendship
Ambassador to the Yaks.
♪♪
This is officially  the most
exciting day of my life!
♪♪
Yoo-hoo, Gummy! Pay attention.
We're in the middle of an
Official Friendship Ambassador
Road Trip Game.
[blinks]
That's better.
OK, I spy with my
official friendship eye
something that is blue.
[whistling wind]
♪♪
[gasp] We're here!
Oh, and by the way, the
answer was "sky." I win!
Yeah, I know that was
a hard one, Gummy.
You're the best Official
Friendship Travel Companion
ever!
[boing] [splat]
♪♪
[rumbling]
What is going on!?
♪♪
Yaks destroy!
All: Yaks destroy!!
Yikes!
[crunching]
Ha ha! Pink Pony!
It's an honor to [crash] er..
be here, Prince!
[crash] Uh, did something
terrible happen?
Is Yikslerbertfest canceled!?
No. This Yikslerbertfest.
Where yaks get
together to stomp.
Ohhhh, I didn't know that was
part of the sacred holiday.
So this angry display
of destruction
is part of the festivities.
Heh. And here I thought you yaks
were just in a bad mood.
No. Stomping relaxes yaks.
Hey ah!
[grunts] [crashes]
Yak's head never been so clear.
♪♪
This is AWESOME!
[shout]
[bang] [bang]
[bang] [bang] [bang] [bang]
STOP!
[bang] [bang]
Pink Pony better check
self before wreck self.
That is century-old sacred
Yak Twig passed down
from generation to generation.
[Gasp!] Oh, no!
I'm so sorry!
I was just trying to get into
the spirit of Yikslerbertfest.
[whining] Maybe I can fix
it--
[whining]
[snort]
Ha ha ha! Yak kidding!
[shouts]
Yak got Pink Pony good!
Horn bump!
Gah!
Whew!
You sure did,
Prince Rutherford!
[giggle]
That was a close
one, Gummy.
This trip has to
be perfect!
After all, we're not
just visiting as friends.
We're on Official Friendship
Ambassador business.
Less talking!
More stomping!
[shouts]
Pinkie Pie: Yeah! Uh! Stomp! Stomp! Stomp!
♪♪
Now, I take Pink Pony
on Yakyakistan tour.
Thanks, Prince Rutherford.
But.. I've been to
Yakyakistan before.
Yak know.
But thought Pink Pony
might not recognize town
since decorated for
Yikslerbertfest.
You're right!
It's so different now that
you've pointed it out. Heh, heh.
Oh, yaks not just have
eye for decorating.
Yaks also amazing builders.
[gasp] No way!
I thought you hired
professional contractors!
[splat]
Here, let me help
you with that.
[splat]
This Ceremonial Yak Fire pit.
Where yaks tell stories.
Ooh!
I have so much to officially
tell the ponies when I get back!
This Yak Eating Hut.
Hut where yaks eat.
[slurp] [bite]
[swallow]
Mmm, the perfect balance
of vanilla extract.
Yaks grow own vanilla bean.
Nothing imported.
[chomp/gulp]
[chomp]
Yak Sleeping Hut.
Hut where yaks sleep.
[hup]
[soft sleepy sounds]
[sighing snores]
Yak Music Hut.
Hut where yaks enjoy
beautiful music.
♪♪
This is beautiful and-
Sssh. Pink Pony
ruin with talking.
♪♪
... And that how yaks
defeat evil and save world.
[knock knock knock]
Pink Pony like yak story!
A-ha! Yak impressed!
Pink Pony can almost
be Honorary Yak.
Official Friendship
Ambassador and Honorary Yak!?
[squeal]
Pink Pony's title
card is full!
Horn bump!
Oh wait, I don't have a horn.
[gasp]
Prince Rutherford, can I
get some honorary yak horns?
No. Yak horn too heavy
for small pony head.
[horn blast]
Yikslerbertfest Stomp Time.
[shouts and crashing]
Stomp harder, yaks extra happy!
Ponies and yaks, friends!
♪♪
[whoosh]
Is this part of the festival?
Pink Pony ask too
many questions.
♪♪
Everything is buried in snow!
What are we going to do!?
[mumbles] Yaks fine.
Snow fall from
mountains all the time.
All the time?
Every Yikslerbertfest.
OK. Avalanches like
this completely bury
all your homes every
Yikslerbertfest?
Really?
This.. is.. big avalanche.
But not a problem,
for yaks are tough!
Yaks dig through snow.
Won't take long.
Oh good, you have an
emergency plan in place.
♪♪
Here, let me help.
[buzzing]
[swallows]
[grunts and groans]
[buzzing]
Whoo, I'm tired!
We must be almost done.
There's still snow
everywhere!?
Yaks keep digging!
[digging]
[rumbling]
Ohhhhhh.
Yaks stop digging!
Makes situation worse!
OK, don't worry,
Prince Rutherford.
I'll go back to Ponyville
and ask for help.
Twilight and the others will be
happy to come dig the snow away.
After all, many hooves
make light work!
Right, Gummy?
Yaks no need pony help!
[grunts of agreement]
Oh. Well, I'm sure
it'll be OK,
cause you probably
have a plan B.
Yes. Yaks wait
for snow to melt.
All this snow!?
It'll take a thousand
moons before it melts!
Yaks known for their patience.
Well.. be that as it may, in
the meantime, what will you eat?
Where will you sleep?
Bah! Yaks can make this work.
Hardship make yaks the
strong yaks that yaks are!
If Pink Pony disagrees, then she
can leave Yakyakistan
and never return!
Ah! Er.. of course Pink Pony
agrees with you! Heheh..
Hey! Let's try out
some snow recipes!
[zoom]
[grunting]
Snow cakes!
Snow spaghetti!
Snow sandwiches!
Heh, heh..
[chomp]
Mmmmm!
Yaks can make this work!
[yawn] Yak tired.
Yak retire to new Sleeping Hut.
♪♪
[sleepy sounds]
Hmph.
[munching]
Snow cake good!
[chomp]
[gulp]
[shudder]
Mmmm.
Just the right balance
of cold and water!
Oh! Stop!
Yak eating new Eating Hut!
Psst, Prince Rutherford,
what are we doing?
It's obvious.
This New Music Hut!
Oh. So we're swaying to... ?
Ssshhh. Pink Pony ruin snow
music with talking.
♪♪
[rumble]
What was yak?
Yak stomach rumbles.
Yak hungry.
Sshh.
Prince Yak will
hear yak!
But snow worse
than yak ever seen!
Yak know.
Yak hungry too.
[gasp!] Gummy, did you hear that?
They can't make it work.
Yaks stop swaying.
Music over.
If Twilight and the others
knew what was going on,
they would be here to help
in a pony's heartbeat.
I have to convince
Prince Rutherford
that asking for help is OK.
Will you help me, Gummy?
Thank you!
And see, asking you to
help wasn't hard at all!
[slurp]
Pink Pony has
gathered you around
the New Ceremonial
Yak Firepit...
... to tell you a story.
A yak tradition, right?
[agreement]
Yay!
This is a story
about a group of...
er.. goats, who live
in the desert.
There was a sandstorm
and their entire village
was buried in sand.
There was nothing they could do.
They knew they could not survive
on only eating sand-wiches!
Get it?
OK.
Anyway, finally, the goat's
brave, wise leader
--let's just call
him Prince er.. Drutherford-- heh, heh
decides that they couldn't
do it by themselves.
So he asked the neighboring
town of uh, Bovineville
to come help them. Yeah! Cows!
The magical cows
helped the goats.
Everyone survived and
lived happily ever after.
Because they asked for help.
The end!
[shouting]
So what is the
moral of that story?
Is it A: asking for
help is OK?
B: asking for help
saves the day?
Or C: asking for help
is good for everypony!?
D: goats weak
and horrible!
Magic Bovines need to stay
out of goats' business!
Um... not quite.
Any-yak wanna shout
out another answer?
[whistling wind]
[groan]
[scrape] [scrape]
Pinkie: Hey,
Prince Rutherford.
I want to talk to you about
something -- what are you doing?
Eh.. Yak snow bed got a
little melty last night.
OK, yeah.
That's what I want
to talk to you about.
You know, these yak snow
beds are the fluffiest
I've ever slept in!
They're so comfortable,
you forget that it's just
a cold block of ice.
And the yak snow
sandwiches, mmm, mmm!
I hate it when food
burns your mouth
or overwhelms
it with flavor.
Oh! Yak hates that too!
You know who would
really, really enjoy
these snow sandwiches?
Twilight Sparkle and
the other ponies!
Oh! Hey, I have an idea!
Why don't I go to Ponyville
and bring them back here?
Ponies like snow sandwich?
Oh! Ponies love snow
sandwiches!
And, hey, while they're here,
you can ask if they'll
clear the snow away.
Fun, right?
When Prince was little yak,
Prince stomped on
ground too hard.
Made deep hole and
fell into hole.
Ice froze over hole.
Prince waved to friends and
family from inside frozen hole.
Waited for spring thaw.
Prince survived on own.
Wait a minute..
You spent the whole
winter in a hole?
Yes. And yak never
ask for help!
[horn bump]
OK, first of all, how did you
make such a deep hole
from stomping?
And how did it
freeze over so fast?
And how could you see
your family and friends
to wave to them from
inside a frozen hole?
Even if all that was possible,
how did you breathe in there!?
YAKS DON'T ASK FOR HELP!
But the yaks are hungry!
And who knows when
the snow will melt?
I just don't
understand why--
Ah yes, is clear now that Pink
Pony does not understand Yaks!
Honorary Yak status rescinded!
Bang! Pretend there
is door!
I just slammed it!
Fine, be stubborn!
♪♪
Oooh! Those yaks are so stubborn!
They refuse to ask for help
even though they need it.
Well, this Official
Friendship Ambassador
is going to take matters
into her own hooves.
I'll show them.
You're right, Gummy.
I am too worked up.
A road trip game would
officially calm me down.
I know!
Let's play "Twenty
Million Questions."
You think of something.
Then I'll ask you twenty
million questions
until I can come up with
what you're thinking of.
Let's go!
Is it blue?
Is it green?
Is it red?
Is it greenish-red?
Is it reddish-blue?
Is it bigger than a bread box?
Is it smaller than a bread box?
Is it a bread box?
Is it bread?
Is it teeth?
Is it Granny Smith's dentures?
Is it you?
Is it a rooster?
Is it a red rooster?
Is it a red rooster eating corn?
Uhp, used up all twenty
million questions.
Oh, well, we're here anyway!
Official Pony
Balloon still here?
[shakes head]
Pink Pony gone because Pink
Pony not tough like yaks.
Horn bump in agreement.
Now!
[horn bump]
[chomp]
Bleagh!
Snow sandwich lose novelty.
Snow couscous for dinner.
[grunts]
Then Prince Rutherford
said -- Bang!
Pretend there is door!
I just slammed it!
Pinkie Pie--
So then Pink
Pony said --
Fine, be stubborn!
Pinkie Pie, we have
to help the yaks!
So in conclusion, we
have to help the yaks!
Hmm?
Just go with it, hon.
Great idea, Pinkie.
We'll be happy to
help the yaks.
This is what friendship
is all about.
Hey! I'll bring
apples.
This season's batch
are extra juicy.
And I shall provide the yaks
with Equestria's
finest textiles.
They'll be silky and
warm with hints of gold
to compliment their horns.
Stop!
We can't bring the
yaks any pony stuff!
Why not?
The yaks are very proud.
They won't ask for help.
You know what they say, you
can lead a yak to water,
but you better not let
him know you're doing it!
Nopony says that.
Do they?
OK then, this will be an
Official Covert
Friendship Mission.
Rainbow Dash: You got it!
Pinkie Pie: Woohoo!
Pinkie: Is it yellow?
Is it slimy?
Is it slimy-yellow?
Rainbow Dash: We're
not playing that!
First, we have to
infiltrate the yak compound!
[clang]
These walls are high.
Sneaking in will not be easy.
♪♪
[grunting]
[door creaking]
Or it's super easy
cause I'm awesome.
Go ahead. I'll
catch up!
You all know
what to do!
[thud]
[snoring]
[pop]
♪♪
[yawning]
Oh!
What happened!?
Snow melted.
Prince Rutherford was right!
[laughter and cheers]
Aha! Yaks tough!
Yaks wait patiently.
Yaks win!
♪♪
Whoo-weee, helping to fix
an entire yak village
sure takes a lot out of you.
Let's get out of here
before--
Prince: Oh Pink Pony!
♪ [scary music] ♪
[nervous laugh]
Just play it cool...
We didn't help fix
Yakyakistan! No no!
We're just here for
the snow sandwiches!
But.. then we got here and the
snow's gone so we thought
we'd hit a diner on the way
back to Ponyville. Buh Bye!
Wait! Yak not mad
at Pink Pony.
Yak not?
Pink Pony helped yaks
without yaks asking.
Means Pink Pony understand yaks.
I do?
Hunh! I do!
Pink Pony the best
kind of friend.
Officially Honorary Yak!
Hooray!
Yay!
Pink Pony Honorary Yak!
Yippeeee!
My own Honorary Yak Horns!
Now I can officially horn bump!
[thunk] Oh!
Yeah, you know this is a little
heavy for my small pony head.
Ha ha ha.
Need some help with
that, Pinkie Pie?
Pink Pony no need
Apple Pony's help!
[giggle]
Just kidding!
Pink Pony got Apple Pony good!
Seriously, this is
heavy. [thud]