♪♪
[croaking sound]
I know!
I can't believe it either!
The map has never
called me before.
I'm sure that's not why
she looks like that.
[shakes]
Actually it is.
Well, it's that and the fact
that you're being called
to the royal palace!
I mean, what in Equestria
could be going on there?
Do you want me to come
with you? No. I shouldn't.
The map just called you
for a reason, right?
Though maybe it's a mistake.
Not because of you!
Because it's never called
just one of us before.
[nervous laugh]
I also wasn't nervous
before, but now...
Don't worry.
For all we know,
it's something small!
Like maybe the cooks
are fighting over
who has the best
butternut squash soup.
Or the royal hairdressers
are fighting over a comb!
Or ya know, maybe
the royal sisters
aren't seeing eye-to-eye
on something.
No!
That's just crazy!
Luna and Celestia
would never fight... again.
♪♪
So, the map sent you to
solve a friendship problem?
Yes, Princess.
Well, there's
nothing wrong here.
Right, sister?
No, everything's perfect
as usual, sister.
♪♪
Agh!
Psst. Psst!
♪♪
Twilight...? Is that you?
How are you here?
I'm not, I'm still home.
It's an easy spell.
I'll show you later.
Anyway, enough
about me!
I had to
check on you.
Not in a
meddling kind of way,
in a friendly
how's-it-going way.
Sooo, how's it going?
Not great.
I think the problem might be
between Celestia and Luna!
Oh, no! That's terrible!
I mean...
What makes you say that?
You know how someponies
say nothing's wrong
but you can tell something's
definitely wrong?
Noooo.
That's basically what
the princesses did
when I said there was
a friendship problem.
Only they did it more,
you know, regally.
I wish I could help
you, but I can't.
Both for map reasons and
because I have no idea.
This is big!
Like really big!
But I'm here if
you ever need to talk.
Or listen to music!
♪♪
Heh.
Comforting, right?
[groan]
Thank you so much for
breakfast, Princess.
I can't believe you
cook it yourself!
Of course, Starlight.
I really enjoy doing it.
It's a small way to
say "I care."
[door opens suddenly]
Good morning, sister!
Join us?
Too tired.
[scrunch]
Please excuse me.
Starlight: Wow. Last night must
have been really hard on her.
Perhaps, but she is
like this every morning.
♪♪
So I think Luna may be hurting
her sister's feelings
without even realizing it.
Poor Celestia.
That's so sweet that she makes
her sister pancakes
every morning.
She's your mentor.
I think you might be biased.
Fair enough.
So what are you going to do?
Nothing. Yet.
I have to get all the facts.
I asked Luna if I could spend
some time with her this evening.
[knock knock]
[door opens]
Princess Luna is waiting
for you, Miss.
[nervous giggle]
Good luck, Starlight!
[whinny]
[door closes]
♪♪
Wow, Princess Luna.
You do this every night?
Lavender's calming scent
is known to aid dreamers
in achieving a
restorative sleep.
[sniff]
That's so thoughtful!
I try my best to make sure the
ponies in this castle
sleep peacefully.
(old woman voice)
So then I said, "touring?
More like boring!"
Ha ha hah!
Celestia: You really are a card!
[polite laughter]
[sigh]
But as always, my sister's
too busy having fun
with dignitary ponies to
acknowledge anything I do.
Humph!
♪♪
So both princesses are hurting
each other without realizing it
and instead of talking about it,
they're just getting
colder and more distant.
And they're Celestia and Luna,
so it's not like you
can just confront them.
Actually, that's exactly
what I was gonna do.
WHAT!?
Are you CRAZY!?
I mean, you do whatever
you think is best.
This is your mission.
Gee, thanks for believing
in me, Twilight.
I do!
But... the last time the
princesses fought,
Luna turned into Nightmare Moon
and Princess Celestia
had to banish her for
a thousand years!
That can't happen again.
Well, I can't do nothing!
The princesses aren't the
best at communicating
with each other.
[gasp]
Sorry.
It's just you
said "princesses"
and "aren't the the best"
in the same sentence
and it's making me nervous!
[clunk]
I'm not much help, am I?
No!
Wow, I almost feel
bad eating this.
It's adorable!
Like I said, I
enjoy this part.
[door opens]
Hi.
Princess Luna! Wait.
♪♪
As you both know, the map
sent me here for a reason
and I think I've
found out what it is.
Really? Oh, that is
wonderful, Starlight.
What is it?
You two.
Celestia: I beg your pardon?
Luna: Excuse me?
I think you're accidentally
hurting each other's feelings
..without realizing it.
♪♪
Princess Celestia, does it
bother you that Luna never
notices the wonderful breakfasts
that you prepare for her?
Uh...yes. It does.
Princess Luna, tell Celestia how
you feel about the fact
that she never
acknowledges the work
you put into
lining the hallway
with lavender every night.
I...Well, it's not
the best feeling.
I'm sorry I never noticed that you
make fruit faces on pancakes.
But nights are long for me!
You might be a morning
pony, but I am half asleep!
You think I don't get tired?
I'm exhausted!
Oh, I apologize for not noticing
flowers in a wall sconce,
but by the time I get
to retire for the night,
I can barely see straight.
Even so, I still make
an effort to smile.
Like smiling is so hard!
I'm sure that's not what
Princess Luna meant to say.
Is that what "exhausts" you?
Smiling and being
adored by everypony?
And you have it so
much worse, do you?
You spend your evenings
flitting around
giving ponies
lovely dreams!
Oh, it sounds just awful.
O....K.
I feel like we should step
back, take a deep breath...
Don't presume to know what it is
like to govern the dream realm!
And yet you know exactly
what it's like to be me?
Oh, please!
Enough!
[zap]
♪♪
There!
Now you'll know exactly what
it's like to be each other!
[gulp]
♪♪
[gasp!] What have you done?
I went with my gut?
Switch our cutie marks
back this instant!
My apologies,
Your Majesties.
But I can't, even
if I wanted to.
This spell lasts
twenty-four hours.
It may have been extreme, but...
I think it's still a good idea?
What?
You said it yourselves.
Neither of you believes
your sister knows
how hard it is to be you.
So this is your
chance to prove it.
Well, I could use
an easy day
followed by a good
night's sleep.
You can try.
I haven't had an easy
day in well, ever.
But now, I get to sleep and
tonight will be a breeze.
All right, Starlight Glimmer.
We will do this.
Good choice.
Not that you had one.
[nervous giggle]
I'm gonna stop
talking now.
[panting]
You switched their cutie marks!?
The actual princesses'
CUTIE MARKS!?
Uh.. I thought we
moved past this!
It was the right
call... I hope.
[gasping]
[knock at door]
Are you OK in there?
I'm good!
Just uh ...
reading an exciting book!
He's going to think I'm nuts!
He's not the only one.
[draw opens/closes]
As you can see, Celestia and
I are switching places today.
Huh?
I assure you, I am more than
capable of handling
all of Celestia's
"duties." Dismissed!
[grumbling]
So what is first on my
dear sister's 'to do' list?
It says you have a few
public appearances.
Store openings, judging the
Royal Rose contest, you know,
that sort of thing.
[huh]
Oh, I knew today would be easy
but I didn't think it
would be that easy.
♪♪
[snip] [snip] [snip] [snip]
[camera snap]
"Princess Luna Unhappy
With Student Fund-raiser?"
But I wasn't unhappy.
Um, you are scowling.
I didn't mean to.
I'd been smiling all day.
My cheeks hurt; I
stopped for one second
and that's when he
took the picture!
Guess smiling all day isn't
as easy as you thought?
It says here that
because of me,
the school didn't raise enough
funds to go on their field trip.
I-I-I didn't mean for
that to happen!
[clunk]
Starlight: I know.
But you can't dwell on that now.
According to the list, some
delegates are about to arrive
for a luncheon.
You need to dispel
rumors of Timberwolves
in the White Tail Woods.
The nearby towns have been in
a state of panic for weeks.
B-B-But I have to fix this!
You can't.
You need to put on a brave
face and help these ponies.
It's what Celestia would do.
[door opens]
HELLO! GREAT NEWS!
THERE ARE NO TIMBERWOLVES!
There are definitely
timberwolves!
I'm sorry, but I
couldn't stop thinking
about those poor students!
Normally, I have all the time
and solitude I need
to work through my
problems at my own pace.
Well, your sister
doesn't get that luxury.
[arguing]
Ready for the
town hall?
[sigh]
[shouting]
Glad that's settled.
That only took
three hours.
That got heated
didn't it?
Still on for
golf?
Oh, absolutely!
You made it to the
end of the day!
Yay?
Hmm? Oh, yes I'm just
going to turn in then.
Goodlight, Starnight.
Oh, hello, Starlight!
I don't know about you, but
I feel very well-rested!
Where's Luna?
Um.. she already turned
in for the night.
Did she now?
It seems my duties were harder
than my sister expected.
♪♪
Moon raised.
It's even easier
than raising the sun!
What's next?
[snoring]
Of course.
Everypony's asleep at night.
Luna works alone.
Oh, but it's nothing
I can't handle!
All I have to do is
watch over Equestria,
visit the dream realm
and protect ponies
in their nightmares.
My list was three
times as long!
All right.
Everypony's asleep.
You're talking to
yourself, Celestia.
But there's nopony
else to talk to!
Yet.
I can talk to ponies
in their dreams!
♪♪
Now to save some ponies
from their nightmares,
which aren't real so it
shouldn't be too hard, right?
Right. Good call, Celestia!
And I'm talking to myself again.
[scream]
I care.
I Care.
[scream]
No!
This is big!
Like really big!
Wah!
Starlight, I'm here now.
Tell me what's wrong.
Going with my gut
was the wrong call!
I was supposed to bring
you two closer together,
but I've only driven you apart!
If you two can't see why
you need each other, then...
Then I am back!
[nasty laugh]
Don't worry, Starlight.
I know how to handle
Nightmare Moon.
Yes, but can you handle.... me?
[nasty laugh]
[screeching laugh]
This can't be!
If Luna can turn
into Nightmare Moon,
you can absolutely turn
into me, Daybreaker!
The better, prettier and
more powerful version of you.
No. I'll never turn into you!
Deep inside you know
how powerful you are.
You don't need Luna.
That's not true.
Even when we were apart,
I knew I needed her.
[laughing]
Oh, please!
You don't need anypony.
You can do whatever you want
and all you have to do
is get rid of anypony
who stands in your way.
[zap]
I never should have
banished you to the moon.
I should have destroyed you!
No! You can't do that!
Day, night, sun, moon -
Equestria needs both of you.
Without balance,
there's no harmony!
[zap!]
Who needs balance when
you can have it all?
[zap!]
You can't get rid of
me so easily, sister.
Unless you plan on
smiling me to smithereens!
Enough!
[cackles]
I told you I was more
powerful than you.
[magical hum]
Ugh. So much black.
We get it, you're sad!
You could really use some.. SUN!
♪♪
[gasp]
[magical shield]
♪♪
[zap!]
This is all my fault!
I never should have
gone on this mission.
Now Equestria is doomed!
♪♪
♪ That smile's too wide. ♪
♪ It's obviously not real. ♪
♪ [eerie music] ♪
Why don't you want us to go
on our field trip?
I don't--
I mean, I do!
♪ That smile's too wide. ♪
♪ It's obviously not real. ♪
Celestia!
I'm so glad you're...
♪♪
[zap]
[magic zaps]
I've seen a lot,
but I haven't seen this before.
It's Starlight Glimmer's.
She's afraid this is what would
happen if we continue to fight!
[sobbing]
What was I thinking?
I'm never going
with my gut again!
If you don't fix this soon, it
could have a grave consequence
on Starlight's psyche.
But my magic isn't
powerful enough.
I thought if we
work together--
I have your magic,
remember?
It doesn't work in
the dream realm.
It has to be you.
Oh, Luna, I can't
do this!
I was wrong. Your job
is so incredibly hard.
You have to battle nightmares
and work in the darkness
and do it all alone!
It takes such a brave, strong
pony to do what you do!
--and that pony is you.
I walked a day in your shoes.
I thought all you had to do
was smile and be adored
all the time, but I was wrong.
There is so much
more to it than that.
[shrieking laughter]
[zap]
[scream]
[thud]
♪♪
[nasty laughter]
Don't do this to each other!
♪♪
In order to defeat Daybreaker,
you need only to trust in
your strength, as I do.
♪♪
[zap!]
You can't destroy me!
I'm everything you want to be!
No, you're not!
You are not real and you
will never exist again!
[whoosh]
[shouts]
[whomp]
You did it!
Only because you were here.
I don't know how
you do this alone.
So um...
did you talk
to yourself?
Um... a little.
[giggling]
Is this really happening?
Or is this still a dream?
[woosh]
Welcome back, sister!
I know you had a long night
so.. I made you some pancakes.
Oh!
How... nice.
Ahem.
[gulp]
They are ...delicious.
Thank you.
[laughter]
I know that face;
they're not.
I know you have to be
perfect for everypony else
and you do an amazing job but
you don't have to do it for me.
In that case...they
are terrible!
[laughter]
In that case...they
are terrible!
[laughter]
I know!
But it means a lot
that you tried.
I love you, sister.
I love you too.
So... this was real!
[yawn]
Or was it not real and
this just happened now
and not in my dream?
I'm so confused.
[laugh]
It's all real.
It was the right call,
going with your gut.
The map was wise to
send you, Starlight.
Nopony else would have been
so bold as to do what you did.
That's a nice way of saying
I came dangerously close
to messing everything up.
It was just
what we needed.
The experience has made
us closer than ever.
[zap]
Wait...
I'm not doing this!
♪♪
I believe that one means
your mission is complete.
Wow. I can't wait
to tell Twilight!
[zap!]
I already know!
I mean I don't know everything.
I just got here to bring
you your toothbrush.
So this is just
a friendly visit,
not interfering because I
was worried! I wasn't.
I knew you could do it and
I'm so so so so proud of you!
Tell me everything! Start
from after I hyperventilated
and don't leave
out any details!
♪♪
Oh, uh, by the way,
there's a field trip
you need to make happen
and a.. timberwolf issue
you need to address.
What!?
Oh! Look there's the sun!
Time for me to turn in!
♪♪