Care for a carrot
ginger sandwich?
Ohh.
You remembered to cut
off the crusts for me.
Of course I did.
I know how you like them.
You really do make
the best finger foods.
What do you say?
Excuse me!
Oh! I really can't
take them anywhere.
Can I trouble you for
another sugar cube?
Oh, no. I'm so sorry,
but I seem to be out.
[pop] Well, I can just
pop us in some more.
Oh that's all right.
I need to go to
the market anyway.
I have to restock my pantry
for our tea party next week.
Oh, I never realized
how much work you put
into hosting these
tea parties.
Oh, it's really
not that much.
No, no, no, no, no.
I've been taking advantage
of your hospitality
for far too long.
It's high time I do
something about it.
What to do... What to do...?
Why don't you host
the next tea party?
I've got it!
Why don't I host the next
tea party at my place?
Hey, that's my idea.
Why didn't I see
that coming?
[escaping air hiss]
So Fluttershy...
what do you think of
my brilliant,
genius, amazing idea
of having the next tea
party at my place?
Are you sure?
I wouldn't want you to
go through any trouble.
You, trouble? Never!
I insist.
Then count me in.
I'm already looking
forward to it!
Me, too!
I'm so excited; I can't wait.
No, really! I can't.
How about we have the tea
party tomorrow afternoon?
Sounds good to me.
You know, Discord, I've never
been to your house before.
Well, that's OK, because I've
never hosted a tea party before.
Oh? I've never hosted
a tea party before.
So much to do!
Thank you so much for
the tea and nibblies,
but I really must be going.
Uh, Discord...
before you go, would you
mind helping me tidy up?
There you go.
Back to normal, just
the way you like it.
See you tomorrow!
I can't wait!
OK, since Fluttershy always
goes out of her way
to host the perfect
tea party for me,
how do I make my
tea party for her
even more perfect?
I'm sorry dearie, were
you talking to me?
Actually, Madam, I'm
talking to myself.
Well, I'm not
talking to you!
It's for Fluttershy.
Oh, all right.
No more holes though.
You have to knock this tea
party out of the park for her.
She was our first
friend, after all.
You don't have to
tell me that.
She gave us a chance
when no other pony would!
She makes us want to be
a better draconequus.
Fluttershy deserves
the best of everything.
Of course. I should get her
the best of everything!
Why didn't I think of that?
Well, are you going
to answer me or not?
Me?
I thought you were
talking to--
--No time!
I'm off to prepare a tea
party worthy of Fluttershy!
Excuse me.
Is this where Fluttershy
usually buys her tea?
Why, yes it is.
Oh, wonderful!
I'll be enjoying her
company tomorrow,
so I will be needing your
very best tea, please.
Something especially special.
I'm sure Fluttershy would enjoy
some of our Rosehip green tea.
Oooh. Interesting.
Does it decorate your hips
in roses or turn you green?
Uh, neither?
It just tastes good.
How boring.
Pass.
Hold on!
Ginseng tea.
Now that sounds promising.
What does it sing?
I'm partial to something
upbeat and jazzy.
Again. It's just tasty,
like all of our tea here.
So.. all this is just
tea you simply drink?
Uh-huh.
Oh! Seems that I got
here just in time.
♪ La, la, baloo. ♪
♪ Sha loo ba doo ba dee! ♪
Singing ginseng!
I'll take it!
Are you sure you're
friends with Fluttershy?
You seem so very
different from her.
Well, of course
we're friends.
She gets me and you
obviously do not.
"Are you sure you're
friends with Fluttershy?"
Why, the very nerve.
I'm sorry, do you validate?
Hello.
Gah!
Uh, can I help you
find something?
Yes you can. Your
finest tea set, please.
I want only the best for
my friend, Fluttershy.
Uh, you're friends
with Fluttershy?
Yes, judge-y clerk pony.
Why is it such a surprise?
Sure, she's on the quieter
side and I'm a bit,
well, more showy..
but I'll have
you know, we're besties.
And that's why I need
the BEST TEA SET!
Perhaps then you'd
be interested
in our classic
"Tea for Two" set.
A teapot that just pours tea?
How positively dreadful.
But that's all tea pots
are supposed to do.
Not anymore!
Much better.
Don't wrap it;
I'll walk it home.
Now let's see, I
have the perfect tea
and the perfect tea service.
What else do I need for
the perfect tea party?
Oh!
Decorations, of course!
Good, but not nearly good
enough for Fluttershy.
Ta da! choo!
Oh, ho ho!
Better.
Oh, I'll need napkins.
I'll simply make them...
I could...
or ...nope.
I've got nothing.
How do I make these better?
What should I do?
Make them...
make them glow.
That's not good
enough for Fluttershy.
Should I make them fly?
Glow, fly and fold!
Glow, fly, fold into
fun shapes perhaps?
[Pinkie Pie] Uh, Discord?
Are you OK?
Pinkie Pie!
Just the pony I need.
As the party pony and
Fluttershy's close-but-not-best
friend, I need your advice.
I'm hosting a tea party for
her and it has to be perfect.
No, it has to be even
better than perfect!
Oh, Discord.
You're waaaay
over-thinking things.
All you have to do is make
Fluttershy feel comfortable,
which should be
pretty easy for you!
You know her so well!
And that's why you're
the party expert.
Thank you, Pinkie Pie.
I feel so much better now.
Eh, it's what I do.
Excuse me, where can I
find the glowing, flying,
self-folding napkins?
♪♪
Make Fluttershy
feel comfortable.
Comfortable. Comfortable.
Well, I mean that
shouldn't be a problem.
♪♪
Aie aie aie CHOO!
♪ Ba da, ba da, ba
da, ba daaaaa. ♪
♪ Ba doo, ba doo, ba doobee ♪
Oh, dear. That might
be a problem.
♪ La la la la! ♪
♪ La la laa. ♪
♪ La la la la la laa. ♪
Maybe it's not as
bad as I think.
Maybe Fluttershy
would be comfortable
having a tea party here.
♪ Ba da, ba da, ba
da, ba daaaaa. ♪
♪ Ba doo, ba doo, ba doobee ♪
Maybe I just need another
set of eyes on this.
What do you think?
That bad?
No... worse!
Fluttershy would never
be comfortable here.
What have you done?
I was trying to make the tea
party different and special...
like me.
But all I did was make it
chaotic and weird... like me.
What if those ponies at the tea
shop and china shop were right?
What if Fluttershy sees how
crazy this place is
and realizes how
different we are
and then doesn't
want to be friends anymore?
Relax. We can fix this.
Time to call in
the team.
OK, chief. What's the plan?
What to do, what to do?
What to do?
Oh! Got it!
We know Fluttershy and
we know what she likes.
First of all, we need to get
rid of all the new stuff.
You heard him.
Strike the new stuff!
Piñatas hate bats.
♪ Ba doo, ba doo, ba doobee ♪
Enjoy your all-expense-paid
trip around Equestria!
Well done everybody, but
there's still more work to do.
We need to make this place
more Fluttershy and less...
well, me.
One thing I know
about my dear friend
is that she loves
comfy chairs...
But not on the ceiling.
And I'm almost certain she likes
stairs.. that lead somewhere.
And although we've
never discussed it,
I'm pretty sure
Fluttershy likes gravity.
OK fellas, this is a good
start, but stand back.
Let me show you how it's done.
We just need some of this...
And a little of that--
Oooooohh. Aaaaaaah.
Wow!
And a whole lot
of those!
Whew!
How boring.
I mean, normal.
Thank you.
Good job.
The window treatments are
perfectly unexceptional.
But we're not done yet.
You don't mean...
Mhmm!
Make-over!
Hating it.
Hating ... how
much I love it!
Agh!
OK, let's give these
conversation cards a whirl.
Ahem.
It is very nice
to see you today.
Have you read any
good books lately?
Your garden looks
positively lovely.
Right on!
Great!
Oh, quite strange, for
the first time in my life,
I don't feel quite strange.
In fact, I feel...
completely normal.
Everything is finally
perfect for Fluttershy.
And just in time.
Discord! I'm so excited to
finally see where you live.
Greetings, friend.
Please do come in.
I can't wait to see how...oh.
Is something amiss?
Um. No, no,
not at all.
It's just.. not
what I expected.
It's quite... lovely.
Please, have a seat.
Where is it?
Right here.
Oh.
I think you'll be quite
pleased with the green tea
I've selected for us today.
Oooh! Does it actually
turn us green?
Is it really envious
of the other teas?
What's it do?
Uh well... it tastes
delicious.
Oh. OK.
What particularly nice
weather we're having.
Yes. Yes we are.
It did rain the
other day, however.
Uh-huh.
But the weather today
is particularly nice...
as I previously
mentioned.
Would you care for
some milk toast?
Uh.. Discord, you don't
seem to be yourself today.
Are you feeling
all right?
What ever do you mean?
Well, it's just...
what you're wearing.
And also, what
you're saying.
And.. also the way
you're saying it.
And um, pretty much
everything else.
Oh, dear Fluttershy.
Worry not.
I can assure you that
for the first time,
I'm feeling perfectly normal.
Now let me top you off.
Whoops!
Butter fingers.
How embarrassing.
Uh...what's going on?
I have no idea...
[gasp] Discord! You're
starting to fade away!
Oh. You don't say.
Have you read any
good books lately?
Huh!
Have you tried
the scones?
They're positively
delectable.
The secret is in
the extra butter.
What is wrong with you?
You're acting so "normal"
which is not so normal for you!
W-What ever do you mean?
This is just me.. being me.
No, it's not!
It's you being like
everypony else!
Eeep!
The more you do it the
more you fade away!
Of course!
You're a creature of
pure chaos!
Being normal is
destroying you!
Oh, haha, how interesting.
That reminds me of something I
heard at the market today.
STOP IT! Please.
You need to go back to being
your not-normal normal self!
Quick, Discord, do something
chaotic before it's too late!
Please!
Do something chaotic?
I'll try....
Ohh, that's not good.
Oooh. Then I guess it's up to me.
Uh, OK. All right.
How about...?
Oh, no.
I tipped over that cup!
That's pretty chaotic, right?
Ooh. What if I...?
Oh, my! Talking with food
in my mouth
after taking a bite from every
sandwich... how wacky!
Doing anything for ya?
Oh... OK. Hmmm.
Maybe I need to start
thinking like you.
Ooooh. What would Discord do?
Well, I guess he'd probably
make another version of himself
to bounce ideas off of.
But one wouldn't be enough.
He'd need more. Way more.
Hey there, Fluttershys, any
ideas on how to Discord-up
this tea party?
Hi Fluttershy,
thanks for asking!
First of all, you gotta
redecorate this place!
I mean this is where Discord
lives! And you're telling me
there aren't any stairs
that lead to nowhere?
On it!
Better, but it still
needs something.
Now that's more like it!
It's working!
OK, what else?
Furniture on the ground?
So predictable!
Let's put them where
they don't belong.
And he'd have a chaise lounge
that would actually chase you
because he's funny like that.
I bet you can't catch me!
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, and Discord would have
a special kind of tea,
like a ginseng that
could really sing!
I would! I-I would!
♪ La, la, la, la! ♪
♪ Lala lala la la! ♪
And he'd serve it
on a floating table!
We've never talked about it,
but I'm pretty sure
Discord hates gravity.
I do! Who wants to be
tethered to the ground
when you can do this?
Haha! Now this is exactly
what I was hoping for!
This is what you
were hoping for?
But this is the complete
opposite of your tea parties.
I wouldn't expect you to throw
a tea party the way I would!
We're different.
I know.
I was afraid that if you saw
exactly how different we are,
you wouldn't want to
be friends anymore!
What!?
Why would you ever
think that?
Because... you and I don't
make sense to anypony else.
That may be true, but
we make sense to me.
I never would have thought
to make singing ginseng
before I met you.
But you've opened me up to so
many more possibilities
and impossibilities!
So I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
I like you because you're
so different from me.
You do?
Of course I do, silly.
Besides, what's Discord
without a little chaos?
Well.. in that case, I certainly
don't need to be wearing this.
Whoops!
Haha. I forgot that I
still had this on.
Now, about that tea party...
You know, your garden
really is looking lovely.
Why, thank you for noticing.
I also couldn't help but
notice that you need a refill.
Aie! Achoo!
Gesundheit!
It really is nice
having you here.
I'm happy to be here.
And I really do like your
place... because it's so you.
Why thank you, Fluttershy.
Now, how about we
try some of those
delicious-looking
sandwiches?
Ha ho!
You read my mind.
♪ La, la, la, la! ♪
♪ Lala lala la la! ♪
Yahoo!