[indistinct chattering]
♪♪
Hmph. Looks like I'm
not the only one
who left Mare's Day
to the last minute.
There's just so many!
How can I choose?
[shouts]
Now hang on, everypony.
We'll help all of you.
HOW?
Rarity: What I would do...
... is pick flowers that
accentuate my mane.
It makes for a
captivating color story
when you present them to
whomever they're intended.
♪♪
That's it!
Color consultations was
a great idea, Rarity.
Now, what can we do for you?
Oh, darling, I need a
dozen lavender pieces
for Photo Finish's shoot
on the Most Beautiful
Manes in Equestria.
I know you're swamped,
but it's for Vanity Mare.
She's going to take
pictures of my mane,
so color coordination
is a must.
Anything for you, Rarity.
♪♪
[blowing]
Have you a single big one?
If the wind came
from one direction,
it would really
intensify the effect.
I don't. But I
could make you one.
It's not like I've got
anything else to do.
[blowing]
[door opens]
Hmm. I do enjoy the
wind-swept look,
but other ponies might need to
see it before they feel it.
♪♪
[door opens]
[exclamations]
My mane will be flowing over
the chaise in the tableau
I have in mind, but I was
hoping to choose the color.
Could you make one
in a pale yellow?
I need something across
the color wheel from.. this. Heheh.
Oooh. If these came
in different colors,
I'd buy one for every room.
Hmm. Sales have been down...
More colors it is!
♪♪
[ding ding ding]
Pinkie?
I need to put Photo
Finish in a good mood.
And nothing creates a better
mood than your confect--
Am I interrupting?
We were just celebrating
the anniversary
of the twins' first sneezes!
♪ [accordion arpeggio] ♪
[ahem]
♪ Just about one year ago ♪
♪ There was a tickle in
your nose. ♪
♪ You snorted through the
nursery HAAAAAPY SneeziveSary! ♪
♪ Achoo! Achoo! Acccchhoo! ♪
Congratulations.
♪♪
Ah! Pinkie, I can't have Photo
Finish shoot my mane like this!
And this party string
won't come off!
Oh, that's because it's
not just party string;
it's Super Sticky
Celebration String!
Grrrr.
Sorry. I guess my sneeziversary
was a little too sneezibratory.
[giggle]
[gasps]
It'll be fine, Pinkie.
I'll find a way to clean this
up before the shoot tomorrow.
Actually, you might
consider doing the same.
[grunts]
If only we had some kind of
super sudsy mane conditioning
shampoo for you and a magical
cleaning remover potion for me.
Oh! That's it!
We'll pay
a visit to Zecora!
She's a wonder with a cauldron.
I'm sure she can mix
a fix for both of us.
Huh?
That's good because it would
take forever to yank all those
baked goods out of this Super
Sticky Celebration String.
I.. think you may still
have some baking to do.
♪ [eerie music] ♪
I do wish Zecora lived in town.
One shouldn't have to brave the
darkest part of the forest
for shampoo.
Do you think
Photo Finish
would want to take a
picture of my mane?
Well.. mmm... I'm not sure that your
style is quite right
for this particular photo essay.
Photo Finish traveled
everywhere in her search
for the most
beautiful of manes.
[shaking]
[squeal]
Even Yakyakistan?
Well, Yaks don't
have manes, per se
and I'm not sure their style is
quite what she's looking for either.
[splash]
Though, at this moment,
neither is mine!
Don't worry!
Zecora will absotively
be able to help!
I'm sure you're right.
Listen, spooky eyes!
Why don't you take a picture!?
It will last longer!
[squeak]
On second thought, don't!
Getting my picture
taken in this state
is what I'm trying to avoid!
Rarity: Are you certain that's safe?
Zecora: I'm sure
they seem strange,
but my methods are mine.
After all, I've been doing
this for quite a long time.
♪♪
I'll have those cupcakes
cleaned off in no time!
You really should bake new ones.
Nah!
For your mane, of course,
just soap will do,
so use my super sudsy shampoo.
Ohhh! What a relief!
I can't tell you
how worried I was
that my mane wouldn't be
ready for the shoot.
Ha ha ha ha! Oh!
You were right to be concerned.
Manes are tricky I have learned.
Ohh.. pfft. Tell me about it.
Cleaning is simple
but a magical fix,
could cause any number
of troublesome tics.
Really?
Oooh.
There are tales I could tell to
make your hair stand on end,
horrifying, terrifying,
attempts to mane mend.
Well, I do enjoy a good yarn,
but I'm not sure I could take
any more mane fright today.
Well, I LOVE a
good scary story! Heh heh.
There's the contagious frizz
that spreads friend to friend,
or the story of the
infinitely splitting end...
AHHHH!
[clattering]
Er um.. Yes, well, very
entertaining.
Ah.. Thanks for the
shampoo. Ta, ta!
Anything about curls
that keep on curling
until your whole body
is one big curl?
[laugh]
There is one story
I nearly forgot,
of an earth pony who needed
to clean up her shop.
Wow. That's just
what I have to do.
Ha! Weird.
Perhaps it'd be better
if I were more clear,
you can't clean up
Sugarcube Corner from here.
Gee, Zecora, I can
take a hint.
With just a few drops,
any mess you'll improve,
if you focus on that
which you want to remove.
It won't be hard to focus on the
Super Sticky Celebration String.
It's kinda the only
thing you can see.
Zecora said it would
only take a few drops,
but I figured we should all
chip in...just in case.
Remember to only focus
on the party string.
We don't want to accidentally
remove anything else.
[baby giggles]
Ooooh! Sudsy!
[giggles]
♪ [humming] ♪
Ah! A relaxing shower really gives
you the chance to focus
on the fabulousity of your mane.
Ha ha!
[happy sigh]
[sniff sniff]
Not the most pleasant scent
but it gets the job done.
[humming]
[squeeze]
My mane feels lighter alr--
--AIIIIIIIIEEEEEEEEE!!
[slurp] [door opens]
It's important that you know
that I am not pointing hooves b--
I don't understand.
Is that you, Rarity?
Why would you think to
point your hooves at me?
Let's just say I understand
why your shampoo
hasn't made a splash
in the marketplace.
♪ [dramatic sting] ♪
Oh... Goodness, Zecora.
You could at least
pretend it isn't that bad.
I'm sorry my dear, but
there's nothing to say.
You just took the wrong
potion from here yesterday.
Oh! Thank goodness!
I thought maybe your shampoo
had triggered early onset
mare pattern baldness.
No, this lack of hair
was put into motion
when you mistakenly washed
with remover potion.
[hysterical giggles]
What a relief!
Well, if you could just whip up
a cure, I'll be on my way.
So much to do before
the shoot tomorrow.
As I mentioned before,
there's no easy fix.
Mane mending magic's the
trickiest of tricks.
Ooo. Sorry?
I doubt that your mane
has left us forever,
there's a chance we can fix
it, I think, if we're clever.
Wa-wa-wait..
There's- there's a chance!?
You THINK!?
I need to focus if I'm
to work any faster,
one wrong ingredient
spells utter disaster.
You should go finish
your list of to-dos.
Keep your mind off all of
these mane-losing blues.
[exclamations]
Oooh. There's nothing to worry about.
Zecora will have a cure before
I've even finished my to dos.
But I don't know if I can even
show my face looking like this.
[gasp]
[baby crying]
♪♪
I'm sorry, miss, but I
can't match your mane
if I can't see it.
What about mine?
Marigold, I should think.
I'm sorry, but I
believe it was my turn
and I-I-I just need
to pick up--
Perfect!
Now me!
♪♪
It's wonderful how this display
shows that your fans provide
just the right amount of air.
Well, I owe it all to Rarity.
Oh, so kind of
you to say!
I-- Kindness has
nothing to do with it.
Rarity always knows how to
make something look its best.
Probably because she
looks so good herself.
That ain't something us
non-fabulous folk here
can understand...
Ah! Non-fabulous!?
[agreement]
♪♪
[exclamations]
I appreciate everypony's
interest in our new sofa colors,
but the yellow
one is spoken for.
Oh thank you, Davenport.
Um, perhaps I can pick it up
once everypony leav-
I'll give you twice
whatever the pony
who wants to buy the
yellow one is paying!
THREE TIMES!
But, but, I--
SOLD!
♪♪
[horrified gasp]
[screams]
I can't believe how
differently ponies treat you
when you can't command
their attention.
Are you sure that's
what happened?
Wait. You can't command
ponies' attention
because your mane's
messed up?
MESSED UP?
Does THIS look
"messed up" to YOU!?
[gasp]
Honestly, how hard is it to
pretend it's not so bad?
Hard.
If today is any indication of
how ponies will treat me
from now on, I can't simply wait
to see if my mane grows back.
I'm sorry, Rarity.
I'm sure nopony means
to make you feel worse
than you already do.
Didn't you say Zecora
was working on a cure?
Yes, well, even if everypony
isn't utterly indifferent
to my presence, Zecora
might not be able
to fix THIS in time for
the shoot!
Can't you do a spell that
restores some semblance
of my mane!?
The thing is, it's pretty
much like Zecora said.
Fixing manes with
magic is--
Tricky! I know!
I don't care!
Make with the tricks!
Huh?
Oh.
[zap]
[shriek]
[shatter]
[whoosh]
[knocking]
Rarity: This won't do..
I need an actual mane!
But it has to come
from somewhere.
Huh. You can't just make
a mane with magic,
the results could
be disastrous.
More disastrous than this!?
[zapping]
[snipping]
Ohh.. I don't think there's
anything else we can try.
But we- But Zecora said there
was still a chance...
At last, Rarity
I've searched for so long.
What I told you before
was totally wrong.
Zecora, you found a cure?
That's amazing!
Oh! You mean I'll get my fabulous
mane back in time for the shoot?
Oh. No.
I'm afraid I can't fix
it before the big shoot.
But in time the hair will
grow back from the root.
There's no magical cure to
hasten us through it
unless you went backward
it time to undo it.
Uh-uh.
I think we can both say
that's not a good option.
[blubbering]
I have always believed that the
right outfit can make up for
any other areas
that are lacking,
but I will need your
honest opinions.
A-ha...!
How awful is it?
Uhhhhh...
[cat yowls]
OH, COME ON!
Can't anypony
pretend it's not bad!?
We could... um.. try.
Maybe....
Well, if any of you have an idea
on how to make this disaster
look good enough for Photo
Finish's piece in Vanity Mare
on the Most Beautiful
Manes in Equestria,
I'm open to hearing it!!
Is that all?
No problem.
♪♪
I don't understand,
Applejack.
How is milking a
cow going to help?
That's just it.
It looks like we hired
a new milk maid.
This is pretty close to my
color as a youngun.
Just a little down
home ingenuity.
It's a good idea, Applejack, but
Photo Finish is looking
for the most beautiful
manes, not bonnets.
Heh heh...huh.
This'll do the
trick, just you wait.
[zipping]
[gasp] You know, this is really
quite fetching--
Yes! Nailed it!
[poof]
--just not portable.
[groan]
♪♪
[growl]
There.
♪♪
Oh, let's face it.
I'll just have to call
Photo Finish and cancel.
I think we all know how
bad Rarity's been feeling,
but I never thought she'd cancel
her shoot with Photo Finish.
You saw her mane, right?
But it's Rarity.
If anypony can turn lemons
into lemonade, it's her.
I guess it's harder for her
when she feels like the lemon.
Well, she's not a
lemon. She's our friend
and right now she
needs our support.
[knock knock]
Rarity: Come in.
[door opens]
[doorbell ringing]
Would you mind closing the door?
I'm more comfortable
in the dark.
[light clicks]
OK, Rarity, you've done
just about enough sulkin'.
Having a fabulous mane
is a wonderful thing,
but it ain't the only thing.
Yeah!
And we're here to remind
you how awesome you are,
mane or no mane!
[sigh] It's lovely of
you to say,
but it's hard to argue
with cold. Hard. Facts.
What facts are those?
That without my mane, I simply
can't shine as I once did
and ponies treat me like the
sad, invisible pony I've become.
Rarity, you're not invisible.
You're our friend.
A friend who started
a fashion empire.
A friend who made us
all feel beautiful
in her lovely creations.
A friend who stuck
by us no matter what.
A friend so generous that she
once chopped off her own tail
to help a sea serpent!
I know you lost some confidence
when you lost your mane,
but unlike your hair,
confidence is something
you can get back right now.
Goodness, you're right!
The only pony behaving
differently today was me!
Besides, one doesn't
shine from the outside in.
Um, Rarity, what are you doing?
I'm preparing to shine
from the inside out.
[approving chatter]
Awesome!
♪♪
It's my own fault.
I shouldn't have bought flowers
without asking Spoiled
what she likes.
Well, we don't have much left.
What does she like?
Um, purple?
Rarity: I have a solution.
♪♪
Rarity, that mane is-- Amazing!
Thank you, although I'm afraid I
missed my chance at Vanity Mare.
Which means I have quite a few
lavender arrangements to spare.
Uh... Is lavender purple?
♪♪
Hm. The wind-swept look
is very last season.
Perhaps you could
set this up outside?
It's sure to draw
in the hoof traffic?
[blowing]
[exciting chatter]
[clinking]
Photo shoot or no, you
can always use a chaise.
Well, Rarity, if you wanted
to shine from the inside out,
I think this afternoon, you
became the brightest filly
in Equestria.
Oh, pshaw, Applejack, I'm simply
making up for all the time
I wasted feeling
sorry for myself.
I don't know why you were so
upset, your mane looks awesome!
I'm just glad that I have all
of you to remind me that
even if I accidentally use
magical remover potion
on my mane, I can look
good on the outside
as long as I feel good
on the inside.
How did you end up using remover
potion on your head anyway?
[gasp] Pinkie!
If I had the remover
potion this whole time,
that means Pinkie
must have the--
WHHHEEEEEEEEE!!! [giggling]
Shampoo.
Shampoo?
Wow, that explains why our manes
are all so bouncy and soft.
♪♪
Uh, perhaps I'll fetch the
rest of that remover potion.
Great!
Hey! Is there something
different about you?
New hoof polish?
So you're sure?
You're sure it's
fully recovered.
Yes, Rarity, it's been months.
Your mane looks fine.
Ooooh, look!
It's the Most Beautiful Manes In
Equestria issue of Vanity Mare.
You should read it.
Oh, honestly, Pinkie,
after all I went through,
I'm not sure it even matters
what mane graces the pag--
READ IT!
But.. I canceled the shoot.
We had a little talk
with Photo Finish.
And explained just how beautiful
we thought you were -
inside and out.
While you were shining
from the inside out,
Photo Finish took
a few pictures.
I don't know what to say.
Luckily, you don't
have to say anything.
Your style speaks for itself.
[laughter]