Pinkie Pie: OK. All we need is a
dot of salt, a dab of sugar
and a spritz of ginger.
Uh, are those real measurements?
How do you keep track
without a recipe?
Pie baking is more
art than science.
And this will be
my masterpiece!
It's to celebrate Rainbow
Dash's seventy-third
Wonderbolt training session!
Seventy-third?
That's specific.
I know!
The pie is blueberry because
Wonderbolt outfits are blue.
The crust is rainbow,
for obvious reasons.
But the most special part is
the seventy-three super-secret
sweets and spices that represent
each training session!
Could you please pass the brown
sugar, pink sugar, sweet-root,
apple-jelly,
berry-mash and a towel?
You sure are going to a lot of
trouble for Rainbow Dash's pie.
Phew! That's because I know
how much she loves them.
My pies are her favorite!
It's worth all the
trouble to see her happy.
Now I'm going to need some
cocoa powder, cocoa flakes...
Ooh! Cocoa bar!
Want some?
Isn't that for the pie?
[laugh] Oh, Twilight!
That's hilarious!
You don't mix chocolate
into a blueberry pie!
This is my mid-morning,
pie-making chocolate fuel that
keeps this pie baking train
chugging down the tracks!
Break time's over!
Now let's finish this pie!
Chugga-chugga
chugga-chugga CHOO-CHOO!
Good training,
everypony.
Nice work, Crash.
You really added that sparkle
to that pressure-diamond-drop.
SURPRISE!
Happy seventy-third
Wonderbolt training session!
My seventy-third
training session?
That's specific.
I know! I'm just so
proud and happy for you
and I've been counting
all your training sessions,
and I was going to wait until your
100th, but I got too excited
and I know how
much you love pie,
so HAPPY SEVENTY-THIRD
TRAINING SESSION!
WHAA? You didn't
have to do this.
I know I didn't have to,
but I really wanted to!
Have a bite.
Whoa! What's that?
Huh. Guess it
was nothing.
But wow, this pie is
the best I've ever had!
Is that.. cinnamon?
I knew you'd love it!
Have more. I made the
whole thing for you.
Really? That's so great!
But I need to go change.
And then I have to
take Tank to the vet.
His sensitive tortoise
tummy's been acting up again.
Do you mind if I take
this pie with me?
Of course not!
I gotta get back to my shift
at Sugarcube Corner anyway.
Congratulations again!
Heh, thanks.
[happy sigh]
I knew she'd love it.
Is that...
Is that...?
STOP!
You didn't see a blueberry
rainbow crust
seventy-three ingredient pie
with a slice eaten out of
it in here, did you?
Uh, n-no?
Right. Of course you didn't.
That would be ridiculous because
I made it for Rainbow Dash
and she loves my pies.
She would never throw them
away like trash, in the trash,
with other trash, right?
RIGHT?
Um, right...?
Hmm. That pie couldn't have
been the one I made,
I must be seeing things.
I did have a lot of
chocolate this morning.
But what if I wasn't
seeing things?
What if that was my pie?
Heh. That would be bananas!
Unless... Rainbow Dash's been
replaced by an imposter
who throws delicious
pies away!
Or has she been brainwashed
by a pie-hating evil queen?
You make a good point.
Rainbow Dash is too
stubborn to be brainwashed.
Plus she hates washing.
Hmmm. There's something
else going on here.
Let's look up a few of the more
recent pies I've made for her.
The boysenberry pie I
made for her birthday...
and her three half-birthday
lemon meringues...
and the It's Not Your Birthday
But Here's A Pie Anyway Day
custard pie!
She ate all of these, right?
[gasp] Another pie!?
Thank you so much!
Whoa, what's that?
[chewing] Guess it was nothing.
Heh heh.
Awesome!
Three lemon meringues?
Uh.. hey, what's that over there?
[chews] Oh, never mind. Heh.
Great pies!
Happy It's Not Your Birthday
But Here's Pie Anyway Day!
Thank you!
No way, check that out!
A-ha! It's not even my birthday!
Oh, sorry, guess
it was nothing.
[slurp] Mm.
But that custard
was everything!
Have I ever really seen Rainbow
Dash eat one of my pies?
And do I always look when
somepony points behind me?
WHAT'S THERE?
Heh. Good one.
But I need answers!
I've sent Rainbow Dash a pie
every month she's
been a Wonderbolt
and you're telling me you've
never seen her eat one?
Er...... Affirmative!
Or uh, negative.
Um.. I-I-I mean, she wasn't
seen eating one.
Hmm... interesting.
Very interesting....
Are we under investigation?
As chief detective
on the pie case,
I've labeled you all
ponies-of-interest
so it's best you tell
me everything you know.
Well, we have been
getting mysterious
monthly pie donations.
Would you be able to pick
these pies out of a line up?
I hear Rainbow Dash's
pet tortoise, Tank,
has been having
tummy troubles.
When did it start?
About a week ago.
Poor Tank had all the telltale
signs of sugar overload:
jittery shell, sleeplessness,
reptilian indigestion.
Hmm...
and this all happened the day
after I made Rainbow Dash a
"thanks-for-lending-me-your-
jacket" peach pie.
It seems the pieces of the
puzzle are plopping into place,
but the picture isn't pretty.
[gasp] Note to self: P
alliteration pie.
Is that everything, Doctor?
Well, there's also this.
Interesting.
Did you have the lab analyze
the flavor of that pie?
No, but you know, Ms. Cheerilee
was in here not long ago.
The class hamster was
having similar symptoms.
[gasp] Perhaps it's a pie pandemic!
Perhaps.
And I just might know
pony patient zero!
Dr. Fauna's right.
I do always have to remind
the foals and fillies
not to share the pies with
the class hamster.
Animals just can't
digest pony food.
Indeed.
But where do these
pies come from?
Well, they're from
Rainbow Dash!
She drops off her
"Day-after-Rainbow
Dash's-half-birthday"
pie every year.
Did you say the day
after her half birthday!?
Very, very interesting.
Because I give her a pie on
her half birthday every year!
And I have a feeling
it's the same pie.
Well, wherever it comes from,
the students just love it.
I'm so glad.
At least I can be
sure somepony is.
She didn't eat the blueberry,
she didn't eat the banana,
she didn't eat the cream and
she didn't eat the chocolate.
SHE DIDN'T EAT ANY OF 'EM.
WHY?
And don't tell me this
all just started recently;
it's been going on for years!
Cheerilee said so herself.
And if there's one thing I know,
you can't escape the truth!
Rainbow Dash doesn't like PIE!
AND SHE'S BEEN LYING TO ME
ABOUT IT THE WHOLE TIME!
AAAAHHHHH!
Pinkie Pie?
Whoa!
Oh. Party Planning
Cave. Right.
You OK?
Or are you just
screamin' for fun?
Screaming is fun,
but I'm not OK!
I've been making Rainbow
Dash pies for years,
but she doesn't
even like them!
She's been lying to me!
But everypony loves your pies!
They're the greatest thing
since sliced apples.
Thank you!
And I could swear I've seen her
eat one of your pies before.
Have you REALLY?
Um, I thought I had;
that's why I said it?
Are you suuure?
Maybe I haven't?
Exactly!
Because it's all been a sham.
Rainbow Dash has been laughing
at my pies behind my back
and scheming of a way to get
rid of them for years!
Bring forth the worst tasting
food in all of Equestria!
And now I will destroy Pinkie
Pie's horrid abominations,
freeing the land of these
disgusting pies FOREVER!
Nooooooo!
Good riddance strawberry
cream and peaches 'o plenty!
Be gone apple crumble
and lemon surprise!
Gone! Gone! GONE!
I really don't think
that's what's happening.
I don't think
so either.
I know so.
Well, I've got just the
thing to get your mind off
all this madness.
We've had a great apple harvest
so I was hoping you could whip
up a few of your delicious pies.
Yes, I will make
pies, lots of pies!
I'm going to make Rainbow
Dash so many pies,
it'll force her to
admit the truth,
or I'll catch her in the
act of getting rid of them.
Operation: Pie of Lies is a go.
Thanks, Applejack.
I knew I could count on
you to come up with a plan.
I don't think
that's what I did.
Also...how do you
get out of here?
SURPRISE!
Ah! What's happening?
Happy unofficial
wake-your-friends-up day!
Uh. I've never heard of
wake-your-friends-up day.
Well, it's unofficial.
But I made you your
favorite pie in celebration!
Ta-dah!
Gifts are the second
most important part of
wake-your-friends-up day!
W-What's the first
most important part?
Accepting the gifts and
enjoying them immediately.
Uh...
Well, I'm sorry I forgot about
wake-your-friends-up day.
Let me make it up to you.
Here!
Achoo!
The pie... where'd it go?
What do you mean
where did it go?
Ha ha. Mm mm.
How!? Where!? When!?
Congratulations on
your seventy-fourth
Wonderbolt
training session!
Here's a pie.
Now eat it!
OK, this is getting
a little out of hoof.
I haven't even
trained yet.
Well, I wanted
to pre-celebrate
because I already know how
great you're gonna do.
Eat the pie!
Pinkie, look out!
I'm not going to fall for-- AH!
Whoa!
Pinkie! Are you OK!?
[struggling] Get me down!
Sorry Ma'am but we have to make
sure you didn't sustain
any internal injuries.
But the pie, what
happened to the pie?
Oh.. The pie was delicious.
You just get better!
NOOOOO!
Ah! Somepony help me!
Rainbow Dash, thank
goodness you're here!
I was trying to fix the top
pie on my pie pyramid
but the whole thing
became unstable.
And there's only one way to save
me: you have to eat the pies!
Don't worry, I got ya!
Oh, right.
Or you could save me that way.
You gotta be more
careful, OK?
Grrrr!
Rainbow Dash!
I wanted to thank you for
saving me from the pie pyramid,
so have a pie.
Have three!
Have fifteen!
I know how much you love them!
Now eat up!
Uh...
Thanks!
I can't wait to
eat ALL THESE PIES!
What? Where did they--
How did you--
Delicious!
You did it again, Pinkie.
Rainbow Dash, there you are!
I made a pie for everypony
and you're the only one who
hasn't eaten hers yet.
So here. Your pie.
For you to eat. Now!
Are you OK?
You seem to be staring
more than usual.
I just REALLY like to watch
others enjoy my pies.
You sure you don't
have to blink?
Me? Nope, I'm not
much of a blinker.
Don't mind me, go
ahead and take a bite.
Well..... do I want to take a
big bite or a small bite?
I just don't know.
Or maybe medium.
No, no, no.
Definitely NOT medium.
Just try some!
Ahhh..
Ah...  Do you have any.... milk?
Ah, never mind.
Your pies are just
too good to resist.
What?
No!
NO!
That's it!
I can't take it!
Uh. Everything OK, Pinkie?
No, everything is NOT OK!
YOU HATE MY PIES!
What are you
talking about?
You know exactly what
I'm talking about!
I saw what you did.
Well, I didn't
SEE what you did,
but I know that you've
been fake eating my pies!
You threw away the pie I
made for your seventy-third
Wonderbolt training session and
I know you SECRETLY somehow got
rid of all the other
pies I gave you!
ADMIT IT!
That's crazy!
What do you think I did,
somehow make them all
disappear into thin air?
Heh heh.
OK, so maybe I made one of
them disappear into thin air.
HOW COULD YOU?
What!? I, um, I-I just wanted to
share these amazing pies
with the folks of Cloudsdale.
So I uh, I was trying to send
them up via balloon mail.
But you just said
they were delicious.
Well, obviously
that's because...
I have amnesia!
I've been brainwashed!
It's.... opposite day?
Your memory's working
fine, you hate washing
and I know today's
not Opposite Day
because I bake you a
pie for it every year.
A pie that you probably
just throw away.
Or give to charity.
Or destroy with your laser
eyes while laughing at me!
Laser eyes?
Oh, oh! So you admit it.
What? No! I can explain.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT!
She won't listen to me; she
won't let me apologize.
[sigh] I feel terrible.
Well, you have
been lying to her.
To all of us, actually.
Yeah, is there anything else
you're lying about
that we should know?
No!
Well, not that I can think
of off the top of my head.
Is it MY fault that
I don't like pies?
And not just Pinkie's
pies, all pies.
I know how much she
loves making pies
and if I told her I didn't like
them, it would have crushed her.
Uh. You kinda
crushed her anyway.
Oh- But I- You're right.
I guess I should've just eaten
the pies in the first place.
[gasp] Wait, that's it!
I know how I can
make it up to her!
Pee-yew! Gummy
is that you?
Huh. What is that?
Oh, it's you.
Pinkie Pie, wait.
I know now that I should've been
honest with you from the start
because lying to your
friends is wrong.
And because getting rid of all
those pies was a giant hassle.
I mean, do you have any
idea how many pies
you've made for me
over the years?
Yes, I know exactly how many.
I have a very detailed
pie-ling system.
Of course you do.
The point is, I thought
the hassle was worth it
just to spare your feelings,
but I was wrong.
So to make up for it, I
made this pie for you.
Well, I guess I made it for me.
To eat in front of you.
Point is, I'm eating
this pie for friendship!
Wait, that smelly circular
monstrosity is a pie?
Yeah!
I know I can't go back and eat
all the pies you made for me
in the past, so instead
I'm going to eat this
giant one for you now.
So.. here I go!
Ahh......
Wait! I can't watch you do this.
I mean, is that crust or
some kind of concrete?
Yeah, honestly, I have no idea.
Oh, I can't believe
you're willing to eat
this terrible pie for me.
It's ridiculous and this whole
thing is overly complicated and...
[sigh] I think I finally
understand why you lied.
Whoa, what's that?
Huh. Guess it was nothing.
I'm so glad you enjoy my pies!
Oh, never mind.
Great pies!
EEEEEE!
No way, check that out!
A-ha! It's not even my birthday!
Oh, sorry, guess it was nothing.
Mm. But that custard was everything!
Seeing you eat my pies makes
me the happiest pony
in all of Equestria!
Heh. I know it does.
You did a lot of ridiculous and
overly complex things to get rid
of my pies because it made
you happy to see me happy.
Just like I went to a lot of
effort to make you the pies
because it made me
happy to see you happy.
Yes!
And if you're willing to
go through all of that,
it really shows how much you're
willing to do for your friends.
Heh. Aw shucks, it was nothing.
Now get out of that
thing and give me a hug!
Just remember, in the future you
can always be honest with me.
Uh. I could've told her that.
Cool...
How 'bout this: Your
hugs are too tight. Heh heh.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
No they're not.