♪♪
Oooh!
Excuse me, when
does the noon train
from the Crystal
Empire arrive?
Uh, noon?
Hm. Right. Sorry, I'm
just a little excited
because my friend
Sunburst is coming.
He's my oldest friend.
I mean, we've known each
other practically forever.
We have tons in common.
We both love magic and games
and jokes. Everything, really.
Now that I think about it, there
isn't a pony in all of Equestria
I have more in
common with.
♪ [music through headphones] ♪
[train whistle]
[train wheels clattering]
[chattering]
[slam]
[hiss]
♪♪
Sunburst: Starlight?
Sunburst!
You made it!
Of course!
I've been looking forward to
this visit for a long time.
Huh..
[thud]
Whoa!
How long are you staying?
Er.. just a... little
reading for the train.
[giggle]
Same old Sunburst.
Huh.
It's going to be so great
spending time together.
Just like old times.
You and me doing the stuff
we like: games, magic...
Antiquing.
What?
You know I like antiquing.
You do?
Um, of course!
Historical knickknacks,
ancient relics.
Oh! You are SO lucky!
Ponyville is antique central!
It is..?
How have we never
talked about this?
We are going antiquing
and you are gonna love it!
OK. Let's drop your stuff
off at the castle first.
Sure! Only.. heh.. we may need
to make a few trips.
[nervous giggle]
This is so great!
Who knew I'd be
the one showing
you the cool sights
of Ponyville?
I'm a little surprised, myself.
♪♪
Wow, what a difference between
the hoof-molded bricks
and the extruded ones, right?
Uh huh. Ha ha.
Oooh! Check out all
these chandeliers!
Sometimes the crystals
have magical properties.
Oh. That's cool.
How do you--
Twilight: Sunburst!
I'm so glad
you're here!
In the antique store?
In Ponyville!
Starlight's really been
looking forward to your visit.
Though I'm glad you're
in the antique store too!
I'm usually the only one...
That's crazy!
Who doesn't
like antiquing?
Right?
Heh heh... right!
Oooh, look!
An ancient map of Equestria
made by the Mighty Helm!
Without the help of unicorn
magic or pegasus flight,
the earth ponies
of the Mighty Helm
were able to map the
entire coast of Equestria!
Coooool..
♪♪
[gasps]
[laughter]
♪♪
You don't have to pretend
to like all this stuff.
What? No. I
do like it. Heh.
I mean, if you
like it, I like it.
Besides, we've almost
looked at everything.. right?
Twilight: Oh, wow!
You have got to see this
Saddle Arabian vanity!
This shop looked a lot
smaller from the outside.
♪♪
Did you see this
Palominian letter opener?
Wow! That goes well with this
ancient Phoenix feather quill.
We could write
to each other!
PEN PALS!
[laughter]
Um.. I really like this
old-timey barrel.
Actually, the stuff I
bought is inside the barrel,
but I can't wait
to see what it is!
Wait, you don't know
what you bought?
Mm-mm! It's a blind buy.
Sometimes shops get too busy
to go through everything
so they load up a box
or barrel and sell it
without knowing
what's inside!
Buying one is sort of
like a treasure hunt.
Once I found a first edition
History of Equestria
in the original Olde Ponish.
" Hliet foresettan pliht."
[laughter]
It's an Olde Ponish saying.
"Reward prefers risk."
Uh. It... loses something
in the translation.
Mmm. [giggle]
Hm. Why don't we look
through this stuff later?
Yeah. What do you want
to do, Starlight?
Well, I don't know if you're
going to remember this, but...
[gasp] Is this...
♪♪
DRAGON PIT!
I remember
that game.
You two used
to play it?
Heh. Pretty much any time we
weren't working on magic.
I can't believe
you found a copy!
Sunburst would get so excited
whenever his dragon got trapped
he'd knock the whole board over!
That's adorable.
Eh.. well, it's an exciting game.
But I have a little more
control over my horn now.
Uh-oh!
Somepony's dragon's
gonna get trapped!
[pop]
Doesn't seem so
exciting to m--
AAAHAHHAHAHH!
Huh. I guess it is adorable.
♪♪
I hope you're enjoying
your visit so far.
Are you kidding!?
I mean, first antiquing and then
spending time with Twilight!
Oh. Yeah.
She's.. pretty great.
Right? I mean, I know
she's a Princess,
but I never thought she'd be so
fun to just hang out with.
Well, she is the
Princess of Friendship.
[chuckle] Right.
I guess that makes sense.
So. Tomorrow
I thought--
I suppose I'm just surprised
at how well we get along.
I don't have much in
common with most ponies.
You two are pretty similar.
I don't know many ponies who
are fluent in Olde Ponish.
Exactly!
I probably have more in
common with Twilight
than any pony in Equestria!
Right.
Anyway, I better
get some sleep.
[yawn] Ponyville might be small,
but there's a lot to do.
Maybe we should ask Twilight
what she recommends we see!
Um, sure.
Great! Goodnight, Starlight.
Um, goodnight.
♪♪
[door opens]
Knock, knock!
Wh-what!?
Oh. Hi, Starlight.
Is it morning already?
Yep!
Maybe a bit early,
but like you said,
there's a lot to
see in Ponyville!
Uh, right. OK.
Heh. Plus, I couldn't really sleep.
I just kept thinking about all
the stuff we have in common
and how much fun
we'll have today.
Great. Is Twilight up yet?
A-Actually, I'm pretty sure she's
busy with Princess stuff today.
Oh. [yawn]
But I've got a full day of stuff
planned, just you and me.
Uh. Great!
Um. Would you mind turning
around, or preferably...
leaving the room so
I could get changed?
Oh! Right! Ha ha,
sorry, ah ha...
[door closes]
[fly buzzing]
One, genuine, Sweet
Apple Acres apple tree!
Because we used to drink so
much apple juice as foals?
Hmm.. I don't remember that.
Really? I mean, it
was all we drank.
Uh.. here.
Try an apple. I bet that'll jog your memory.
[kicks tree]
Oh! Ow..
Trixie?
What are you doing here?
I often seek the privacy of
the orchard to practice
new feats of amazement.
And, also I fell asleep.
Oh. Well, Sunburst and I
were just catching up, so...
[gasp] I don't suppose the two
of you want to see
a never-before-witnessed
magical marvel?
Sure!
[sigh] Why not.
Behold, visiting friend
from Starlight's past
and be amazed by the
Great and Powerful
and current best friend
of Starlight, TRIXIE!
[explosions and whistles]
♪♪
I give you...
THE UNICORN ESCAPE!
[grunts]
One more...twist...
and... [grunts]
The great and
powerful Trixie
requires a little
assistance.
I know this trick.
There's a special link,
but I could never
hold the chain up long
enough to find it.
♪♪
[muttering] [struggling]
[poof]
♪♪
Well, if I could
do magic like that,
I'd have a whole slew of new
tricks at my disposal.
I always liked close up magic
because I knew I could do it
if I just practiced enough.
[giggle]
♪♪
Starlight, why
didn't you tell me
how much Sunburst
and I had in common?
Gee. I don't know.
I know Trixie's "magic"
is, you know, fun...
but the Mirror Pool
is actual magic.
Whoa! This place
is pure ponylore.
Yep. I mean, it's supposed
to be all dangerous.
I guess I shouldn't have
broken the seal to get in,
but you wanted to see the
sights of Ponyville, right?
So, Pinkie Pie just dove in
and made copies of herself?
Mm-hm!
If we made copies of ourselves,
we could get a year's worth of
hanging out over in one day.
Eh.. not that we would.
[tapping]
Do you hear that?
Ooh. I hope it's not a
left over Pinkie Pie.
Maud: Not exactly.
Maud? How did
you get in here?
This cavern's actually
connected to mine.
Ah.. what are you doing?
Tapping.
Maud isn't
super chatty.
I mean, you and I could sit
around and talk all day,
but she looks pretty busy.
[tapping]
Are you taking some
kind of core sample?
Not exactly.
I'm uncovering this section
of strata for closer study.
You might want to step back.
[clunks] [cracking]
[coughing]
I'm studying this
area's metamorphic--
--foliation!
Is this gneiss,
phyllite, or slate?
Wow. The pressure above
must be pretty uniform
to get the planar fabric
to be this consistent.
You know about geology?
I dabble.
For example, by the
speleothems in this cave,
I kinda figured there
was another way out.
Because of the
calcite deposits.
[big sigh]
♪♪
Starlight?
Where's Sunburst?
Doing stage magic with Trixie?
Studying new rocks with Maud?
You're here so I guess you
two aren't off translating
some ancient Olde Ponish text.
What are you talking about?
Why would Sunburst
be doing any of that?
I thought he came to
Ponyville to see you.
I thought so too, but it
hasn't worked out that way.
When we were foals,
we had more in common
than any two ponies
in Equestria.
But now it seems like
he's got more in common
with my friends than
he does with me.
[clunk]
Oh. Everypony changes,
but that doesn't mean
there aren't still
things you both like.
You both love magic, right?
Magic?
Sure. You're
really good at it
and Sunburst practically knows
every spell that ever was.
[gasp] You're right!
Thanks, Twilight!
You're the best!
Eh. I try.
Starlight, what happened?
Maud and I found some
fascinating sedimentary stratum,
but when I turned to
show you, you were gone.
Maud does have a way of making
rocks really interesting,
but I wanted to work on
something a little more "us."
What's this?
Just a little
something I made up.
Whoa! You made up this
spell? Just now?
Yep!
♪♪
[whoosh]
Wow.
I know, right?
But wait, there's more.
[whoosh]
Cool, right?
Um, sure.
Now we can play Dragon Pit!
Just like we used to.
[zoom]
Actually, I thought we
could go with Maud and--
I mean, nothing was better
than just you and me
playing this game when
we were foals, right?
Starlight..
Do you what to be red or blue?
Starlight!
I don't want to play
the game at all!
[zap]
[poof]
[door opens]
What's going on in here?
Nothing. I was trying to have
fun doing the ONE thing
I thought we still
had in common,
but I guess we don't even
have that anymore.
♪♪
I don't understand...
Starlight and I have known each
other since we were foals,
but that doesn't mean we
have to be foals to hang out.
Hm. Starlight does have a
tendency to over-do.
I mean, it is surprising how
well I get along with
all of her friends, but she and
I still have tons in common.
Maybe you just need to remind
her what those things are.
That's it!
That's exactly what I'll do.
Right after I think of them.
Oh.
Obviously you and I hit it
off. I am quite impressive.
And we share a love
for prestidigitation!
[pop]
Right.
And Starlight and I share
a lot of things too.
I just need to
think of them.
What else do you
guys have in common?
Well, we've both made
not-so-great choices in the past
[pop pop pop]
and we're self-conscious about
everypony judging us
even though we've
both changed
and are trying hard
to be better.
[sawing]
Yeah... we don't really have that.
[clop clop]
Hmph! I can think of
something you have in common.
You're both poor
practice audiences.
[flump]
Starlight and I don't really
have a lot in common.
Other than feeling
different from most ponies.
And comedy.
Comedy?
[clunk]
I'm very funny.
Was that a joke?
No.
Well, that's more
than I can think of
that she and I
have in common.
We don't really spend that much
time talking about that, though.
Mostly we're just comfortable
around each other.
[sigh] We used to be...
We did everything together.
But now I'm wondering if we've
spent so much time apart
that we don't connect
over anything anymore
and if we can't
connect over anything
then maybe we're
not even friends!
Well, at least
it's not serious.
That.. was a joke.
[sigh] I appreciate you trying
to help, Twilight.
But it seems pretty clear that
Sunburst and I have grown apart.
I understand.
But I feel like that only
happens if you both let it.
You still want to
be friends, right?
I created a spell so we could
re-live playing a game
in our childhood home...
and bodies.
Right....
I'm just not sure Sunburst
wants to stay friends too.
I think you might
be surprised.
[door opens]
Prepare yourself...
For the new
and improved
Dragon Pit!
We had to take out a few
spaces to get it to fit
but you hardly miss them.
Maud made the dice.
♪♪
Pumice is the
lightest igneous rock.
It seems the
best choice.
And I added the special effects.
There's nothing like a little
well-placed magic smoke.
[rumbling]
Looks like somepony's dragon
is going to get trapped.
I thought you didn't
wanna play this game.
Well, I didn't want to
pretend to be a foal,
but I know you
wanted to play.
I thought it'd be fun to
play a version big enough
for full grown ponies.
What do you think?
Fun, right?
♪♪
Actually, it's
missing something.
[zap]
[cracking]
AHHHGHHHHHH!
[thud]
[chuckle] Now it's fun.
[giggling]
♪♪
I don't know why I got
so worried about us
not having anything
in common.
Yeah. I kind of think
it doesn't matter
as long as we enjoy
each other's company.
Trixie: And that game was
certainly enjoyable.
What made it even better
was getting to play it
with all my friends.
♪♪
See you soon?
You bet.
I want to hear if you find
anything interesting
in that barrel.
Trust me, Starlight.
You'll be the
first to know!
♪♪
[train chugging]
♪ [ominous music] ♪