♪♪
Thank you so much, Zecora!
I never would have found the
crisscross moss without you!
Of course!
I know where it grows
so it's not much to ask.
Though retrieving it has
been a difficult task.
Oh, but the oxen visiting
Sweetfeather Sanctuary
next week will surely
appreciate it!
It really adds a
shine to their coat.
[squelching]
There we go. Now, that
wasn't so tough.
Fluttershy tell me,
will this be enough?
Gee, I don't know, it's
a pretty big pack,
so maybe enough to
fill up this sack?
[gasp] [giggle] Oh, my!
You're rubbing
off on me, Zecora!
♪♪
Oh! [shouts]
[splash]
[scream]
Oh, no, oh no, oh no!
[gasp]
Zecora! Are you all right?
No need to fret,
I only got wet...
At least now I can easily grab
all the crisscross moss
there is to be had!
♪♪
[poof]
[gasp]
What's happening to you?
Honestly, it's hard to tell,
but suddenly I
don't feel so well.
[horrified gasp]
♪♪
All right, Zecora,
let's have a listen to
the ol' ticker!
♪ [jazz drumming] ♪
Hmmm...
Hmmm.
♪ [jazz drumming] ♪
Do you think it's
serious, Doctor?
Well, that wasn't a good sign.
I can't believe a
flower did this!
I take back thinking
it was pretty!
[coughing]
♪♪
[shaking]
We're looking for any
color other than red.
Phew!
[huge gasp]
Oh! It's just as I thought.
I'm afraid you have a very rare
disease called ...Swamp Fever!
[thunderclap]
Tell me, Doctor,
what should I do?
I've never heard of
Swamp Fever, mind you.
Unfortunately, very little is
known about the disease,
except, of course, its symptoms:
change of coat,
coughing bubbles,
shock sneezing, confusion
and the last stage...
The afflicted turn
into the very trees
that drop the disease-
spreading flower.
Oh!
Is there anything
that can be done?
For such a terrible
conundrum?
A cure has yet to be discovered.
I'm sorry, Zecora.
Hmmm...
It's a lot to take in..
I'll leave you
two to discuss.
[slam]
Zecora, this is
all my fault!
If you hadn't been helping
me get the crisscross moss,
you wouldn't have
gotten Swamp Fever!
I'm so sorry.
Fluttershy, you
are not to blame.
These things happen,
all the same.
I refuse to accept that!
There has to be somepony
who can help you.
Oh!
There's a healer of legend
who never would fail.
But I only know her
from ancient folk tales.
Mystical and masked,
she came in the night
and cured everything from
hoof cough to fur blight.
What became of the
healer, nopony knows,
for she disappeared
ages and ages ago.
The Mystical Mask, of course!
My parents would tell me about
her whenever I was sick in bed.
There's so many accounts
of her power to heal
She can't just be a legend.
I think she's real.
If that's who we need to cure
you, then I'm going to find her!
And I know just the
pony who can help!
[panting]
[door opens] Twilight!
Twilight!
Oh, I'm so sorry
to bother--
are... are you cooking?
Yeah, Spike and I are
having a cook-off.
My cauliflower bites blew
her sweet potato muffins
out of the water!
I'm glad you're
here, Fluttershy,
because we're going to need
a second opinion about that.
[munching]
Um... they're both
delicious. But ...
Zecora has Swamp Fever
and there's no cure
and it's all my fault
and the only pony
who can cure her is
the Mystical Mask
and I need your
help to find her!
Twilight: Er...
So what'd she pick? The
cauliflower bites, right?
♪♪
[sigh] That's the last book
on ancient ponies
and still no mention of
the Mystical Mask.
Hmm, did we check the
unabridged versions?
Yes. And the books
on rare diseases,
the books on rare plants
and the entire section
on bog habitation.
Well, we might have to look
through every book
in the entire library, but I
know we'll figure it out!
Oh...
♪♪
Oh, another dead end...
Have you found
anything yet, Twilight?
[snoring]
-Twilight?
Ah! [crash]
Goodness, are you OK?
[sigh] I'm fine.
Fluttershy, you know that
I want to help Zecora.
But I think we'd be a lot better
off if we got some sleep.
We've been at this for hours.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
I didn't realize how
late it had gotten!
No problem.
I'll grab you
a pillow and--
Oh, no no no, I meant
you should sleep.
I can't rest until
Zecora is healed!
I understand how you feel, but I
still think we'd have more luck
if we tried again
in the morning.
Just promise me you'll
take a break soon.
Mm-hmm.
[yawn]
Good night, Fluttershy.
[door closes]
[mumbling] 9 by 13 inch pan...
Twilight!
Non-stick pans!
[sigh] What's all the commotion
in here, ladies?
Sorry! But I figured out
who the Mystical Mask is.
[gasp] You did?
All I had to do was
cross-reference
a book about masks
with another book
on ancient
Equestrian healers,
then use a third book
to translate it all
from Old Ponish
and there it was!
Zecora was right!
The Mystical Mask
wasn't just a legend.
was MAGE MEADOWBROOK!
[gasp]
The ancient sorceress
from Hayseed Swamp?
We studied her at
Celestia's school.
Are you sure!?
Absolutely!
Mage Meadowbrook wasn't
just a sorceress,
she was also a
healer and back then,
healers wore masks so they
wouldn't get sick themselves!
Fluttershy, I am so
incredibly proud of you
for using your research
skills to figure this out!
But... Meadowbrook
lived ages ago and...
Didn't she disappear?
Mm hm. But if we go
to Hayseed Swamp,
maybe we can find
something she left behind.
Something that could
lead to a cure!
It seems like a long shot,
but I guess it's possible.
We have to try! I've got
our route all planned out
and on the way we can
check up on Zecora and--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're leaving now?
Of course!
Every second we spend waiting,
is a second Zecora
is coughing bubbles!
But Fluttershy,
you haven't slept.
And that's a long journey.
There's no use trying to talk
me out of this, Twilight!
We've got no
time to waste!
Can we at least
grab some breakfast!?
I packed cauliflower bites.
Aww. No sweet
potato muffins?
I.. uh.. ate them all.
They were actually
really good.
...and that's when I
realized the Mystical Mask
was actually Mage
Meadowbrook!
[cough]
That's marvelous, Fluttershy!
I am quite impressed.
While you're gone
on your journey
I'll try not to be ... worried.
[gasp] Oh, no! Zecora,
you didn't rhyme!
You must be getting worse!
Oh! No, no, no! Not at all...
Something, something... ball?
Achoo!
Ah! That's it!
We have to go now!
Lead the way, Fluttershy!
[thud]
[groan]
♪♪
[frogs croaking]
So... where do you think
Meadowbrook lived?
[yawn] I'm not sure.
Maybe there's
somepony we can ask.
I think we might be
the only ponies here.
Wait! I recognize that tree!
♪♪
Oh! Yes, this has to be it!
It's just like the
illustrations of her home!
Anypony who lives in
a tree is OK by me.
[grunts]
Phew!
Well, if the doorway
is sealed up,
we just have
to dig our way in.
Back up, Twilight; I don't
want you to get hurt!
[panting]
Or we could try
the handle.
[giggle]
It really blends
in with the bark.
Easy to miss.
[door creaks open]
Wow, it looks like this place
has been abandoned for years.
♪♪
[gasp] Twilight! Look!
It's the same kind of lily pad
that gave Zecora Swamp Fever!
Hmm. I wonder if Meadowbrook
was looking for a cure
for Swamp Fever too.
[gasp] Do you think she found it?
I hope so. But let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
[high-pitched squeak]
That's exactly what
I'm talking about.
You're making your excited
squeaking noise.
Uh, I wasn't making my
excited squeaking noise.
[creaking]
Ahhhhhhhhhh!!
Y'all can stop screaming now.
Didn't mean to scare ya.
I do that a lot.
Scare ponies?
Or rock creepily in the dark?
Well.. both, I s'pose.
Name's Cattail.
Pleased to meet ya!
Likewise, but um, may I ask,
why are you in Mage
Meadowbrook's home?
Oh, I take care of the place.
I ain't much of a cleaner but..
from what I hear,
my kin wasn't either,
so I doubt they'd mind a few
cobwebs in our ancestral home.
[gasp] You're related to
Mage Meadowbrook?
Mm hm.
Oh, my goodness,
Twilight, we did it!
Not only did we find Mage
Meadowbrook's old house,
we actually found one
of her descendants!
Honestly, I would
not have guessed it.
So, you lookin' for
some kind of cure, huh?
Well, now, I know
Meadowbrook was known
to always be writing
in her journals.
If she had the cure you want,
I reckon that's where it'd be.
Come on! I'll show
ya the library.
Library? Now
we're talking!
♪♪
Oh. Well, libraries come
in all shapes and sizes.
This is good!
It'll take us less time
to go through everything.
[clattering]
"Today my mom made me eat peas.
Peas are yucky."
And... we can probably
skip this one.
Unless she found a cure
when she was a foal...
"I met a colt today.
He pulled my mane so I
put a frog on his head."
Also not helpful.
But I do kind of want to
see where it goes.
Huh.
Wait, listen to this!
"Today, I tried again to
brew an un-sniffle elixir...
" ... and I finally
got it right!
Achoo!
[slurp]
[sigh]
Meadowbrook, I think
it's time you had this.
[gasp] My very own
healer's mask!
You think I'm
ready, Mother?
Mm hm.
[knocking at door]
[door opens]
[gasp] What caused this?
Mother calls it "Swamp Fever".
We've been trying to find a
cure, but it hasn't been easy.
[poof] [coughing]
[knock at door]
[door opens]
[coughing]
The fever's spread
like wild fire.
[coughing and sneezing]
I fear if we don't
find the cure soon,
everypony will be
in grave danger...
[coughing]
With mother sick, I didn't
think I'd ever find a cure,
but staring at those
cursed flowers today.
I saw something...
♪♪
[poofing]
[gasp] Flash Bees!
I realized the flower's poison
didn't affect the Flash Bees
and if they were
immune to Swamp Fever,
their honey could be the cure!
♪ [adventure theme] ♪
[buzzing]
[snap]
[zapping] [buzzing]
[sting]
[thud]
But they were so aggressive
defending their hive,
I didn't know how I
was going to get it!
[buzzing]
Here goes nothin'!
Today I cured Mother and
the rest of the bayou.
It was the greatest feeling
I've ever experienced
and I promise to
dedicate my life
to curing ponies all
over Equestria.
Cattail: And she did just that.
Right up till she
disappeared without a trace.
So all we have to do is find
those aggressive Flash Bees
and get them to give
us their honey!
Of course, it doesn't
say how she did that.
♪♪
What? Is my mane messy?
I know I haven't slept
in a while but...
♪♪
[gasp] Oh, no! I've caught
Swamp Fever!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
Huh?
Are you sure these
are necessary?
What?
I said, are you sure
these are necessary?
YES! I won't risk
infecting you or Cattail.
What you can't risk
is getting any sicker.
If you don't rest, your
symptoms will only get worse.
[coughing]
Mm-hm. You really should rest
up before going up
against those
Flash Bees.
They are nasty critters.
Um, you don't know
this about me,
but I'm pretty
good with animals.
And besides, Dogtail...
Cattail.
Um, Zecora is counting on me.
I have to help her just like
Meadowbrook helped her mother
and all those bayou
ponies long ago.
But Fluttershy, as
much as Meadowbrook
took care of other ponies,
I'm sure she also
took care of herself!
You're not going to
change my mind, Twilight!
Ooh. For being sick, she
sure is strong.
Cattail: The Flash Bee
hive is just up yonder.
Are you sure you don't
want me to come with you?
No, it's too
dangerous, Twilight.
Besides, I've already
gotten one friend hurt.
I won't let it
happen to another.
Phew. OK, Fluttershy.
You can do this!
[coughing]
[panting]
♪ [adventure music] ♪
Mind over matter!
[groan]
♪ [adventure music] ♪
[struggling]
[buzzing]
Hello, Flash Bees!
I was hoping I could
get some of your honey.
[angry buzzing]
Oh, I see.
You don't let others have any.
Well, I'm sorry, but
I really need it.
[squeal]
Huh. I didn't want it to
have to come to this
but I'll just have to use...
The Stare.
[buzzing]
[stings]
[scream]
[cough]
You really are
aggressive.
[intense coughing]
[buzzing]
Oh, dear.
[faints]
Ooh. What happened? Where am I?
Oh. I'm so glad you're OK!
You're still in
Meadowbrook's tree.
You fainted but Twilight shot
some magic up and caught ya.
It was crazy.
Goodness gracious!
[coughing]
Have you heard from Zecora?
Is she OK?
Uh...
We got word your zebra friend
has started sprouting leaves.
She's already
turning into a tree?
I thought we'd
have more time.
Actually, you've been
asleep for three days.
Three days!?
Mm hm.
You were asleep so long, we were
afraid you wouldn't be able
to move when you woke up,
but thankfully you just
wore yourself down.
Oh, dear.
We have to get
back to the hive.
I've wasted so much time-
Now hang on there,
Fluttershy,
those Flash Bee
critters are tricky.
Cattail's right.
I can't even use magic
to calm them down.
We'll have to find another
way to get the honey.
We've tried everything
from disguises
to things I won't
even speak of.
[shudder]
He's been through a lot
these past three days.
Wait...
disguises...
[buzzing]
[gasp] That's it!
I know how she did it!
I know how Meadowbrook
got the honey!
[buzzing]
This is how Meadowbrook got
the honey from the Flash Bees.
She threw a mask at 'em?
I wouldn't recommend that.
No. The male bees aren't
aggressive around the queen bee
and this mask has the same
stripes that she does!
Fluttershy, that's brilliant!
A-A-Achoo!
Whoa!
There's no time to waste!
Hooves crossed!
Oh, golly, I can't watch!
[coughing]
Mind over matter!
♪♪
[buzzing]
[Fluttershy buzzes]
[squelching]
Twilight!
It's working!
♪♪
[gulping]
I think she's cured
now, Fluttershy.
Oh, I do feel fine,
and this honey is divine.
Oh, you're
rhyming again!
Welcome back,
my friend!
Thank you Fluttershy,
for all you endured.
If not for you, I
would not be cured.
Oh.. If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't have been
sick in the first place!
Regret is not what
you should feel,
because on this journey,
you've learned a great deal.
That's true.
I certainly learned that if you
don't take care of yourself,
you won't be able to take
care of anypony else.
In fact, if I had rested, like
Twilight suggested all along,
maybe I would have thought to
use Meadowbrook's mask sooner.
[coughing]
Please tell me you
found the cure.
A-Achoo!
Achoo!