Please put your hooves together
for your next performer...
Maud Pie!
[clapping]
[taps on microphone]
What do you call an Alicorn
with no wings and no horn?
"Earth Pony."
[Pinkie Pie shrieks
with laughter]
But seriously, being an
Earth Pony isn't so bad.
We've got magic powers, too.
Like walking around...
and picking stuff
up with our teeth.
[confused murmurs]
That's sarcasm by the way.
[Pinkie Pie laughs]
It's funny cause it's true!
My favorite thing to
listen to is clastic rock.
The accumulation of sediments
over millennia forming
to create sandstone,
shale and breccia.
It sounds something
like this.
[feedback]
[silence]
And that's my time.
Pinkie: Hahahahaha!
Isn't my sister Maud the
most hilarious, entertaining,
AMAZING comedian ever?
[hooting laughter]
♪♪
[door opens]
Your jokes!
Your hilarious delivery!
Your.. your EVERYTHING!
How was my... timing?
Ha! You got me!
C'mon! Let's celebrate,
sister style!
We could get matching stickers
that say "Eyes on the Pies!"
then show them off at the
Ponyville Sticker Convention
that I could plan for
tomorrow if you want?
Actually, I'm
busy tonight.
Aw, that's what
you said yesterday.
And the day before that.
And the day before
the day before that!
[sigh] It's just, we haven't hung
out in a really long time
because you always
have other plans,
even when you promised to build
whip cream pyramids with me.
[squirt]
I know. I am sorry, Pinkie. The
reason is I have a--
Apology accepted.
As long as we get some
serious sister time
before your birthday.
And there's uh,
definitely no reason
I want to hang out
before your birthday.
Just, you know, not
planning anything special.
OK.
What about
tomorrow morning?
OK.
Yay!
Just you and me!
Best Sister
Friends Forever!
Friends Forever.
I can't wait for
tomorrow to be today!
Eeeeeeeee!
Tomorrow is today!
Who's ready for some fun
times at Sugarcube Corner?
The answer is YOU!
I would also accept "Maud."
Maud?
MAUD?
[echoes]
[gasp] Oh, I get it!
We're playing hide
and go seek!
♪♪
[splash]
[crash]
♪♪
[knocking]
Ah-HA! Found you!
[clattering]
♪♪
Where's Maud?
I've already checked
Discord's dimension,
Granny Smith's wax
museum, AND Yakyakistan!
She HAS to be here!
Nope, it's just me, reading.
[pages flipping]
Story checks out..
OR DOES IT?
It does.
But are you sure
there's nopony hiding...
IN YOUR CLOSET?
Pinkie...I don't
have a closet.
Is everything OK?
No. I was supposed to go
birthday cake shopping
with Maud today.
And ruin her
surprise party?
I wasn't going to
tell her why, silly!
But now I can't
even find Maud.
I'm usually way better at
hide and seek than this.
Oh, she probably just found
a new rock formation
and forgot you two
were gonna hang out.
Tell you what, you
take care of the cake,
and I'll look for Maud.
Really?
Thanks, Starlight!
Just checking.
♪♪
I've got to get very important
ingredients for a very important
pony's cake, and it's gotta be
tippy-top-super-duper-secret.
Technically... it's
not your turn yet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to cut
in front of anypony.
Um, whatcha doin'?
I am currently speaking to a
pony at a baking supply shop
two minutes before it
closes for lunch.
Riiiiight.
OK..?
It's just that I'm trying
to plan a party here,
and the clock is
ticking while you, uh...
What are you doing, anyway?
I am currently
speaking to--
I mean, can I help
you move this along?
What are you looking for?
Rolling pins? Cupcake tins?
Cookie cutters with
tails and fins?
Goodbye.
[crash]
THAT'S what you've been standing
here all this time to say?
I was deciding between
"goodbye" and "see you later."
Uh...but...they're
the same thing!
Technically?
They're very different.
"See you later" implies an
event in the near future
wherin we see each other.
"Goodbye" expresses good
wishes where parting
or at the end of
a conversation.
Yeah. Same thing.
[clang]
I will not apologize for
speaking with precision.
In that case,
apology not accepted!
Goodbye-later-seeya-same thing!
[slam]
Ah! Can you believe that guy?
Huh?
"Out to lunch?"
Oh, come on!
Ugh. No Maud, no cake, no anything!
And how annoying was that pony?
Who takes that long
to say goodbye?
Or was it "see you later?"
UGH, now he's got me doing it!
[thud]
Hello, Pinkie Pie.
MAUD!
Found you!
My turn to hide!
[crash]
I'm sorry I wasn't
around this morning.
Oh, psh, what are you
apologizing to me for?
I'm not upset, you silly willy.
The reason is I
met somepony--
Want to hang
out right now?
I mean, I can see you're
not doing anything
with anypony else.
Unless they're invisible
or really small.
Pinkie.
The reason I've been so busy
is that I have a boyfriend now.
A WHA?
A boyfriend.
A WHAAAAAA?
That's so exciting!
MY sister!
IN LOVE!
Technically, we're
"in like."
Tell me EVERYTHING!
[zoom]
Who is he? What's
his favorite color?
Does he like ice cream?
If he were a bird, what
kind of bird would he be?
Wait. Is he
actually a bird?
Oh! I don't know because you
haven't told me anything yet!
You'll like him.
We have a lot in common.
Well, I love you,
so I know I'm going to
love your boyfriend!
Oh! I can't wait
to meet him!
You don't have to.
[gasp]
He's a rock!
And you love rocks,
so it's perfect!
[gasp] Is Boulder jealous?
No, behind the rock.
Mudbriar, are you back there?
Technically?
Not anymore.
[gasp] WHA WHA WHAAAAA?
Pinkie Pie,
meet Mudbriar.
Technically?
We've already met.
You...?
Yes.
You?
You.
Yes.
I mean... haha, you!
You! You! You!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry, let's
start over.
Hi! I'm Maud's
sister, Pinkie Pie.
I know.
So...
How did...
You two meet?
At a rock show.
Oh, you're into
rocks too?
No. I like sticks.
Then why were you
at a rock show?
It was a petrified wood show,
which technically
makes it a stick show.
Except that in the
permineralization process
of petrification, all organic
material is replaced with
silicates, i.e. rocks--
--while retaining the original
structural elements of wood.
Q.E.D. It was a stick show.
I'm... really
into sticks too!
They're great for
hitting piñatas!
Aaahhh!
Pinkie!
Oh, you
wanna go first?
That is stick abuse.
It is?
I'm sorry.
Oh, this is awful, I am not
being a very good sister.
Let's start over.
I'm Pinkie Pie,
nice to meet you.
Technically?
We've already met.
You should introduce
Pinkie to your pet.
Oh!
Your pet likes fetch!
This is my pet.
So no.
Aw. Look at Twiggy and
Boulder playing together.
They're adorable.
It's just a stick.
Don't be rude.
Ah! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
One more time...
I'm Pinkie Pie,
nice to meet you.
Technically?
We've already met.
[growl]
[straining]
AHHHH!
I don't get this guy!
Wow! Maud has a boyfriend?
Agh!
How can she like
someone so weird?
He has an inanimate
object for a pet!
So does Maud.
Boulder has TEN times
the personality
of some random stick.
Mudbriar too, for that matter.
He's not like Maud AT ALL.
Maud is hilarious, friendly,
caring, and easy to talk to!
Yup, that's Maud.
But this guy is awkward,
quiet, and kind of...
strange!
Uh, that also
sounds like Maud.
Hah! You're so
funny, Starlight!
Maud is nothing
like Mudbriar.
If she were, then we wouldn't
be best sister friends forever.
Well, Maud obviously
likes something about him.
[growl]
Maybe you just need to
spend more time with him,
find out what you
have in common.
That's easy.
Nothing!
You both care
about Maud.
I know! He could help
you with her party!
I guess...
And I'll keep Maud busy
while you and Mudbriar
plan the best surprise
birthday ever!
That, I can do.
Listen. Maud's
birthday is tomorrow
and there's no
time to waste.
You're not afraid
of slides, are you?
No, wh-aaaahhhhhhhh!
[crash]
No reason!
Weeeeee!
[crash]
[yell]
Welcome to my PARTY
PLANNING CAVE!
Technically?
Due to the speleothems
growing from the ceiling,
this is more of a
cavern than a cave.
Maud taught me that.
Yeah OK.
♪♪
Here's what I'm thinking for
her surprise party:
edible rock candy plates,
gem-shaped ice cubes,
a pebble piñata--
--uh, we'll skip that one.
Might I make some
suggestions?
Oh, suggest away!
That's why you're here.
You and me,
planning... together.
Friends.
I have a vision board of
everything Maud loves,
and none of those
things are on it.
Hm.
Let me see this "vision board."
It's not a physical thing.
I'm envisioning it.
[whoosh]
I enter through the large
door of my mind palace
and enter to the back where
I have all of my books
and possessions and what do I
encounter, The Maud Room.
None of those things are there.
Just as I thought.
Maud doesn't like surprises.
Where does it say that?
She never told me that!
Mm. It sounds like she was
protecting your feelings.
She's very caring that way.
Stop acting like you know
my sister better than me!
Technically, I never said that.
Well, technically,
I don't care!
And since I've been best sister
friends forever with Maud
my entire life, I think
I'M the expert here!
Oh, but fine. If you don't
believe me, let's ASK HER.
BUT WE HAVE TO BE SUPER SNEAKY!
Can you be more specific?
NO!
♪♪
Huh! You must
be Mudbriar!
I'm Starlight Glimmer,
nice to meet you!
I've heard great things.
I'm so glad the two of you
are spending time together!
So, how's it.. going?
Mudbriar and I have just spent
the BEST time bonding
and we're really starting
to make some headway
becoming besties, except
for one teensy weensy
disagreement that maybe
you could settle, Maud.
See, Mudbriar here
seems to think
that you don't like
surprise parties.
Isn't it funny how
WRONG HE IS?
I like surprise parties...
Hmm?
...because I know they
make you happy
when you throw
them for me.
See?
WAIT, WHAT?
I'd rather just do something
small with you, Starlight,
Boulder, and Mudbriar
for my birthday.
No party?
NO. PARTY?
Did he put you
up to this?
Mm mm.
Maybe you should
consider, I don't know,
taking things a little
less serious with Mudbriar,
because he's kinda, sorta...
IMPOSSIBLE TO LIKE.
Hey, Mudbriar!
Have you ever flown a kite?
Lemme tell you
all about it, see,
the first thing
you should do is...
I just can't believe you would
choose sitting around with him
over a party with
your own sister.
I didn't "choose" either of you.
Technically?
I said I wanted to
be with both of you.
[gasp]
TECHNICALLY!?
UGH! You even like
the way he TALKS?
Everything about
him makes me happy.
[gasp]
Then I guess you don't need
a best sister friend
forever forever anymore.
♪ [sad] ♪
Pinkie...
Wait, let's all slow down
and talk about this--
No! [blubbering]
See you later!
[crying]
I don't understand!
How could Maud like Mudbriar?
Is it opposite day?
Nothing makes sense!
I'm not shy!
And I hate animals.
Fashion?
Not for me, Darling.
Pthew, an apple a day
is downright disgusting.
Slow and steady wins the race.
I never learned to read!
[laughter]
WHAT IF I DON'T LIKE CUPCAKES?
[scream]
[rooster crows]
Good morning!
Oh, wait... bad morning.
[groan]
GET OUTTA BED, SIS!
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE
HERE, YOU GOTTA WORK!
Oh.
[clanging]
You're probably wondering why I
came back to the family farm
in the middle
of the night.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, it all
started when--
Less talking,
more farming!
Mmmmm.
It's just... Maud
has a boyfriend.
I'm not jealous.
Who said anything about jealous?
Don't be!
He's super-duper weird!
And somehow he tricked
Maud into liking him.
And now I'll never get
to see her again.
I came home because you two
know her better than anypony.
What am I missing?
What does she see in him?
What does he have that I don't!?
[loud crying]
Buck up, Pinkie Pie!
You look as miserable
as I feel all the time.
[splat]
It's just.. that I love Maud
and I WANT to love Mudbriar,
but I can't see anything
to LIKE about him!
Ugh, fine.
We're taking a work break.
C'mon.
I'm looking at a sparkling
bright blue and white rock.
See it?
You mean that lumpy gray one?
No, the beautiful blue and
white one, right there.
I would not describe that as
beautiful, blue, or white,
but... heh heh, OK!
Show her.
[crack]
[split]
It's a geode.
The outside looks
like a regular rock,
but the inside is filled
with beautiful gems.
So you're saying...
I should crack open
Mudbriar like a rock!
IT ALL MAKES SENSE.
No wait, it doesn't.
It's a METAPHOR, Pinkie!
You see Mudbriar as a rock,
but Maud sees him as a gem.
Even if you never see
past his dullness,
you CAN see how
happy he makes Maud.
And to a sister, that's
all that matters.
Mmm-hmm!
♪♪
Oh, Limestone,
Marble, thank you.
I don't know what I'd
do without you two!
PIE PILE!
OK, OK. You're crushing
me to gravel, Pinkie!
I really owe
Mudbriar an apology.
[gasp] And I owe Maud a party!
I just hope I'm not too late!
♪♪
I brought you an olive
branch to say sorry.
I was really unfair to you,
and I'm ready to listen to your
ideas for Maud's birthday,
if you still want to
plan it together.
Technically, this isn't
even an olive branch.
It's a quercus, most
likely castaneifolia.
OH COME ON!
Uh... Sorry.
Keepin' it together...
And I love a
good quercus.
Friends?
Friends!
Now, do you have any
ideas for the party?
There is one...
[happy chattering]
[door opens]
SURPRISE!
[chattering]
♪♪
This is my favorite party ever.
It was all your amazing
boyfriend's idea.
He said the best present would
be me throwing you a surprise
party you didn't have to go to.
Technically?
It wasn't a surprise because
she could see the pre-party
preparations from up here.
"Technically..?"
You're right!