♪♪
I'm so glad I made it to Las
Pegasus before the fastest,
most thrilling ride of
all time closes for good!
Wait. The fastest, most
thrilling ride of all time?
[gasp]
She hasn't heard of
"The Wild Blue Yonder"?
[scoff] Of course, I have!
It's that one where uh...
All right, you got me.
What is it?
Only the coolest
roller coaster ever!
Pfft. You can't really call
yourself a Wonderbolt
if you haven't
been on it.
♪♪
Oh, it looks incredible!
Oh, it is.
First, you strap yourself into
the cloud rocket car
and then you're catapulted
straight through...
a series of daring dips
and terrifying turns...
flipping upside
down so many times,
you don't know
which way is up...
[splat]
[whoosh]
till finally, you climb to the
highest peak on the rails...
then drop towards the
ground at lightning speed
before coming up to
a screeching halt!
It's the coolest
ride ever to exist
in the history of Equestria!
So.. when did you ride it?
Oh. Heh heh. I haven't.
[groan]
[grunt]
The ride closes this week!
Forever!
But I can't go to Las Pegasus
because I have to teach
at Twilight's school.
I'm going to miss out
on the coolest roller
coaster of all time!
Unless...
Why do I feel like you're about
to ask me a mighty big favor?
Can you cover my classes?
Absolutely.
Really? Awesome!
On one condition.
You tag along with a few other
ponies goin' to Las Pegasus.
[laughter] Surely you don't
mean Granny Smith?
No, no. Of course not!
I mean Granny Smith and the rest
of the "Gold Horseshoe Gals!"
Hurry yer haunches, Hinnies!
♪♪
Grand-Auntie Apple Sauce,
Cousin Apple Rose,
and Cousin Goldie Delicious!
[meow]
Why, I'm sure they'd be plum
tickled to have ya join
their annual Grandmares'
trip to Las Pegasus.
It'll be perfect!
I'll teach your classes, and
you can look after them for me.
[thwack] Look after them!?
So they don't get
too carried away.
Usually, Big Mac goes
along as a chaperone,
but I'm sure he'd
love a break.
[crash]
There is NO way I'm going to
Las Pegasus with a bunch of
old, slow grannies!
So you don't mind
missing your only chance
to ride The Wild Blue Yonder?
♪ [tense music] ♪
Fine! I'll go.
Hah! That's the spirit!
Now skedaddle so I can
help 'em get ready.
Granny: Applejack! Have you seen
my Cranky Flank cream?
I can't find it in this
whole tootin' farmhouse!
It's uh... gonna
take a while.
[clock chimes]
Urghh.
Why is this taking so long?
The Wild Blue
Yonder's gonna close
before we even get
to Las Pegasus!
Here, I made a list to help
ya keep the grandmares
out of trouble.
Don't want to have to
bring 'em back home
before you get to go
on yer roller coaster!
That could happen!?
Only if you don't
follow the rules!
These grannies
need a lot of care.
If one of 'em overdoes it,
it's bye bye Las Pegasus
for the lot of ya.
"Make sure they
get their naps...
eat only soft foods...
careful when dancing...
don't get too excited"!?
Seriously!?
And don't let 'em out
of your sight. Ever.
Wait. Then how am I supposed
to go on the roller coaster?
You'll find time. And you might
even learn a thing or two
about havin' a good time
from these old gals.
Yeah, that'll happen.
All right,
y'all.
Time to get this
show on the road.
Heh. Or in the sky,
in this case.
[muttering approvals]
Ugh!
Come on, come on!
[meow]
[groan]
[whooshing]
Go go go go go!
♪♪
Agh!
Everypony OK
in there?
Dandy as a pansy
in a plant pot!
You know, this hot air balloon
ride reminds me of the time
I climbed a tree!
Have I ever told you that story?
Only about a million times!
HUH? What did ya say?
They said they've
heard the tree story!
Oh, you want to
hear the tree story? OK!
Here we go again..
Back when I was a young filly,
I was afraid of tree-climbing!
Knees knocking,
hooves sweating...
Have you ever had
the hoof sweats?
Well, they're just
the worst thing.
You know, Cousin Strudel,
she used to get em too.
Now, of course she was a
champion fritter thrower-
♪♪
[screams]
The Wild Blue Yonder
is IN OUR HOTEL?
Uh, I bet you grannies
are feeling super tired
from your journey.
Nope. How about a
trot down the avenue
to see the
sights, girls?
Oh, forget the sights!
I came here to play some
serious horseshoe toss!
Oh, can we see the rainbow
fountains at the water show?
They're so magical.
My pores are crying for a mud
mask at the Prism Palace spa!
You know what would
be REALLY FUN?
Relaxing in our room!
C'mon! Last one to the
hotel is a rotten apple!
[zoom]
Lemme get that for ya.
[grunts]
[crash]
[gasp]
Omigosh, omigosh,
omigosh, omigosh!
There it is..
The best rollercoaster ever!
Oow! Warm up those withers, ladies!
There's a horseshoe hurling
trophy with our names on it!
[groaning]
[ghostly voice] Don't let
them get too excited.
Or you'll have
to go home!
[gasp] Whoa, whoa, whoa,
That sounds a
little too exciting.
Why don't we get you
checked in first?
Oh, my, you are a strong
pony, aren't you, Sugar Hocks?
[gulp]
[giggles]
Ugh.
[door opens]
Welcome to our Gold
Horseshoe suite!
Only the best of the best
for our favorite guests.
Which of course means
you lovely mares.
Why, thank ya a
bushel and a peck,
you scrumptious morsel
o' frosted carrot cake!
Oh, uh... Thank
you, ma'am.
I think he was sweet on me.
Maybe I should ask him
to accompany me to the
magic show tonight.
Bah hah!
Sure your name's
not Apple Saucy?
Better find the brakes
on that buggy, sugar!
We just got here!
You're right. Better see what
else is out there first.
The day is young and I am not!
[giggles]
Uh. Granny Smith's right!
Let's not overdo it.
How about a nice nap so you
can really enjoy Las Pegasus?
[noisy yawn]
Good idea!
We could use some
shut-eye, hm?
But I'm not tired....
Oh! Right!
Uh, yawn...
You go along now and explore
while we rest, sugar booger.
Yawn.
If you say so!
What? They'll be
in here sleeping
the whole time
I'm gone.
Quit judging me!
[slam]
♪♪
[Ahem] One ticket for the
coolest roller coaster
of all time, please.
♪♪
[gasp]
But... but... This
line never ends!
I know, right?
Good thing we can just
stand here all day
without any responsibilities
waiting for us!
[groan]
Oh, hey, thanks!
Enjoy the ride.
[door opens and closes]
Heh. They didn't
even know I left.
[meow!]
Whoa!
Meow?
Gaaahh!
♪♪
[gasp]
They're gone!
[panicked whimpers]
Granny Smith! Apple Rose!
Are you here?
Apple Sauce?
♪♪
Goldie?
[groan] I'm the worst chaperone ever.
Don't let them out
of your siiiight!
I know, I know!
Excuse me, sir?
Have you seen a group of
old mares around here?
Lady, you just described half
the ponies in this place.
Oh! This place is huge!
They could be anywhere!
[chanting]
Goldie! Goldie! Goldie! Goldie!
Can they do it?
Can good ole Goldie Delicious
and the Gold Horseshoe Gals
break the all-time
resort record, folks?
[clang]
[cheers]
Now that's how you
hurl a horseshoe!
Hah! No way! Goldie's
totally got game!
Make some noise for the
best-played game of horseshoes
this resort has ever seen!
Can you believe
your eyes, folks?
[cheers]
Yeah! Go Goldie!
Stand back; she's
getting excited!
Huh?
Uh oh.
[exclaims]
Uh... Mind if I try?
[clang]
Whoops, guess I'm no
good at this game.
Sorry.
And the Gold
Horseshoe Gals are out!
Looks like the show's
over, everypony.
Awwwww!
[chattering]
Oh, I'm so glad I found you.
Everypony feeling OK?
Not too excited?
Pretty much the
opposite right now.
Good.
From now on, I'm not letting
you grannies out of my sight!
In that case, let's paint
the town candy apple red!
Oooh! We could
play more games!
Or go shopping for hats!
Have I ever told you about
the time I got a new hat
and it turned out
to be a bird? Ha ha ha ha.
THAT'S what we oughta do!
REALLY?
Hit the buffet!
All that horseshoe tossin'
sure works up an appy-tite.
[sigh] Uh huh.
I love me some nachos!
I'mma set my dentures
loose on these viddles
until the crumbs cry uncle!
They can only
eat soft fooods!
You're a nacho away
from no rolleycoaster!
[zoom] [chomp]
Come on, Granny!
You know you
can't have those.
They're super crunchy!
[zoom] [zoom]
How about some nice,
soft carrot soup instead?
I thought you was supposed
to be the fun one.
Wait! I am fun!
P.A. System: Attention
all thrill-seekers!
There's only one day left to
ride the ride of all rides:
the Wild Blue Yonder,
before it's gone for good!
Get in line! Now!
So, what does everypony
want to do tonight?
I was thinking...
go to our room and put
on eyemasks and earplugs?
[crunching]
I'd rather hit the club and
show off my dance moves.
I'm quite a legend when
it comes to rhumba.
[excited chatter]
Sounds kind of intense.
Aren't you all exhausted
from your big day?
Heck no!
We save up our energy all
year for Las Pegasus weekend!
Isn't that right, girls?
Mm hm!
Ugh. Dancing it is, then.
I'll be there...
[splat]
♪ [steady electronic beat] ♪
[haunting voice]
Careful when dancing!
UGH! Stop doing that!
♪♪
Uh, that's probably
enough dancing for now!
Right, Apple Rose?
Oh, that was just my warm up!
♪♪
Look! It's our
favorite magicians...
Big Bucks and Jackpot!
And aren't they looking
handsome as ever!
♪♪
[ahem]
You little fillies have
got some smooth moves!
[giggling]
Say, how would you Gold
Horseshoe Gals like to bring
some of that good energy
into our magic show tonight?
Here's five complimentary
VIP tickets
to our most amazing trick, in
the Pony Fantastique Theater.
Just over there.
Sugarcube, we never
miss your show.
Fabulous!
We'll save a spot for you...
on stage.
And.. in our hearts.
So gross.
[excited whoops]
Yeee haw, girls!
Apple Sauce landed us some Very
Important Pony tickets
for the show tonight!
Hee hee hee hee!
[happy murmurs]
Oh, come on!
You said you were going back
to the room after dancing!
So each pony could
have some alone time?
Oh, now don't be a
stick in the mud.
Trust me, you'll
love this show.
It's the best thing
in Las Pegasus.
Whoo hoo!
[happy chatter]
Oh, hey, thanks for giving
me your place in line!
They said I'm one of
the last ponies ever
to ride the Wild
Blue Yonder!
♪♪
[cheers]
And now, for the trick
that made us famous.
The most dangerous magical
feat known to ponykind.
♪♪
We'd like to invite some very
special mares to the stage.
That's our cue, girls!
Hey! Where are you going?
Come back!
[tock tock]
Meet our lovely assistants.
[applause and whistles]
They will make a
Splashtastic Escape
using only the instructions
we give them...
with our minds!
Don't try this at home, folks!
♪♪
[water running]
[gasp]
Do I really have
to say anything?
Release those
grannies right now!
[alarmed shouts]
♪♪
[grunts]
[sploosh]
[shouts from the audience]
What'd ya go and do that for?
That was our big star moment!
You were in danger!
I saw the water!
You were trapped!
Oh, pish tosh!
This is a magic show.
We've seen it a
thousand times.
Everypony always escapes.
[murmurs]
That's right, folks!
Because of our.. um... uh...
skill as magicians!
And now, a disappearing act!
[poof]
Well, I hope you're happy.
We've been waiting to be picked
as the lovely assistants
in that trick for years!
You keep ruining our fun!
I had a hot hoof goin'
in that game
you decided to lose for us!
And I wanted to eat those
nachos at the buffet.
And I could have torn
up the dance floor,
if you didn't
keep stopping me.
They're being too polite
to say it, so I will.
Rainbow Dash, we
thought you'd be a hoot,
but I ain't never
met a wetter hen!
What?!
She's right.
You've had your mane in a
twist ever since we arrived.
Is something the
matter, dear?
I'm so sorry, everypony!
The truth is, all I've wanted
to do for this whole trip is
ride the Wild Blue Yonder!
I mean, it's why I came to
Las Pegasus in the first place!
Applejack told me not to
let you out of my sight,
or you might overdo it and
we'd have to go home early.
Applejack put
you up to this?
[murmuring]
Well, now it's too late.
I ruined your trip and
it's the last day ever
to ride the Wild
Blue Yonder.
The line is so long,
I'll never get to go on it.
[laughter]
Hey! What's so funny?
[chuckle] Is that all you wanted?
Well, fish-flavored
kitten-kibble.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
Come on, girls!
♪ [fanfare] ♪
We're "Gold Horseshoe" members!
The most exclusive
club in Las Pegasus.
And she's with us.
We've been comin' here every
moon since we can remember.
Even some we don't remember!
It definitely has its perks.
Like fancy suites and
roller coaster rides?
That's right!
And I hope you like
riding in the front.
Um, YES!
[giggle] This is amazing!
Isn't this amazing?
Sugar. You probably want
to hold on 'bout now.
♪♪
Whoo hoo!
[shutter clicks]
I'm sorry I misjudged you
for being older ponies.
You mares are
actually pretty cool.
Rainbow Dash?
Yeah, Granny?
The gals and I have
been talkin' and well...
we think you're
a hoot after all.
We'd like to invite you to
become a permanent member
of the "Gold Horseshoe
Gals"! Hoo hoo!
O-oh! Really!?
Mm hm.
Same time next year?
I wouldn't miss it for anything.
♪♪