♪♪
[quacks]
[thunk]
Don't worry, Angel.
I won't forget you.
♪♪
[sigh] There's nothing so peaceful as
a Cuddly Friends picnic!
[Rarity screams]
FLUTTERSHY!
[panting]
Oh! Goodness, Rarity,
what's the matter?
[tire screech]
[gasp] A better question would
be, what isn't the matter!?
Oh, dear.
Do you want to have some
lettuce and talk about it?
Er. Oh, I would love to, darling,
but I just don't have time.
The Canterlot Royal Fashion Show
is practically upon us
and the cornerstone piece of my
collection.. just isn't working!
That sounds serious...
Ohhh, it's serious.
The entire collection
is designed around it.
Do you need help knitting?
I've started
making tea cozies.
It's an elephant.
[ripping]
Yes, well, I don't need
help making clothes;
Sassy Saddles is pitching
in. Plus, I'll be pulling
all three of my
Manehattan assistants.
All three?
Does that mean you'll have
to close Rarity For You?
That's just it, darling.
This is Manehattan's
busiest shopping season
and I can't just
close the shop,
so I was hoping you might
consider running it?
Of course, I'm happy
to help, though...
I'm surprised you picked me.
Well, I may have
asked a few others...
Sorry, but we've got a
Wonderbolts show coming up.
[zoom]
Sorry, but it's pie season and
the pie orders are pie-ling up!
Sorry, I've got a
curriculum to make up.
Nope.
♪♪
My calendar's packed, but
I hear Fluttershy's free,
and you haven't
asked Boulder.
Uhh...
Oh?
Ha ha!
It doesn't matter
who else I asked
because I couldn't be happier
that you agreed to help.
♪♪
I think I forgot how
big this shop was.
How do you find anything?
Oh, darling, it's
easy to track.
The store is divided
into sections:
Chic, Classic, Modern,
Sophisticated,
Avant Garde,
Traditional, and Obtuse.
And, of course, each
section is divided by
season, color, and price.
It's a classic SCP system.
Then it's just a little
ringing ponies up,
[ka-ching]
a little fluff and fold...
voilà!
But of course, that's
the easy part.
[gasp] It is?
Mm hm! As you well know, the
real focus at Rarity For You
is on the customer.
[door opens and closes]
Care to give it a try?
Um... OK.
Hello. Um...
Welcome to
Rarity for You.
What can I help
you with?
I need something
classic but modern.
Something with drama,
but also understated.
Um... aren't all those
things opposites?
Yes. So?
But, how can I...
I'm sorry. Are you asking me
how to do your  job?
No! But I just, um...
If I may!
I'm thinking noir-esque
minimalist but with a twist...
perhaps a tapered hem?
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[gasp] It's like you read my mind!
Are you a fashion psychic?
[pretentious giggle]
Hmmm...
The inseams say.. yes!
[pretentious giggle]
[ka-ching]
Wow. You make it
looks so easy!
Oh, darling, come now.
You've conquered your shyness
a thousand times over.
You can't let a few fashion
ponies undo all that progress.
I guess not.
You simply must access
your inner strength
and allow it to
shine through!
How?
Uh... Daily affirmations?
Meditation?
Ooooh, power posing
works wonders
whenever I feel
intimidated!
Try these!
Confident warrior!
Gold medalist!
Showpony!
[thud]
Hm. Or. Not.
We need to leave now
if we're going to catch
the train to Canterlot.
Oh, goodness!
Look at the time!
Yes, yes, yes,
yes. Go! Go!
I'm right behind you!
You're not going
to be here?
In your workroom?
Oh, darling, I simply can't.
The fashion show is
in Canterlot tomorrow
and I'll be up all night,
even with the help
of all of my assistants.
[gulp]
Well, not all my assistants.
Smokey! Softpad! Smokey Junior!
[cooing]
Ever since you convinced me
to let them live in the shop,
these beasty sweeties have
been nothing but helpful.
And I'm sure they'll help me let
my inner strength.. shine through!
[chittering]
Oh, I wish I could stay
and offer more help.
Oh! Why not try.. a new outfit?
♪♪
Think of it as the costume
for your role as "Shop Pony."
You know what they say,
"Clothes make the pony!"
Um. Who says that?
You know, them.
All right. I'm sure you and your
furry friends will do just fine.
Ta-ta!
[door opens]
Ah, I hope she's right.
♪♪
Whew... Here goes nothing.
[chittering]
Welcome to Rarity For You.
What can I help you with?
What's the thread
count of this shirt?
I can't be seen in anything
less than a thousand.
Um... thread... count?
Um...
Oh, I'm not sure.
Let's see... One,
two, three, four...
[chittering]
Um, excuse me for
just one second.
[panting]
Oh! I'm afraid I don't know
enough about fashion
to satisfy these customers.
What am I going to do?
♪♪
Oh I've never tried to act before,
but I suppose it's worth a shot.
♪♪
Ahem!
[firm voice] Severe,
but not unapproachable.
Acceptable business
attire.
[normal soft voice]
Oh...
Does that sound like
a shop pony to you?
[cheering chitters]
♪♪
So sorry for the wait, the shop
has some staffing issues today.
Yes. Well, I still haven't had
an answer on this thread count.
Here at Rarity for You,
our merchandise defies
typical attempts
to quantify its quality,
but rest assured, it will make
you the envy of all who see it.
Oh! In that case, I'll take three!
[ka-ching]
♪♪
Ta-ta.
[door opens and closes]
[groan]
[thud]
[panting]
Ahh! Smokey Junior!
I can't believe it worked.
[snobby voice] I suppose
clothes really do
make the pony after all.
♪♪
I don't know about you,
but I have a full day
of shopping planned.
And if even one shop pony
isn't up to my standards, well,
I shall make my
displeasure quite plain.
Oh! You are wicked!
[pretentious laugh]
Canterlot fashion show or no, I
simply can't leave Fluttershy
to fend for herself with
these Manehattanites!
♪♪
[panting]
Rarity!
Oh, darling, I'm
afraid I can't stop.
Potential emergency
at the boutique!
Oh. Well, whatever it is, I am
quite certain the pony
you left in charge
can handle it.
Oh, she's simply divine!
Oh! Well, I always knew
Fluttershy had it in her, ha ha!
And there's still time to
catch the train to Canterlot!
It's a unique play
on the old standard.
We call it a Rarity-cut with
a triple cross stitch hem
in a guacamole chèvre
patterned fabric.
Don't you mean chevron?
If I had meant chevron, then
that's what I would have said.
Heh. Of course!
It's so unique!
So in vogue.
It must be mine!
[ka-ching]
♪♪
[cheering chitters]
Aw, thanks, everyone, but I
feel like I should
push the snootiness further.
[chittering]
If you really wanna help, I
suppose serving tea
would be nice. Oh!
If you don't mind.
♪♪
I like my accessories
bold and shiny,
and I'm just not seeing anything
nearly bold and shiny enough.
I'm afraid bold and shiny
won't work with your whole...
modèle.
Perhaps...
pointy.
Pointy? Yes!
I must have pointy!
Not everypony can pull
off a "found object,"
but you nearly get there.
[ka-ching]
[valley girl accent]
I need, like, a red-carpet
glitz and glamour gown
that's also casual
but, like, still
artsy and a
total head turner.
Yes, casual-chic prêt-à-porter
is very branché this season.
Uhhh...
Like I don't understand
any of that, so, like,
I don't care about it?
Um. One moment please.
[zoom]
Oh... I think I need
a new character.
♪♪
OK, I've got, like, this high-
key, savage look for you.
It's a totally live ensemble
with a little, like,
thingies that sparkle and
make the whole squad go,
"Whoa, that pony is woke!"
That is, like,
exactly what I need!
This store is a desperate
wasteland of nothingness.
Do you have
anything in black?
Can you, like,
chill for one sec?
BRB.
It's not like the futility of
shopping can be made better
with black leather and metal
studs, but they help.
Uh... That jacket
completes me.
[spray]
[Cockney accent]
This tea's like, lukewarm.
It's barely drinkable.
This tea must always be
at a precise temperature.
See that it doesn't
happen AGAIN!
♪♪
Whoa, that color is like...
almost too lit for you!
The blackness of this vest
is a reflection of your soul.
This hemline is nothing
short of an inspiration
in craftsponyship!
Are you sure you deserve it?
♪♪
[knock knock]
♪ [action music] ♪
[gasp]            [shriek]
I don't know what's worse, that
you've spilled the tea
or that it's still cold!
Either get it right or
GO BACK TO THE FOREST!
[smash]
Ugh! It is so hard to find
good help these days.
[angry chittering]
OK, OK!
Slow down, everyone.
I'm doing my best.
♪♪
So...
Rarity is busy at an
important fashion show
and Fluttershy is running
her shop in Manehattan
but to do it, she's playing
different shop pony
characters that
are all mean?
[cheering chitters]
How in the world did you
figure that out, Spike?
I'm not dragon charades
champion for nothing.
I can't imagine Fluttershy
would ever be mean
to her animal friends.
This sounds serious.
Spike, tell everyone it's time
to head back to Saddle Row!
I wouldn't think it was
possible to make something
so dowdy even more matronly,
but ... here you are!
It's like a scream
in the void.
Empty and ultimately
meaningless.
I would seriously help you right
now, but, like, I don't wanna,
you know?
[chittering]
You weren't kidding.
This is worse than we thought.
She's being horrible
to everypony.
Uh... are you sure
that's even Fluttershy?
Maybe it's just three
really, really fast ponies
that really, really
look like her.
Well, let's find out.
Hey, Fluttershy, are
you running the shop
or performing in a
one pony show?
If you don't mind, I can
only improve the taste
of one customer at a time.
You have to wait your turn.
Ugh!
Honestly, these small town
ponies come to the big city
and think they can behave
any way they please.
WHAT?
You are a small town pony!
And your cottage isn't
even in the town!
Look, Fluttershy, we came here
because we were worried
and we care about you.
Let's get out of this
aura of positivity
before it consumes us.
As fun as this Fluttershy
swithcheroo game is,
Smokey, Smokey Junior and
Softpad are really concerned.
Yeah. They came all the way
to Ponyville to get us.
[chitters]
They should have,
like, stayed there.
This shop is, like,
a no-rodent zone now.
[gasp]
She called them RODENTS?
Fluttershy, I understand why you
think you have to act this way
for these customers, but
there's gotta be a better way.
Goodness, you are so right.
Please, step this way so that
we may discuss your concerns.
I knew you'd come
to your senses.
[slam]
Indeed!
♪♪
[crowd buzzing]
Oh! The centerpiece of my collection
and it's still not right.
Oh, darling, I'm afraid we've
literally run out of time.
It's up to you.
Go out there and sell it!
Now... ATTITUDE!
[cheers]
♪ [techno pop] ♪
I don't understand.
When I left Fluttershy, she
had everything well in hoof.
Well, things might have seemed
all right when you left,
but they're definitely
not all right now.
She's acting worse than the
worst Manehattanite I ever saw!
She kicked us out of the shop!
She called Smokey, Smokey
Junior, and Softpad-- RODENTS!
Wh-wha... RODENTS?
Why didn't you say
that from the start?
She obviously needs help!
Come on!
♪♪
Your melancholy is way
too shallow for a look
with this much
unfeeling depth.
Ha!
Ugh! Your style isn't
even on the same page.
Turn away!
Don't even look at it, OK?
[gasp]
I can't. Even.
♪♪
I think not, dear.
This is all far too fashion
forward for the likes of you.
Oh! Well, I never!
[door opens and slams shut]
Told ya it was bad.
Bad? This is worse than I
could have possibly imagined!
Rarity, I'm so
glad you're here.
[kiss kiss]
Finally, a pony who understands
that the couture in this shop
is far too brilliant to
even consider selling.
WHAT?
You, like, totally get
how lame customers are!
Watching them leave filled
me with a sweet sadness.
And you'll be pleased to
hear that I've taken care
of your rodent situation.
[chitters]
Will somepony tell her
to stop saying that!
That's it!
Fluttershy, I'm afraid
you've left me no choice.
You are terminated!
Well! Good luck
replacing me! Huh!
[sigh] Well, thankfully I--
AHHHAAAAHH!
I always thought she
was too controlling.
You-you are
terminated too!
Whatever.
Now I--AIIEEEEE!
I know, right?
I mean, O-M--
Actually, you're, like,
totally terminated as well.
Like... OK.
[gasp] Well, I'm glad
that's ov-AAAAH!
I guess I owe
everypony an apology.
[sigh] You think?
I got so caught up
trying to please all of
your customers that...
What customers?
I might have taken my salespony
characters a little too far.
[squeezing]
I'm sorry if I
hurt your feelings.
You know I was only
pretending, right?
[happy chitters]
But Fluttershy, why did you
think you needed to be
somepony else to
run the shop?
I guess acting like the
ponies of Saddle Row
gave me the confidence to
interact with them.
Darling, I'd never trust some
horrible Saddle Row pony
to run my shop.
That's why I wanted
a friend to do it.
Well, I'd definitely
rather be myself anyway,
even if I don't exactly have
what it takes to be a shop pony.
I wouldn't sell
yourself short.
Those salespony characters
all came from you.
Yeah. I think you totally
have what it takes.
Maybe a little too much.
Indeed.
You have all the inner
strength you need,
but I think we
prefer it coming
from our sweet,
regular Fluttershy.
[giggles]
And that's just given me the
inspiration I'm looking for!
And last one...there!
The missing piece for
my new collection:
The Warrior of
Inner Strength!
[excited chatter]
Gorgeous!
Oh, it's lovely, Rarity. I'm
just sorry you had to leave
the Canterlot Royal
Fashion Show early.
Oh, darling, making the perfect
dress is scads more satisfying
than showing it off.
[excited chatter]
Ooh. Striking dress, Rarity.
I certainly hope you aren't
trying to undercut the
Royal Fashion Show by ducking
out and debuting it here.
What? No, I-I--
Have you considered
the possibility
that the Royal Fashion Show is
trying to undercut Rarity's
by continuing on
in Canterlot
and not moving the
whole affair here?
Hm? HAVE YOU? HM?
I, uh, no.
Hmph! Just as I thought.
Oh! [giggle]
Inner strength.
[laughter]