Twilight: This happened
while we were gone?
Applejack: Friendship quests
beyond Equestria?
Twilight: We're
gonna open a school!
Neighsay: We expect you to
do things by the book.
Twilight: We have a huge
responsibility,
and I need you all to
do this by the book.
These ponies are the
heroes of Equestria?
Gallus: This is just a quick
mental health break!
Neighsay: The school
is under attack!
Those are students!?
I am shutting
this school DOWN.
Oh!
Twilight?
You feeling OK?
Look on the bright side!
Sure the EEA closed
your Friendship School,
but now you've got
time to do other stuff!
It's like being on vacation!
Whoa!
A failure vacation!
I'm supposed to be the
Princess of Friendship.
And all I did was make enemies
with Equestria's allies,
upset my friends,
and get my school...
unaccredited!
THERE IS NO BRIGHT SIDE!
OK then. I'm gonna
need backup.
Operation Cheer Up is a go!
Come on, Twilight!
You can't sit around in
the boring dark all day!
Exactly!
What you need is a double dose
of Granny Smith's apple mash.
Whenever I'm sad, a
hug from Angel Bunny
always makes me
feel better.
Oh!
Uh. Maybe it's just me.
I find that nothing brightens
my mood like a new ensemble!
[sigh] Thanks, Rarity.
It's a great dress...
[sobbing] for somepony who
knows how to run a school.
You didn't tell me
this was a pity party!
I would've brought ice cream!
I appreciate you trying
to make me feel better.
But not everything can
be fixed with dresses and cupcakes.
WHAT!
I just need some time
to be alone and think.
Oh!
I wondered how
long you'd take
to get tired of
pillow fort pouting.
Everypony's already
tried to cheer me up.
It won't work.
I'm not gonna
cheer you up.
I'm gonna tell you
what you did wrong.
What!?
You gave up too easily.
Hey, you made me a
guidance counselor.
That means tough love.
Neighsay was right.
I failed.
The school WAS a disaster.
So was I when
you met me!
But you showed me that
when you know in your heart
something is right,
you stand up for it.
You did that for me.
Why not for this?
I can't go against the EEA!
They're in charge of all of
the schools in Equestria.
And you're in charge of all
the Friendship in Equestria.
Why should you
let somepony else
stop you from
doing your job?
But the EEA rule book--
[splash]
Doesn't matter.
You can write
your own rules!
Because you're doing
something new.
Something important.
You're right!
WHY we're doing this
is way more important
than HOW we're
doing this.
And we ARE
doing this!
Now that's the
Twilight I know.
How can I help?
You already have.
[door opens] Guess what?
The School of Friendship
is back in business!
WHAT?
But why?
Oh no!
Bad idea.
Do we still get
to guess?
No offense, Twilight, but
teaching at that school
was the most boring,
horrible, awful thing ever.
Uh. Pretty sure she's gonna
take offense to that.
No, Rainbow Dash
is right.
I owe you all an apology.
I was so focused on
doing things the EEA way,
I didn't listen to
any of you.
I'm sorry. I
promise this time,
we'll run the school
like friends should.
Together.
So we'd be allowed to
teach however we want to?
No more scary
pop quizzes?
Confetti cannons
for every creature?
Whatever you need to teach
the elements of harmony.
Yippppeeeeee!
Well, in that case, we're
behind you 100%, Twilight!
Spike: Ahem, just
two small problems.
The school is still
unaccredited...
And we don't have
any students.
I'll take care of
the first part,
if you five can
round up our class.
Totally!
Uh... how?
Roundin' up the pony students
ain't gonna be an issue but...
The creatures from
the other kingdoms
seemed pretty
upset with us.
Pfft. Nonsense!
I'm certain we can win them
over with our charm and style!
Cupcake gram for
Prince Rutherford!
Why Pink Pony here?
Yaks mad at ponies.
Beeee-cause you don't
have to be mad anymore!
We're reopening Twilight
Sparkle's School of Friendship
and it's gonna be super-
ooper-dooper
better than before!
We're ever so sorry about
the misunderstanding.
All creatures are
of course welcome!
We would be really happy
if you sent your student
back to class.
It won't be the
same without 'em!
We're open and ready
to start teaching...
...right now!
So? What are you
waiting for?
Get your student
and let's go!
Not happening.
Aw, do you need me to
do the whole apology
and explanation thing again?
OK.
Listen, missy.
It's not happening
because--
YOUR STUDENT IS GONE!
WHAT!
Prince Rutherford: WHERE YONA!
This all Ponies' fault!
You're pretty quick
to blame them.
What are you
hiding, Yak?
Uh, can we just focus on
finding our lost students?
Nice try!
You grubs are probably
hiding the whole lot of 'em!
Please, everycreature, if
you can just explain
what happened...
The students left us notes
before they disappeared.
When the school closed, they
didn't want to say goodbye
to each other.
They claim they ran
away to stay together.
I can't believe it!
They did learn friendship!
Sorry.
The students couldn't have
done this by themselves.
SOME creature is hiding them!
If the niece of our
queen is not found soon,
I promise there
will be retribution!
Yeah? Well, my dragons
will burn every kingdom
until we find which of
you is hiding Smolder.
Tell it to the Griffon Army.
Yaks fight griffons
and dragons!
The Changeling
Empire can't afford
an international incident.
If any creature blames the
Changelings for this--
What are you up
to, shape-shifter?
But we're friends...
Find the students
quickly, Twilight.
Or I fear our world
will be at war.
Twilight: OK. Let's
review what we know.
Smolder, Ocellus,
Silverstream, Yona,
and Gallus
disappeared together.
That's all we know.
They're probably just
off hidin' somewhere.
Unless they used some kind
of spell to disappear.
Ooh! Or went undercover!
Maybe they were attacked
by a ferocious shrimp!
Nopony EVER expects that.
[gasp] Shrimps can attack?
Nope. That's why
nopony expects it!
Whoa!
Hi, Sandbar!
Are you having a party?
No! I'm just, uh...
really hungry.
We need to think
like our students.
If someone told us we would
never see each other again,
what would we do?
Go someplace we
could all hang out
and eat lots and
lots of cupcakes!
What..?
Sandbar was friends with
all of the missing students.
And he just got
plenty of cupcakes.
Huh... He was at the
farm this morning,
picking up a
wagonload of apples.
And I saw him in a shop
buying pillows and blankets!
[gasp] He must be
taking all that stuff
to the other students!
We gotta follow him!
Heh. This place is way cooler
than I thought it'd be.
Even I'm impressed.
What's it called
again, Ocellus?
The Castle of the
Two Sisters.
I remembered it from class:
Princess Twilight's History of
Pre-Equestrian Friendships.
Huh. Who knew?
School was actually
good for something!
Yona not really like school.
But Yona like new friends.
Smolder...Like...Breathing.
Silverstream: Hey, you
guys!
Sandbar is back!
Cupcakes are best cakes!
Agh!
Huh. Thanks for the
assist, Gallus.
Pff. I was saving the cupcakes.
Pillows, how nice!
The castle is going to
be so much more comfy.
And fun!
Pillow fight!
Silverstream: YOU GUYS!
I just found...
STAIRS!
And ... we care because...
Stairs are awesome!
We don't have anything
like 'em underwater.
Cause you know...
No way to climb 'em.
Ohhhh.
This place has everything!
If only my family back
home could see it!
I wish the other Changelings
could meet you all.
You're not nearly as
strange as the stories say.
Gee, thanks.
But yeah, hanging out
with other creatures
is actually...not bad.
Uh, MOST other creatures.
What is THAT thing?
[sigh] Am I the ONLY one who
didn't sleep through
Professor Fluttershy's Critters
of Comfort and Conflict Class?
It's a puckwudgie!
Maybe I can make
friends with it!
Oops.
Yak plan better.
YAAAA!
Think, Ocellus!
Did Professor Fluttershy
say anything about
how to beat Puckwudgies
in her lecture?
Ah! I'm sorry, I can't remember.
I'm gonna go ahead and
guess it's not pillows,
apples...... or cupcakes.
Wouldn't class have been about
how to make friends with them?
Uh, guys? They're
getting really close...
Yona not scared.
Yona have friends.
Is that Professor Egghead?
Aw, yeah!
Oh! Don't hurt them!
Just ask them to leave nicely.
Not bad!
For pony...
Wow. They're amazing.
I had no idea our teachers
were actually cool.
I've been trying to tell you!
Did you see that!?
Rainbow Dash was like zooooom!
And then whoooaa!
The Puckwudgies went flying!
And then the birds came and...
Yeah. We all
just lived it.
But you're right.
That was pretty amazing...
even by dragon standards.
Is everycreature all right?
You're lucky we
got here in time.
You know, this probably
isn't the safest place
for a campout.
Does that mean you're going
to send us back to our homes?
Not exactly.
We have another
option in mind.
We're listening.
It's pretty clear you've
already started learning
friendship without
your teachers.
But we'd like to show
you even more...
if you come back to school?
Not much of a choice.
To be honest, we felt
exactly the same way
when Twilight told us she
was reopening the school.
But this time, we guarantee
it shall be different.
Oh, yeah. With
class run my way,
it'll be TWO HUNDRED and
twenty percent cooler.
And without the EEA,
it'll be much friendlier.
Plus all your nations
won't go to war
if you come back with us!
Bonus!
Wait, what's happening?
Celestia: Twilight!
I was so relieved
to get your letter.
As was Queen Novo.
Oh, we're just glad you're
all right, Silverstream.
Don't expect a welcome
party from me, sonny.
It's time you got home.
I'm not leaving.
WHAT!?
None of us are.
Sorry, Thorax.
Yak not understand.
This pony joke?
No. We're going
back to school.
How? You can't
even get inside.
School is back in session.
Who dared remove my seal?
I did, Chancellor Neighsay.
And I respectfully
ask you to step aside,
or classes will start late.
Classes won't start at all!
The EEA has spoken.
And NONE SHALL PASS!
Yak pass if Yak say! HMPH!
This is for the greater good.
The school was disorganized!
The teachers unqualified!
And those dangerous and
unpredictable "students"
put ponies' lives in danger!
Grr! I'll show you unpredictable.
Hold on, please!
I'm sure Princess Twilight
Sparkle has a good explanation
for all of this.
I do.
It's true that my
School of Friendship
is EEA unaccredited.
Look! She said it without
doing the eye thing!
Then it is not a school!
It's not an EEA school.
It's a friendship school.
With its own rules.
I should know.
I wrote the book.
These students reminded me
that every friendship
is special.
So the way we teach it
has to be just as unique.
My school is going to
do things differently.
Allowing all of
these creatures
to attend your school...
changing the rules for them!
It simply won't work!
I seem to recall something
about Earth Ponies,
Unicorns and Pegasi doing
something similar, don't you?
I promise you, Chancellor,
my school will help
protect Equestria.
Or destroy it.
Hmph. How's this school gonna be
any different from last time?
♪ This brand new
School of Friendship ♪
♪ Is home to everyone ♪
♪ We're learning how to trust.♪
♪ We're here to all have fun ♪
♪ With friendship
ties that bind us ♪
♪ Tighter than the
strongest bonds ♪
♪ We're hoof-in-hoof ♪
♪ In hand-in-hoof in
wing or even... claw! ♪
♪ There's a griffon
in the garden ♪
♪ Hippogriffs hang in the hall♪
♪ And the door will be open to
all creatures great and small ♪
♪ And a yak or two or three ♪
♪ Sing in perfect harmony ♪
♪ That might have been a
Changeling... ♪
♪ But it kinda looks like meeeeee ♪
♪ The School of Friendship
is for all of us ♪
♪ A place where we belong ♪
♪ Where we all learn
to share and trust ♪
♪ The only rule here is
to find your way ♪
♪ And friendship always wins
at the end of the day ♪
♪ Some things you just
can't teach with books ♪
♪ Some things you only know ♪
♪ So trust your heart
and let us lead ♪
♪ And your friendship's
sure to grow. ♪
♪ And once we
we master kindness ♪
♪ We will spread it
'cross this land. ♪
♪ And give the gift
that's ours to share ♪
♪ so others understand ♪
♪ The School of Friendship
is for all of us ♪
♪ A place where we belong ♪
♪ Where we all learn to
share and trust ♪
♪ The only rule here is
to find your way ♪
♪ And friendship always wins
at the end of the day ♪
Ember: Aw, fine!
If you promise to stop
singing, Smolder can stay!
Wahoo!
Ah.. If dragon stay, yak stay.
I know you will make the
Changelings proud, Ocellus.
You belong here.
Now can you show me those
stair-things you mentioned?
Aw, yeah! [giggle]
What?
You belong at home.
You think I care if
you've made friends?
Please, Grandpa
Gruff?
Wha- All right! Stop doing that!
Guess I make a pretty good
Guidance Counselor, huh?
Yes! Writing a rule book
was the most fun ever!
I can't wait to start working
on the new lesson plans!
Ahem.
With some help
from my friends.