Twilight: Oh. I've been planning
this retreat for weeks
and we're already
ten minutes behind.
Where is that photographer!?
Oh, no, oh no, oh no.
I'm SO SORRY.
Can you forgive me?
I don't expect
you to forgive me.
Forgive me?
Of course.
I'll help you set up your--
Princess Twilight,
thanks SO much for this!
The Canterlot Historical Society
is thrilled to document
the friendship work
your teachers do.
Let me just pretty
you all up!
OW!
Hey!
Don't want a single hair
out of place, do we?
This is for the history books!
Now...
Well, that's that! Bye!
WAIT!
You forgot Starlight!
She needs a picture too!
'Kay.
Now I'll get out of your manes!
I know how busy you are!
Now I have everything I need.
Yes, I know.
We have been planning
this for quite some time.
Oh, thank you, Applejack.
My spell can create a
copy of anypony I desire.
All I need is an image
and a piece of the pony.
Oh, and this.
Why copies, Rarity?
Because Princess
Twilight and her friends
control the Elements
of Harmony.
The most powerful
weapon in ALL Equestria.
Which means YOU...
will, be, able, to,
use, them, too!
And serve.. me!
Together, we will destroy
Twilight Sparkle
and her meddlesome friends!
OF COURSE I HAVEN'T
FORGOTTEN STARLIGHT GLIMMER!
She stole my hive.
Turned my subjects against me.
So I'll take her "friends"
away while she watches.
And then... I'll destroy her!
With the Elements
under my control,
I'll build a NEW hive of earth
ponies, unicorns and pegasi.
And I will rule as
Queen ONCE AGAIN!
Hmm. At least our retreat isn't
TOO far behind schedule.
Get ready for fun!
Are we talking FUN fun?
Or learning
pretending to be fun?
Both! We've all been
so busy teaching,
we've hardly had a chance to
hang out with each other.
And I may have scheduled some
friendship activities as well!
Count me in!
We can do friendship trust
falls and pony pyramids...OH!
And hide and seek!
QUICK! FIND ME!
Well, I love the idea of some
quiet time with my best friends.
AH! YOU FOUND ME!
Rarity, why is Applejack
carrying all your stuff?
Oh, that's not mine.
Yes, I used to overpack a tad.
But now it's JUST the
essentials for me.
I'm a simple filly.
Normally I wouldn't
lug so much gear,
but did y'all know this is
Starlight's FIRST time campin'?
I just never really
felt the need to...
hang out in nature.
Home has books, tea,
fewer bugs, a roof...
That attitude right
there is why I brought
the whole kit n' caboodle!
I'm giving Starlight the FULL
Apple family camping experience!
Um, where ARE we camping?
Right next to the elements that
brought us all together
in the first place.
The Tree of Harmony!
LISTEN to your Queen!
We must retrieve The
Elements of Harmony!
Hunting down some
lame Elements?
This is the worst
day EVER!
No. NOW it's the
worst day ever.
Those elements are MINE!
Along with this rock.
Oh, and that twig.
I got all kinds of Elements
right here under my hat.
I'll letcha see
'em for five bits.
Huh. Losers.
Why didn't you
just attack them?
Excuse me?
You were close enough to
pull hairs from their manes.
Why not just take
your revenge then?
They've defeated my army.
I know better than
to strike alone.
I need--
Friends?
SERVANTS.
And the power of
the Elements.
Right.....
So, where are these
Elements of Harmony?
The location of the most
powerful weapon in Equestria
isn't something made
known to just anypony.
I learned they were hidden
somewhere in this forest.
Yeah well, it is a big forest.
Everypony stop!
And smell these roses!
Aaah!
Pinkie: Oh, yeah!
Twilight: All right! Roses! Fun!
Now... let's try and
stay on schedule!
Applejack, darling?
Anything in that wagon
for mane maintenance?
Uh, let's see here.
I got a bandana?
An entire wagon
and no anti friz?
Darling, you're
not even prepared!
I am. For campin'.
How you doin', Starlight?
Great.
Oh, no!
You and your sister fell out
of your nest and got separated?
That's terrible!
Here.
I'm sure your home
isn't TOO far away.
WAH! PINKIE!
If we keep stopping
to have fun,
we're never going to get to the
fun things I've got planned!
Ah! Good point!
LAST ONE TO THE TREE OF
HARMONY IS A PARASPRITE!
I'm so bored!
Are we there yet?
WHERE yet?
We don't even know
where we're going.
The quicker we
search the forest,
the quicker we
find the Elements.
I know where the Elements are.
This uh, here boulder
just told me. I swear.
You tried to fly out of the
nest, but you fell and got lost?
Hope ya like walking!
Come get me when I should care.
Where.  Are.  The others?
Uh, a uh Bugbear in plaid socks
flew down and uh grabbed 'em.
Then disappeared!
Craziest thing I ever did see.
Turn around.
We're going back.
No! Keep searching.
I'll find the others.
We can accomplish more if
we split our resources.
Very well.
You have my permission.
"Permission"?
You need us way more than
we need you, "Your Majesty".
The others are fools.
But with me to lead them,
there's no reason we can't find
the Elements and keep
the power for ourselves!
YOU'RE IT!
Hey, how did you
get ahead of me?
You're fast!
Ugh.
I'm looking for Fluttershy
and Rainbow Dash!
Aren't they back there?
They are?
Sure!
Unless they're already
at the Tree of Harmony.
What is the TREE of Harmony?
Oh, ha ho!
This is one of your
"activities" right?
Like a friendship quiz?
It's the crystal tree that
holds the Elements of Harmony!
BOOM!
[gasp] Where is it?
Bzzzz! It's at the bottom
of the stairs in the ravine
by the Castle of the
Two Sisters!
A double BOOM!
How do you know?
You've SEEN it?
Mm hm!
Honestly Twilight, these
questions are SUPER easy.
Right where you belong.
Oh, dear.
This isn't where I belong.
Oh, Rainbow Dash!
I'm so glad you're here.
I was lost!
Bummer. Later.
What just happened?
[yelling] Fluttershy!
Ugh. Fantastic. First Pinkie
races ahead of us,
and now Fluttershy is lost
somewhere behind us.
My retreat is off
to a great start.
It's not like Fluttershy
to disappear like this.
We'll split up and
search for her.
We can all meet
back at the Tree.
Starlight, take the
navigation gear and--
Go with Rarity? Great!
Rainbow Dash, YOU can
go with Applejack! Heh heh.
I'll find Pinkie Pie.
Bored bored bored.
This is ridiculous! Where
are my other minions?
Probably plotting
to steal my things. Grrr.
They're at a secret party
up in that there tree,
run by a squirrel named er... Jerome.
But uh, you need a
password to get in.
[growl] ENOUGH!
You will GO out there
and find the others.
You will BRING them back here.
And we will STEAL the
Elements of Harmony,
so I can destroy Starlight's
life like she destroyed mine!
Understand?
Uh huh!
The party password is: Rutabaga.
Why don't you fly
up to your nest?
Oh, that's right.
YOU CAN'T.
Oh, Nopony asked you.
I hope you all
freeze this winter.
Hello again, little friend.
I think I may be
walking in circles.
Oh, my!
Where did you learn
that kind of language?
Um. Excuse me.
Finally! You found her!
Me? We're looking
for Fluttershy!
Where's Starlight?
Well, if I knew THAT...
Hey!
THIS is mine!
And this as well.
Oh, and this is ABSOLUTELY mine.
Rarity, what in the hay are ya
gonna do with a fishing rod?
I don't know.
But I WANT it.
Starlight, darling.
Your'e a gloriously bad camper.
And coming from me,
that is saying a lot.
I know.
Want to break it to
Applejack for me?
Who's breakin' what now?
Who are you?
Very funny, Applejack.
Still me under all
this gear, Starlight.
Starlight..?
How about that.
Y'all better come with me.
It's.. dangerous out here!
Applejack darling,
are you all right?
You look a little peaky.
And where's your wagon?
Uh, stolen!
I barely got away!
Follow me and I'll
tell ya ALL about it.
Pinkie!
There you are!
What are you doing?
YOU CALL THAT A POP? UGH!
I thought you were
racing to the retreat!
Please.
Why would I waste my time on a
boring, lame, no-fun retreat?
What..?
Rainbow Dash!
I think something's
wrong with Pinkie.
Not my problem.
And then all we grew SUPER long
manes with ALL kinds of colors
and your castle grew out of the
ground and everypony was like
"WHOA!" And then we sang this
song about Rainbows and--
Fluttershy! What's wrong?
Everycreature is mad at me!
[gasp] What? That can't be right.
Can we hurry this up?
We're on a schedule here.
Twilight, your
schedule can wait!
Fluttershy's upset!
Well, tell her to get over it!
I'll go get the others.
STAY. HERE.
Oh great.
You upset Fluttershy, too?
You know what, Twilight?
Maybe if you weren't so
worried about schedules,
you'd realize you're the
one ruining the retreat
for your friends!
[gasp] Well.. if my friends don't care about
the retreat I planned for them,
maybe they should've
stayed HOME!
CAN'T WE ALL JUST GET ALONG?
Keep it together.
You can do this.
You NEED those imbeciles if your
plan is going to come together.
YOUR plan?
Uh, THE plan.
I'm just trying to do your
bidding, Your Majesty.
Grubsitting you six is nothing
like controlling my hive.
Give me one good reason why I
shouldn't just destroy you all
and start over.
Because I know where The
Elements of Harmony are.
You NEED me.
Mine! Mine!
I'm guessing some kinda curse?
Maybe Poison Joke?
Well, somethin'
sure ain't right.
What are you
plotting back there?
I can HEAR you, you know.
Don't think you're going
to steal my things!
Oof!
Hang on.
I got a shovel we can use to
whack those vines outta the way.
I KNEW IT!
I KNEW YOU WANTED IT
ALL FOR YOURSELVES!
YOU CAN'T HAVE IT!
IT'S MINE! YOU HEAR ME!
ALL MI-I-I-INE!
So there I was, just me
and a.... a bucket of honey!
Yeah, yeah that's the ticket.
Uh. But I- I survived all by
myself in this here forest
for.... 127 hours!
Really?
I can't believe you've never
told us that story before.
She's making a point.
WE GET IT.
You're the GREATEST camper
in the history of Equestria.
Well, I sure don't need
any of that silly stuff
YOU'RE luggin' around.
The things you
gave me are SILLY?
Just look in a mirror!
Guess I shoulda told
ya that before, huh?
Heh heh heh!
Glad I was so
entertaining for you.
I'm going to make sure she
doesn't break a hoof out there
and then you and I are going
to have a serious talk!
FINALLY!
There. That's all of you.
Nopony leaves without
my say so.
Now wait a second.
Weren't you just--
The time for my revenge on
Starlight Glimmer has come!
Let's see if you're telling
the truth about this tree.
Ha ha ha!
Rarity: Starlight!
Oh, please stop running.
Twilight: Of course I care
about Fluttershy!
Then you got a super-weird
way of showing it!
Wh- What in Equestria
is going on here?
Twilight is so
into her "retreat"
that she doesn't even care
if her friends are upset!
She just wants us to STAY.
ON.
SCHEDULE!
Well, I'm SORRY Pinkie!
If I KNEW you thought this was
a "boring lame no fun retreat"
I wouldn't have invited
you in the FIRST PLACE!
I NEVER SAID THAT!
Sorry, y'all.
We woulda been here sooner but
we had to take the long way
after RARITY ran off
with all my stuff!
Wha! I most certainly
did not!
What? You know I
ain't no liar!
Where's all your gear?
Why? So you can LAUGH
at me some more?
Hey hey! We're
all friends here!
FRIENDS?
You left me alone
in the woods!
EVERYPONY, QUIET!
Listen.
We know each other really well.
The great stuff and how to
get on each other's nerves, too.
I wanted a fun trip
with my friends.
But instead, I got carried
away with plans
and ruined everything.
If you want to forget it all and
head home, I won't be offended.
I just want us to stop fighting.
Hey, sorry if I
got carried away
with all that
campin' stuff.
I'm sorry, too.
I should've just told you
I'll never like camping.
Also: I'll never
like camping.
Well, if we're all
being honest...
I can't survive with just
this tiny efashionable
little saddle bag!
I miss my things!
I'm sorry that you thought that
I thought your plan was lame!
Your plans are
the most unlamest!
And I always have fun
when we're all together.
Even if it's learning
pretending to be fun.
So... does that mean you still
want to have the retreat?
YES!
If... everypony likes me again.
Let's get to that Tree!
I have the whole campsite
set up and ready!
Ugh. What's this garbage?
Badger installation art.
Ya see...
JUST. RETRIEVE.
THE ELEMENTS!
Once we get the power of
the Elements, no creature,
not even "Her Majesty"
can tell us what to do.
Just follow my lead, got it?
Oooooh! That one's mine!
Oops. I'd say
sorry, but I'm not.
Stop it, fools!
We need the elements
to take out Chrysalis!
HOW DARE YOU!
I CREATED YOU!
Imbeciles!
You ruined everything........!
Servants always
fail you in the end.
Just wait, Starlight.
I WILL HAVE MY REVENGE!
[gasp] Are you kidding me?
This was.
The worst. Day. Ever!
Come on, everypony.
We can fix this
campsite in no time.
Spoken like a true camper.
Eh, don't push it.
You know, if we can
survive a day like this,
I think our friendship is
strong enough to handle
anything the world
can throw at us.