Oh! Rarity! Just the
pony I'm looking for.
Can you come to Twilight's class
with me? It won't take long.
Oh, I'd love to help,
but I have to meet Rainbow Dash
for our day of fun together.
Twilight wants to use you as
an example for the students.
Oooh!
Your example is here!
Ha ha! Oh!
I thought I was the example.
You both are. Because together,
you perfectly demonstrate
my lesson on compromise
in friendship!
Rainbow Dash and Rarity have
very different interests
that keep them busy. But being
friends is so important to them,
they always manage to
make time for each other.
Our Day of Fun was hard to plan,
what with Rainbow Dash's
extremely time-consuming
and erratically scheduled
Wonderbolts practice...
And Rarity's weird
fashion seasons.
She's working on her
winter collection
and it's not even summer yet!
But you still found
time to be together,
and that's what counts!
See, class? These
ponies are models
of true friendship in action.
Thanks for stopping by!
Enjoy your "Day of Fun"!
Ooh, ooh! What amazing stuff
are you gonna do together?
Shoe shopping!
Obstacle races!
Dress shopping!
Flight goggle shopping!
Aw, come ON! I even said
shopping that time!
Perfect! We'll go
shopping first.
But, I brought
stuff for Buckball-
Are we supposed to be
learning something here?
Cause this doesn't sound
like compromising at all.
Yeah! You guys have nothing in
common. How can you be friends?
Even though Rainbow
Dash and Rarity
enjoy doing different things,
there are plenty of reasons
why they're friends.
Uh, like what?
Tch. We've always been friends!
Always?
Well, no. Not always. But
for like a super long time.
And we know all
the same ponies.
Um, is that it?
There was that time during the
Cloudsdale Best Young Flyer
competition when I totally saved
Rarity's life!
Yes! And I once proved
Rainbow Dash's innocence
to her beloved Wonderbolts
when she was being framed
for a mysterious incident!
Cool! What else?
Heh heh..
Uh, look, it may seem like
Rarity and Rainbow Dash
don't have that
much in common
when you try to put
it into words..
But sometimes friendships
can't be explained.
You just have to see them
in action to understand.
Actually... that's
a great idea!
Just go about your Day of
Fun as you normally would!
You won't even know we're here!
Game On!
Rarity! You were supposed
to be holding your bucket!
Hmm? Oh, sorry, darling! Wearing
this drab jersey gave me an idea
for a Buckball-inspired
line of "athleisure wear"
that would allow for maximum
flexibility and style.
But I'm ready now!
Good. Cause this time I'm
gonna try something new
and super-intense!
Rarity! Are you even
paying attention?
What? Oh, I mean, of course! I
held my bucket and everything!
But you have to
CATCH the ball.
Really? Well, that
sounds dangerous.
Oh, forget it. She's
never gonna understand
the point of this game.
Buckball time is over!
Ah! Finally!
Er.. see? They did something
Rainbow Dash likes,
so now it's time for something
Rarity likes. Compromise!
Hmmm. I'm genuinely not
sure. Are they too in style?
Uh, isn't that what
you want them to be?
Yes, yes. But they should
be ahead of the curve.
If they're in
fashion right now,
then they're
practically already out!
That doesn't make any sense.
Hmm. Perhaps I should get
the stilettos instead.
What do you think?
Unless you like tripping
with every step,
heels on a horse
are pretty useless.
[snort] Au contraire! They're perfect
in a multitude of situations:
Formal functions, afternoon
teas, evening teas, high teas,
tea by the sea, royal tea--
Can they clean up glitter?
Ew! It's on my hooves!
Are we done yet?
Agh!
This is so boring!
Rainbow Dash and
Rarity are just... er..
showcasing an aspect of
friendship called "banter":
the playful and friendly
exchange of remarks!
It's all in good fun!
Ooh I cannot wait! Collecting
gemstones is my favorite.
Finally, something we can
agree on: treasure hunting!
See, everycreature?
That didn't take long.
Now they're having a
great time together.
Ooh Magnifique! This will
be perfect for the
emerald-encrusted romper
I've been working on.
Cool! Now what would
be even cooler
is if we could find a treasure
chamber or something.
Now if I were a secret
door, where would I be?
Rainbow Dash! Could you please
refrain from all of that racket?
It's muddying my
concentration.
[gasp] Look! A lever!
It's stuck. Come
help me, Rarity!
[sigh] Just a moment.
[gasp] You ruined my gems!
Yeah, well. You ruined
my treasure hunt!
Ugh. This wasn't about treasure!
It was about finding gemstones
for my winter collection.
Who cares about clothes!?
We're supposed to be on
an adventure together!
Uh oh.
That. Is. It! This "Day of
Fun" is officially OVER!
Fine by ME! Maybe I can spend
some time doing something
I actually like now!
Er.. heh heh heh.
Surely you don't mean that!
You're just having
a little.. disagreement!
Sometimes that happens between
pals. But no matter what,
they can always get past the
problem and stay good friends!
I don't think we can.
You don't care about any
of the things I like!
It's always about you
and your boring fashions.
Oh, Please! You don't even
give my interests a chance!
You have absolutely no
respect for the finer things.
NO RESPECT, I tell you!
[both]
I guess we're just
NOT FRIENDS ANYMORE!
Oh!
And then there was the
time Rainbow Dash
called my Cloudsdale
Couture Boutique idea
"impractical"! Imagine that.
Just because I'd
needed Twilight
to perform the Butterfly
Wing spell on me
whenever I wanted to
deliver merchandise.
And I told her a thousand
times Pegasi don't even want
restrictive, heavy dresses! We
need to be able to fly. Duh.
Not to mention the day I was
wearing a really gorgeous hat
and Rainbow Dash
didn't even notice!
The Wonderbolts
show was RUINED!
Rarity's hat was blocking
everypony's view!
ENOUGH!
Guidance counseling is for
talking out your problems,
not telling me everything
that's ever happened
in the history of Equestria!
But I've learned sometimes
talking isn't enough.
You need to put yourselves
in one another's shoes.
No way am I wearing those.
[groan]
What I'm saying is,
we need a way to help you
two reconnect. Follow me!
The library? And
this helps us how?
You both love books!
Rainbow Dash never
stops talking about
Daring Do adventures.
And you're a huge fan of
Shadow Spade mysteries.
Your point?
The perfect way for you
two to reconnect as friends
is to read each
other's favorite book.
I'll read them, too! Then
we'll all discuss afterward.
It'll be a "Good
Friends Book Club"! OK?
I'll bring snacks..
Ugh, fine.
If you insist.
Great! We're all here! To
start, why don't you two
share one thing you liked
about each other's books?
OK, I'll go first! Erm.. I
really enjoyed the part in
"Daring Do and the
Razor of Dreams"
when Daring used a vicious
Cragadile as a raft and then--
Please!
Uh, what's so funny?
Uh sorry, it's just that I
find those action sequences
so ridiculously
over-the-top.
But they're real.. you've
even met Daring Do!
Yes, but the book's
descriptions just drag on.
And what about all those
silly, unpronounceable names?
Doctor whozit, whatsit...
Cab-a-YAIR-on?
CAB-A-LER-ON! Just like it
looks! How hard is that?
Uh tea, anypony?
Cucumber sandwich? Heh..
Or we could go over some nice,
friendly talking points!
Hah! Seriously? Don't
even get me started
on those clothing
descriptions in Shadow Spade!
What a yawn fest!
B-But... the outfit
descriptions are an integral part of the plot
of "The Colt in Crimson:
A Shadow Spade Mystery"!
You see, if you
didn't know
that Sir Fluffingsworth
von Radishfield
wears only silk,
double-breasted waistcoats,
you'd never deduce that
he, in fact, was the culprit!
Wait, he was?
[gasp] You didn't
even read it!
I can see I'm gonna
need reinforcements.
Not my fault it's so
boring it put me to sleep.
If you can't be bothered
to read the thing I like,
that just further
illustrates the point
that we have nothing
in common anymore!
At least we agree on
that! From now on,
I'm only hanging out
with ponies who "get" me.
Your drama can wait!
Twilight needs help, now!
Any luck?
No! It's GONE!
What's gone?
The Amulet of Aurora.
Agh! One of the magical items
you've been keeping
for Princess Celestia?
That amulet can reverse the
tides and summon tsunamis!
If it falls into the
wrong hooves,
Equestria will be
in grave danger!
Don't worry, Twilight!
I know tons about searching
for lost treasure!
And if I follow the
culprit's clues,
I'm certain I can find
who took your amulet!
Thank you! I'll
feel so much better
knowing you two are
looking for it.. together!
While WE work on
a locator spell!
It's the perfect solution!
There appear to be
no signs of damage
to the surrounding
artifacts,
suggesting the thief
did not leave in a hurry.
RARITY! Your boots are leaving
sparkles all over the floor!
Pfft. Those aren't from my
boots. Mine are magenta,
not blue. See?
I mean, really!
Turns out these boots were
not "made for trotting",
as advertised.
Uch!
Where are you going?
We promised Twilight we'd work together!
Don't you see?
The Amulet of Aurora is
made out of Azurantium!
Azurantium? You know,
the same metal
that the Amulet of Atonement
from Daring Do Book
4 is made from?
It always leaves sparkles
wherever it goes!
Just like this. Remember? It's
from the book you JUST READ?
[nervous chuckle]
That book yes. The one I - I just read. Heh.
Seriously? After giving
me all that grief,
you didn't read
mine either!?
Oopsie?
Grrr. As soon as we find this
amulet, we are DONE with each other!
Fine by me!
Oooh!
Rainbow Dash, slow down!
You're flying past important clues!
It's a print, but
definitely not a hoof.
Are those claw marks?
Who cares? I found
a bigger clue.
I hope you don't
expect me to...
[shudder] WADE through that.
Nah, it's too deep.
We'll get stuck.
Ooh clever! What Daring Do book
did you get that from?
Actually, I learned it at
Scootaloo's Filly Guides camp.
Ach. At least you can fly across...
Nope! If one of those geysers
burns off my wingfeathers,
I'll be out of the
Wonderbolts for weeks.
[sigh] I could try and
slingshot my way through,
but I'd need two
perfectly placed trees,
some stretchy rope,
and a pith helmet.
Hm..
Too bad we can't
do what Daring Do did
in book 4 and find a
Cragadile for a raft.
Ta da! The SS Cragadile,
at your service.
Uh. That. Is... Awesome!
I-I mean... it's all
right. I guess.
How did you know
how to do that?
Hm! We may have been friends
"for a super long time",
but you don't know
EVERYTHING about me yet!
[gasp] The glitter trail! It's gone!
How are we supposed to find
the Amulet of Aurora now!?
[very quietly] Ow, ears!
Why hoof-hoofs yell?
Too-too loud.
Sorry, what did you say?
I think it's a Bufogren! They
have really sensitive ears.
[whispering] Did you happen to
see anycreature
with a sparkly
thingy go this way?
Saw it.
Gah!
Hold that thought.
His breath smells so
bad I can't think!
But we can't hear him
from back here. Now what?
Hmm.
Aha! I think I have
the perfect solution.
An old unicorn beauty trick.
That is, if you can somehow
procure us a tiny
bit of cloud?
Now that! I can do!
Oooh! It's adorable!
[nasal] Uh. Excuse me, kind sir.
I have a special
treat for you
in exchange
for your information.
Uhm. What's that?
It is a magical
Unicorn delicacy
called "Effervescence".
Very now, very chic.
Ooow!
Sorry. Sorry. Enjoy!
Mmmmm. Mm.
Muh mouth. Fresh and minty.
Ah! Good! Now which way did
the sparkly thing go?
Up-up! Up there.
Thank you!
Well, what are you
waiting for? Go on!
Fly up there and
get that amulet!
Uh.. we're doing this
together, remember?
But how can we? Oh!
Sorry, but I wasn't leaving
you behind in that swamp.
[gasp] Thank you.
Huh... maybe the key to
unlocking this thing
is in these inscriptions.
Or.. perhaps the
key is right here!
I couldn't decide between
the boots and the stilettos,
so I got both.
High heels can
do that!?
And you called
them useless..
I shouldn't have said that. Or
made fun of the other stuff
you like to do. Some of
it's actually sorta neat.
I owe you an apology, too.
Buckball may not be my thing,
but it's something you enjoy.
And you're very good at it!
I never should have
treated your interests
like they were worth
less than mine.
So... does this mean
we're still friends?
I would very
much like that.
Now let's go find
that amulet!
Yeah! Ha ha!
Wait. That tunnel
leads to the SCHOOL?
A secret passage!
AWESOME!
[gasp] Spikey-Wikey, you
stole the Amulet of Aurora!?
Twilight: Not exactly.
You mean... this was a
setup to make us get along?
Sorry to interfere,
but you both--
Reaaally needed it.
So even though you don't like
any of the same stuff,
you two are friends again?
Heh. Always. I think we just
needed a teensy reminder.
Yeah. We don't have to
love the exact same things
to have fun together. I
mean, imagine if we did!
How boring would that be?
When we give each other
a chance to share the
different things
we enjoy, it can be
surprisingly wonderful!
Ah. Too bad we wasted
our Day of Fun.
We still have a
little time left!
You wanna... go hit the shops?
I could actually
use your help
picking out some
new Buckball gear!
DO I?
But... only if you help me choose
some Buckball fan attire,
so I can cheer for
my favorite player
at the drop of a fabulous hat.
Uh, YEAH! Let's go already!
See? Good friends always work
through their differences.
[chuckle] Even if it takes
a little help.