♪ Ponies' voices
fill the night ♪
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve is
here once again. ♪
Come on everycreature, sing!
♪ La la la la la
La la la la la la la ♪
[hesitantly]
♪ la la la ♪
Not everycreature celebrate
same way, you know.
Yeah. Dragons don't
do pony holidays.
Spike: Sure we do!
I LOVE Hearth's
Warming Eve.
It's all about friends,
and presents, and family,
and.. presents!
It's also about putting aside
differences to come together,
like the Earth ponies, pegasi,
and unicorns did
on the first holiday.
Oh! Is that why you put
their fire of friendship
on top of the tree?
To help us remember
their unity?
AND 'cause it looks cool.
This is my favorite
day of the year!
Not that I don't
like the other ones.
Tuesdays are great!
Yona like any day that
is start of Winter Break.
Two whole weeks
without classes.
How will Ocellus survive?
Heheh..
I think you'll all
enjoy the time off
to be home with
your families.
To celebrate your
own traditions.
Attention, everycreature!
School is officially out!
Happy Holidays,
and we'll see you
after the break.
And for those of you
traveling outside Equestria...
Yeah, shouldn't you guys
be getting ready to go?
If you miss that train,
it's a really long walk.
Go pack up, and we'll
take you to the station.
It's that new bowtie
I wanted, isn't it?
You'll have
to wait and see!
I'm waiting!
But in the meantime,
I'm shaking.
Wh--what happened?
Everything's ruined;
that's what's happened!
And I don't think
it was an accident!
Somepony was up here!
Over there!
Outside!
That's the Students' Quarters!
Might as well
give up, whoever you are!
We got ya
cornered!
Hello?
Is anypony there?
I'll check the
back door!
What's happening?
[gasp] Another decorating party!?
Has anycreature come in here?
Well... yeah.
All of us did.
To pack?
Like you told us to?
After that.
Did you hear
anything?
Uh uh.
What's up?
Yona done packing!
Is something wrong?
The back door's locked.
No way out!
But whoever did it had
to have come in here.
We saw them!
Whoever did what ?
Whoa... That...
Is so not cool.
And whoever did it
ran into your rooms.
No one came out. And all
of you are still here.
One of you must have done this!
But why would any of you wanna
sabotage Hearth's Warming Eve?
Uh! Yak not do this.
Yona offended by accusation.
We don't know what happened.
Maybe this wasn't
even on purpose.
But I want to give
whoever caused this mess
a chance to tell the truth
and explain themselves.
I'll make it easy for you.
Close your eyes.
Now, if you did this,
raise your hoof.
Or claw.
Or whatever.
C'mon, Spike.
Looks like we have to--
Spike. You can
open your eyes.
What? Oh!
Er.. what about me?
You ALL can.
Heh heh!
But since nocreature took
responsibility for this mess,
you're ALL gonna have
to help clean it up
before you can go home.
Why do I have to stay?
Aw! But the holidays!
While you're cleaning,
we'll bring you into my
office one at a time.
Since Honesty is one of
the Elements of Harmony,
we want to give you each a
chance to tell us the truth.
And once we find out who
did it, just you wait!
We're gonna--we'll...
What are we gonna
do exactly?
[sigh] The guilty party
won't be going home
over Hearth's
Warming Break.
She or he will stay here
for some one-on-one
friendship lessons.
But what if none
of us confesses?
Then...
I guess there's no
holidays for anycreature.
You'll all stay
over the break.
All right, let's get
to the bottom of this.
Who wants to be
interviewed first?
Eh. I'll go.
Beats mop duty.
Hey, I know!
We can make a
game out of this!
See who finishes
cleaning up first!
Whoo hoo!
Yak win!
Yak best at cleaning!
Let's save time and
cut to the chase.
Which one of you did it?
I would never do
something this horrible!
I love Hearth's
Warming Eve!
And I do NOT want to
miss going home for it.
Huh. I didn't even know Changelings
celebrated Hearth's Warming.
Oh, yes!
It's our favorite holiday!
Well, since Headmare Twilight
shared it with us last year.
She gave our hive very
clear instructions.
[ahem]
"Welcome to the traditions
and fun of Hearth's Warming!
Here's a guide to help you
enjoy this celebration
of pony history.
Families start the holidays
by putting the tree up!"
"Thirsty?
Dive into some Holiday Punch!"
"Just before bed, everypony
exchanges gifts."
It doesn't say how long
we keep doing this.
"And to finish celebrating,
you can build a fire.
Light it up.
And sing carols."
♪ Carols
carols carols carols ♪
You might have misunderstood
things just a little.
Eh, we may not have
done everything
exactly the way you do.
But we made our
own traditions!
And I can't wait to do
it all again this year!
If we ever get out of here.
Ocellus? Your turn.
What happened?
What do you think happened?
I told her I didn't do it.
Agh! Yona tired
of waiting.
Yaks ALWAYS home
for holidays.
How do you celebrate Hearth's
Warming in Yakyakistan, Yona?
Yaks do not.
Our holiday MUCH better.
Is called "Snilldar
Fest." Night before,
yaks gather things to smash,
and put them in big pile.
Then in morning,
we smash them!
In afternoon, we smash them
again. In evening--
So.. it's just about
smashing stuff.
Like all your
other holidays.
No! How griffon
get that idea?
This holiday about
so much more.
Last year, for
example.
Most perfect
Snilldar ever...
Whole family.
Grandpa Grandma Yak,
Yona's Brother Sister
Mother Father Yak.
All go to woods,
singing Yak Song.
♪ Yak song! Yak song!
Not very long! Sing again! ♪
Calves in family pick
out perfect Smashing Log.
Then Yaks smash it.
Then Yak Family build perfect
snow fort... and smash it!
Then we hang perfect things
on perfect moss pile, and...
[All] You smash it.
What you think Yaks
are, barbarians?
Moss pile is for
special family rituals.
Last year, ritual for Yona.
All Yak family
gather around Yona.
And braid Yona hair
for first time.
So to recap... your holiday
is about smashing things,
and family.
Two most perfect things
ever, put together.
Happy Snilldar Fest!
Happy Snilldar to
you too, Yona.
It's so cool to learn new
traditions from new friends!
Yeah, well one of
these "new friends"
has gotten us
all in trouble.
And they'd better
confess soon.
Ocellus: Sandbar?
Sorry, but they said they
want you to go in next.
Why the rush to
get home, Smolder?
Like you said, dragons don't
really have holidays, do they?
Meh.
[gasp] That's so sad!
You must do something
in the winter for fun.
Well, we do have
"The Feast of Fire".
Every dragon gets together
and tells stories.
The best one wins a
pile of gemstones.
Ooh! What story won last year?
It was called "A
Dream Come True."
Come on, now you've
gotta tell it!
Uh. Fine.
Once upon a time, there was
this sad little dragon.
Her name was Scales.
She lived alone in
the wilderness with
nothing to eat.
But one night, as she sat
alone in a storm, she
heard something.
It was the Dragon Lord!
Scales was scared, but the
Dragon Lord told her
not to be afraid; that he was
taking her to the Dragon Lands
for a great feast.
Scales sat with the Dragon
Lord's family and friends and
had the biggest, best dinner
of gemstones she'd ever eaten.
Then, while the dragons
were telling stories,
Scales thought it would be
so easy to seize power
from this feeble and
sensitive Dragon Lord.
She saw her chance
and TOOK IT!
She claimed the
bloodstone scepter
and took over the
Dragon Lands.
Bwahahah!
...and forced the Dragon Lord
to live out in the cold
just as she used to do.
That's a horrible story!
Maybe to you..
But dragons like
hearing about weak,
kind creatures
getting defeated.
[Rainbow Dash] Silverstream!
You're up.
Let's go!
So, did you tell
them you did it?
What? No way!
Why would I say that?
You already live
in Ponyville.
Staying here over
break is no big deal.
School of Friendship good place
for pony to have pony holiday.
I'd still rather spend it
with my family at home.
Oh! That reminds me!
I have the BEST
holiday story ever!
It's called "The Day My
Hearth's Warming Doll
Almost Fell into the Fire!"
[All] Ohhhhh!
Just before we went to
bed, my mom, my dad,
and my sister all put our
Hearth's Warming Dolls
up on the mantle, just
like we do every year.
But THIS year...
I put my doll too close
to the edge and it FELL!
[slowly] NOOOOOOO!
And!?
My doll hit the floor.
BUT! It could have
gone in the fire!
That's a great story.
And you told it
really well.
Yeah. It was a Hearth's
Warming miracle!
Next!
Smolder, come with me.
Yona, Twilight's
waiting for you.
The last two.
So if neither one of them
confesses, that means...
We're never going home!
We'll be here forever!
Beyond forever.
But I can't miss the Three
Days of Freedom Celebration!
How long does that last?
It used to be only ONE day, but
now to commemorate our escape
from the Storm King,
we're adding two more
days of awesome!
See!
There's a book?
Mm hm! Queen Novo had these
made for the Mt. Aris
board of tourism. To
explain it all to guests!
We'll spend the first
night in Seaquestria,
thanking the ocean
for protecting us
from the Storm King.
Sea-dancing, whale-singing,
shell-stringing...
Lots of "ings."
The second day will
be on Mt. Aris,
with sky dancing,
and a wind song
in the Harmonizing Heights
to celebrate the Storm
King's defeat.
Then the third day,
everycreature will party
together, on land AND sea.
Grandparents and parents
and sisters, uncles,
brothers, acquaintances,
neighbours and cousins.
And at the end of the night,
Queen Novo is going to
give out presents!
Wait. Hold on. Cousins?
What are those?
Your aunt's and
uncle's children?
You know, part of your family.
Heh. Oh, you're teasing
us again, right?
I'm guessing neither
one of you confessed.
Headmare Twilight
say wait here.
Maybe they're changing their
minds about sending us home.
Why would they?
Face it. We're stuck here.
But, but, I
HAVE to go home!
My mom makes the
best kelp fritters.
How can you be so
cool about this?
We're mad.
We just show it
differently.
More like you don't
show it at all.
What pony getting at?
Maybe it wasn't
just one prankster.
Maybe there were
three of you!
And you're trying to hide
your guilt by not being upset!
It does make sense..
Guys, stop it.
Or maybe whoever did it is
only pretending to be upset.
To throw us off.
Me? But I didn't!
Come on, let it go.
Come on, Ocellus,
you know you did it!
Just fess up!
I SAID stop fighting!
That's not what the
holidays are about.
No matter what you call
them, or how you celebrate.
Do you know how
lucky you all are?
With your stories about
sharing, and kindness,
and getting together
with everycreature
that you care about?
But... Griffons do
that too, don't they?
Some holiday
about a moon?
[sigh] Blue Moon Festival.
The one time of year
when Griffons are nice to each other.
Well, as nice as we can be.
Families get together to
eat and then complain
about the food.
And give each other
presents they don't like.
And mostly just try not
to yell at each other.
Well, at least you get
to be with your family!
No...
Because I don't have a family.
Sandbar: What about
Grandpa Gruff?
Gallus: That's just his name.
He's not anygriff's
actual grandpa.
I felt like I never had
a place in Griffonstone.
Then I came here,
and well, met all of you.
So I don't want to
go home for the break.
And that's why... I did it!
[gasp] Griffon mess
up decorations?
Yeah....
It was me.
I put goo powder in
the Fire of Friendship.
So it wasn't Ocellus?
Why would you ruin
things for us?
I didn't plan to!
I just figured if I
made a mess,
our teachers would make
us stay to clean up.
We'd be together
a little longer.
Well. It worked, didn't it?
Better than I thought.
When Headmare Twilight
threatened to cancel
winter break, that
meant I would get to
be with all of you,
through the entire holiday!
That's why I didn't confess.
So why are you
admitting this now?
I hated seeing all you fighting
and blaming each other.
That's the opposite of what
ALL your holidays mean.
Except maybe yours, Smolder.
I can't keep all of you from
the happiness of your homes
and families just
because I feel bad.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, you won't
have to tell our teachers.
I will.
Twilight: You don't have to.
We already know.
We kinda guessed
it was you.
But we wanted to give you
the chance to tell the truth.
I'm proud that you did.
And I'm glad to see you've
been paying attention
in Professor Applejack's
honesty classes.
But you're still gonna
have to make amends.
And stay over break for
extra friendship lessons,
by yourself.
I'll stay with him.
Me, too!
Yona stay also!
I'm staying!
What?
All right.
I guess pony holidays
can't be that bad.
Now you can finally
know what it's like
to spend Hearth's Warming with
friends who care about you.
Looks like they don't really
need any extra lessons.
Since you obviously know
that Hearth's Warming
is about coming
together, I'd be honored
if all of you would
join my friends as guests
at our holiday table.
After we finish cleaning up.
Hey, this reminds
me of another story!
The Time I Almost Spilled
Grape Juice on the White Couch.
Does it have a
depressing ending?
I'm not sure pony
stories work that way.
Um. Gallus want Yona
braid feathers?
Uuuh. Pass.
♪ Hearth's Warming Eve is
here Once Again! ♪