I don't know, folks.
She's been in
there a long time..
Do you suppose the
Terrifying Trunk Escape
is too much for her?
What if the Great and Powerful
Trixie can't--
Escape..?
But if you're there,
who's in here!?
Why, our volunteer of course!
Crab-apple surprise!
You should oughta tell a pony
before you go a-poofing 'em
around a stage!
Trixie, that was
an amazing show!
Flurry Heart and I loved it.
I'm so glad we decided to come.
You two have a real chemistry.
The Terrifying
Trunk Escape
does require a great and
powerful assistant.
The way you two worked together,
it's like you've known each
other as long as
Twilight and I have.
It was pretty fun.
Of course, it was!
There's nothing better than
a bond with another pony.
You can share all
kinds of things.
♪ Sunshine, sunshine,
ladybugs awake. ♪
♪ Clap your hooves and
do a little shake! ♪
I think we'll stick to
the stage magic for now.
The great and powerful
Trixie doesn't chant.
As much as I love
my one-pony show,
it's always nice to
come to Ponyville
and perform with my great
and powerful assistant.
Cadance is right! We
do work well together.
Doing a show with you is almost
as much fun as counseling
students at Twilight's school--
[gasp] -which I'm supposed
to be doing right now!
See ya later!
Excuse me,
Ms. Powerful?
Heh heh! Usually ponies
just call me Trixie,
but Ms. Powerful
has a nice ring!
From here to Saddle Arabia,
I have seen nothing
that compares with
your wondrous show.
Would you consider blessing
my homeland with it?
I was just about to
set out on tour... ugh..
but Saddle Arabia is much
farther than my usual route--
Heh heh.
--and uh, my caravan might not
be suited for an extended tour.
Mine is new and
quite spacious.
If it would help
persuade you,
I would happily trade
it for yours.
Trade it? Heavens no!
This is more than just some
great and powerful wagon
you see before you.
It is shelter.
It is transportation.
It is my only friend in the long
and lonely nights on the road!
Very well, then I must see as
many of your performances
as I can. If I
cannot convince you
to bring your tour
to Saddle Arabia,
I must be prepared to
relate its magnificence
to your many fans there.
Many fans, you say?
Well, I suppose I could
consider the trip.
Wonderful!
I look forward to
seeing you on the road.
And if you change your
mind about the caravans,
my offer remains open.
Hmmm..
It's just so far away!
Of course, I love visiting
new and exciting places,
I am a traveling
magician after all.
Hmm. Sounds like
your mind's made up.
Not quite.
The road is a lonely place,
and this trip even more so.
I was hoping I might convince my
great and powerful assistant
to come along.
Really?
Of course!
You're not just my assistant
and my counselor,
you're also my friend,
and what's better
than a road trip with friends?
Nothing!
This will be the best
magical road trip ever!
I should probably get somepony
to cover my student counseling
duties while we're gone..
Trixie, are you all right?
One caravan for two all set!
Oh, you brought luggage.
Heh. I mean, of course
you brought luggage!
You bet I did.
Everything two ponies need for
the road trip of their lives!
Three one-thousand piece
puzzles, one copy of Dragon Pit,
the best board game in
the history of ponies,
my famous collection of campfire
spices and an inflatable raft.
Did I forget something?
I can pop back to the
castle and grab it.
Oh, no. It isn't that...
Yeah... Maybe we
don't need the raft.
Ah! We just
needed a little
great and powerful
reorganization!
Now... everything...
Fits... Just...
Fine!
Ugh. Who am I kidding?
My wagon is too small for us.
I understand if you're
having second thoughts.
Second thoughts?
Are you kidding?
This wagon isn't
small, it's.... cozy.
And there's no such
thing as too cozy!
Well all right, then!
I guess it's time
to hit the road!
I'll-- start us off...
OK, maybe there is such
a thing as too cozy.
You're sure you
wouldn't rather ride?
I'm sure.
And you're not backing out?
The two of us sleeping in that
"cozy" caravan could get tricky.
Trixie, there's plenty
of high-quality inns
to stay at on the way.
Don't worry about it.
I am not backing out of the
greatest and most powerful
road trip bonding experience
two ponies could ever have!
Well, when you put it like that,
I'm actually kind of excited!
Me too. Ah!
Thank goodness we're not
Twilight or the others.
They'd probably sing
a song about it.
♪ [big band swing] ♪
♪ We're off on the
road to friendship. ♪
♪ Our ride might be
tiny and small ♪
Beats walking though, eh Trix?
I am walking.
♪ But road trips are
a great way, ♪
♪ we've been told,
to get along ♪
♪ I'm glad we're sticking to
it, we've already got a song. ♪
♪ We're off on the
road to friendship ♪
♪ Side by side just
like peas in a pod ♪
♪ Our bond of friendship ♪
♪ is stronger than
this tour's demands. ♪
My offer to trade
caravans still stands.
Wait, what did he say?
Nothing!
♪ We're so tight
we can't move around ♪
♪ I guess we're stuck together
cause we're friendship-bound. ♪
Sure is great travelling
with you, Buddy!
You too, Buddy!
♪♪
♪ We're off on the
road to friendship ♪
Yup we are!
♪ We've each got the
other to blame. ♪
♪ Any trip can be exhausting
if you make a fuss. ♪
♪ But we get on so
well, that there's no
way that could be us! ♪
♪ We're off on the
road to friendship. ♪
♪ And there's nowhere
that we'd rather be. ♪
Was that off key?
♪ In summer, winter,
spring and fall ♪
♪ we're friends
throughout the year. ♪
♪ For untold seasons
yet to come ♪
♪ our friendship
will be here! ♪
For nine, at least.
♪ We're so tight we
can't move around. ♪
Like a race where you tie
your hooves together
and have to move in perfect
synchronization to win.
♪ We're friendship bound. ♪
Or, like a buddy movie where the
two protagonists can't get away
from each other because
they're wearing hoofcuffs!
♪ We're friendship bound! ♪
Oh! The marketplace.
Perfect.
I've learned the hard way that
life on the road requires very
specific supplies and we
only have so many bits,
so we'll have to
spend them wise-ly.
Heh. Sorry about wasting
bits on street food.
Oh, it's fine!
Falafel Bonding, right?
Besides, we still
have enough for...
haycakes and juice.
Um... why don't
we go there?
Oh, no no no.
I always buy my
haycakes here.
So, we're just going to wait
in line for hours...
uh.. which is totally cool!
Waiting In Line Bonding, right?
After our falafel purchase,
we weren't able to get
everything on my list,
but we are definitely
set for breakfast.
And I'm sure we'll find
out that waiting in that
super long line
was worth it.
A few hiccups always happen;
we'll be back on the road
to friendship after a
good night's sleep.
We're all full!
I-I'm sure we'll find something.
Nope.
Sorry.
All full.
Ah, the Glowpaz Festival.
Somnambula is no doubt
filled to the brim.
Luckily, travelers such as
ourselves have our caravans.
Heh heh.
You said there'd be
plenty of places to stay.
"Don't even worry
about it," you said.
You might have thought
to make a reservation.
Um... I've been with you
singing and standing in line.
When would I have done that?
I don't know, but I'm starting
to think you aren't as great
and powerful an
assistant as I thought.
So, you just brought me
along to do your legwork!?
[sigh] No. Of course not.
I'm sorry.
I'm just frustrated!
I was really looking forward to
a relaxing night in a nice room.
[sigh] Me too, but since there's
literally no room at the inns,
I guess it's lucky
we've got the wagon.
Sleeping In Tight
Quarters Bonding...
Yaaaay.
Is there something I can do
to make things more
comfortable for you?
You could get rid of this junk.
Yes, well, before we throw away
the magical items it's taken me
years to collect, we could
try switching hammocks.
Fine!
Ah!
Starlight?
Starlight!
I think there's a
wild animal outside!
Starlight!?
STARLIGHT!
Wha...? Huh?
WHAT?
I'm sorry.
Your snoring is a bit...
Loud? Heh heh.
Yeah. I do that.
I had my village convinced
we were being attacked
by bears every night. Heh.
[ahem] But we probably need a
better solution here.
[sleepily] Ladies and gentleponies!
The Great and Powerful
Trixie will now...
Seriously!?
Prepare to be
amazed....!
Sleep well?
Sure did.
Is uh, that the last
of the hay cakes?
Oh. yeah. Sorry.
It's fine.
I don't suppose
there's.. more juice?
[glug glug] Ah!
I guess we'll have
to re-supply.
What a glorious
morning!
I can't tell you how much
I am looking forward
to the first show
of your tour.
Is he going to be following
us for the whole time?
I do not know.
She's been in there a long time...
Do you suppose the Terrifying
Trunk Escape is too much for a
pony who drinks all the JUICE
and talks nonstop in her sleep!?
What if the Great and Powerful
Trixie can't--
Sleep because her roommate
snores like an Ursa Major?
But if you're there,
who's in here?
There's not much
room in here.
At least you don't have to
sleep in it with another PONY!
This show was much
better in Ponyville..
Oh! Would you like
the last carrot?
I know how fond you are of
eating the last of things.
Oh, no. It might
make me thirsty
and we don't have
anything to drink, so...
The good news is I'm so
exhausted I could sleep
through a stampede
of WILD boars,
which you'll be
delighted to know
is only slightly louder
than your snoring.
Well, I'm looking forward
to rehearsing the act
with you all night.
So diligent of you to go over
it and over it in your sleep.
Practice makes perfect.
Not today, it didn't.
Well, I'm sorry
you're so miserable!
Really!? Because if you wanted to
make things more comfortable,
you could always
pare down a bit!
Well, since you're so
concerned about space,
you can have it all!
I'll sleep under the stars where
at least the wild animals
will be QUIETER THAN YOU!
I do not mean to interrupt, but
it seems there is trouble
on the road to friendship.
Ha ha ha ha. Ya think?
WHERE'S MY WAGON!?
I traded it to that pony
from Saddle Arabia for his!
He even threw in
a pair of robes!
♪ [horror sting] ♪
YOU WHAT?
I traded the old, worn-out wagon
that was too small for us
for this nice, new, spacious
one that we can both enjoy.
BUT [spluttering] WHO SAID
YOU COULD DO THAT?
Nopony. I just did it.
Ah! Now we both have
plenty of room
and you didn't even have
to give anything away.
Au contraire!
I DID give something away!
I gave away my wagon,
and my best friend.
Oh, I'm sorry!
I didn't realize you
were better friends
with that beat-up old wagon
than you are with me.
Well, it's easy when the
wagon is a better friend.
It would have NEVER
traded you away!
That's ridiculous.
Oh, it is ridiculous.
In fact, this whole
tour is ridiculous.
I don't even know why I
invited you in the first place!
Well! Maybe I should
just head home!
I think that's a
very good idea.
And you can take this horrible,
giant caravan WITH YOU!
Fine!
Good!
Goodness! Ms. Powerful.
But where is
your assistant?
I had hoped providing you
with a more comfortable
means of conveyance would
allow you to once more
dazzle the crowds with
mystifying feats of magic!
Normally, that sort of
flattery would suffice,
but today we must discuss your
dishonest and unfair procurement
of my wagon!
I desired your wagon and
provided one of equal
or better value in return.
It seems like a perfectly
honest and fair trade to me.
Unfortunately, it is
more nuanced than that!
I'm sure it is, but I
am eager to set out.
If you'll excuse me.
I am willing to wait
as long as you are.
Hah! We'll just see about that!
You know, even if I was
willing to reverse the trade,
you don't have my caravan
to offer in return.
Ooh! Details!
You all seemed...
a lot less threatening
when there were two of us!
Ah!
This place is awful!
How did I not see it before?
Hey! It's one of those
traveling ponies!
Your song really
inspired us!
We decided we need to head off
on the road to friendship too.
It sure beats the
road to deliveries!
Yep. Sometimes traveling
together is hard.
You reminded us you
can also make it fun!
Thanks again!
Whoo hoo!
Steaming hot beverage?
Thank you, no.
What are you two doing?
Taking a stand!
By lying down!
Not that you care,
wagon trader-awayer!
I'm afraid I'm still
not interested,
despite your assistant's
convenient appearance.
Trixie, I came
back to apologize.
I should never have
traded away the wagon.
It wasn't mine to trade!
It belongs to my friend.
Hmmm. If you truly
were friends,
I suppose I'd be honor-bound
to reverse the trade.
OK. Fine, we're friends.
Best friends who
share a deep bond,
but weren't prepared for
the emotional challenges
of traveling. Happy?
I am still unconvinced.
Perhaps you could
prove your friendship.
How!?
Er... we could do our
friendship chant.
Oh, right...
Our world famous
"Chant of Friendship"!
That we do all the time because
we're such great friends.
[making it up as they go]
Mmmagic, tri--mmagic.
Poo-uff of sma-oke,
Wondu-wave your hoof-ooves
and tal-ell a
lo-ittle jawww-oke!
Ha ha!
That was the worst friendship
chant I have ever heard
and you two were clearly
making it up as you went.
But! Only true friends
would be willing
to act so ridiculous
for one another.
So you'll give back
the wagon?
Though, I'd suggest
heading back to Ponyville.
I'm not sure Saddle
Arabia is ready for..... this.
That's fair.
I'm sorry your Saddle
Arabian tour was ruined.
Honestly, I don't think I could
have stood one more second
on the road.
At a certain point, I don't
even like traveling with myself.
It is a lot harder
than I thought.
Still, I'm glad we tried.
Mostly so we know
not to do it again.
I think it's made our
friendship greater
and more powerful than ever!
You know, there's actually
plenty of room in here
for a one-pony nap.
Is the show over?