♪♪
The Tree of Harmony remains one
of the most powerful sources
of magic known to ponydom.
And though it has been at the
"root" of Magic and Friendship
from the moment it was planted,
its ways are mysterious.
Almost as if it has
a mind of its own.
Mind? Pfft. It's a tree.
A tree that grew
a castle!
Was that before or after
Discord made chocolate rain?
[whisper] After.
I'm never going to
learn Pony history!
[bell rings]
You can all show me what you've
learned on tomorrow's test!
Friendship's effect on the
course of Equestrian History.
[groans]
Remember, study groups are
both fun AND effective!
Sandbar: So.. who wants to
study together?
With other students?
This is Equestria!
If you want the real scoop,
there's only one place to go!
Hello, oh magical
Equestrian tree!
Can you tell me everything I
need to know about friendship?
[groan]
[laughter]
♪♪
The Elements of Harmony
grew the tree?
[sigh] No. The pillars
grew the tree.
The tree grew the elements. And
then the box with six locks.
But our professors
found six keys
and unlocked
the box.
I'm so gonna fail..
You guys! Check
this out!
That's a plumbing diagram
on how to fix a sink.
[giddy giggles]
What does that have to do
with Equestrian History?
Nothing. I just can't believe
that's how sinks work!
Where's Yona?
[loud snoring]
[chuckle] Apparently, yaks no
love study groups!
Shhhh. Haha.
[snoring]
SPIDER! NO!
[laughter]
Hey Cozy. What are
you doing here?
I volunteered to help Professor
Sparkle organize these books.
So? Experts on
Friendship History yet?
I think I'd be better off
studying the plumbing book.
This stuff is impossible.
[whoosh]
Oh, come on, Gallus! With good
friends and solid study habits,
anything is possible!
[laughing]
How about you just tell us
what's on tomorrow's
test, Professor?
Yeah! Please! Come on!
Now hold on a sec. I can't
give y'all a sneak peek!
That there wouldn't be honest!
[hooting laughter]
Ahem. Golly, it's so inspiring how
relaxed you all are about
studying friendship
considering your disadvantage.
What cute pony mean?
Just consider where
you all came from!
If Sandbar hadn't sacrificed
so much of his time
to get you up to speed? Who
knows how behind you'd be?
That's not--
I mean, growing up as a
love-starved changeling!
Or hiding underwater from an
evil king all those years!
Trusting any creature
must be so hard for you!
And Griffons never want
to be around any creature.
Even other griffons!
And dragons are so
fierce compared to us.
There must be days you
can't wait to get away
from all us cute ponies.
Everypony know "yaks
think yaks are best".
Making friends with
any other creature
must seem like a step down.
It's just so impressive
how you keep trying
to understand friendship,
even though it isn't
in your nature.
Oh! I'll let you borrow my
notes! It's what friends do!
I'll be right back!
We should get
back to studying...
[claws drumming on table]
[louder drumming]
Could you stop that clicking!?
I'm trying to focus.
Dude...
What? We have a test. I
don't know every detail
about every adventure the
professors went on like you do.
That's why we're
studying together.
Right. To help us
"disadvantaged" creatures.
Yona confused. Why
we all upset?
[clang]
I only glanced at
that plumbing book,
but I'm pretty sure this
isn't supposed to be here.
What are you doing?
Dragon. Strange Magical Cave.
What do you think I'm doing?
[squeeze]
♪♪
Did we know this was down here?
I don't think anypony
knows this is down here.
[echoing hooves]
Welcome.
Headmare Twilight?
Where are we?
Where you need to be.
Uh. Yona confused.
It is as I feared. You are not
one. What has happened?
We were studying Friendship's
effect on History but then...
Since friendship just isn't in
our nature, what's the point?
You do not believe
friendship is in your nature?
That is NOT ACCEPTABLE!
[rushing sound]
Our headmare is
glowing, you guys!
What is going on!?
We should probably get back
to studying for the test.
A test. Yes.
By sunrise, this
door will be closed.
Finish the test before
then and you may go.
Fail the test and
here you will stay.
[zap]
Huh?
[frightened whimper]
OH!
[splash]
Mt. Aris!?
Headmare Twilight
sent me home?
Wait. Am I suspended?
Hello?
Anygriff here?
Hmm.
They must be topside.
[growl]
Huh?
Oh!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Agh!
Ah!
[growl]
THE STORM KING?
He's BACK?
Big room. No exits.
Big deal.
[rumbling and cracking]
Not cool..
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Nothing for yaks
to be afraid of.
Just empty cave. Nothing
in here can hurt...
...Yona!
Ugh. Things like this just don't
happen in the Dragonlands.
-Huh?
-And I told her she was the
cutest pony of all ponies!
Oooh! Aren't you just
the most ADORABLE thing?
Come join us!
No. On so many levels, no.
[screeching brakes]
Huh?
Come sit by me and let's
compliment each other!
Agh!
[gasp] Why do you look
like that?
What do you mean?
We all look the same.
Not me.
Of course not you,
Your Majesty.
We'll go drain the love from
those pathetic ponies
in Ponyville just
as you ordered!
[gasp] NO!
Oh, thank HEAVENS
we've found you!
There's an emergency
and we need YOU, Sandbar!
Ah! My first friendship adventure!
Yes! Count me in!
I've been waiting
for this--
Wait. The others!
We don't need them!
We need you! Come on!
♪♪
[scrape]
[rumbling]
Come on, Gallus.
Get it together.
Deep breaths.
[breathing]
Ah...ah...ah choo!
[shattering rock]
[frightened whimpering]
OK, if this is a test,
there's got to be a way out.
It's just a puzzle...
that will squash you
if you don't
figure it out.
♪♪
[rumbling]
Ah ha!
No pressure.
[rumbling]
Oops!
[panting]
[rumbling]
[grunts]
Grrrr.
Look. I have to get out of here
and find my friends,
so just tell me what I have
to do to pass this test.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Um. I don't know.
Seems like she's afraid to be
cute and adorable, doesn't it?
Or maybe she's just
afraid to admit
she likes being
cute and adorable.
Mm hm.
Just this once.
[ahem] May I have
some tea, please?
Oh, but you can't have tea
if you aren't dressed for it!
OK. But let's keep
this between us.
♪♪
[giggle]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[panting]
[whimpering]
Ah!
[crash]
[scream]
[whimpering]
YONA NEED HELP!
WHERE YONA'S FRIENDS
WHEN YONA NEEDS THEM?
[scream]
Huh!?
[squeak]
Yona no mean to scream...
Yona love making friends.
Spiders... friends?
[squeak]
Wait. What little spider say?
[crackling]
What happened
to you?
What happened to you?
You never saw ANY
of that, got it?
[crackling]
Maybe the others got out
already and we're the last ones?
Yeah. That totally seems like
something they would do...
Hmph. Any other dragon or griffon
would save themselves
and get out of this crazy cave.
Guess we aren't just any
dragon and griffon anymore.
Guess not. You go that way.
I'll check over there.
♪♪
Wait. I really should
find my friends.
Darling, it was so generous
of you to take the time
to teach those other
creatures about friendship.
But.. if you're going to join us
and do something that really
makes a difference, we need to
know where your loyalty lies.
You do want to impress
us, don't you, Sandbar?
♪♪
[sobbing]
Huh?
Ocellus?
Go away.
We're still in those weird
caves beneath the school!
We've got to get out of here!
♪♪
[gasp] Chrysalis!
Where's Ocellus!?
[sob] It's me! I'm HIDEOUS!
[sobbing]
Hello!?
Where are--Whoa!
[splash]
SHHHHH! The Storm
King will hear you!
The Storm King?
He was defeated.
We're still under
the school.
This is all just
some crazy test!
[growling]
OK, that's horrifying.
I can't find any
hippogriffs or seaponies!
They must all be captured!
[splash]
Gallus! Get back down here!
[growling]
[growling then silence]
It's not real!
Yes, it is!
He's back and I'm never going
to see another sunset
or fly through a cloud
bank or study plumbing!
He's going to take
away everything I love...
I'm going to be trapped
down here forever!
I'm afraid of
being trapped too.
I'm scared of
small spaces.
Really?
Yeah...
And I was stuck in a
room that kept shrinking.
But I realized I had to face my
fear and I found the way out.
This is your test. He
isn't really here.
[growling]
But what if he is..!?
Then tell him exactly
what you think of him!
[zap]
H-h-hey!
Storm King!
You're nothing but
a big ole bully
with a silly name
and a goofy crown!
You thought you could scare us
into doing whatever you wanted!
But we learned that together
we're STRONGER than you!
And now that
we're rid of you,
we're gonna SOAR THROUGH THE
SKY and go on adventures
and NEVER GIVE YOU
ANOTHER THOUGHT. EVER!
[crash]
[shattering rock]
Haha!
I did it!
I told him!
OK, hug time later.
We still have to get
back to the library.
You're a changeling.
Just.. change back.
I can't.
[whoosh]
Maybe my past
was so horrible,
it's still inside me just
waiting to come out again!
That's ridiculous.
That's not who you are anymore.
You've changed.
Maybe we can't really
change THAT much.
[mumbling] I like cute, silly stuff!
I'm sorry, what?
I LIKE cute,
silly stuff!
But ever since school started,
I've realized that sometimes
I kinda don't mind cute stuff.
[shrill laughter]
If a dragon like me can
admit she likes... tea parties,
that's proof we
CAN change.
I was gonna invite you to a
top-secret tea party with me,
but if you want
to stay down here...
Oh, no! I wanna come!
[whoosh]
I thought that
might work.
Come on, let's go!
Where's Yona
and Sandbar?
The way out
is closing!
We aren't leaving
without them.
[scuttling]
YONA FIND YOU GUYS!
Argh!
Hey, Yona. Who's
your.. spider army?
Yona always scared of spiders
but then Yona meet Spindle!
[squeak]
Yona realize no
reason to be afraid!
Spiders and yak friends!
So Yona ask new friends for
help finding old friends!
Do you think your new friends
can help us find Sandbar?
[skittering]
Of all the strange things
that have happened tonight,
that's the strangest, right?
♪♪
OK. Enough!
I'm not going anywhere
without my friends.
So you don't care about
anypony but your friends?
Are you really
that selfish?
Honestly, you really are
such a disappointment.
I've always looked up to you.
You would never turn
your back on each other.
And that's what
makes you strong.
And now I have a group
of friends that I think
is every bit as
amazing as yours.
If I have to give up on
them to make you proud,
then you aren't the
ponies I thought you were.
I don't care if
I disappoint you.
You disappoint me.
[whoosh]
Did you just tell our professors
you were disappointed in them!?
Something tells me those
weren't actually our professors.
Besides, they tried to get
between me and my friends!
That's all very sweet.
Now can we please
get out of here?
[creaking]
You! You're not Headmare
Twilight, are you?
[gasp] You're the Tree
of Harmony!
The Tree of Harmony turned
into a sparkly version
of our headmare to talk to us?
Did I miss a chapter in class?
Like all living things,
I change as I grow.
As I have grown, so
have my abilities.
I'm a bit rusty
on Pony history,
but since when does the Tree
of Harmony trap creatures
in a cave with their
biggest fears!?
You chose what you saw
in my roots, not me.
[gasp] Our friendship got
us past our fears!
You were more concerned with
each other's well being
than your own.
You were strong when
your friends were weak.
You let each other in and
showed that you would be there
for each other,
no matter what.
Friendship IS in
your nature.
[whoosh]
[cracking]
We just learned a friendship
lesson from a tree, didn't we.
You're all right!
I came back with my
notes and saw this
and didn't know
what to think.
We're better than
all right!
We just got tested by
the Tree of Harmony!
And we totally passed!
The Tree of
Harmony? Here?
Yeah! Well. Below here.
Under the school!
We found this and went down and
met the Tree and Gallus was all
"friendship is NOT
in our nature"
and the tree was like WHAT!?
And it tested us!
Long story short.
Friendship IS in our nature.
The Tree said so.
I guess we should tell somepony
there's a giant magical hole
in the library.
[clang] Or not.
We have to tell our
professors about this!
They won't believe--
You can't!
Why no?
Because... it's my fault!
You were all getting
along so well
and I felt left out.
I was jealous.
And it upset you so much the
Tree of Harmony had to test you!
Oh! I'm gonna get
expelled for sure!
[sobbing] Please don't tell
anypony about this!
Especially the Professors!
PLEASE! PLEASE! PLEASE!
OK!
[yawn] I'm actually too tired
to do anything right now.
Yeah. But we can't
go to sleep.
We'll miss the test.
The TEST! I
almost forgot.
[yawn]
We're all gonna fail.
[snoring]
What if I tell Professor Sparkle
I needed help organizing
these books and you were all
kind enough to pitch in?
I'll get you an extension!
[yawn] Thanks, Cozy.
That's nice of you.
I'm just so sorry I
caused all of this.
You're such good friends.
I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
Mmmm. No prob.
Friendship is.... Zzzzzzz.
You get some rest.
Don't give any of
this another thought.
Just let Cozy take
care of everything....