Twilight: I can't believe
you two are going
on a Friendship Quest!
This is amazing!
What do ya mean, Twilight?
We've been on one
together before.
Exactly!
This is the first time
the map has teamed up
the same ponies for
a second quest!
That is special!
Heh. Must be 'cause we're extra good
at solvin' friendship problems.
Twilight: I hope so.
Cause it looks like this one
might be a little tricky.
You're going to
the Peaks of Peril.
The... Peaks of... P-P-P-Peril!?
Aw, it's just a name.
It doesn't mean anything.
Like how Cloudsdale
is in the clouds,
and the Crystal Empire
is made of crystal?
Fair point.
So what can you tell us
about the place, Twilight?
Only what Rockhoof told me.
Back in his day, nopony knew
much about the Peaks of Peril.
Except for the legend on
this ancient shield.
It says a group called the
Kirin used to live there,
known for their kindness
and truth-speaking.
Now we know why
the map called us.
Unfortunately, other
creatures also lived there.
The Nirik. Fearsome beasts
of pure fire.
[shudder] Maybe...you should go
instead of me, Twilight.
[nervous giggle]
Sorry, Fluttershy.
Flanks don't lie.
Aw, I'm sure the two of us'll
get that friendship problem
solved, no matter what
kinda creature has it.
[nervous giggle]
[chugging train]
[whistling wind]
Guess nopony else is goin'
out as far as we are.
Maybe they know
something we don't..
Now Fluttershy, I've
told you a dozen times!
There's nothing
to be scared--
[growl]
[both scream]
[old pony's voice]
I'm sorry.
[scream]
You really startled us!
Oh it's just that I'm not
used to seeing anypony
taking the train to...
the end of the line.
[ominous]
The final destination.
The last stop!
We get the picture. Why?
Nothing but uncharted terrain
and wild beasts out that way...
[bursts of evil laughing]
Well, maybe there's a little
somethin' to be scared of.
Eeyah!
♪♪
[splat]
[buzzing]
Agh!
♪♪
[panting]
Those must be the
Peaks of Peril. Phew.
Tough goin', huh
Fluttersh-- Fluttershy?
Agh!
[grunt]
Oh!
[chittering]
♪ [sweet music] ♪
There. That should be enough
flowers to keep your tree cozy.
Fluttershy!
What are you doin'!?
This is no time for
visitin' varmints!
We're on a friendship
quest, remember?
Yes, but actual--
-Come on!
We're burnin' daylight!
I know, but what I
found out is that--
Now, we gotta get up that peak.
I figure if we use some
rope and elbow grease,
we can make it up half--
APPLEJACK! CAN YOU
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME?
[Ahem] What I'm
trying to say is,
the squirrels told me
a short cut they take
to the Kirin village.
[grinding rock]
Oh. Heh heh.
Sorry, Fluttershy.
I s'pose I got a little too
caught up in the adventure.
That's all right.
If you hadn't come
back to get me,
I probably would've talked
to the squirrels all day!
[gasp]
♪♪
[laugh]
[rustling]
I hope that's not a Nirik..
[frightened whimper]
[rustling leaves]
Show yourself!
♪♪
[whimper]
Well, hi!
I'm Applejack, and this
here is Fluttershy.
If you have any friendship
problems, we're here to help!
Huh. Quiet bunch,
ain't they?
We're from Equestria.
And we're plum-tickled
to meet y'all.
S-So...
What are your names?
APPLEJACK.
FLUTTERSHY. Remember?
Maybe they don't
understand us.
Do.
You.
Understand.
Ponish?
Oh! But you
don't speak?
Don't or won't?
Will you excuse
us for a moment?
You have to ask "yes or no"
questions, or they won't answer.
Like talkin' to
Angel bunny?
Not exactly.
I can always tell
what Angel is feeling.
But these Kirin,
don't show anything.
Well, how are we gonna
solve a friendship problem
if none of 'em will
tell us what it IS?
♪ [scary music] ♪
♪♪
These Kirin are quieter than
an apple blossom on snowfall!
Still. There's gotta be some
way to make 'em speak.
Heh heh. Beautiful day,
ain't it?
[snort]
Knock knock!
Now you say "who's there?"
Police!
Police who?
POLICE say somethin'?
Uh oh. I feel a
sneeze comin' on!
ACHOOOO!
Fluttershy:
Gesundheit!
Ugh!
Don't ANY of y'all talk?
♪♪
Now we're gettin' somewhere!
A dark spooky path that
leads into unknown territory!?
Tell ya what,
sugarcube.
You stay and see if
you can get anything
out of these here Kirin.
I'll go try to find
one that talks.
Phew! Be careful! And
watch out for Niriks!
[teeth chattering]
♪♪
[rustling leaves]
Aaaah!
Phew...
Aaah!
Oh! Have you seen a
Kirin that talks?
Any idea where
I should look?
Oh, for the love
of Celestia!
Can't you just
say SOMETHIN'?
[laugh] Gotcha!
Sorry, sorry but
that was too good.
Oh, you don't know
how much I miss jokes.
HI-larity! Am I
pronouncing that right?
Some words I haven't said
in a wil.. While.. While.
Hi, I'm Autumn Blaze.
You've just arrived and perhaps
you're tired or hungry,
or reflective, and want to
sleep and eat and journal?
Which you should do! Of
course. But first, OH! OH!
What joy to talk with another
creature, it's been so long!
You must tell me
everything about you;
there's so much to
say, so much to DO!
Oh, look at me, I'm going
on and you haven't seen--
I mean have you seen--?
What am I saying?
Of course, you haven't,
you just so I will-
Follow me.
That was somethin', all right.
♪♪
[wind whistles]
Oh, wow!
This.. is amazing!
Oh, you think so too?
The way the light shimmers
off everything like...
like it all suddenly woke
up the moment you saw it,
and you realize maybe the water
and the mountains and the forest
and the, yes the rainbow
and the stars and the sky
are all looking back at you
thinking the same thing?
That we are a part
of the everything.
That maybe there's just one
thing, and we are all it!
I was gonna say "it's
pretty," but yeah.
Ha ha ha! [sniff] Mmmmm.
And this is just the
first stop on a journey
of amazing things to see,
smell, tiptoe through!
Oh I haven't been able to share all
of this with anypony in forever,
since they all took
that vow of silence,
so it's a lot for me to, you
know, PROcess. Pro-CESS.
Er. Deal with.
Whoa, there...
Vow of silence?
That's uh, that's why
they asked me to leave.
I hope it's not a sore subject,
but you mind explaining
why y'all went quiet
in the first place?
It's a long story.
[sigh] You'd rather not
talk about it?
No.
-I under--
I'd rather SIIIIIIIING!
♪ La, lalalalala lalala,
lalala LAAAAAA! ♪
♪ the Kirin used to speak and sing
we weren't always quiet ♪
♪ we told stories and funny jokes
my stand-up was a riot. ♪
♪ but then one day a
fight broke out ♪
♪ and hurtful words were said ♪
♪ flaring tempers were inflamed
destruction quickly spread ♪
♪ and flaming red from head to
head even burnt our.. bread! ♪
Sorry, I forgot how
much I love rhyming!
Where was I? OH RIGHT!
♪  my happy village lay in ruins,
relationships got worse ♪
♪ spoiler alert: we'd
quickly learned ♪
♪ that words could be a curse. ♪
♪ "NO MORE TALKING"
yelled our leader ♪
♪ the last thing said out loud. ♪
♪ into the stream of silence
we stepped as a crowd. ♪
♪ the water cooled emotions
and peace was soon restored ♪
♪ but with no way to
speak my thoughts ♪
♪ I got super... bored. ♪
Seriously. There's
only so long that
Sudoku can keep
you entertained!
♪ cause rainbows won't
light up the sky ♪
♪ unless you let it rain ♪
♪ and shiny apples
sometimes come with worms. ♪
♪ Though you can't give
up your laughter ♪
♪ cause you're scared of
a little pain ♪
♪ it's a lesson that
the Kirin never learned. ♪
♪♪
♪ I was stuck in silent prison
with the voices in my head ♪
♪ till I tripped over my salvation
in a helpful flower bed ♪
♪ I'd found a cure
to clear my pipes ♪
♪ and I became quite
chatty ♪
♪ with years and years
of stored up words ♪
♪ I drove my village batty! ♪
♪ They didn't like my
jokes and songs ♪
♪ and daily dose of news ♪
♪ the plays I wrote, the speeches
spoke, variety reviews, ♪
♪ or the story about the Kirin
who hid below an opera stage ♪
[spoken quickly] and fell in
love with this opera singer
and he wore a freaky half mask
thing and played the organ a lot
and got all broody because
the singer was in love with
another dude so he took her away
on this underground gondola
I mean, who doesn't
love musical theatre!?
♪ The village leader made it clear,
I had to make my choice ♪
♪ I could stay and live with them
or I could keep my voice ♪
♪ so I came here,
but left the couch alone, ♪
♪ they're hard to move. ♪
♪ With just the view for company
until you heard me groove! ♪
Take it away, boys!
♪♪
♪ Cause rainbows won't
light up the sky ♪
♪  unless you let it rain ♪
♪ and candles just won't
glow until they're burned. ♪
♪ though you can't give
up your laughter ♪
♪ cause you're scared of
a little pain ♪
♪ it's a lesson that
my village never learned. ♪
♪ No matter how hard
I schooled them ♪
♪ fear of hurt is still
what ruled them ♪
♪ sometimes you
gotta let it RAIN! ♪
♪  Yeah, sometimes you've
gotta let it.. rain. ♪
Ah! I can't believe it!
No pony should give up
feelin' their feelins,
just to keep from
gettin' angry.
That's what I said!
Y'know, when I
started talking again.
[gasp] I bet this here's the problem
that Fluttershy and I
came to help y'all with!
Really? Who's Fluttershy?
Oh, did you name your shadow!?
Mine's called Silhouette
Gloom of the Sundown Lands.
Riiiight...
Well, I'm thinking if we just
go talk to the other Kirin,
we can get 'em to welcome
you back proper-like.
Maybe even convince
'em to take your cure!
Oh, Yes, Yes
of course!
Oh.. Just one
small thing.
The antidote from
my anecdote?
It's gone.
There's no cure left!?
I used the last of the Foal's
Breath flowers to make it.
And I haven't seen
them bloom since.
Huh. Well, this wouldn't be a
Friendship Quest if it was easy!
I'm gonna start by gettin' your
friends to welcome you back.
You know? Between you and me,
I'm not sure she's
going to convince them.
"Nope."
But... I hope she does.
[panting] Fluttershy, guess what!
Both: I figured out the
friendship problem!
Me too.
Go ahead.
[giggle]
Bet that's a problem
the Kirin never have.
[giggle] No.
Anyhow, we gotta get
'em all talkin' again.
Oh, no-no-no-no-no!
We can't EVER let that happen!
I thought you said you figured
out the friendship problem!
Was somethin' lost
in translation?
The Kirin are usually
peaceful and kind.
But when they get mad,
they turn into Niriks,
creatures made of
fire and vengeance!
That seemed less scary
when it was in a song.
The last time they all
argued, they got so angry,
they accidentally destroyed
their whole village!
So the Kirin decided
to make sure
it would never happen again.
But that's no reason
to stop talkin'!
Yes it is!
Fire is dangerous.
Especially in a
forest like this!
Think of all the
animals it could hurt!
Not if they don't turn
into fire-breathin' Nirik
in the first place!
And how can you be
sure that won't happen?
There's gotta be
a better way
than givin' up all
your feelings!
APPLEJACK!
You're not LISTENING!
Cause you're not
TALKIN' any sense!
Um, what
are they doing?
Woah! Hey!
Maybe they got worried because
we were arguing with each other.
Aw, shucks.
We were just havin' a
normal, civil disagreement.
Honest!
Where are they taking us!?
[fluttershy moaning]
To the Stream of Silence!
If we hit that water, we'll
never be able to talk
or FEEL anything ever again!
[gasp]
[evil voice]
PUT THEM DOWN!
♪♪
[frightened squeal]
It's all right, I
think I know this one.
And she's tryin' to help.
[whoosh] Well, yeah!
Can't have them silence the
only friend who'll speak to me.
She talks!?
You have no idea.
Fluttershy, meet Autumn Blaze.
Thank you for that,
um, wall of fire.
But.. I thought Niriks were
dangerous when they're angry.
How did you know you could
control your temper?
I didn't. I guess anger's
like other feelings.
It's not about having them,
it's what you do with them.
And giving up happiness to keep
away anger is no kinda life.
I never thought
of it that way.
I can't imagine not being able
to talk to my animal friends.
Fern Flare, you used to
love to laugh at everything.
And Rain Shine, you sung the
most beautiful harmonies.
Don't you miss it?
I know you're worried
about fightin'.
But friends can disagree
without causin' a ruckus.
Every pony gets mad sometimes.
Even Applejack and I argue.
What? When do
we ever argue?
Ahem. On the way here!
And about the
Kirin being silent!
And RIGHT NOW!
[chuckle] We don't
always see eye-to-eye.
But we never let that get in
the way of our friendship.
And if you're really angry,
then take some time away
to be a Nirik where it
won't hurt anypony.
I think they're tryin'
to say somethin'.
OK. Are you hungry?
Oh, no! Somekirin
trapped in a well?
OK, Baby?
Baby fish?
Baby- Baby fish mouth?
Something? Anything?
Ah just write it down!
Ugh! This is making me furious!
Would you excuse me?
I'll be right back.
[roar]
You were saying.
Oh! You want the cure for
the Stream of Silence!
That's wonderful!
Uh, isn't it?
Well, it would be.
Except there aren't any
flowers left to make the cure.
Are you sure?
Oh, beyond sure.
Believe me, I've had a
lot of alone time lately.
I searched the entire forest
seventy three and a half times.
Although I wonder if that second
half could make a difference..
Hm. I wish she'd told us what kind
of flowers she's looking for.
They're called Foal's Breath.
I've never heard of that.
[chittering]
Uh Fluttershy?
A little help?
[chittering]
[gasp] He says he knows where
to find Foals Breath!
Well, what are
we waitin' for?
Lead the way!
♪♪
[gasp] THAT's what Foal's
Breath looks like!?
Autumn Blaze never would have
made it past the Peaks
to search here!
I owe you an apology.
Why?
'Cause if your kindness hadn't
made you stop to help
the squirrels, we never would've
found this here flower.
And if your honesty hadn't
convinced the Kirin to talk,
we wouldn't NEED to find it.
Heh heh. Guess it's a good
thing the map sent both of us, huh?
♪♪
[gasp] You found them!
Where were they?
Tell me everything, and
feel free to add
complicated descriptions
and comedic tangents.
Oh, right. First things first.
♪ [majestic music] ♪
[excited chatter & singing]
Autumn Blaze, you
have given us a gift:
the realization that
anger is within us.
But it is our choice
how we let it out.
We would very much like it if
you came back to live with us.
I can't say how much we've
missed your beautiful voice.
♪♪
♪ Cause rainbows won't light up
the sky unless you let it rain ♪
♪ and candles just won't
glow until they're burned. ♪
♪ Though you can't give
up your laughter ♪
♪ cause you're scared
of a little pain ♪
♪ it's a lesson that
my village never learned. ♪
♪ Oh yes, cause rainbows won't
light up the sky ♪
♪  unless you let it ... ♪
♪♪
♪  RAIN! ♪
[toc!]