Order, order everypony!
I hereby call to
order this meeting
of the Rainbow Dash Fan Club!
First order of business:
Let's celebrate the one
and only Rainbow Dash!
Yay! She's amazing. Now
if there's nothing else,
that concludes this meeting of
the Rainbow Dash Fan Club.
Thank you all for coming.
Any questions?
Huh?
Meeting adjourned!
I'd like to call to order
the first ever meeting
of the newest and
most exciting club...
of which I am the president,
founding, and only member...
The Washouts Fan Club!
Oh, hey Scootaloo, I was
just in the neighbor--
Oh, what's this?
Did I interrupt your
fan club meeting?
Hey! What are
you doing here?
I could ask you
the same question!
Oh uh, you know... stuff.
Definitely not starting a
new fan club or anything...
HA! It's no use
pretending.
I heard everything
when I was outside eavesdropping
like I do for
every meeting!
You eavesdrop on
every meeting?
That's... weird.
Well, sure it sounds weird
when you say it out loud.
And I probably shouldn't because
eavesdropping is wrong,
but still...
Why are you starting
a new fan club?
I just think maybe it's
time for me to explore...
other fan clubs.
What is a "The Washouts?"
Only the newest and greatest and
ONLY stunt troupe in Equestria!
Stunt troupe?
How can I explain it?
Like the Wonderbolts,
just TWENTY BAJILLION
PERCENT COOLER.
Twenty bajillion!?
They do all sorts of extreme
stunts that focus on daredevilry
and sheer guts, rather
than boring old
flight-and-formation junk.
Boring old flight
and formation junk!?
Are you just repeating
everything I say?
Only because my brain
feels like it's strapped
to one of those rockets
about to explode.
So you do
get it!
Aren't they awesome?
Can you believe she
actually said that?
Pfft. Well, yeah, eavesdropping on
every meeting is kinda weird.
I mean she basically said that
the Wonderbolts aren't cool!
And.. and it kinda sounded like she
didn't think I was cool either.
But pah! We all
know that's crazy.
I mean, I'm definitely
not worried
about her looking up
to somepony else.
Heh. Nope.
Not.
At.
ALL.
Well, I'd understand
if you were.
It'd be like if Apple Bloom
started lovin' bananas
more than apples!
Hahaha!
Y'all tell me if that
ever happens, you hear?
But what could the Washouts
possibly have that I don't?
Why don't you find out?
They're doing a show in
Ponyville this weekend!?
Wow... they do look pretty
amazing...ly unamazing. Heh.
Trying so hard to look
amazing, is what I mean.
NICE SAVE, TWILIGHT!
[groan] I knew we should have
lined up last night.
I'm sorry for making us late.
Who would have guessed
X-TREME CHOCOLATE AIR SHOW
CUPCAKES would take an...
x-tremely long time to bake?
Look at this! It's a
total Wonderbolts rip-off!
What do you mean? The show
hasn't even started yet!
Yeah, but look at what
we're sitting on.
Hello!
The Wonderbolts
have bleachers too.
We practically invented
sitting on bleachers.
Ugh!
And look at that! Popcorn
and cotton candy? RIP-OFF!
Huh!? Yeah!
[aggressive announcer]
This is the time.
This is the place.
This is the team...
THIS IS... THE WASHOUTS!
Eh. Quality confetti
cannon work!
Agh!
Oh, yeah!
Say it with me now, the
Washout's official motto...
"LEAP BEFORE YOU LOOK!"
Lame.
Remember ponies, while
they're amazingly awesome,
The Washouts are highly
trained professionals
with protective
fireproof flight suits!
Do not try this at home!
Whoa.
Come on! Come on!
She's not gonna make it!
[collective gasp]
THAT. WAS. INSANE!
WHOO HOO!
I told you!
I mean... [ahem] it
was pretty cool.
Who are these guys..?
I can't just go up
and TALK to them!
You can if you're with me.
After all, one of the reasons
there's a Rainbow Dash fan club
is because I'm
fearless. Observe.
Hey!
Uh... so...
as a fellow aerobatic
professional,
I really enjoyed
your show.
Heh, actually, you might
recognize me since I'm a...
"pause for dramatic effect..."
A Wonderbolt.
Join the club!
OK....?
No, I mean literally join
the club. We're called
"The Washouts" because we
all used to be Wonderbolts
just like you... until
we "washed out."
No way!
Yep. Ah.
Name's Rolling Thunder.
I got booted out of
Wonderbolt Academy cause of
"flagrant disregard for
hazardous weather." Psh.
If doin' barrel rolls through
nine-hundred million volts
of electricity in a raging
thunderstorm is wrong,
then I don't want to be right.
Cool!
Heh. This here's Short Fuse...
Ah. Nice to meet you.
What's your story?
ANGER ISSUES!
GET OFF MY BACK!
Uh, OK.
So... who's the leader?
Only the most reckless
ex-Wonderbolt of all time...
♪♪
[gasp] Lightning Dust!
Rainbow Dash.
Scootaloo. I'm
Scootaloo. Hi.
Lightning Dust...
I should have known you
were the brains behind
a crazy idea like
the Washouts.
Or should I say
"lack of brains."
You two really know each other?
OH MY GOSH THIS IS SO COOL!
Your friend got me kicked
out of the Wonderbolts.
Oh. That's, uh... less cool.
And it was the best thing
that ever happened to me!
Great to see you,
"Wing Pony!"
I heard you're a
full-fledged Bolt now!
Yeah, well,
I'm still--
Mad at me?
Look, was it wrong
of me to endanger
the lives of your
friends? Yeah.
But hey, now I only
endanger these knuckleheads!
Don't call me knucklehead.
Come on, you know you miss me.
Me and her? We blew
everypony out of the sky.
Really!?
Actually yeah, really. All that
wind was totally dangerous.
But we had fun, right?
Two fastest times
on the Dizzitron.
If I remember correctly, I had
you beat by half a second.
Only because when I went, I
cranked up the dizziness factor!
Well, I'm glad it
all worked out.
Your show was
pretty dynamite.
Wanna know the secret?
We basically ignore
everything the Wonderbolts
ever taught us about safety.
Well, we do have safety
rules for a reason.
Don't listen to
her, kid.
All their "rules" were just ways
of keeping their little club
exclusive so they could
feel good about themselves.
It's not about making
anypony feel bad,
it's about finding
the best flyers.
The best of the best.
I started the Washouts
because I believe anypony
can be the best of the best.
You know...
Rolling Thunder is gonna
be out for a while...
Ah! During the finale, I
caught the ol' hind leg
in the Crushinator Jaws of
Smash-a-lot, patent pending.
There's a spot on the team
if you want to join up.
I appreciate the offer, but
I'm already a Wonderbolt.
I'll do it! Can I do it?
Lemme think: no?
I wasn't asking you.
Aw, you're cute.
But technically, you haven't
"washed out" of the Bolts,
which is kinda... our thing.
And also... "No!"
Oh! What if I joined and
dropped out super-quick?
That's it! You're
coming with me!
Where are we going?
To hear what the actual
Wonderbolts think about you
joining just to drop
out for the Washouts.
Say "hi" to Spitfire for me!
Ever seen two
simultaneous
inverse displacement
rolls before?
Pfft. Woulda been alot
cooler through the
Crushinator Jaws of
Smash-a-lot, patent pending.
You... What!?
See, this is what I
was telling you about!
I got this.
You know what happens
when something goes wrong
with the Crushinator
Jaws of Smash-a-lot?
"...Patent pending?"
You end up in a
full-body-wing-and-hoof cast
drinkin' through a straw!
But with enough practice...
Practice!?
Well, la-dee- doodle -da!
Let me give you a
different scenario.
You're probably
saying to yourself,
"I'm young, I'm strong.
I'm gonna go out there
and "stunt" some "tricks"
with my new friend,
Lightning Dust.
Well, I'm here to tell
you if you play that game,
you're gonna find out it's
pretty hard to "stunt tricks"
in a FULL-BODY-WING-AND-HOOF
CAST DRINKIN' THROUGH A STRAW!
I think she
gets the point-
I'M NOT FINISHED!
Listen, I get it, kid.
I used to be like you.
Tellin' myself: "I'm
gonna touch the sky!"
I don't--
Well,
WHOOP-DEE-DOODLE-DOO!
You think you got it
made in the shade?
Well, things are gonna
be pretty shady indeed
when you can't go out in the
sun cause you're in
a FULL-BODY-WING-AND-HOOF
CAST DRINKIN' THROUGH A STRAW!
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
Excellent.
Have a hat.
Er, sorry. That was a
little... intense.
I just want to make
sure you don't get hurt.
That way you can
follow in my hoofsteps.
Everypony's dream, right?
More like "follow
your wing-flaps."
Same difference.
Thanks, "super-
talented flyer,"
for clearing up
what I should do!
Clearing things up is
one of my specialties.
Now come on, let's go rip up
all your Washout posters
into tiny pieces and
throw 'em off a cliff.
I just thought of a great
way to raise awareness
for your original fan club.
You know, the one about me.
How about a silent
auction where every item
is just a picture
of yours truly?
Haha, nahhh, I'm just kidding.
That makes me seem too
egotistical, doesn't it?
OH OH! But maybe
if they're framed,
it's like, "Wow, she's so
humble", you think?
Scootaloo...?
Er. Scootaloo?
Anypony seen Scootaloo?
My fault, my fault--
sorry, I... Twilight!
Sorry, I was just, um...
Please tell me you got that
stuff so you could rip it up
and throw it off a cliff.
They were doing an autograph
session before practice..
Seriously? Ugh.
You haven't seen
Scoot, have you?
Actually...
I can't believe
Scootaloo ditched me
to watch them "practice"!
Why can't she see how
dangerous they are?
That's kind of
the whole draw.
It's exciting.
But it's like the harder
I try to convince Scoot
they're dangerous, the
more she likes them!
You can't control her
actions, only yours.
Teach her what's safe and what
isn't, like a good role model,
then hope she makes
the right decisions.
But what if she
chooses them over me?
She's gonna get hurt.
I think I know somepony
else who might get hurt
if that happens.
Maybe you're right.
But this isn't about me.
I'm just worried about Scoot.
Wow, you're really working
hard on this new stunt.
WHAT KIND OF SORRY EXCUSE FOR
A TOMATO SANDWICH IS THIS?
Sorry Dash, autograph
session's over.
Unless you want to buy
Short Fuse's limited-edition
half-eaten
tomato sandwich.
I'M NOT SIGNING
THAT ABOMINATION!
You haven't seen
Scootaloo, have you?
Oh! Isn't she that pony
that used to respect you?
I'd appreciate you
helping me find her...
so I can apologize for trying
to make her quit liking you.
[mean laugh] Oh, I'm pretty
sure she still likes us.
Lightning Dust, I
know we go way back,
but I can't let
her do this!
I don't need you
standing up for me.
Obviously you do, because you
can't see how dangerous this is.
Do you not remember
what Spitfire said?
Ugh, lemme guess,
"You'll be in a
full-body-wing-and-hoof cast
drinkin' through a straw!"
That doesn't even
sound like Spitfire.
That's it,
we're leaving!
Just because I
look up to you
doesn't mean I
have to BE you!
But based on your definition
of what makes somepony great,
I have bad news: I'll NEVER
be the "best of the best",
or a Wonderbolt
because I. CAN'T. FLY.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
But not being able
to fly doesn't mean
I can't do
something awesome,
like strapping my scooter to a
multi-stage liquid-fuel rocket
and jumping twenty
two wagons lined up
in front of a
roaring crowd!
That was awfully specific.
That's cause it's what she'll
be doing in the show tonight.
Half-off for Princesses!
Bring your friends.
Scootaloo, are you sure that's
what you really want to do?
Absolutely.
And there's nothing
you can do to stop me!
You're right. You're
your own foal
and you have to make
your own decisions.
Good. Because I already have.
Oh.
I'm sorry for making
us late again.
Who would have guessed
Scootaloo's Super-
Difficult-Stunt-Special
Cupcakes would have been
so super-difficult to bake?
Whoo wee, looks like all
of Ponyville's here...
except for Rainbow Dash.
[Announcer] And here to
introduce the most
dangerous stunt
we've ever performed, it's
your fearless captain...
La La La Lightning Dust!
In just a moment, the newest
member of the Washouts
will be ROCKET-SLEDDING down
that hill, up that ramp,
and over all twenty-two wagons,
to land on the other side...
in one piece...
..heh ...if she's lucky.
Put your hooves together
for HALF-PINT DYNAMITE!
Whoo yeah!
Lightning Dust?
I have to tell you, I actually
started Equestria's first
Washouts Fan Club...
as far as I know.
So this is a real honor, ma'am.
Umm, do we call you ma'am?
You land this jump, you can
call me whatever you want.
Wow, that sure is...
Dangerous? Nahh.
Well, maybe a little.
Has anypony tested it before?
Where's the fun in that?
There's MORE?
You're not thinking of
backing out, are you?
No! I'm just thinking about
drinking through straws.
Are you the president
of my fan club, or not?
Of course, it's just...
You wouldn't want to get
impeached for dishonoring
my wishes, would you?
I-- Is that a thing?
Light it up!
OK, now I am thinking
about backing out!
Too late!
I know I was supposed to let
you make your own decisions,
but that doesn't mean I
can't swoop in and save you
from time to time.
If I'd known you
were gonna bail,
I would have done
the trick myself!
Great! So you won't
mind how that rope's
about to coil around your hoof!
Rivals for LIFE!
Wouldn't have it any other way.
I'm sorry for joining
the Washouts...
Lightning Dust wasn't
who I thought she was.
She didn't care about me being
scared or putting me in danger.
She only wanted a good show,
even if it meant I got hurt.
That's not the kind of
pony I wanna look up to.
I'm the one who should
be apologizing...
for not acting like somepony
who deserves a fan club.
I've been lucky enough
to have somepony
who thinks I'm
the coolest,
but there's nothing cool
about making you feel like
you'll never be
as awesome as me.
I think we should cancel
the Washouts Fan Club,
because I know a fan club that
could use some new members.
The Rainbow Dash Fan Club!
Welcome to the
first ever meeting
of the newest fan club
for the awesomest,
previously under-appreciated
pony in Ponyville...
with founding member and
president Rainbow Dash
presiding, it's the...
Scootaloo Fan Club!
You know, Rainbow
Dash was right.
Eavesdropping on your own
fan club isn't weird at all.