♪ [Scottish music] ♪
[clanging hammer]
[thud]
[aggressive grunts]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
You're gonna have to
work faster than that
if you plan to dig up
my whole village, lass.
Let me help.
Ah!
[crash]
Er, thank you, Rockhoof.
But we're trying to
carefully preserve
every bit of history here.
Aye, this place is
full of memories.
Did I tell you about the time
our chieftain knocked down
five boulders with the
kick of a wee ball?
OH! STOP THAT!
But.. that's what this is for.
Maybe in the past!
Now, it belongs in a museum!
Safe. Preserved. Untouched.
Bah! Next you'll be saying
I shouldn't have used
the old sweat lodge.
[gasp]
[rumble and crash]
So you see why Rockhoof isn't
an ideal fit for my team.
Perhaps you could use
his, uh, unusual talents?
Of course, Professor Fossil!
We'd be honored to have a Pillar
of Equestria on our staff.
Oh thank Celestia.
[slam]
[crunch]
Blech!
Agh that apple's made of wood!
What a horrible trick to play!
[crash]
Hm.  Has anypony seen my
decorative centerpieces?
They were right here.
Good luck!
[excited conversation]
So join me in welcoming
Professor Rockhoof
to our faculty!
[cheering]
Thank you, thank you all.
I know I'm new to your world,
but there's one thing I learned
when I saved my village from
a rushing river of hot lava...
There's nothing you can't do
with hard work... and a shovel!
[smash]
[audience gasps]
[crash]
Except maybe stand on stage..
[grunt]
So, um, everycreature
dismissed!
We'll... see you in class!
You think that new
pony is gonna be
the weirdest
teacher at school?
Or just one of the weirdest?
Yona like new teacher!
He big, like yak!
And he smashes
things like a yak.
He smells like a yak...
Yes! He perfect.
Guys, he's one
of the Pillars!
He's like...
Pony history!
HELLO CLASS!
[smash]
Well, Um...
I'm er.. your new "Theory and
Defense of Friendship" teacher.
[creaking]
But I haven't had
a chance to look
at Headmare
Twilight's notes yet.
What have you all
been learning?
We just studied all about how
Princess Celestia and Luna
used a spell to trap
Discord in stone sleep
for hundreds of moons.
Oh, hohoho...
so it's a class
about stories, is it?
Stories, yeah!
And we never, ever,
ever get homework.
Good! The best way to
teach colts and fillies
is by experience.
Like the time I was in the woods
and ran across an Ursa Major.
Really!?
We're not doing
that, right?
You fight Ursa Major?
All alone?
Aye! And I
defeated her too!
Now this, I'm interested in.
How Professor Rockhoof win?
Well, that's quite a tale.
From what Professor Fossil said,
it sounds like Rockhoof
just hasn't settled into
modern times yet.
Our school is the
perfect place for that.
Plus, we get a new teacher!
Heh. This may be the fastest
friendship problem
you ever solved.
[crash]
Dodge! Thrust! Shovel Leap!
Shovel Throw!
[crashing hoofsteps]
Shovel Whack!
Now you lot be the Ursa Major.
Lotsa growling, mind!
[growls]
Ha ha ha ha!
[cheers]
Maybe classrooms were less
breakable in the old days?
Ooh ooh ooh! What
happened next?
Heh heh. The huge beastie jumped
out of the moonlit mist,
her fearsome fangs at my throat!
But I rolled clear!
[crash]
Then what!?
She backed me up against
a wall, ready to pounce!
[gasp]
I looked at her...
she looked at me.
And I say--
Uh Professor
Rockhoof?
Nope, guess again!
Ahem. Oops.
Sorry to interrupt.
Class, why don't we go ahead
and take lunch early today?
Rockhoof, can we
take a walk outside?
Our school is about finding
your own special way to teach.
And we can already tell
you're a smash with the class!
But maybe you could do a little
less smashing in the classroom?
Sorry about that. I did get
a bit carried away.
The students were so
interested in my tale!
[shudder]
I know it's a big change,
but I think you're
gonna fit in just--
[fire roaring]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
FIRE!
Rockhoof, wait!
No time! The building's ablaze!
We have to get everypony out!
Professor Rockhoof
best teacher ever!
[sigh] Day cannot get better!
[crash]
Let's get you
outside, wee ones!
Day just got better!
Wow!
Ally-Oop!
Rockhoof!
What are you doing!?
Saving the school!
♪♪
Just like fighting a volcano
in the good old days!
Would somepony
kindly explain
what is the meaning
of all this water?
I'm not sure, but I
think it's "Surf's up!"
Wheeeeee! Cowabunga!
Sorry, Rarity.
But I had to put out
the raging inferno!
Inferno? Where?
Did you not see the
smoke and flame?
Yeah, that was us.
Y'know, DRAGONS?
Having a firebreathing
competition?
You... what?
They do it all the time.
That's what we were
trying to tell you.
We know you're used to
being a hero, Rockhoof.
Only... what we need
here is a teacher.
One who doesn't ruin an entire
class's friendship quilts!
Do you know how hard it is to
stitch a pineapple pattern!?
Oh. My deepest apologies.
I'm not used to
living with dragons.
Or much else in
this modern time.
Professor Fossil
made it clear
I'm not welcome back
in my old village.
Seems I don't
belong here either.
WHEEEE!
So apparently,
finding Rockhoof a new job
is a lot harder than we thought.
Has anypony had any luck?
Uh uh. Nope.
I thought you were gonna try
him out at the post office.
We did.
Do you know where I can
find Cranky Doodle Donkey?
I need to deliver his medicine!
He has a rash in a very
embarrassing place!
[shudder] I did not
need to hear that.
Yep! Rockhoof's time
as a spa masseuse
didn't work out either.
Now just let me know if
this is too much PRESSURE.
[shriek of pain]
Well, at least Rockhoof's
really strong.
Maybe we could find him a
job carrying heavy stuff?
I tried that already!
Zecora needed somepony to
help her get supplies, but...
[knocking]
I know you said you only
needed a few leaves,
but I figured why not
bring you the whole thing?
[buzzing]
Oh, how horrid.
None of the other Pillars
seem to be having trouble
fitting in to the modern world.
Then maybe they can show
Rockhoof how they did it.
Get him used to
livin' in this time.
Great idea!
Rockhoof's old friends
would be happy to help.
And I bet he'd
love to visit them.
Hmph.
Even Canterlot looks
different from the old days.
Aw, I'm sure once you see
your ol' pal Flash Magnus,
you'll feel right at home.
Trot, 2, 3, 4!
Keep it lively, rookies!
Visitors on site!
Company, halt!
Rockhoof, you old
ditch-digger you!
Flash Magnus, as I
live and breathe!
Is this your squadron?
After we got out of limbo, I
went looking for work for a pony
with experience in
the Royal Legion.
Once a soldier,
always a soldier.
Princess Celestia was happy to
find a new drill sergeant
for her Guard!
Yeah.. that's great.
She really put you in a
job that big... so soon?
Oh, this is nothing!
You should see what
Mistmane is up to.
They made you the Royal
Landscape Artist
for the Crystal Empire?
Wow.
Your work is
beautiful!
Oh thank you.
I've never worked
with crystal before,
but in my heart, I know
I'm where I belong.
You always could find
the beauty in things.
But there's not much demand for
shovel ponies like me nowadays.
Don't give up hope!
See Somnambula.
She'll help you
find your purpose.
Somnambula's a
motivational speaker.
Bet they didn't even have
those back in your time.
Because we didn't
need them.
Ponies knew what to
do with their lives.
Focus on my voice, and feel
yourself unlock your potential.
[deep inhale and exhale]
Imagine everything that
troubles you as one big cloud.
Now let it float away.
You are relaxed.
Free to do anything you wish.
[loud snoring]
Guess he wished he
could take a nap?
Rockhoof: Mage Meadowbrook!
Your home looks just the
same as the old days.
Wish I could say
the same for mine.
Well, I've had to
expand my clinic a bit.
Many creatures need healing
in this modern world.
Oh! Looks like you
could use some too.
What's got you
heartsick, Rockhoof?
[thud]
Thing is, I can't do
my old job like Flash.
Or adapt like Mistmane.
Or succeed at something
new like Somnambula.
Or go home, like you.
Give it time.
Even Starswirl's still
learning about friendship...
Applejack: Yeah!
And I bet Stygian took
plenty of time to fit in.
Hey, look what I found!
"Me and My Shadow,"
the third hit novel
by former villain Stygian!
I'm impressed! He's
really thriving!
[moan]
Rockhoof? Where are
you going?
I'm not sure.
Maybe I just don't belong
in this modern world.
Now this here is a
right mash of apples.
'Stead of solving
Rockhoof's problem,
we made him feel even worse.
I'll tell you the
real problem here!
We haven't given Rockhoof the
chance to be who he really is.
A pony with a metal shovel
and a heart of gold?
Tch. A hero!
What we need to do is find him
a job that's as epic as he is!
Hm. I might know
just the thing...
Rockhoof: I'm honored to serve
in the Hippogriff Navy,
General Seaspray.
I promise I'll prove my worth.
Think nothing of it.
I know how hard it is
to adapt to a new home.
After our many years
below the waves,
land customs seemed strange.
Like you didn't fit in, no
matter how hard you tried?
As though the world had
moved on without us.
Never fear, Rockhoof!
We shall be as brothers in this
bright future above the waves.
Uh, why do the
Hippogriffs need ships
if they can turn
into seaponies?
Maybe they just like cruises?
General!
The fog's too thick to see
our way out of the harbor!
[rushing water]
Heave to, swabbies!
Halt the ship and hold
her till the fog passes!
Wait, General!
We can navigate the same way
my Coltic ancestors traveled
through the Selkie Mists!
We'll look to the stars!
There in the
northwest sky
is the constellation
for O'Bridle's Pelt!
Steer the ship toward that!
You heard the pony, crew!
Make full sail!
[rushing water]
Yeehaw! Rockhoof did it!
[smash]
But... I don't understand!
The stars have always
steered me true!
Oh, no. Stars can move
slowly over time.
They must look different now
than over a thousand years ago.
It was an honor serving
with you, Rockhoof.
But it seems our paths lie
in different directions.
♪♪
Hey, mistakes happen.
We'll think of something
else for you to do!
Oh, there's no need, lass.
I already know what
I want to do next.
Really? What?
I heard there's a
statue spell
that sends creatures
into stone sleep.
I want you to cast it.
On me.
[gasp]
[groan]
Twilight: No!
Rockhoof: Yes!
-No!
-Aye!
[groan]
No!
AYE!
Hey guys.
Need me to help you
decide something?
Rockhoof wants me to cast a
spell to turn him into a statue.
The answer is no.
Well, it should be "aye", because
I wouldn't even be here
to be turned into a statue
if Twilight hadn't cast a
spell in the first place!
[stomp]
Whoa. I thought you were
arguing over ice cream flavors.
The answer is still no!
Why would you want to
be turned into stone?
Because I'm a relic
of a bygone age.
I belong in a museum.
Safe.
Preserved.
Untouched.
I don't belong in this time.
It's up to you to
make that right!
But there has to
be a better way!
Twilight, please understand.
I want to be remembered
as the hero I was.
Not the disappointment
I've become.
But you're not!
Rockhoof, wait!
Spike, can you teach
my class today?
Er, you're not really going to
turn him to stone, are you?
Only because it's temporary.
As soon as I think
of a new solution,
we'll wake Rockhoof up.
I KNOW he has more to offer the
world as a pony than a statue.
Did you hear Rockhoof caught all
the bees in the Everfree Forest,
and gave 'em to
Zecora as a gift?
Wow! Terramar said Rockhoof
called down the stars
and sunk the whole
Hippogriff navy!
He's definitely weird.
But in a fun way.
You never know what's
gonna happen next with him.
Professor Rockhoof best pony!
Hey, class.
Welcome to the Theory and
Defense of Friendship.
Another sub?
Let me start by telling
you we don't get homework,
and we only do field trips.
Yeah, nice try.
Er, Twilight sent me to tell
you she won't be in today
'cause she has to cast a stone
sleep spell on Rockhoof.
[gasp]
Like Discord? But why!?
Rockhoof isn't a bad guy!
Hm.
Your instructions are
to write an essay on
"Heroism: And What It
Means To You."
No!
Oh, don't worry.
It doesn't have to
be a long essay.
Maybe like.. this?
Or on three legs... Hmm.
What will give the wee birds
fewer places to uh, decorate?
Yona: Professor Rockhoof!
Dragon said you want
to turn into stone!
Yona not believe it!
Aye, I'm afraid it's true, lass.
But... Pony need finish
Ursa Major story for class!
It's sweet of you to try
to get me to stay, Yona.
But... I'm afraid old
stories like mine
aren't worth anything
in this day and age.
Fine! If Pony no want
tell Yona story,
then Yona tell Pony story!
From class report!
"When Yona come to Pony
school, Yona not fit in.
Pony ways strange.
But Yona find friends!
Yona meet Professor Rockhoof.
Pony brave and strong as Yak!
Not afraid! Hero!"
When Yona grow up,
Yona want to be just like
Professor Rockhoof!"
Well.... since you went
to the trouble
of writing something
that nice, I suppose
the least I could do is tell
you the rest of the story.
Yona tell whole school
Rockhoof is best!
Now ALL want to hear story!
OK. I have the spell,
but will you please
reconsider. Rockhoof!?
The Ursa Major tried to
grab me by the gullet!
But I ducked her claws!
[gasps]
She had me cornered.
So I look at her..
she looks at me.
[gasp]
And I say, "Sorry you won't be
having any dinner tonight, lass!
Guess you'll just have
to.. grin and bear it!"
[laughter]
And then I tossed her away with
my shovel, high into the sky!
And she's been a constellation
up there ever since.
Or so I'm told.
And that's the end of my story.
One more story!
No no. Thank you
for listening.
But it's time to say good-bye.
Wait!
You said there wasn't anything
in this time you were good at.
What about telling stories?
It was just a tall tale...
One that captured the
hearts and imagination
of everycreature here.
Plus pony story super fun!
[cheers]
As the Princess of Friendship,
I'd like to appoint you
as Equestria's official
Keeper of Tales!
Can you do that?
Meh.
I uh.... That's
very kind of you.
But I still think these old
bones are more suited
to a museum display.
You are a living
record of our history.
Your stories can inspire and
teach generations to come!
If you're a statue,
that's all lost.
But will I ever really
belong in your world?
Rockhoof Yona's friend.
So Rockhoof belongs.
You know, that reminds
me of another story...
Once there was a small Yak that
knew more than a great hero.
Hey, don't forget the
dragons in this one!
Aye, there were dragons!
And ponies.
And plenty of hippogriffs...
Plus a changeling and
a griffon that flew...