[panting]
♪ [tense music] ♪
Oh, good, we're all here!
So everypony got an urgent
summons to the castle
with no explanation?
Yup! I just love a good
mysterious summons.
What's it about? Do you
think it's a surprise party?
Hey, why are we running?
Because something could
be terribly wrong!
Somepony turned bad,
another evil creature
back for revenge!?
Don't you think you're
being a little paranoid?
Why else would the princesses
send scrolls in such a hurry?
Good point. They'd know
better than to make us worry.
Plus, I like it when
you run so fast;
the walls get all blurry!
Wheee!
Race ya!
♪♪
[door opens]
[panting]
Girls, thank you
so much for coming.
What's wrong!? What can we do!?
That's just it. Nothing's
wrong. Everything's perfect!
Did y'all call us down
here just to tell us that?
With all due
respect, Majesties,
you might want to save
your urgent summons
for matters that are a
bit more... well, urgent?
[chuckles]
Well, there is more to it.
Equestria is currently
enjoying its longest period
of harmony in recent years.
And it's all thanks
to you, Twilight.
And your
friends, of course.
Who, us?
Oh, pshaw! [giggle]
It's about time
you noticed!
Thank you!
Because of your efforts,
there's been less
and less for us to do!
So, after much consideration,
my sister and I have decided
it is time for us... to retire.
[everypony gasps]
[zap]
Breaking News! The royal
princesses retiring?
I have so many
questions.
Who'll take over? Who
will run Equestria?
Will it be someone
tall, dark, and handsome
or will it be the
Lord of Chaos?
[zapping]
Ugh. Fine, go with
the obvious choice.
[stressed yell]
You're retiring!?
Princesses can retire?
Of course we can! I, for
one, am looking forward
to a little R&R, maybe
a trip to Silver Shoals.
And you want me to
take your place!?
Mm hm!
With the help of your
friends, of course.
We can't think of
anypony more worthy.
Over the years, we've
watched you grow.
You've faced
task after task.
...challenge
after challenge.
...countless adversities. Yeah,
yeah, we get it.
And you've always
prevailed.
Thank you, but that
doesn't mean that I'm--
that we're ready
to do what you do!
Oh. Of course you are. I realize
this is a lot to take in, but--
Nope! Makes perfect
sense. We're awesome.
[gasp] Does this mean we
get all your powers!?
Ooo-oo! I call dibs on showing
up in everypony's dreams!
You can't be ready to step
into their horse shoes
just like that!
Well, if the Princesses
think it's time to retire,
we're not a bad choice.
We always have Equestria's
best interests at heart.
That's a fair point,
which should be taken
into consideration
when we have a
roundtable discussion.
Well, I'm in.
Darlings! We'll all need a
complete wardrobe update.
And I would love to pick your
brain about mane maintenance.
When you have a moment.
As long as we all have each
other, I'm sure we can do it.
Yay!
Protectors of Equestria
on three. One, two--
[sigh]
If you're all on board,
I guess I am too.
All: Protectors of Equestria!
It'll be a bit of
an adjustment,
but I imagine the
transfer of power
will be a lengthy process
which will give me--
Actually, we just
need a few days
to put together a
little ceremony.
Heh heh. A few DAYS!?
[groans]
But... that's so soon!
Shouldn't there be some
sort of training program?
That lasts weeks, no,
months, if not YEARS?
Everything you've gone
through over the years
has been a
training program.
OK, but there's got to be
a guide or a rule book?
Yes, I have it right here:
"How to Rule Equestria"
by Nopony McPretendsmith.
The Friendship Journal
you wrote yourselves
is a better guide than
any we could provide.
[frantic gasping]
We have the utmost
confidence in you.
And we hope you have
the same in yourself.
[gasping]
[blowing]
Oh, I'm absolutely
certain she does.
I am not confident
about this at all!
Well, that's what I thought.
I was being sarcastic before.
[spraying]
What? This is all
so predictable.
Now's the part where you all
tell little Sparkle here
that everything is
going to be fine.
But she won't believe you.
[groan] I don't need to be here for this.
[zap]
It's just, I know I said
yes, but then they said
"in a few days" and there's
still so much to figure out!
It's all happening so fast!
[gasping]
I think I need some--
[slurp]
[gulp] OK. I'll feel
much better--
Once you make
a plan?
Oh. Wow. It's
like you--
--knew you were going to
react this way? We did.
Classic Twilighting.
"Twilighting?" You...
you made me a verb?
It's not a bad thing, we just
know you have a.... process.
Stage one. You get big
news, and you're like "No!"
But then you pace, and
you chart, you worry...
It's OK. You go
ahead and "Twilight"
and we'll be here for you.
You're all acting so calm,
but this is a big deal!
What will we do if
something big happens
and the princesses
aren't there to help?
Um... If you think about it,
they literally
almost never help.
Huh.
And.. we still always win!
Like when Sombra almost took
back the Crystal Empire,
or when Chrysalis
pretended to be Cadance,
or when Tirek came back and
absorbed all the magic,
or the other time Chrysalis
tried to take over,
or with Cozy Glow and the
school. [gasp] Am I missing anything?
Pony of Shadows.
Starlight when
she was evil.
Discord when he was evil.
Do Flim and
Flam count?
See? We've almost
always done things
without the princesses' help.
Which makes sense now because
it was all just training
for you to take over.
And it worked. I mean,
if you think about it,
there hasn't been
a single villain
that we couldn't defeat.
Phew.
One day, you'll see.
I will defeat Twilight
Sparkle and her friends,
and they will pay for
stealing my kingdom!
[zap]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Pssst! Tirek!
It is Lord Tirek
and what is it now?
I just want to make
sure you can see my
"best friends rock
sculpture" from over there.
[groan]
[whoosh]
[crumple]
♪♪
[whoosh]
Lord Tirek.
A changeling?
See? She gets it.
Chrysalis, Queen
of the Changelings.
Or at least I will be when I'm
restored to my rightful place.
Why did you summon
me? What do you want?
Wah! Oh, golly! We
didn't bring you.
I thought you freed
us from Tartarus.
Tartarus? Whoever
pulled you from there
must have been somepony
very powerful, indeed.
[laughter]
♪♪
King Sombra! You
have returned?
Why did you
bring us here?
Deep voice: He didn't.
♪ [ominous music] ♪
[whoosh]
[crash]
It was I.
You may call me... Grogar.
[gasp]
The Grogar?
I thought that you
were a legend.
I've heard of you!
Who..?
I assure you, I
am very real.
And you have all been brought
here as part of my plan
to rid Equestria of Twilight
Sparkle and her friends
once and for all!
Heh heh heh heh.
I am so sorry, but
the name Grofar
just doesn't
ring any bells.
GROGAR! I have
been away too long
if my name no longer
strikes fear into the heart
of one so tiny.
Perhaps a demonstration
of power is in order?
♪♪
[zapping]
[kiss]
Grogar is ancient and
extremely powerful.
The land that would
become Equestria
was a mere collection
of farms and pastures
until he declared himself
Emperor of all he saw.
I remember hearing tales of
his tyranny when I was young.
I have also heard of the
first Emperor of Equestria,
the "Father of Monsters."
I gave life to the
foulest of creatures
and allowed them to run wild,
taking what they wanted
and destroying the rest!
My reign was a glorious
fear-soaked epoch
of darkness in Equestria.
Ha! Until Gusty the Great
rose up and banished you.
That fool believed taking
my bell would defeat me,
but she only weakened
me temporarily.
Um, Tirek is really old. No
offense, you look great.
But if he knew about
you when he was young,
we have super-different ideas
about what "temporarily" means.
Silence! I have spent
millennia gathering power,
biding my time, waiting
for the perfect opportunity
to seize control of Equestria!
And watching all of you.
I've seen each of your
humiliating defeats
at the hooves of
six puny ponies.
And do you know why
they've always bested you?
Because they cheat.
Because they are
annoyingly lucky.
I'm just a kid, so...
It is because they
work together.
Where one is weak, another
is strong and thus unified,
they are a formidable force.
But we shall use their own
strategy to defeat them.
What are you suggesting?
I suggest nothing. I
DEMAND that you join me
and together Equestria
will be ours!
I don't do "ours",
I only do MINE.
[whoosh]
I will take back the
Crystal Empire on my own
and I will destroy anypony
who gets in my way!
Such confidence.
Go. Try to take
back your kingdom.
I shall send you
there myself.
If you prevail, you
may keep it.
But when you fail,
you will submit to me.
And if I refuse this... deal?
Then I shall return
you to the darkness
from which you
were summoned.
Fine. But this is
a waste of time,
as I will crush
those who defy me.
I will defeat all who
get in my way. I--
[zap]
I advise the rest of you to
prepare to work together.
Well, working together
sounds an awful lot like
making friends, so
you two are in luck
because I know all
about that!
[knocking]
Twi? You in here? With the
school closed for the summer,
I didn't think anypony
would be here.
So much to do, not enough
time. No! I already did that.
Wait. Nope. I didn't.
OOOH, NOT ENOUGH TIME!
HELP! She's spiraling.
We're at the "my plan
needs a plan" stage
of a Total Twilight
Melt Down!
Oh. Got it.
Twilight?
Did I write down "eliminate
redundant lists"
on my School of
Friendship to-do list,
or my personal to-do list?
TWILIGHT!           Gah!
Starlight! Oh, good, you're
here. I need to talk to you.
Oh-kay...
Hang on, I had "talk to
Starlight" written down
on one of these. Just let me
find it so I can cross it off.
Wow, you are
"Twilighting" hard.
You say
Twilighting too!?
Well, EXCUSE me, but
this is the first time
I've ever been asked
to run A WHOLE KINGDOM!
Ah! You're right. You're right... Heh.
So.. what did you want
to talk to me about?
Ah! Here it is. I
wrote it down.
Starlight, you have blossomed
into one of the strongest,
smartest, most
caring ponies I know
and I can't think of anypony
better to leave in charge
of my castle and the
School of Friendship.
So what do you think?
WHAT? You want ME to
take care of the castle
and RUN THE SCHOOL?
Yes?
Ah! I can't! I'm
not ready!
Remember what happened
the last time
you left me in charge!?
And now you want me
to do it PERMANENTLY?
What if I don't do the
right things!? [gasping] What if--
Starlight! Get a
hold of yourself.
You've risen to every
challenge you've ever faced.
You can do anything you put
your mind to. You've got this.
Ha! And so do you!
See what I did there?
You just said everything
YOU need to hear.
Ha ha ha! Nice try, but running
a school and running a country
are two very different things!
Now if you don't
mind, I have 7,432
more things to take
care of before I become
the new Ruler of Equestria!
[gasping]
It was a valiant effort.
♪♪
[panicked shouts]
[ching]
[crash]
♪♪
[crackling]
The guard says Sombra's
breached the castle!
Hurry, Twilight! We need you!
Do you have
Flurry Heart!?
I thought
you had her!
[gasp]
Ah!
[galloping hooves]
[whining] Mama!
[gasp]
You won't get
away with this.
Oh, but I
already have!
[baby protests]
Ha ha ha ha!
With the Cyrstal heart
now in my possession,
there is nothing to
stop me from ruling
the Crystal Empire.
Kneel before Sombra!
Ah. Long live the King.
♪♪
Thanks for coming so quickly.
[zap]
Sure thing, but if you're
going to be the ruler
of Equestria, you may want
to work on your penmanship.
This looks like it says,
"Cadance sent an
emergency message.
Sombra's back and he's taking
over the Crystal Empire."
That's exactly what it says!
But... But how is that possible?
I thought the Crystal
Heart had dispelled him
into the Ether!
I have no idea, but he's
back and it's up to us
to save the Empire
and my family!
Shouldn't somepony
tell Celestia and Luna?
Oooh. Good point.
One of us should probably
loop in the real rulers
of Equestria.
No. If we're going
to run Equestria,
we'll need to handle things
like this on our own.
Oh, Twilight! Could
this mean that you finally
have the confidence to
ascend to the throne
like the princesses
believe you can?
Maybe... Unless you'd consider
taking care of Sombra for us?
Oh, no no no no no. You
were absolutely right.
You need to learn how to handle
these things on your own.
Ta-tah.
Handling things on our
own is all well and good,
but last time we defeated
Sombra with the Crystal Heart.
What if he has it already?
How are we gonna stop him?
[gasp]
♪♪
With the Elements of Harmony!
With those, we can defeat
anypony, even Sombra!
Ah no no no no.
You didn't need
the "Elements" the last
time you defeated Sombra.
And I'm not sure using
them still counts
as handling things
on your own.
My family is in danger.
I'm not taking any chances.
She's got a point.
Ugh. Fine.
What's his problem?
Starlight, can you stay here
and take care of the school?
I've got you covered.
[poof]
♪♪
[zapping]
[poof]
[zap]
It's cute that you think
that will do anything.
It might not, but they will.
Cavalry's here!
[battle cries]
[chuckle] How can I be surprised
when I'm waiting to show
all of you your greatest fear?
[whoosh]
♪♪
[clang]
[whimper]
Oh, Twilight. How
disappointing.
Equestria was in your care
and you let it be destroyed.
[explosion]
You should all surrender.
Nothing can defeat
your own fears.
♪ [music turns uplifting] ♪
We didn't need to defeat them.
We just needed to face them
long enough to distract you!
♪♪
NO!
It's cute that you think
that will do anything.
[zapping]
[rumbling]
You may have won the battle,
but I shall win the war!
♪♪
[zapping]
Ya hoo hoo hoo!
♪♪
We totally just wiped
the castle with that guy.
♪♪
Thanks, Twily.
But that was fun!
And.. easy.
As magical battles go,
that was a cakewalk.
Mmmmm, "cakewalk".
[laughter]
We did handle this
pretty well.. on our own.
Does this mean--?
I still don't feel like I'm
one hundred percent ready,
but will I ever?
Knowing you? Nope.
I have you guys, and we have
the Elements, and together,
we've never failed.
We'll be OK.
[cheers]
Once again, Equestria is safe.
What should we
do to celebrate?
I vote for a cakewalk!
[crash]
[whoosh]
[rumbling]
What's going on?
I don't know!
[smashing]
[smashing glass]
[gasps]
[whoosh]
[evil laughter]