♪♪
I know how hard you've
been working lately,
so I figured you
could use a break.
[happy gasp]
Trixie, this looks amazing!
But my job doesn't
really seem like work...
[bracelet chimes]
Ooh! Speaking of...
[poof]
[sigh]
Sure, being counselor
for the students
at Twilight's School of
Friendship is demanding,
but... [chimes] Oh, one sec.
[poof]
What was I saying? Oh, right.
Being able to use
the experiences
of my checkered past
to help young students
feels pretty great.
Oooh! Yum! Mm. Thanks.
Of course, I feel
nothing but admiration
for the work you do, but it
is a little all-consuming
and I miss spending
time with you.
What are you
talking about!?
We're spending
time right now.
Well...
[bracelet chimes]
Hold that thought!
[poof]
Grrr!
[poof] Hah! Sorry. I cast a spell
on the door to my office
so this bracelet goes off
whenever there's a knock.
Yona is having the worst
time with her braids lately.
Anyway, you were saying?
[slurp]
[nervous giggle]
♪♪
I totally respect my
younger cousins' decisions
to stay seaponies,
but they've never
been on dry land.
Preparing for a visit with
them is almost as much work
as the research assignment
Headmare Twilight gave me
on Hazardous Fauna of
the Everfree Forest!
How would you describe
a shower to creatures
who live in water?
So far, I've got
warm and steamy.
Actually, steam
has water in it...
Silverstream, there
are a lot of students
who want to see me today.
I just need a few
shower adjectives
that don't rely
on the wet part.
[sigh] Well, there's
clean, relaxing, um...
Relaxing? I don't know.
A nap's relaxing too.
Warm and clean are OK.
Wow. I have to give
this some more thought!
Oh. OK. Well, I'm here to
help. My door's always open!
Except for today, of course.
[slam]
[whimper]
If we leave now, we
can finish everything
before sundown!
Trixie, I can't leave!
It's almost Spring Break.
Twilight and the others
have already left
to celebrate the Spring
Solstice in Canterlot
and I have to help the
students with any issues
before they head
home for the holiday!
[knocking]
[door opens]
[slam]
I know you're busy, but I
hope you haven't forgotten
about the Spring Sols-tastic!
The party Maud and
Mudbriar are throwing?
Sunburst is coming to town?
You and I promised
to make the cake..?
Oh PFFFT! How could I possibly
forget about that..!
[knocking]
[door opens]
[growl]
[creak and close]
Nopony is saying your
job isn't important,
but plans you make with your
friends are important too!
[sigh] I know. I'm sorry. I
shouldn't have forgotten.
Obviously, I need to be
available to my students,
BUT! That doesn't
mean I can't help
with all the things
we have to do.
Good!
Great!
So... what are all the
things we have to do?
Hmph!
Maud needs streamers
for the decorations.
Sunburst wants us to pick up
a genuine, pre-Equestrian,
Spring Solstice chafing
dish from the antique shop.
Of course he does.
Mudbriar wants a "bouquet
of flowering sticks,"
whatever that means.
And I thought we were BOTH
looking forward to Mrs. Cake
teaching us the secret recipe
to her famous Spring
Solstice cake.
Oh! I totally am!
But.. we could just buy
a cake from her, right?
We could, but then we'd
miss out on baking together.
Plus the time I spent
flattering and convincing
and begging her to share the
recipe would be for NOTHING,
and we promised to MAKE
a cake, not BUY a cake
and the great and powerful
Trixie keeps her promises!!
OK! Why don't we just
split up these jobs?
I'll get the streamers
and the chafing dish.
You ... [chiming] get
started on those sticks
and I'll be right back!
[nervous laugh]
You know, why don't I
just hang onto this?
Wouldn't want to forget
the things I just said
I'd take care of...
because I am TOTALLY going
to take care of them!
[poof]
Could it be plum blossom?
I have no idea.
[poof] Wha!
Whoops! Sorry Rose,
but I need a bouquet
of flowering sticks, STAT!
I thought I was getting
the flowering sticks.
Uh, I'm still not exactly
sure what they are...
No one is!
Right. Got it.
You get the sticks;
I'll get the streamers...
[chiming]
right after I take
care of what I am sure
is an even smaller student
problem than the last one!
Ha ha!
[poof]
[squirting sound]
I think I have the shower
thing under control,
but I can't figure out
how to describe a towel.
[chiming]
[poof]
Now Smolder, I
understand the school
can be a bit drafty,
but that doesn't mean
you can breathe fire
anywhere you want!
What do you mean Trixie already
picked up Sunburst's genuine,
pre-Equestrian,
Equine-ox chafing dish!?
That was my job...! I
think. Wait. Was it?
[chiming]
Agh!
[poof]
Ocellus, it's perfectly
normal for a changeling
to struggle with
identity issues, but...
Counselor Starlight?
When you're done,
I need some synonyms
for the word "dry."
Or really just help
explaining the concept.
[poof] Oh, wait! Mrs. Cake!
You can't close!
Trixie and I need
to learn the recipe
for your Equine-ox cake!
Oh, it's fine, dear.
Trixie was already here.
I told her everything
she needs to know.
What? NO! Ah! The Great
and Powerful Trixie
might keep her promises,
but the busy and distracted
Starlight sure doesn't.
I promised to help her today
and I haven't done
a single thing!
[thud]
Oh, that does
sound hard, dear,
and I'm not sure quite
how to tell you this,
but.. your hoof
is glowing.
[chiming]
Of course it is...
[thud]
[poof]
Trixie!? What are
you doing here?
It's the one place I
knew I could find you.
I am so sorry about
today. I'm just so...
Busy. I know.
Obviously, your students
are more important
than your friends!
That's not...
[knocking]
Starlight, do you have a minute?
Actually,
Silverstream, I don't.
Besides, I need to lock up
the school for the holiday
and it's time you
caught the train home.
I'm sure a smart and
capable student like you
can figure out the solution to
any problem over the break,
but for now, the counselor's
office is closed.
[click]
I have a cake to bake.
♪♪
[clunk]
Ow! Is this cake
supposed to be so sharp?
[snarl]
I mean, it looks
really... interesting.
Technically, it's
not symmetrical
or aesthetically pleasing.
[trixie growls]
Maybe it's not the best cake,
but we made it together
and that's what counts.
I'm glad you brought
it, and everything else.
I'm very excited.
This is going to be the
most perfect party ever.
And with all of your students
home for the holiday,
I won't have to worry
about you being summoned
to your office in
the middle of it.
Mm-hm! Nothing is going to take
me away from this party.
Hello!? Starlight? Starlight?
Sorry, this is a
private cavern.
Is Starlight here!? I
was told she'd be here!
What's wrong?
I'm Terramar,
Silverstream's brother.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Silverstream is missing!
[gasp]
I don't understand.
Silverstream didn't come home?
Mm-mm. I was supposed to meet her
at the Mount Aris train station,
but she never showed up!
It's a long way between
Ponyville and Mount Aris.
She could be anywhere.
Our parents are leading
teams of hippogriffs
and seaponies, searching
the land and sea
between here and our home.
They sent me to
check the school.
But the school's closed!
All the students are gone.
Are you sure?
I know she had a big
project due for Twilight.
Do you think she might
have stayed to finish it?
She never told me
about a project...
Well, to be fair,
you closed your office
the last time she came by.
Really..?
[nervous laugh]
What kind of counselor
turns away a student
with a problem!?!
The kind with too
much on her plate.
Starlight has always
gone out of her way
for her students.
And I mean, ALWAYS.
Except apparently
when it matters.
This is all my fault!
You all go back
to the party.
Terramar and I will
check the school.
We'll find your sister.
[poof]
I should have known
it couldn't last.
Party perfection is
more of a "Pinkie" thing.
Mm. I wasn't going to
say anything,
but these flowers
are just glued on so,
technically it wasn't
perfect already.
But that's probably
not important.
[poof]
You check the grounds
and I'll look inside!
Silverstream?
[echo] Hello?
[poofing]
Anycreature!?
[splash] [poof]
She's not down here.
I don't see her anywhere!
Did you check her room?
[poof]
Well, she's not here.
No, she isn't. But look at this.
A cockatrice?
Could that be what
her project was on?
You don't think she went
into the Everfree Forest
to find a Cockatrice
by herself, do you!?
I don't know, but I'm
going to find out!
[poof]
[poof] Ha ha! [poof]
♪♪
[shouts]
Oh! What are you
all doing here?
We came to help.
We couldn't let you
handle this alone.
Technically, she
wasn't alone...
but we wanted to help anyway.
Thanks, all of you,
but the students are
my responsibility.
I'm the one who
didn't do my job
when it actually
mattered!
I might share a
bit of the blame
for pressuring you into
leaving work early...
But I don't want
to ruin your party!
We can still
have a party.
A search party.
Can we talk about
all this later?
Silverstream might be in
the Everfree Forest alone!
[gasps]
We think she went in to do
research on Cockatrices.
What!? The gaze of the
cockatrice is known
to petrify any who
dare to cross its path!
And the reptilian birds
are elusive and solitary!
Where would we even start!?
I have a lot of
experience telling ponies
that I have experience with
the dangerous creatures
of Everfree Forest. Follow me!
♪ [adventurous music] ♪
♪♪
The great and directionally
astute Trixie says
we go left!
♪♪
This way!
[sniffing]
[wind whistles]
♪♪
[owl hoots]
[slurp]
♪♪
♪ [music fades out] ♪
Weren't we just here?
Trixie, do have any idea
how to find a Cockatrice?
No. But usually when
there's a dangerous creature
in the forest I
don't want to meet,
this is how I meet them.
We might need a
more concrete plan.
Hm! Suit yourself.
Um, according to
Silverstream's research,
"the Cockatrice prefers rocky
terrain and ample shade."
Rocks and shade.
Hmm, I can't imagine where
we'll find THAT in a forest...
Actually, rocks aren't the
most hospitable environment
for shade trees.
Technically, pine
trees like Pinus Cembra
or Pinus Sylvestris can
grow from narrow crevasses
or cracks in a
rocky rhizosphere.
You complete me.
There's some pine
trees over there!
[clucking] [hissing]
[squawk]
I thought you said
they were solitary!
They are! This must be
some kind of migration.
Ooh! At least there's no
sign of Silverstream...
I can't imagine getting caught
in the middle of that flock.
It's just lucky
we're all over here
and they're all over there.
[squawk]
[snarling]
Technically--
Don't even say it!
Whatever you do,
don't look at them.
Their gaze can
turn you to stone!
So what do we do!?
[screech]
RUN!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[scream]
[thud]
[moan]
[poof] Sunburst!
[zap] [screams]
Stop! It's me!
Starlight! I'm so sorry!
We have to get out of here!
I know. Hang on!
[poof] [poof]
We can't leave!
Silverstream might
still be in the forest.
Stay here. I'll get the others.
Be careful!
[aggressive clucking]
The clucking is coming
from everywhere!
The Great and Powerful
Trixie fears no cluck!
[whoosh]
Come on!
[poof]
[squawking]
Ah!
[thwack] [thwack]
Ah! Maud! We've got to
get out of here!
I'm not leaving him.
[gasp]
[poof]
[gasp] Mudbriar's been turned to stone!?
I didn't think I could
love him any more.
We've got to get out of here!
But we haven't
found Silverstream;
we can't leave yet!
[screeching]
We can't stay here. Come on!
♪♪
[scream]
This way!
♪♪
Now what!?
Let's hope Silverstream
found a good place to hide!
There could be hundreds more
Cockatrices on the way!
If this really is a migration,
it'll take a full lunar
cycle to complete.
Oh! I have to get word
back to our parents
that Silverstream
could be surrounded
by those terrifying birds!
And as handsome as
Mudbriar is now,
we should probably
catch one of them
to turn him back to normal.
UGH! This IS all my fault!
I'm never taking time off
from my counseling duties again!
That seems a little extreme.
Really!? If I hadn't galloped
off to a holiday celebration,
Silverstream would be
safe with her family
and you'd all be
enjoying Maud's party!
Instead, my student is missing;
we're surrounded by a flock
of petrifying.. chicken-snakes!
And Maud's boyfriend was
turned into a hunk of rock!
You got the hunk part right...
And to top it off, we have
no idea if Silverstream
even came to Everfree at all,
but I have no idea
where else to look!
Has that always been there?
What? Oh. That's the
students' Treehouse.
Apparently, it grew from
the Tree of Harmony and...
[gasp] Of course!
That should have been the
first place we looked!
[scraping]
♪♪
[happy sigh]
[gasp] Silverstream, look out!
Counselor Starlight, no!
[hiss]
Wait!
[happy clucking]
This is Edith. She's
helping me with my project.
I.. don't understand.
After you encouraged me
to solve my own problem,
I decided to get my
project done before I left.
That way I could really
focus on my family
during my visit. The school
was closed so I came here.
Why didn't you tell anyone?
Mom and Dad are worried sick!
Oh, no! I'm so sorry.
Once Edith volunteered to help,
I guess I lost track of time.
Cockatrice's are really friendly
if you know how to
interact with them.
[clucking]
I can't believe you figured out
how to trigger her
nesting response.
They are really
fascinating creatures.
Did you know that they migrate
to the Everfree
Forest once a year!
Can you imagine
what would happen
if you stumbled on a
whole flock of these!?
I have a few ideas...
Agh!
I'm sorry you got turned
to stone looking for me,
but I'm glad Edith was
able to turn you back.
How do you tell the difference..?
I have mixed feelings about it.
Technically, I will
always be a stick pony,
but the experience has given me
an even deeper appreciation
for the density and
permanence of rock.
Swoon.
Silverstream and I
should get going,
but I wanted to thank you
for everything you
did to help find her.
I just wish I
hadn't abandoned her
in the first place...
Starlight, you
didn't abandon her.
I might as well have!
And even though it
turned out all right,
things could have
been a lot worse.
You can't be expected to
supervise your students
every second of every day.
I'm not so sure...
I like that you're
always available,
but it kind of makes
it OK to come to you
with stuff that maybe
isn't super important.
Of course, being a
school counselor
is a big responsibility,
but always being at work
isn't fair to anypony.
Especially me.
Do you think if I had
set times to see me,
it might help you decide
what you really
need to talk about?
To be honest, you really
weren't very helpful
with the other stuff anyway.
Yeah... Wait, what!?
Happy Spring
Sols-tastic, everypony!
Who wants a piece of
Mrs. Cake's famous--
[clank]
Sunburst: Petrified dessert!?
You had me
at "petrified".
[laughter]