I thought Pinkie Pie said
to get here right away.
She sure had a burr in her
britches about something.
So, where is she?
Pfft. Yeah. What is
taking her so long?
[giggle]
Just kidding.
You guys really need to look
behind you once in a while.
Uh, Pinkie, you said you
had something important
to tell us.
Not telling so
much as showing.
In fact, what
you're about to see
may SHAKE the very foundations
of your perception
for all time!
Um...a cupcake?
YES! But wait!
There's more!
[click] [boing]
It's an invitation
to visit
the Cheese Sandwich
Amusement Factory!
Cheese Sandwich
opened a factory?
Heh. What do they make
there? Rubber chickens?
That's ridiculous. They
make way more there
than just rubber
chickens!
Gosh, Cheese hardly
seems the factory type.
I just assumed he'd
continue to wander Equestria
throwing parties. Still, you
must be excited to see him.
I am! I can't wait to tour
his factory, catch up,
have him tell me my life's
purpose, swap gag tips...
Whoa-whoa-whoa.
What did you say?
Uh, catch up? I mean,
it has been a while.
I think Applejack's
asking about the part
about Cheese Sandwich
and your life's purpose?
Oh, that. Yeah. It's just all
of you have found your thing.
You're going to rule
all of Equestria.
Rainbow Dash is
a Wonderbolt.
Fluttershy has her
animal sanctuary.
Rarity has her boutiques.
Applejack has that
hat... and the farm,
so that's, like,
TWO things!
I don't even have one.
[groan] [munch]
When I first got Cheese's
invite, I was a little jealous.
It felt like even
he was moving on
to bigger and
better things
and everypony was
leaving me behind.
But then I realized Cheese
Sandwich is a party pony
just like me!
If he figured out his purpose,
he can help me figure out mine!
I think talking to Cheese
Sandwich is a great idea,
but the only pony
who can really find
your life's
purpose is you!
I know, silly. That's
why I'm going to visit
Cheese Sandwich's factory
so I can ask him to help ME!
[chomp]
Uh, Pinkie, are you
sure this is edible?
I am not!
[chomp chomp chomp]
♪♪
Yep. Anypony with
a smile like THAT
is exactly the kind of
pony I want helping me.
♪♪
Oh, hey guys. Pardon me.
Just gonna squeeze by.
Can we help you?
You sure can! I'm here
to see Cheese Sandwich!
Cheese Sandwich
doesn't "see" anypony.
This factory
is shut tight.
Nopony ever comes out
and nopony ever goes in,
including YOU!
So, move along.
Oh, that's a shame.
To think I came
all this way
because of this
personal invitation
from Cheese
Sandwich himself.
You...you have
an invitation?
Well, why didn't
you say so?
[wailing siren]
[gates open]
Next time, I get
to push the button.
Oooooh! Desolate-y.
Hello? Anypony there?
[frightened squeal]
Cheese! I'm so
happy to see you!
[stretch]
Hmmm. This should have
gotten a big laugh.
I wonder if we need to
add more carpet rolls.
I suppose it could
be the mask...
Let's try taking the nostril
flare down 10%. Thoughts?
I have a thought.
Who are you?
So sorry. Sans Smirk,
Vice-President of
amusement integration.
Mr. Sandwich is very
excited you're here.
If you'll just follow me,
it's a short trip through the
factory to Cheese's office.
Wow! A whole factory
dedicated to gags!
Ooh! I bet this is the
fun-est place ever!
[crash]
Huh.
[conveyor whirring]
Maybe the fun
is behind all this
boring-looking
factory stuff.
[clang]
The fun is the
factory stuff.
We take a fairly serious
approach to comedy here.
Observe.
Oh, look. A pretty flower.
[sniff sniff]
[splash]
The squirting
flower's a classic.
Ohhh! What if the flower
was part of a shirt,
but the flower didn't
squirt; the shirt did!
That. Is. Literally.
The funniest thing
I've ever heard.
Oh [giggle], come on! That's just
off the top of my head.
You probably get like
seventeen thousand ideas
like that from
Cheese every minute!
We'd have to
use a series
of interconnected
tubes in the fabric.
What do you
think of this?
[raspberry noise]
I think it's a
whoopie cushion.
Yes...?
But what if you made
the embarrassing sound
come from
somepony else!?
I sit on it, but the
sound comes from you!
We could call it the
"Ventriloquoopee Cushion"!
[excited murmurs]
So... which way is
Cheese's office again?
Right. Of course. It's
been quite a while
since we've had the
opportunity to work
with true comic
inspiration like this.
What about Cheese?
Oh! One more thing.
Our "Super-Slip
Banana Peel."
Still in development, but we
think it's pretty special.
♪♪
[falling yells]
So? Too slippery?
Oh-ho-ho! What if instead of
slipping, you were sticking?
One step on THIS banana peel
and you can't get it off!
[giggle] That's funny!
Wow. Just wow.
You're exactly the pony
Cheese Sandwich needs to see.
Great!
Because he's exactly
the pony I need to see.
[door opens]
Uh? Hello?
[quiet and subdued voice]
Pinkie, I'm - I'm glad you came.
Of course I did!
Your factory is.. big!
It really seems like
you found your purpose,
which is perfect, since
I came here for help.
That is perfect! I knew I
could count on you to help me.
Well, that's triple
perfect because- Uh, wait.
Why do you need my help?
Because, Pinkie, I,
[clap clap]
I've completely lost my laugh!
♪ [horror sting] ♪
You lost your laugh!?
Is that some kind of joke?
Because it's not a funny one.
It's not a joke.
And even if it was, I wouldn't
be able to laugh at it.
Right....
Why don't we continue
this discussion
over some delicious
canned peanut brittle?
[pop] Ha-ha!
[thud]
Wow. You did lose your
laugh! That's horrible!
Sorry to interrupt,
but it occurs to me
that a 7% tighter wind
on the snake springs
would yield a 12% increase
in giggle output.
This is why
we're a team.
Sans, here, has always been
able to eke every last laugh
out of my gags. Which,
which is a help,
since I haven't come up with
any good ones in a while...
Wait. So you can tell if
a gag is funny or not;
you just can't
laugh at it?
YES! And it's torture!
How did this happen!?
I don't know.
Back when I was a party pony,
I laughed at everything.
♪♪
I spread my party cheer
wherever it was needed.
I even started
making individual,
one-of-a-kind
novelty gags
for each and every
one of my parties.
♪♪
[whack]
[clatter]
[laughter]
Soon, it seemed like everypony
in Equestria wanted one.
♪♪
[zap]
Ha ha!
It was more work than
my hooves could handle,
but I didn't want
to disappoint
all those smiling faces.
Luckily, Sans Smirk came to me
with the idea for a factory.
A gag factory.
♪ [majestic music] ♪
I could finally
keep up with demand
and make everypony happy.
Soon we were sending
gags all over Equestria.
♪ [busy music] ♪
♪♪
[spray]
♪ [music slows
down and stops] ♪
But then, one day my
laugh was just.. gone.
I haven't left
the factory since.
I-I don't want anypony
to see me like this!
I-I mean look at me!
Boneless 2
doesn't even
recognize me anymore!
[chair squeaks]
So can you help me,
Pinkie? What do you think?
I think I've got two words
for you! Knock. Knock.
Who's there?
Boo.
Boo who?
Don't cry because I'm gonna
get you your laugh back!
Let's start with
something small.
Excuse me, Mr. Smirk,
but is there
something in my.. EYE?
Top notch eye-googling, Ms. Pie.
Hm.
Why thanks, Sans, old
pal. Put 'er there!
[loud buzz]
Oh! Sorry about that.
Let me make it up to
you. How about some... pie?
Googly eye to hoof buzzer
to pieface pratfall.
Mwah! Masterful.
Meh.
Come on! Those classic bits
put Rainbow Dash's funny bone
in a cast for a week!
Don't blame yourself, Pinkie.
Whatever I got, I got it bad.
Hmm. Maybe we need to
start even smaller.
You can't run
before you can walk
and you can't laugh
before you can smile.
And your smiler's
all out of whack.
Now let's see what
we're working with.
Gimme your biggest,
bestest smile!
[moan]
[forced] Am I doing it? Am I smiling?
I feel like I'm smiling.
Almost! Maybe I just need to
spot you for a rep or two.
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
[grunts]
OK! You've got this!
It's all you! Ready?
Anything?
[groan]
Gah.
I'm not giving up
on you yet, Cheese.
I know there's
something somewhere
that'll make you laugh.
I just have to figure
out where to look...
I would like to take
this opportunity
to point out that we
are in a.. gag factory?
[door opens]
This is where the
magic happens.
Research and development.
It's where we figure out
the science of funny.
How do you science funny?
Of course, there's no
one-size-fits-all joke,
no grand unified gag theory.
But, if we figure out
the funny of one gag,
we can combine it with
the funny of another gag
and make a third,
funnier, gag.
[splat]
I.. guess that makes sense.
Rule of threes. Hm,
one, two, three.
Yep, that math checks out!
Hmmm. At this point,
I'm willing to give
anything a try!
♪ [dance beat] ♪
♪♪
[clang]
[splash]
♪♪
I don't understand!
I've tried everything!
Stand-up, classic gags,
physical humor, prop comedy,
vaudeville, surrealist
alt-scene character pieces...
Nothing's worked!
It seems we've
exhausted every avenue
that even the science
of comedy can provide.
That's it, then.
What do you mean?
[sigh] I appreciate everything
you've done, Pinkie,
but if you can't make
me laugh, nopony can.
But, sir, you can't
just surrender.
It doesn't look like
I have a choice.
I need to figure out how
to live.. without a laugh.
I know you tried your best,
but it's time you went home.
[gasp]
I too am horrified.
So that's it? You're
all just giving up?
I'm afraid Mr.
Sandwich is right.
You are the funniest
pony in Equestria
and if you can't
bring back his laugh,
it.. is surely
gone forever.
But.. Cheese was just
as funny as me!
I.. can't believe
that's all gone!
None of us can.
I shudder to think what
will become of the factory.
You're not going to
close down are you!?
I thought this place was
Cheese's life's purpose!
It certainly was mine,
but if Mr. Sandwich
has finally given up,
there's only so long
we can re-tool
his old ideas
before we run out
of gags to produce.
I don't suppose.. you'd
consider working here?
Your fresh take on
our classic gags
rivals Mr. Sandwich
in his prime.
I need to find my
life's purpose,
but I don't
think that's it.
I'm a party pony!
I need to make ponies
happy in real time!
Ah, yes. In our early days,
nothing brought Mr. Sandwich
more pleasure than seeing the
laughter his gags brought
to ponies first hoof.
Guess it's back to
the drawing board.
Well, there will always
be a place for you here
if you change your mind.
Hold on. What did
you just say?
There'll always
be a place for you here?
No-no-no-no. Before that.
Back to the
drawing board?
That was me!
Nothing brought Mr.
Sandwich more pleasure
than seeing the laughter
his gags brought
to ponies first hoof?
YES! That! We've been going
about this all wrong!
We don't need to
make Cheese laugh.
HE needs to make US laugh!
[zoom]
Cheese! I figured it out!
I know why you can't laugh!
What? Why?
You started this factory
because you didn't want
to disappoint
smiling faces,
but in here you
can't see any!
It does make a
certain sense, sir.
Spreading laughter has
always brought you joy.
But spreading laughter is
what this factory does.
Except you don't SEE it.
You're a party pony like me.
You need to make
ponies smile in person!
Here! Just try it!
OK... Um, why did Boneless 2
cross the road?
To prove to Boneless
1 he wasn't a chicken.
Very funny sir. Excellent
joke. Oh! I mean, Ha. Ha, ha?
Really..?
Sorry. Not much of a laugher.
Here. Try me. I
promise I'll laugh!
Pinkie, you laugh
at everything.
I appreciate what
you're doing,
but I think it's a cost
laws, er, a lost cause.
[snickering]
What. Was. That?
I-I'm sorry. But when
you swapped the letters
of those words,
it was just a bit...
...Funny?
Uh huh.
♪ So you're saying
it's a mix up ♪
♪ of the sounds
that I just made ♪
♪ that coaxed the snicker
from your throat ♪
♪ in a delicate cascade? ♪
♪ If I did it one more time,
if I reproduced that feat ♪
♪ Mixed up some letters
here and there ♪
♪ you'd lelly baugh
tout suite? ♪
[laughter]
♪ Then that's all I
need to do ♪
♪ that's who I need to be ♪
♪ I thought I needed laughter
but it has to come from me ♪
♪ Squirting flowers
and knobby knees, ♪
♪ Rubber chickens
my expertise ♪
♪ If you want laughter
then stick with Cheese! ♪
Pinkie: Yeah!
♪ I suppose now I
should amp things up ♪
♪ to get the thing I'm after. ♪
♪ Move whole syllables around ♪
♪ and change emphasis
to get laughter! ♪
♪ I can't stop now I'm on a
roll, I've almost got it back ♪
♪ Bright folks like you
aren't subject to ♪
♪ my play on words attack! ♪
♪ With something else
I'll have to play ♪
♪ to get me where I'm going. ♪
What you
gonna do?
[high soprano]
♪ Some Commedia dell'arte ♪
♪ to get the
laughter flowing. ♪
♪ And it's what I need to do ♪
♪ it's who I need to be! ♪
♪ I thought I needed laughter
but it has to come from me. ♪
♪ Follow right behind,
if you please. ♪
♪ Walk this way and
I guarantee. ♪
♪ If you want laughter
then stick with Cheese! ♪
Accordion solo!
Shred it, Cheese!
♪ [fast accordion] ♪
♪ And it's what I need to do ♪
♪ it's who I need to be! ♪
♪ I thought I needed laughter
but it has to come from me! ♪
♪ Whoopie cushions and
dungarees. ♪
♪ I know jokes like my ABC's. ♪
♪ If you want laughter ♪
♪ then stick with Cheese! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And now my biggest test, ♪
♪ the hardest fish to fry. ♪
♪ Oooh-ooh-ooh! ♪
♪ A mind so analytical ♪
♪ a sense of humor dry. ♪
♪ So dry! ♪
♪ To make you laugh
would prove to me ♪
♪ that this experiment's done.♪
♪ Oooh-ooh-ooh! ♪
♪ Something ridiculous
and not too smart. ♪
♪ Something.. like a pun! ♪
Hey Sans, how did the
laughing bird's eggs hatch?
They cracked up!
Sir. That is so... ridiculous!
[raucous laughter]
♪ Then that's all
I need to do ♪
♪ that's all I
need to see! ♪
♪ I thought I needed laughter
but it had to come from me. ♪
♪ Squirting flowers
and knobby knees, ♪
♪ rubber chickens
and dungarees. ♪
♪ If you want laughter then
stick with Cheese! ♪
♪♪
[giggling]
It's so good to
have you back, sir.
Finally we can get the factory
back to how things used to be!
Sans, my good pony,
I don't think I can run
this factory anymore.
But YOU can!
Without.. you? I
don't understand.
Pinkie was right!
THIS is what I need!
[laughter]
I just can't have
funny ideas!
I need to wander the land and
see ponies laughing at them.
You can run the factory,
but I need to LIVE!
And don't think I've forgotten
about you, little buddy.
I knew you'd be on board!
Don't worry. Out in Equestria
I'll have more great ideas
for gags and I'll
send them all to YOU!
Sir, are you sure this
is what you want to do?
Of course! It's
my life's purpose!
Hey! That's what I
came here looking for.
You did? Well, come on!
Let's figure it out!
[laughter]
Actually... I
think I'm good.
♪♪
And then I said goodbye,
and then I came here!
Oh, and then I gathered
you all together
and started telling you
about it. First, I said-
Well, that sounds
like quite a trip!
And Cheese Sandwich just
left his own factory?
Yep. But I think
Sans Smirk's hooves
were the perfect
ones to leave it in.
As much as Cheese was
born to wander Equestria
and make ponies
laugh in person,
Sans was born to
run that factory.
And you don't so
sound so worried
about finding your
life's purpose anymore.
Nope! I figured out Cheese and
I are pretty much the same.
We both need to see ponies
laughing to feel fulfilled.
And I already do that.
My life is purposing
itself all over the place!
[chuckle] I agree
completely.
Thanks. Oh, I
almost forgot!
I got you all a little
something from my trip.
Who likes peanut brittle..?
[explosion and squeals]
[laughter]