♪♪
OK, Spike. You know you
might get distracted
by the stacks of books
and copious charts,
so remember what to say:
"Twilight, I know
you're in full prep mode
for Trivia Trot tomorrow, but
you need to get some sleep!"
Huh, nice work!
You got this!
[door opens]
[gasp]
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
This is weird...
Twilight! What
are you doing?
Great question, Spike!
And the answer is:
[ding] Going to bed!
Brains need eight
hours of sleep
to perform at
optimum levels!
Oh! Cool. I thought I'd have
to force you to go to bed
since tomorrow is your
chance to be the first pony
to win Ponyville trivia
three times in a row.
That is
tomorrow, right?
The answer is:
[ding] Yes!
Ask me another one.
Another what?
Another question! I
wanna stay in the zone!
That way, I can sleep in the
zone, wake up in the zone,
and be totally in
the zone tomorrow!
Uh, this is a whole new level
of Twilighting, isn't it?
The answer is: Yes!
Are you OK?
The answer is: YES!
Well, goodnight,
Twilight.
Good luck with
your brain sleep
and getting
that third win...
The answer is: [ding]
Goodnight AND YES!
That wasn't a question.
I'm glad you decided
to come watch
your first Trivia
Trot, Spike!
I hope the rules
aren't too confusing.
Rules? Isn't trivia
just asking questions
and answering them?
[laugh]
The Trot is a little
more involved than that.
Let's start with the
first category of rules:
Categories! Rule 1:
Each category must be
categorically designated
and thoroughly researched
in all categorical...
...participating
in Trivia Trot.
And that wraps
up rule 41.6!
Of course, the exception
to that, 41.6a,
is interesting
itself because...
Oh, look we're here!
Oooh! I can't wait to see who
my partner's going to be!
You don't get to
pick your own team?
Rule 20.16b, Spike!
To keep things fair, the
teams are randomly selected!
20.16b. How
could I forget?
And, based on the
regular attendees,
I've charted every
potential teammate's
strengths and weaknesses,
plus my percentage of
winning with each one!
Ha! I knew there'd be a chart!
Glad I'm just watching...
I don't think I could
handle being your teammate.
What if I let you down?
[chuckle] You could never
let me down, Spike!
But I'm glad you're
watching too.
I'm going to need all
the support I can get
for win number three!
[door opens]
[hum of conversation]
Well, well, well, if it
ain't our reigning champ.
Think you can win again
this week, Twilight?
Everypony here has a
different area of expertise,
so it really is
anypony's game.
But, YES!
Then you'd better hope
you get paired with me,
because I am gonna
rule this game!
Sunburst: We'll just see
about that.
I didn't come all the way from
the Crystal Empire to lose.
And I hope you realize I
have the highest percentage
of correct answers, and I
aim to keep it that way!
Pfffft!
I hope YOU realize
not every category
is gonna be
"Spells So Old
Not Even Starswirl the
Bearded Remembers Them."
Fluttershy: I
hope there's one
on fur maintenance for
adorable creatures.
Because I've been
brushing up.
Hee hee hee.
Technically, that was
a category last week.
It won't be in
the game tonight.
Rule 37.2c, no
back-to-back categories.
But I think
Fluttershy was joking.
Pinkie Pie: Sure sounded
like a joke to me!
Heh heh! Woohoo!
Pinkie Pie!?
Present!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
♪♪
What's wrong, Twilight?
I hadn't anticipated Pinkie
Pie as a potential player!
She's never played before!
My chart is completely off!
I have no way to
predict what will happen
and unpredictable is NOT good
for a Trivia Trot Three-peat!
Do I have to do that
thing where I list
all your successes as
Princess of Friendship
to put things
into perspective
and remind you this
is just a game?
SPIKE! This has nothing
to do with being the
Princess of Friendship!
And this is not just a game!
This. Is. TRIVIA. TROT!
[knocking]
OK, settle down everypony.
I'm fixin' to pick
these here teams!
[excited chatter]
[gasp] It's starting! But I have
to revaluate my chart!
Spike, I need you to find
the part on match-ups.
Can you look outside?
[zaps]
[door opens and closes]
What'd I miss?
Granny's about to call
out the fifth team!
Sunburst gave me the
highest chance of winning,
but he's been paired
with Cranky Doodle!
[thud]
[mumbling] What?
At least Rainbow Dash and
Applejack aren't together.
Team AppleDash is
basically unstoppable!
♪ [dramatic stings] ♪
And apart, they'll
spend all their energy
trying to one up each other,
so that only helps my chances.
LET'S DO THIS! YEAH!
And not every team
is a threat,
but there aren't
many ponies left!
All righty, hold on
to yer horse shoes
cause the next pair
of players is...
Maud and Mudbriar!
[loud complaining]
What's wrong?
Maud and Mudbriar have been
paired together every week!
It's a statistical
improbability!
Which would be fine, if
they weren't so good!
♪ [busy music] ♪
[long gasp]
Oh, no! According
to my calculations,
the only pony who could really
threaten my winning streak is--
And our final pair of
contestants for this week's
Trivia Trot is...
Twilight and Pinkie Pie!
Pinkie Pie: Twilight!
It's you and me!
Isn't that great?!
Yeah! Great...!
Spike: So, I'm
guessing the one pony
who could mess up your
winning streak is Pinkie.
Twilight! I can't believe
we're partners! For a game!
I LOVE games! And I'm super
duper excited for THIS game
because it'll be my first
time ever playing it
and I get to play it with you
which makes it even funner!
Twilight and Pinkie
Pie forever! Ooh!
We can be team Twinkie! Or...
Team Pinklight! Sparkle Pie!
No, no, no, no... TWIPIE!
Pinkie... I'm glad
you're excited,
but tonight's
game is special.
I could be the first pony ever
to win three consecutive Trots
in a row and I'm
really hoping I do..!
You don't have anything
to worry about.
I'll do everything I
can to be the bestest
and most funnest
teammate ever!
[bell ringing]
So... still think
you can win?
[sigh] I know I can. Pinkie might not
be the partner I expected,
but I can coach her along.
And besides, I'm pretty
good at this game.
If she misses a few, I'm
sure I can pick up the slack.
[horn blast]
LET'S GET THIS
PARTY STARTED!
[nervous laugh]
Now the first order
of business is
we need somepony
to keep score.
I'll do it!
Heh heh. I'm not sure you wanna
take that job, Spike.
The scorekeepin' can
get a might intense.
Yeah, Starlight used
to do it, but now...
Well, I can't even SAY the
word trivia around her...
Phh, applemash! Don't
let them scare ya.
You'll be fine! Now
let the games begin!
[cheering]
Get ready to       Get ready to
get squashed!      get squished!
Hey don't copy me!
♪♪
The first category is
"Literary Figures!"
[groans]
Oooh! A category about books!
We're off to a great start.
Hee hee!
Ahem.
Who is the pony that
despises the holiday season
in the old classic, "A
Hearth's Warming Tale?"
[ding]
The answer is NOPONY
because everypony ends up
loving the holiday with
singing, festive cakes,
and thoughtful presents!
Well, as much as that
ain't exactly wrong,
it ain't exactly
right neither.
Heh heh.
[whimper]
Just doing my
job, Twilight.
[sigh]
Sorry! I didn't know we
could have negative points.
It's fine,
Pinkie...
But maybe it'll
help our chances
if I coach
you as we go.
Tip one... try
sitting still.
Can do, Coach Twi-
AND.. don't get distracted
or be distracting.
Oh! And remember to
listen carefully!
Also it's best to keep
quiet between questions.
Got it...
Ooo! Sitting still, sitting still..!
Granny: Which topographical
locale used to be a cavern,
but after thousands of years
of erosion, is now a gorge?
Pinkie!
- WHAT?!
[ding]
The answer is The
Ghastly Gorge.
That is 100% correct!
♪ [horror stings] ♪
♪♪
The next category
is... APPLES!
RIGGED!
I didn't hear
you complain
when the category was
Wonderbolt History.
But-ah. That-that's
totally different!
OK, Pinkie, remember
the category is apples.
Keep your mind
on apples!
Apples. Apples. Apples.
Apples! Oohh, and oranges.
And grapes! And
strawberries!
[gasp] Strawberry cupcakes!
I'm hungry.
Which variety of apple
only blooms for five days?
Rainbow:
Don't choke!
Now why would I choke on
a question about apples?
Uh... what was the
question again?
You kidding me?
♪ [game show music] ♪
Come on, Pinkie! You know this
one. Mysterious apples...
Only around for
five days..?
[gasp]
[stomach gurgling]
Quiet down there!
Pretty sure there's a rule
against tummies ringing in...
[ding]
Um, I'm just guessing,
but is it Zap Apples?
Finally! Yes,
Fluttershy, it is.
At least somepony
here knows her apples!
YEAH!
[crash]
[thud]
♪♪
[stomach rumbling]
One minute left in the
refreshment slash
bathroom break-AHH!
Spike! I don't think I can
coach Pinkie well enough
for us to get my three-peat!
I don't want her to feel bad;
she's trying so hard,
but I might have to start
answering
everything MYSELF!
Look, Twilight!
No more belly growl
interruptions
for team TwiPie!
[gulp]
Maybe instead of
focusing on Pinkie,
you should just focus
on how you're playing.
Or... I should look at how
everypony else is playing....
Hope yer all in yer seats
'cause the break is over
and it is time for
more questions!
Dum di dum. Lemme see..
How do you say
'reward' in Old Ponish?
[gasp]
[ding]
"Reward" in Old
Ponish is 'hlight'.
Correct!
SLEEPING!
[murmurs]
Ahem. Sunburst's
partner is sleeping
and according to rule 57.6,
sleeping at the table
is subject to
disqualification!
Well, lookie here.
That's an actual rule!
Cranky is disqualified.
I'm sorry Sunburst,
without your teammate,
you can't play neither.
Awww! Fine. But I'm counting
that as a correct answer!
Can't stay awake
for five minutes!
Don't worry, Pinkie. We're
not out of this game yet!
[gasp]
[ding]
Is the answer.. carrots?
Ah! Rule 13.2!
No help from pets!
♪♪
Rule 72.8. No sticking
tongues out at opponents!
♪♪
Motion to establish
new rule:
No expressionless
contestants!
Nice try.
Fine.
The next category
is, cupcakes!
Ah! Twilight? I know all about
those! You have to let me help!
[exasperated sigh]
SURE! Just when we're
finally back in the game! Heh heh heh!
Why, that sounds
perfect, Pinkie, BUT!
Oooh! Isn't that a Confetti
Appreciation Parade I see!?
Where!?
What flavor cupcakes did
Princess Celestia order
for Princess Luna's surprise
birthday party last year?
Wait. What!?
[ding]
Double midnight
chocolate fudge
with chili pepper
frosting!
Correct!
♪ [fanfare] ♪
Hey, I knew that! I
made those cupcakes!
Sorry, Pinkie, but you
were looking at the parade
and I didn't want our team
to miss out on the point.
I guess that makes
sense. But...
Which way did that Confetti
Parade go, anyway?
♪♪
[ding]
1547 Pony B.E.
♪♪
[ding]
Vanhoover!
♪♪
[splat]
[ding]
Cutie Pox!
♪♪
[ding]
BANANAS!
♪♪
The category is:
Sticks and Stones!
I don't know
anything about those!
That's not any
kind of category!
Technically, it's
a kind of category
where we know the
answers and you don't.
[big breaths]
Don't worry fellow Twipie!
I grew up on a rock farm.
I'm sure I know
some of these.
[faster breaths]
What kind of stone can
be used to start a fire?
[ding]
The black one!
The answer
is flint.
Yeah! That one! We
both get points, right?
Sorry, Pinkie. Rule 4: Answers
must be specific and exact.
I'd help you if I could. I know
this category pretty well...
Gee Pinkie, I forgot the
name of that famous rock
in Griffonstone.
Could you ask Maud?
You got it! Hey, Maud!
What's the name of the famous
rock in Griffinstone!
Pinkie, you can't
ask me that.
Sure I can! I just did!
[indignant murmurs]
What?
You can't go and ask
another player about rocks
when that's the category. It's
in the rulebook. Somewheres.
Um, sorry, Pinkie, but
you're disqualified.
WHAT!?
♪♪
I can't believe
I'm disqualified!
Heh heh....
I'm sorry, Pinkie. I guess
I forgot about that rule!
Oh, no! If I'm out, you
don't have a partner!
You won't be able to
get your third win!
Actually, since
there's another player
who has also had his
teammate disqualified...
Rule 19.7b. Whereby
players whose teammates
were disqualified
may form a new team.
Oh. OK. Um, I'll just cheer
you on from... over there.
♪ [mournful music] ♪
Granny: The next category
is: Ancient Legends!
Oh, we're going to
crush this round!
I don't know, Twilight. You
seem out of the zone today.
But don't worry. I
can pick up the slack.
WHAT? I am the
reigning Trot champ!
If there's any slack
that needs picking,
I'll be the up!
I mean, wait...
I'm just saying. You
seem a little frazzled
and I do have a correct answer
percentage to maintain.
Who traveled to Equestria
from a distant land
seeking to steal the magic
from its pony inhabitants?
[ding]
That would be Lord Tirek.
Technically, that
answer is incomplete.
The answer is Lord
Tirek and Scorpan.
But Scorpan tried to
convince Tirek NOT to do it!
So, technically, he
wasn't part of it,
even if he started
out... Uh... Never mind.
♪ [sluggish music] ♪
[ding]
♪♪
Look, Sunburst, I
realize I may have been
a little off
earlier,
but I'm really
good at this game.
How many holes are there
in Daring Do's hat!
[ding]
Twenty!
Correct!
HA!
Twilight! I knew that one!
You just cost us a point
AND the correct answer I
needed to boost my percentage!
Well, I knew it too!
You're not the only pony to
ever read a book, you know.
You're right, Twilight.
I'm sorry, but now
that I think about it,
I'm not so sure
about Dash's answer.
Could you do a
quick fact check?
Oh, I know it's twenty!
But if you want proof...
Wait! According
to rule 18.3,
I can't check outside
reference material!
[gasp]
Are you trying to
get me disqualified!?
What kind of pony would do
that to their OWN TEAMMATE!?
You're right, Twilight! I
don't know what got into me!
I was so focused on
my correct answers,
I wasn't thinking straight.
Can you forgive me?
It's OK, Sunburst.
I understand.
And I have a teammate of
my own to apologize to.
Lucky for you, Cranky's awake
and according to rule 57.6b...
...players previously
disqualified for sleeping
may rejoin the game. Provided
they're well rested...
Where am I? What
time is it?
Where are my
morning hay cakes!?
♪♪
Pinkie, you were the best
teammate I could ask for,
but I let wanting to win
keep me from seeing that.
Pfft. I knew you
wanted to win,
but I probably could
have helped a little.
And even if I
couldn't...
we still could
have had fun.
I'm so sorry for
not realizing it.
I got so obsessed
with one thing,
I forgot what
really mattered.
No! That doesn't
sound like YOU at all!
Well, win or lose,
nothing is more important
than my friend or my
team. TwiPie forever?
I don't know....
I understand. I guess even
the Princess of Friendship
can mess things up
with her friends.
Oh, it's not that.
It's just that I already
changed it to Team TwiBurst.
Now I guess I should
change it to SunDoodle?
[munch]
Actually, I have
a better idea...
According to rule 13.2,
players can join the
game at any time,
provided they
start from zero.
Wow. These rules are
really convoluted.
But doesn't starting from
zero mean we'll lose?
Well, our chances
aren't good,
but the odds of having fun
on team TwiPie are 100%!
What is the name of the
Ponyville Day Spa's
most popular candle?
[ding]
-Candle-licious Melty Wax!
-Competitive Library Musk!
Uh... no.
Ha, ha, ha! Musk! You!
[laughing]