Oh, Spii-iike? Are you in here?
Hellooooo? ...Spike?
Mm-hmm.
Oh! There you are!
I was starting to
think you weren't here.
I realize this
is last minute,
but I've decided on a
quick trip to the Gem Cave!
I am on an urgent
mission to find
some facetted iridescence
for my new design
and I can't think of anypony
I'd rather have along
than my favorite basket
holder slash body guard.
Spike.
Spike!
Spike?
SPIKE!
Wha? Oh. Hey, Rarity.
Honestly, Spike.
It's almost as if you
haven't been listening!
Oh, uh... of course I was,
but just to be sure,
could you say it all again?
[sigh] I was saying that I planned
on visiting the Gem Cave and--
Spike: Oh, no!
Is that the time!?
Ah!
♪ [bustling music] ♪
Of course,
you're right.
This is a bit of
a late start
and those gems won't
pick themselves!
Uh-huh.
But the real question is.. which
basket do you want to hold!
The smaller one, right?
Ah ha ha ha.
Oh, right. Sorry Rarity, can
I take a rain check on...?
What was that again?
The... Gem Cave?
Right. Sounds great,
but I need to get to the
post office before noon!
Ha ha! All right.
Very funny.
Obviously, you'll get the
bigger basket and I sh-
Spike?
Hello?
I don't understand.
For as long as we've
known each other,
Spike has never turned down an
opportunity to join me here.
It's his favorite place!
Ideally, you catch
the gems, dear.
And for a trip to the post
office of all places!
Maybe you should move closer?
And why would Spike need to
go to the post office at all!?
He sends mail by BREATHING!
Breathing, darling!
Breath mail!
Honestly, Applejack, if
you're going to fill in,
you COULD make an ATTEMPT
to hold the basket
the way Spike would!
And how's that?
Well, for one thing, Spike
knows how to keep things quiet
so as not to waken the BATS!
AND he usually
follows me closely,
so no gem ever
touches the ground!
Rarity, Spike's been
following you closely
since he got
to Ponyville.
And in case you
hadn't noticed...
I AIN'T SPIKE!
ACTUALLY, APPLEJACK,
I HAD NOTICED!
Um... hi, Rarity.
What's up?
Agh!
Besides my mane? Well, that
is a question for Spike!
Oh. Well, Spike isn't here. I
think he's at the post office.
Again? What is it with
Spike and the post office?
Rarity, what's
going on?
Spike declined my
invitation to the Gem Cave
and I intend to
find out why!
Hmmm. That doesn't
sound like Spike.
Did you two have
some sort of fight?
A fight?
Goodness, Twilight!
What in Equestria
would we fight about?
I've had arguments
with friends before
and they can put a real
strain on friendships.
Well, certainly, but
I think I'd remember
if we had an argument.
Maybe you didn't
realize it?
Do you think you could
have done something
that unintentionally
hurt his feelings?
Well, if I didn't
realize what I did,
how would I know what I
have done when I did it?
I wonder if that's it...
It certainly would explain his
behavior. I must apologize!
For what?
Oh, pfft that's hardly the
point! Poor Spikey Wikey!
THIS calls for a
GRAND gesture!
OK. Good talk.
♪♪
Wow! That's a big crate
of stuff you're mailing.
I'm not mailing it.
Then why are you pushing
it into the post office?
Oh! I didn't realize
Griffins worked
at the Ponyville
Post office.
Oh! [giggle] No! I don't
work here, exactly.
I'm the official mail
carrier of Griffonstone.
Gabby Griffon.
Nice to meetcha!
Ah! Yes, well! These things
aren't for sending...
They're for
apologizing to Spike.
Oh! Spike was just here.
He went to go make us a-
That's perfect! It'll give
me a chance to practice.
You stand there
and tell me
if I hit the right
apologetic notes.
What are you
apologizing for?
Darling, I don't see
why that matters.
♪ [sappy music] ♪
And that is why I simply
cannot bear the thought
of having hurt yoooou!
And even though I don't
know what it is that I did,
I want you to know
that it doesn't matter
because I'm prepared to do
anything to make it right!
And scene.
Oh, sorry,
dear. Here.
I said.. that sure
sounds genuine!
Well, of course it sounds
genuine! It IS genuine!
Spike: Rarity?
What are you doing?
Obviously, I'm working on
my apology to you, Spike...
I don't know how I could be
MORE genuine I mean... [gasp] SPIKE!
♪ [sappy music] ♪
Oh, Spike, I am so
sorry! Please forgive me!
YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME!
I don't know what I did
or why you're mad at me;
just please say you
forgive me! [blubbering] Pleeease!
Of course, I forgive you.
But, uh, what are
you apologizing for?
Why does everypony
keep harping on that!
Wait. Don't YOU know..?
No. I'm not mad at
you about anything.
But-but I don't understand.
If you're not upset with me,
why in Equestria would you
refuse to go to the Gem Cave?
Uh, because I
had other plans?
[crash]
With me!
I don't understand. You
two know each other?
Gabby and I are
sort of pen pals.
Yeah! There was this whole
thing where I pretended
to get a cutie mark because
Griffons don't get cutie marks
so Princess Twilight had Spike
send a bunch of letters off
to Griffonstone about
the first Griffon ever
to get a cutie mark, which
I really didn't have.
Gabby wrote back explaining
things, and after that,
we just started
writing back and forth.
Turns out we have
a lot in common!
We both come from cultures
that don't have the
friendliest of reputations...
AND we're both in the
message-sending business!
Uh huh!
[splat]
I sure wish I could
send scrolls with my breath!
Ah-ha yes..
Now I understand why you
didn't come to the Gem Cave.
Having a friend in
town is a rare treat.
Look, since you're
busy today,
maybe we can do something
tomorrow. Fabric shopping?
I know how you love to
pick out the colors...
Er. Actually, now that there's a
Griffon at Twilight's school,
Gabby's here all the time!
Grandpa Gruff asks
for a lot of updates
about how Gallus
is doing.
Ah! Speaking of which,
I'd better get going!
I'll fly with you!
Well, all right.
You two fly along..
I'm sure Spike and I can do
something some other...
...time?
♪ [sad music] ♪
I cannot decide which shade
of purple is the most royal!
And there's the PINK!
How will I ever choose!?
Gah. Too bad Spike's not here...
I bet he could help
you narrow it.. down.
He is a good sounding
board, isn't he?
♪♪
♪ [upbeat music] ♪
Hmph.
Could you bring the pin
cushion a little closer, dear?
I suppose now that Spike's
always so busy with Gabby,
I'm just now realizing
how much his presence
has meant to me
over the years.
Even closer, darling. I
don't want to prick you.
I have to admit
everything feels a bit
'less than' without him.
Too close!
Oh, darling, it's no use.
Thank you for trying.
I'm just accustomed
to the help
of a small, highly
attentive dragon.
Maybe you should let Spike
know how grateful you are
for everything
he's done for you.
Agh!
Oh, I am sorry, Spike! I
didn't mean to frighten you!
Rarity? What are
you doing here!?
Well, I realize it's
late, or rather early,
but I have a surprise
and I just couldn't
wait to share it!
The Great Gem Crevasse
of the Crystal Mountains!
Whoa..
It is only accessible
once a year
and I thought a little day
trip would make a wonderful
thank you for all the
help you've given me
over the years!
Oh. But I'm supposed to meet
Gabby today for her rounds.
I see. Well, there's
always next year...
You know what? I'll
just write her a note.
Are you sure!?
Absolutely.
Wow! Rarity, you
weren't kidding.
The Gem Crevasse
was amazing!
I'll be snacking on
these for a week!
What did I tell you?
Gabby: Hey, Spike!
Gabby! You won't believe
where I went today!
Actually, I think I
will! I got your scroll.
The Great Gem Crevasse
sounds a lot better
than doing my rounds.
Mm hm.
Whoa! It was
definitely better!
I gotta get back
to Griffonstone,
but you have to tell me all
about the Crevasse tomorrow!
Absolutely!
[grunt] Thanks again, Rarity.
What a great day.
OK! Start from
the beginning
because I wanna
hear everything!
Well, to get to
the Crevasse,
you have to climb
across a rope bridge
because the air's
too thin to fly!
That is amazing!
Then what?
[thud]
Whoa!
Sorry, Rarity!
Oh, no apology
necessary, Spike.
In fact, I was just
looking for you.
You were? Why?
Because I just
acquired.. these!
Passes to Power
Ponypalooza!? For today!?
Mmmm! I know we just
went to the Crevasse,
but I feel I've barely
scratched the surface
of expressing my
gratitude for all you do.
Ah.. Of course I wanna go, but
that'll be two days in a row
we haven't hung out.
Aha... are you kidding? It's Power
Ponypalooza. You have to go!
And.. now you'll have two
things to tell me about!
OK! Come on,
Rarity, let's go!
♪ [melancholy music] ♪
Whew. Are my claws sore!
Indeed! I had no idea
how much walking there is
at a Power Pony
convention!
I know I told Gabby
we'd hang out tomorrow,
but I might need the
whole day to rest.
Ooh! I know
what you mean.
Perhaps you could, uh just
send her another note.
Heh. I think maybe
you're right.
Honestly, I might
need to spend tomorrow
putting my hooves
up as well!
Ha ha!
I hadn't counted on
Power Ponypalooza
being quite so draining,
but I thought we might
spend the day
recuperating together.
No way! Ogres
& Oubliettes!?
Well, I know how
much you enjoy it,
and this seemed like
the perfect opportunity
for you to teach
me the game.
♪♪
Spike? I got your note.
I figured I'd come by
before my rounds with a bowl
of energizing turnip soup.
♪♪
Can Princess Shmarity use
her Shield of the Coiffure
to defend herself
from the purveyor
of poor color
coordination?
Eh. She can try...
Success! Shmarity's
shield holds against
the Green-Eyed Monster's
attack and then...
Spike!?
Oh, hi, Gabby.
We were just...
Your scroll said you were too
tired to do anything today,
but I guess you were just too
tired to do anything with me..
No, no, no, no!
That's not true!
I can come with you on
your rounds right now!
I don't think
so, Spike.
Maybe I'll just handle the
rounds on my own from now on.
Ooh! Princess Shmarity
uses her Prismatic Beam
to change that poor
monster's color
to a more pleasing
shade of purple!
♪♪
What do you think,
Spike? Solids or prints?
[sigh] Prints, I guess. You already
have a lot of solid colors.
Oh, you are so
right. Prints it is.
So nice to have
you back, Spike.
Although I hope you're able
to reconcile with Gabby.
I'm pretty sure she
doesn't want to.
♪♪
I quite enjoyed our
day together, Spike.
Yeah.
Hi, Spike!
Uh-huh.
Hmm. I've never seen
Spike this sad before.
Do you know
what happened?
Ahem.. Yes, well, perhaps
he's still just tired
from Power Ponypalooza.
I don't think
that's it...
Wh... I suppose
it's possible
it could have something
to do with...
[cough] Gabby not wanting to spend
time with him anymore.
What? I thought the two of them
were hanging out all the time!
They were! Honestly, it
took everything I had
to convince him to spend
any time with me at all.
But between crystal
gem crevasses,
Power Pony conventions and
a marathon game of O&O,
I managed to get
some time in.
It sounds like you made
sure he didn't have any time
to spend with Gabby at all..
What? Pfft! I
certainly did not!
Well, I suppose I may have
monopolized him a teeny bit!
I've just grown so used to
having Spikey-wikey around,
I wasn't prepared for how much
I'd miss him when he wasn't.
Friendships change,
but just because Spike
made a new friend
doesn't mean he
stops being yours.
I know, but now I
have to share him!
Which I suppose I'll
have to get used to...
[gasp] Right after I fix
this mess I've made!
Good talk.
Rarity!? Is all this
stuff for Spike again?
Wouldn't it be easier
to just give it to him?
And why are you even here?
I am here to apologize.
Actually, more to confess.
And all of this stuff
isn't for Spike.
It's the evidence
against ME!
Evidence? For what?
For my acts of
utter selfishness!
I don't understand...
These are the items
I used to lure Spike
into spending as much
time with me as possible!
They are? You did?
Spike: Rarity?
What are you doing?
Well, obviously I'm
apologizing to Gabby
so the two of you can renew
your friendship, Spike...
Now please, even if
you can't forgive me
you simply must
forgive... SPIKE!?!
Oh, I actually owe
you an apology too...
You apologize a lot..
Oooh. I wish I didn't need to,
but the more time you
two spent together,
the more I missed
my time with Spike
and the more I used every means
at my disposal to get it back.
I am truly sorry.
You really missed
spending time with me?
Oh! Of course!
I have to say, after not
hanging out with you,
I understand why.
You're kinda awesome!
And.. I know what it's like
to miss that now too.
So, do you think maybe we
could start hanging out again?
Absolutely!
I don't suppose you'd
like some company
on your rounds
right now?
I sure would!
Wonderful! I can't tell
you how pleased I am
that the two
of you have...
Heh.
..reconciled.
I suppose Twilight is right.
Friendships do change.
Of course, Spike and I
will always be friends
and I can get used
to sharing him.
Oo ah ooh ooh!
Sorry! I just didn't
want to drop another one
and wake the bats!
Darling. Catching the gems
is what the basket is for.
Spike: Wow. You two need
to be a lot quieter.
Spike! How wonderful
to see you!
Yeah. Gabby and I
had a great day,
but I'll always still
want my Rarity time.
Ohhh! So that's how it works...