♪♪
I got here
as soon as I could,
but Friendship Ambassador is
a full-time job these days.
Making peace between
Abyssinians
and the Diamond Dogs
has not been easy.
That's why I picked
you for the job!
♪♪
But I'm glad
you could come.
So, what's the emergency?
Ever since I took over
Celestia's School,
my focus has been
on teaching magic.
But now it seems my
top student has missed
the most important
lesson of all.
What do you mean?
Let's just say it'll be good
to have my Royal Advisor
and Friendship
Ambassador by my side.
Gallus: Your Majesty...
She's here.
Send her in, Gallus.
Your Majesty.
Luster, I may be the
ruler of Equestria,
but I'm still just
your teacher.
And you've been wonderful.
I've enjoyed every moment
at the School of Magic,
but.. I'm just not sure it's
the right place for me.
I see.
And it's not the work.
I could spend WEEKS in the
library doing research.
It's just that.. there's a lot
of focus on making friends.
If that's your problem, you've
come to the right place.
But that's just it. I
don't want to make friends.
WHAT!
So, you'd rather leave
the School of Magic
than make friends?
I was hoping to set up an
independent course of study.
I want to accomplish as
much as you have someday.
It'll be hard to do
that without friends.
I'm not so sure...
Friendship looks like
more of a distraction
than anything else and
ultimately a waste of time.
WHAT?
I know you and your friends
accomplished a lot together,
but that was SO
long ago and,
as far as I can see, you
rule by yourself now.
Uh... hello? Royal
Advisor right here.
...And I don't think there's
anything wrong with that!
In fact, I think
it's better!
Plus, if friendships
ultimately fade,
why even make them
in the first place?
You know what, Luster
Dawn? You're right.
WHAT!?
♪ [dramatic sting] ♪
Friendship is more
trouble than it's worth!?
THIS is your top
student?
Friendships take work,
and there's no
guarantee they'll last.
♪♪
They can be complicated.
They can be messy.
And they never go
the way you plan.
Friendship is a hard
thing to navigate.
I remember the first
time I realized
it might not last forever..
Twilight? Uh... I'm pretty
sure that's everything.
I'm just doing a
final check, Spike!
But we did a final
check. Of every room.
Twice.
Ah-ha!
See? An issue of Power Ponies.
Now, aren't you glad
we triple checked?
Thanks, but I already
read this one.
I don't need to take
it to Canterlot.
No, no, no. You love Power
Ponies! We're taking it.
♪ [rushing music] ♪
Really, Twilight, we don't
have to bring the comic.
I'm not even sure how much
longer I'll collect 'em.
A lot is changing and
I.. am getting older!
Just because things change
doesn't mean you leave
everything you love behind!
You're not still worried about
ruling Equestria are you?
No. I know it took some time,
but I've never been more ready
for anything in my life.
Just because I'm ready to sit
on the throne in Canterlot
doesn't mean I'm ready
to leave Ponyville!
When we were all fighting
to save Equestria from
Tirek, Chrysalis,
and Cozy Glow,
I was too busy to
think about it, but now
it's all happening at once!
What is?
The coronation, moving,
leaving our friends...
I thought we'd all be
ruling Equestria together.
Of course we will, but
it won't be the same.
They all have lives here.
We're moving away
and they're not
and I can't help but feel like
we're leaving them behind.
What if we all..
just drift apart?
I guess I hadn't thought
about it like that.
Maybe you should talk to them.
I bet they're
feeling the same way.
You're right, Spike. Thanks.
Sometimes talking to a good
friend is all it takes.
♪♪
So, you're not worried about
how things might change
with me living in Canterlot?
Of course not!
Change is natural,
like the seasons.
That's.. just life on
the farm.
I guess so..
Anyhoo, I really need
to get all these boxes
packed and sorted.
There's a lot more
work now that the folks
beyond Equestria are coming
to the coronation too.
Worried? Pfft! No way.
Unless you're talking about
the coronation,
because then yes.
Obviously, the
cakes are handled,
but there's the whole rest of
the party to stay on top of.
And honestly, I'm
not convinced
Gummy really took
care of the fireworks.
But what about AFTER
the coronation?
Don't you think things
are going to be... different?
Well, since I'll be in charge
of all the Canterlot galas
from now on, I'll have
to go there a lot more.
So I guess that's different,
but I don't think I mind.
No. Of course not..
♪♪
Wonderful work, everyone!
We couldn't be more ready.
Josephine, if you and the
rest of the doves leave now,
we should all arrive in
Canterlot at the same time.
Eloise and Hubert,
you should go too.
I know it's a long
way, but don't worry;
I'll bring plenty of snacks
to restore your energy
before we perform.
Everyone else gets to ride,
since the trip's too much
for your little wings.
We need everyone in tip-top
shape for the coronation.
I'm glad we got the chance
for one last rehearsal.
Everyone's so excited, but
I can't imagine anypony's
more excited than you! Moving
to Canterlot. Being crowned...
I can't think of a single
bad thing about any of it!
[weakly] Heh-heh.
Yeah. Me, neither..
Rainbow Dash:
In...3...2...1...and...
♪ [heroic music] ♪
Look, Rainbow Dash, I know
this is important to you
and we all want the
routine to be special,
but are you sure it needs
to be this complicated?
Of course! And I know
we can pull it off.
Sorry, Twilight. I
don't have time to talk.
We've got a LOT more work
to do before the coronation.
Darling, change is an
integral part of fashion.
I myself am considering
opening boutiques
for non-ponies.
Things must evolve or they
become stale. For example...
I was just struck with
a sudden inspiration
to change my design
for your gown
by including the webs
of these star spiders.
They glow for a short
while after they're spun.
They won't have much
time to weave the sash,
but the effect will be
dazzling. You see, darling?
Change can be fabulous
if you embrace it!
Starlight is supposed
to come over soon.
There's a little something
we wanted to give you
before we leave.
You know what? I think
you're right, Twilight.
I SHOULD take my
comics to Canterlot.
We can't leave the
Power Ponies behind.
I don't think the Power
Ponies care, Spike.
Just like all of
our friends.
All right, Twilight.
Are you ready?
We all wanted to see you off,
but there's still a lot to do.
Aren't you coming
on the train?
I gotta go with Big Mac so we
can go over our packing list
or we won't know who
gets what deliveries.
And I'm gonna meet
the Wonderbolts
so we can go over the
routine one last time.
I'm going with Gummy.
He SAID he knows
when the fireworks
display should start,
but does anypony
really believe that!?
And I still need to pick up
food for the swans and doves
who flew ahead to Canterlot.
If I don't get them fed,
they'll be too
pooped to perform.
Well, I'll be living
in Canterlot alone..
Might as well take
the train alone too...!
Bye! I guess..
Oh, you won't be
traveling alone, darling!
I'll have just enough
time on the train
to weave the star spider
sash for your gown!
But we should leave now.
There's no time to dawdle
if you want the
coronation to be perfect!
That's the problem!
You're all so worried about
making my coronation perfect,
that I'm leaving Ponyville
and none of you even CARE!
Exactly. You moved away.
Your friends didn't
care and that was that.
Actually, not exactly.
Of course we care that
you're moving, Twilight!
I can't believe
you think we don't..
What could possibly
make you think that!?
I tried to talk to you all
about how I was feeling,
but you seemed more worried
about what you had to do
for the coronation!
It's true. I was there.
I suppose it gave us
something else to focus on..
I knew you were worried
about everything changin'..
I guess I thought if I made it
seem like everything was OK,
it would be..
I was just trying to
make you feel better.
That way, I wouldn't
feel so terrible.
Before I moved
to Ponyville,
I didn't really know
what friendship WAS.
You've all taught
me so much.
I can't believe it
all might be ending!
But when I imagine the future,
all I can think about is
that we won't be together!
I'm literally moving away
from you and it's terrifying!
I'm scared, too.
Me, too!
Rattled to the core!
Eeyup.
I wouldn't say scared..
But.. just because I won't say it
doesn't mean I don't feel it..
[sobbing] I'm going
to miss you SO MUCH!
I just can't stop
thinking about
how much things are
going to change!
What-what if we
don't see each other!?
What if we don't
talk as much?
stay friends?
I know it's weird, but knowing
you're all are as upset as I am
actually makes me less worried.
That's nice, but you
should be more worried...
about missing the
train to Canterlot!
Sorry I'm so late! I actually
thought I'd missed you-
Spike: There's no time!
Oh, no. We missed it!
But maybe...
OK. We're on the train.
Everything should
be fine, right?
I'd worked out exactly
how much time I needed
to weave my star spider
sash, and now I'm behind!
I hope Big Mac
can figure out
who gets what
deliveries on his own.
I assume these contain the
FINEST sparkling apple juice?
Eeyup!
Ah, the Sweet Apple
Acres applesauce
for my coronation parfait!
This is the applesauce?
Ah... Eeyup?
I don't have the snacks the
doves and swans will need
to perform after
their long flight!
I'd better find the food car.
And I need to meet
the Wonderbolts!
Where's the coronation team!?
Well.. they waited, but
when you didn't show,
they thought you musta meant
to meet outside of Canterlot.
The only thing
I'm worried about
is Gummy handling the
fireworks display.
[uncertain] ...but
I'm sure it's fine! [nervous laugh]
Well, it could always be worse!
♪♪
Goodness, Twilight,
are you all right?
My friends and I had a
few hiccups on the way,
but everything's fine now.
We really are both
just so proud of you.
If you need a moment,
that's all right.
It is your coronation..
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
Although it would be nice to
get started. Are you ready?
Rarity: NO!
She can't possibly be crowned
without her coronation gown!
Very well.
Celestia: Citizens of
Equestria and beyond.
My sister and I have ruled
this land for quite some time,
but even we know that change
eventually comes to us all.
And though we know it can be
unsettling, it's as natural
as the rising and setting
of the sun and the moon.
Both of which my sister
and I feel confident
leaving in the hooves of the
pony who-
Eh...
You look amazing.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Celestia: And so
without further ado,
I give you the new
ruler of Equestria,
Princess Twilight Sparkle!
Agh!
Sorry..
♪ [musical flourish] ♪
Crowd: Ooooh!
Uh... Twilight..?
Oh, dear. I know these aren't
the snacks I promised,
but it's all I could find.
Well, Dash or no Dash,
Twilight's about to get that
crown. Wonderbolts, roll out!
No! Wait!
♪ [majestic music] ♪
To Twilight!
♪♪
Hm. Close enough.
Luster: OK. I get it now..
Your coronation
was such a disaster
that you and your friends
never really recovered
and that's why you
all drifted apart.
Well, you're HALF right.
So.. the coronation
wasn't a disaster
and your friendships just
faded away over time?
Not exactly...
Sorry I'm late, but it is
SO hard to find a sitter
with a sense of humor
for Li'l Cheese!
Honestly, I would
have been here sooner,
but you would not believe
how busy Yakyakistan
is these days!
Maybe we could get
to places on time
if you let me do
some of the chores
instead of always doing
everything yourself!
Maybe I would if you
did them the right way..
Oh heh, sorry. We're not
the last ones, are we?
Discord's headed to
an O&O convention
or he'd be joining us.
I just assumed that
since you aren't together
all the time now...
That we aren't friends?
That's not the
point of my story.
It's true my coronation
was a disaster...
Well, at least the
coronation is over!
That was something!
I was just about to
say the same thing.
I know maybe it wasn't the
coronation you planned,
but it's good to see
all of you laughing.
We wanted to give this to you
before you left Ponyville,
but things got a little hectic.
Since you're moving away,
we thought if you missed
any of us, or Ponyville,
this might help.
♪♪
Awww!
It's a book of memories!
And we all chipped in some.
No matter how much
things change,
you'll always have
this to look back on.
I love it. Thank you
SO much.
But I don't want
to only look back..
Obviously, the coronation
wasn't perfect,
but that doesn't matter.
It's our relationships
that really count
and we have to maintain them.
But now that we're
living in different places,
I'm not exactly sure how..
I am. I suggest we
meet once a moon.
In fact, my first royal
decree as ruler of Equestria
is to establish this
Council of Friendship!
Celestia: And what a
wonderful decree it is!
We always knew that whatever
adversity you faced, you and
your friends would find your
way through it together.
We know Equestria is in the
perfect hooves with you
AND your friends
looking out for it.
And while we'll always
be here if you need us,
it's time for us
to be on our way.
You're leaving..?
We hope you'll come and
visit us in Silver Shoals.
But now it's time for
you to rule on your own.
You're all MORE than capable.
Thank you. For everything.
So, even though
everything changed,
and you moved away
from your friends,
you didn't grow apart?
And THIS is the
Council of Friendship.
That's what you're
all doing here?
Duh. This time every moon!
Heh. What she means is, this is how
we've been ruling together!
And how we've continued
to face every problem
and threat to Equestria
over the years.
But mostly, it's how
we keep in touch.
No matter how busy life gets!
Sometimes friendships
can be hard,
and it takes work
to maintain them,
but without friends,
things can be a lot harder.
I never thought
about friendship
being something to work
at.. and I don't mind work.
I guess if they don't
have to fade away,
maybe making friends isn't
the waste of time I thought!
But.. I've been so
focused on my studies,
I wouldn't know
where to start.
That's all right,
because I know exactly
where to send you.
♪♪
♪ When I started out
I was unsure ♪
♪ I thought I knew
all that I needed ♪
♪ Didn't know what to expect ♪
♪ But when my walls came down ♪
♪ I saw the truth ♪
♪ All along something
was missing ♪
♪ And I think you'll
see it too ♪
♪ This is where the
magic happens ♪
magic lives ♪
♪ Our friendships weave
together stronger ♪
♪ The bonds grow
deeper lasting longer ♪
♪ And the greatest
spell you'll know ♪
♪ Is how the magic
of friendship grows ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And no matter how
much time goes by ♪
♪ The party will
still be here ♪
♪ with some fun
new games to try ♪
♪ Big adventures waiting,
obviously ♪
♪ Long as we're
still here together ♪
♪ We'll be flying happily ♪
♪ This is where the
magic happens ♪
♪ This is where
the magic lives ♪
♪ Our friendships weave
together stronger ♪
♪ The bonds grow
deeper lasting longer ♪
♪ And the greatest
spell there is ♪
♪ What the magic of
friendship gives ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And it's something
true to pass on down ♪
♪ To generations yet to come ♪
♪ And we'll never
stop believing ♪
♪ In the generosity ♪
♪ Of the friendships
we've won ♪
♪ And because the love
that I feel ♪
♪ For every single
living creature ♪
♪ Is something that is real ♪
♪ Friendship happens
so naturally ♪
♪ Oh, and how I used to wonder
what friendship could be ♪
♪ This is where the
magic happens ♪
magic lives ♪
♪ Our friendships weave
together stronger ♪
♪ The bonds grow
deeper lasting longer ♪
♪ And the greatest
spell you'll know ♪
♪ Is how the magic
of friendship grows ♪
♪ How the magic of
friendship grows ♪