I think you really spruce up
the office, Ms. Philodendron.
Oh! I'm going to
call you Phyllis!
[funny voice] Don't you
look good, Phyllis.
[knock at door]
[same funny voice] Come in!
[cough]
[normal voice]
I mean, uh, come in!
Uh, were you just
talking to someone?
No. Why? Heh.
Starlight, I have something very
important to discuss with you.
If this is about
leaving early yesterday,
I didn't have any
students on my schedule
and Trixie was having
a "magical emergency,"
which actually turned
out to be nothing.
[giggle]
It's not anything
like that!
Ahem!
Twilight Sparkle, the
Princess of Friendship,
in light of her
impending ascension
to the throne of Equestria
and in anticipation
of her many duties and
responsibilities forthwith,
does hereby intend
to make good
on her previous offer to
you, Starlight Glimmer,
of replacing her as Headmare
of the School of Friendship!
I want you to take over the
school when I move to Canterlot.
I KNOW!
It's just so.. amazing!
I'm a little...
Do you think I'm
really up for it?
Of course you do.
I've covered for you every
time you've had to run off
and save Equestria,
but, I mean, yes!
Of course!
Thank You!
[squeal]
[thud]
You're welcome.
And I can't think of any pony
who'd be better for the job.
I'm a little nervous,
and excited,
I'm mostly just
nervous.
I understand.
Of course I'll have a lot of
important responsibilities
as ruler of Equestria, but
I'll always be available
to help whenever
you need.
[Spike exhales]
Are you supposed to be at
a Royal Etiquette lesson
with Celestia and
Luna right now?
Right! Can't underestimate the
important responsibility
of Royal napkin
placement..!
[poof]
Wow.
I mean, no biggie,
right Phyllis?
I've totally got this.
[smash]
[nervous laugh]
♪♪
You know I'm nothing but
proud that you've been
officially offered the
position of Headmare.
[tentatively] Thanks...
But, I can't
help wondering
if it's going to cut into
our social schedule.
What do you mean?
Take now,
for example.
Instead of heading to the
delightful lunch I had planned,
we're striding with
determination toward
what I can only assume
is Twilight's office.
Obviously, our lunch
is super important,
but so is taking
over the school
and the only pony who's really
run the School of Friendship
is the Princess
of Friendship.
And I'm worried about
doing it all alone,
so I want to get as much
advice from Twilight
as I can while
she's still here.
But Twilight's never
really done anything alone.
She always has
her friends.
But that just
gave me an idea!
Thanks, Trixie!
You can give good advice
when you don't mean to.
Uh, thanks?
Are we still doing lunch?
♪♪
Getting Royal Place
Settings just right
is a lot harder
than it looks.
OK, umm..
I know how busy you are, but
I wanted to talk to you
about running the school
because, honestly,
I was a bit worried about
taking it over all on my own,
but I just realized
YOU never did it alone.
Having a friend help
out is pretty great.
Exactly!
So, what do you think about me
hiring a Vice-Headmare
to help run things?
I trust you to run the
school any way you want.
And if that means
hiring a Vice-Headmare,
I think it's a great idea.
Really!?
Like you said, I've always
had ponies around to help.
And don't worry, you can
always call on me to--
Uh, Twilight?
Rarity says you were supposed
to be at the boutique
five minutes ago for your second
fitting for the coronation gown.
Ugh. How many fittings are
there going to be?
A lot?
Anyway, good luck finding
your Vice-Headmare.
I know you'll pick the
right pony for the job.
[poof]
Wow. I heard the
whole thing
and all I can say
is, I am humbled.
Uh, why?
I hadn't ever
considered it,
but hearing you say it
out loud made me realize
what a great and powerful
Vice-Headmare I'll be!
Plus, we get to work and
socialize at the same time!
Oh. Well, sure, that
would be fun, but
I can't just
give you the job.
Oh, oh, no. Of
course not..
I imagine there's a lengthy
"process" to go through
before you inevitably hire the
"best pony" for the position.
Wink!
Exactly..
I'll probably
interview several ponies..
Of course.
"Several." Wink.
Why do you keep
saying wink?
I'm not saying wink!
Wink.
[nervous laugh]
I'm glad you all decided to
be part of the search
for the School of
Friendship's Vice-Headmare.
Honestly, if you're looking
for somepony to fundraise,
I can bring in
enough bits
to have several buildings
named after me.
Well, that's not the
primary responsibility
of the Vice-Headmare,
but anypony
is welcome to apply!
I think the selection
process I've come up with
is pretty special.
[loud whisper]
Albeit unnecessary.
Wink!
Ahem.
Since you ALL have to prove
you have what it takes to be
Vice-Headmare, I've designed
the interview in three stages.
Each stage will test a different
skill the Vice-Headmare needs.
Only those who do WELL will
move through the stages
until finally the best
candidate rises to the top!
So, without further ado,
it's time for stage one:
Substituting for
the teachers!
[excited chatter]
Once the students
get a sample
of my great and
powerful instruction,
they might not
want to go back
to the regular
faculty.
[groan]
♪♪
Wow, that seam
is so straight!
You really learned how to sew
from mending apple sacks
on the farm?
Eeyup.
Obviously, loyalty
is the foundation
of friendship and trust.
But nothing gets more loyalty
than a big stack of bits.
This book on business will teach
you all how to earn your own.
Chapter one: Equity.
♪ [orchestral music] ♪
[laughter]
♪ [out-of-tune blast] ♪
♪ [walking jazz bass] ♪
[laughter]
♪♪
[bubbling]
Ahhhh!
[bird chirps]
[cheers]
In the Pre-Equestria Era, year
1322, Abraxius the Bold did...
[mumbling]
ooh a bunch of boring stuff...
for a really long time.
OK, I know history's important,
but I never learned any of it
and look how I turned out.
[bored murmurs and snoring]
[sleepy noises]
Wink.
Ugh.
OK, Phyllis, obviously
those three are moving on..
What about the rest?
Mmhm. I think we're in
agreement on this one.
[groan] I know what you're
going to say.
But it would be SO much fun
to have my Vice-Headmare
be a friend.
She just needs a little
more hoof-holding
than some of the others,
but it could still
work out, right?
[door opens]
Starlight, I've given
this a lot of thought
and even though I
still believe naps
are a valid use
of class time,
you'll be the one
running the school.
So, if you say no
naps, then no naps!
And I know I can be
a little stubborn
and not the
best listener,
but I just can't
WAIT for us to
tackle this job
as a team!
Two great and powerful
friends taking on the world!
And I know you still have
to go through all this
"interview" stuff, wink,
but I just had to tell
you how excited I am!
[door closes]
See? I told you
it could work...
♪♪
[groan]
All right, remaining
Vice-Headmare candidates.
Welcome to Stage Two!
All of you are here because
you performed well...
or.. well enough, to face
your next challenge.
Parent-Teacher conferences!
The Vice-Headmare will need to
be a master communicator
and I can't think of a
better test of that
than meeting with our students
and their parents or guardians.
I eagerly look forward to
sharing my love of science
with both progeny
and progenitors!
Indeed.
An orchestra is made up of
different parts
and good communication
is the key to harmony.
Eeyup!
A lifetime on stage has taught
me that good communication
is essential to holding your
audience's attention,
which is why Trixie
is also known
as a great and
powerful communicator!
Life at the School of
Friendship is like a song,
and although she started out
singing her part pianissimo,
Ocellus is now
soloing fortissimo!
That's good, right?
Heh. Indeed!
The science curriculum at this
school is somewhat lacking,
but Yona has taken to the
subject like a yak to smashing!
If fostered, I believe she
could easily blaze a trail
and expand our understanding
of science itself!
YAKS BEST! YAKS BEST! YAKS BEST!
Gallus is a
fantastic student.
He's even taught me a
thing or two about napping!
[yawn] Is that why you're
putting ME to sleep?
Um... Excuse me?
I don't know why I have
to come to these things.
Well, most parents or guardians
WANT to be involved
in our students' lives.
Maybe we should find a
different representative
from Griffonstone to
be Gallus' guardian!
Oh, that'd be great!
If you find one,
LET ME KNOW!
I'm so CONFUSED!
You're saying
Silverstream is exuberant?
Eeyup.
And enthusiastic?
Eeyup..
But aren't
those the same?
And are they good?
I mean, you could be trying
to tell me she's unfocused,
but then you might
just be explaining
that you appreciate
her high energy.
Ah. Nope, Eeyup, er...
Maybe?
There seems to be a lot of
nuance here and I just want to
make sure I understand
exactly what you're saying.
So what are you saying?
Uhhhhhh.
Gallus doesn't need to
know I'm "proud" of him!
And he certainly
doesn't need me
trekking all the
way to Ponyville!
Good! Because you're
no longer WELCOME!
Oh! Well fine
with me!
Trixie, what
happened!?
I'm not sure, but we'll
have one less conference
to worry about
next semester.
[slap]
I really appreciate
your honesty, Big Mac,
and you're right.
Parents expect a lot of
detailed communication
when it comes
to their kids
and if you aren't
comfortable with that,
Vice-Headmare probably
isn't the job for you.
Yeah, nope.
♪♪
Starlight, I know why
you wanted to see me
and you don't
have to worry.
Oh, good!
It's thoughtful that you'd
want to check in on me
after my shocking confrontation
with Grandpa Gruff,
but never fear.
I shall recover.
Trixie, that's not exactly what
I wanted to talk to you about.
You can't get into a
shouting match with parents!
Or guardians.
For the final stage of
the interview process,
you'll each have to put
together a field trip
and if you really
DO want the job,
I need yours to
be exceptional
because if I had to pick a
Vice-Headmare right now,
it wouldn't be you.
Oh, I see what
you're doing!
Obviously, you're not going to
give the job to somepony else,
but you want to see my best.
Well, message received!
Wink.
Ugh, Trixie, I...
The Great and Powerful Trixie is
about to pull out all the stops!
I hope you're ready for the
most exceptional field trip
to ever grace this school!
[poof]
Is it wrong for me to think
she might actually pull it off?
Oh, don't answer that.
[loud yawn]
Not looking forward
to the performance?
I know Octavia
loves music,
but a field trip to a
classical music performance
isn't my idea of
an exciting time.
♪ [loud synthesizer
accompaniment] ♪
[shouts and cheers]
♪♪
OK. I take it back.
When I heard we'd be
arranging field trips,
I knew right away I wanted
to take you all to my lab.
I can think of
no better trip
than one through
the quantum field!
I am referring to
time travel!
I've been working on a
temporal transportation device!
A chair?
And 3, 4, 5..
Congratulations!
You are now five
seconds into the future.
You see we are all
already time travelers!
Who's next?
Uh now what?
Oh. I hadn't actually thought
that much beyond.. this.
[groan]
[poof]
[coughing]
Ponies and other students!
Welcome to the greatest and
most powerful field trip
of your lives!
Where Yona and
friends going?
I am thrilled you asked.
Because today we're not doing a
normal, old, boring field trip,
where you GO somewhere...
So.. not field trip.
Au contraire.
I could have easily taken
you to Froggy Bottom Bog.
But we don't need to leave
the comfort of the classroom
for our field trip.
I can bring the
field trip to us!
[zap] [crash]
[shouts]
[cracking]
[zapping]
♪ [action music] ♪
Trixie! What did you do!?
Well, I found the perfect
little patch of bog
to teleport into
the school.
[buzzing]
I guess I just didn't
consider the possibility
that a hive of flash bees
might have nested there..
[zap]
[buzzing]
[screams]
Oh! Ow!
Who told you bees to nest in
my patch of field trip bog!
[zapping]
[screams]
Trixie, go with
the students.
I'll handle
this!
I was only trying
to give them
an exceptional field
trip experience
which you have
to admit I did!
Woah!
We'll talk about
it later!
♪♪
[zap]
[explosion]
Um... Starlight?
[clunk]
Hey, there.
So um...
they're gone?
Yes..
Nice. Teamwork.
Am I right?
Are you kidding?
I don't know what team
you're on, but it isn't mine.
This was a disaster.
It was DANGEROUS!
I think the words you're looking
for are "great and powerful".
IT WASN'T EVEN ACCEPTABLE!
You went from not taking it
seriously to blowing things
so out of proportion, you put
every creature in danger!
And I wanted to work
with a friend SO much,
I ignored the fact
that you would NEVER
be right for the job!
I'm confused. What
are you saying?
I'm saying you'll
NEVER be Vice-Headmare!
But, but, I thought you
created the position for me...
WHY WOULD YOU THINK THAT?
I created the position
because I need HELP,
but I can't think of any way
that you would ever help me!
But Twilight's friends
always helped her..
Oh, that's because Twilight's
friends are competent.
They care about
what they're doing,
AND they know how
to do it!
Well, I guess I won't take
up any more of your time,
Headmare Starlight.
♪♪
[splat]
Starlight?
I just thought I'd check
in to see how the search
for a Vice-Headmare
was going.
[zap]
A lot better now.
OK...
I really wanted
it to be a friend,
so I ended up pushing aside
some pretty big signs
that it wasn't
gonna work out.
Not everypony is
right for every job,
but everypony has
something to contribute.
The trick is
figuring out what.
What if you and your
friend can't figure it out?
If you have a job to do, you
have to decide what's best
and be upfront and honest,
even if that means
you can't work with
a friend on it.
So, I guess that means talking
to them at the beginning
instead of stringing them along
until you get so frustrated
you totally lose it and say a
bunch of really awful things?
Pretty much.
[groan]
[knock knock]
Trixie?
I know you're in there.
Well, you're wrong!
[clinking] [coughing]
I'm sorry for all
those things I said.
I just really wanted
it to work out,
even though I knew
it probably wouldn't.
I should have said
something sooner.
Obviously, we can't
have what we want
because I'm TERRIBLE
at everything
and could never
help you with anything.
You aren't terrible.
And you have a lot
of great qualities.
Maybe not Vice-Headmare
qualities,
but great and powerful
friend qualities...
[door opens]
Well, you really stand by
the ponies you care about.
Gallus even said no creatures
EVER stuck up for him
the way you did
with Grandpa Gruff.
It would have been nice to
run the school together,
but not everypony is
right for every job.
I know how you take your
responsibilities seriously.
And maybe I should have known
I wasn't exactly a perfect fit.
If it makes you feel
any better, nopony was.
What do you mean?
Well, Dr. Hooves has decided to
go back to his experiments
and Octavia is worried the
responsibilities of
Vice-Headmare will take too
much time away from her music.
Maybe getting a Vice-Headmare
was a bad idea..
Starlight.
Obviously, you'd like some help,
and hiring a Vice-Headmare
IS a great idea.
But.. who could it be?
Well, you need somepony
who's responsible like you,
and detail-oriented,
like Twilight.
And smart, obviously, it
is a school after all.
It would be nice if I
got along with them,
since having it be a
friend can't work out.
Maybe it can!
[explosion]
...and I knew as soon as
I read Trixie's scroll
that it was the exact right
thing for me to do.
But what about being
Flurry Heart's Crystaler?
Well, honestly, now that
Flurry Heart's a little older,
there really isn't
much for me to do
outside of the occasional
tradition or festival.
And working at a school is what
I always thought I'd do,
I mean, if you'll have me..
Are you kidding!?
You're hired!
I had a feeling
this would work out.
Oh, Trixie, thank
you so much!
Between being insightful
when I want to be
and giving good advice
when I don't mean to,
I suppose I can be a
pretty good friend.
More than that, actually.
You really did
give good advice,
and you helped me talk
through the problem
of finding the right
pony for the job.
And we know you care
about the students..
Trixie the Great and
Powerful Advice Giver,
Problem Talk Througher,
and Student Care Abouter!
Eh. I think I'll go
with friend.
Friend is perfect, but.. there's a
position here at the school
you might be
right for too..
What would you say to being
the School of Friendship's
NEW student counselor?
I'd say, this office needs
a bit of redecorating!
Potted plants
scream desperation..
Phyllis! No!