Spike: It's not every day
the Princesses pass
all their responsibilities
on to you and your friends.
Luna: You wanted to boost
Twilight's confidence,
so you brought back Chrysalis,
Cozy Glow, and Tirek
to attack her!?
[thud]
Discord was Grogar!?
You've been setting up
challenges for us
the whole time,
haven't you!
My bad.
The ultimate battle for the
fate of Equestria ...
is coming!
Applejack: We'll hold them
till you get back!
Discord: Fly, you foal!
Cozy Glow: And NOW for your
complete DESTRUCTION!
Won't that be FUN?
Chrysalis:
Patience, Cozy.
Destruction
is so... permanent.
We need to show the
rest of Equestria
that we've broken
their heroes first.
Besides, we should have
fun with our guests.
No! We should hunt
down Twilight Sparkle.
As long as she's out
there, she's dangerous.
Is that big
strong minotaur
THAT scared of
one little pony? Relax!
It's not like her friends
are going anywhere..
The fools brought the remains
of my throne to Canterlot
to protect themselves!
[cackle]
Those shards block
their magic.
Careful. Too close and the
shards cancel even our powers.
But on THIS side
of the cavern,
we're the most powerful
beings in Equestria,
thanks to Grogar's Bell.
Isn't that right... GROGAR?
[chain clinking]
WHAT are you doing!?
You saw what happened
when you tried to take
Discord's chaos magic.
Yeah, but there's
alicorn princess magic
in there now too!
I could be sooo much more
powerful if I just could have..
What do you mean
YOU could be?
Um hello, I'm the best one out
of all of us, nobody sees me--
-What are you talking about!?
-The best at what!?
This is really bad!
We gotta find Twilight.
She's probably already
figured out some way
to defeat those monsters.
Any idea HOW we get
out of here to do that?
[stretch]
Too sticky.
There's no way anypony
could get through this.
Discord: I'm so sorry.
It made so much
sense in my head.
Twilight defeats
her worst enemies
and is filled
with confidence.
I truly did have
the best intentions.
I swear I'll make
it up to you.
THAT'S gonna need to be
a pretty EPIC make up.
STAY AWAY FROM THE
BELL, YOU PEST!
NONE of us can use
the alicorn's magic
until we figure
out how to handle
that fool's ridiculous
chaos magic!
Discord: I could
always tell you how...
It would give you
power over all reality.
But you'd have
to ask nicely...
AND spare my friends.
No, Discord! This
isn't the way to help!
[baby talk] Discord,
could you pleeeease...?
Threats are more
my speed. SPEAK!
He's lying! He
won't tell us.
I certainly
won't tell YOU
after the way you lied to
ME last time we teamed up,
you musclebound cretin.
This "cretin"
could destroy you
before you blink so choose
your words carefully.
You're right. "Cretin"
is too polite.
How about 'pathetic
centaur who uses magic
to compensate for the fact
that deep down he's afraid
he'll never be enough
to please dear old
Dad, King Vorak?
[blasting]
[laughter] You missed!
Starlight: Did he, though?
[zap]
[crash]
GET HER!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[zapping] [crashing]
♪♪
Get Twilight!
No way. She's always
needed you guys!
[magic blast]
[whoosh]
Ugh!
Find Twilight! We may
not have our magic,
but we aren't
completely helpless.
We'll hold them off
as long as we can.
That... was a
pretty epic make up!
Just save Equestria! And
keep Fluttershy safe!
[magic blasts]
[crash]
Why are you out
in the open? HIDE!
Where IS everypony?
The unicorns have
been gathering
in Celestia's School of
Magic ever since the attack.
That's where I was
headed when I saw you!
What about the earth
ponies and pegasi?
It's everypony
for themselves!
That ain't right!
Well, YOU can all stand
out here and debate.
I'm going where I'm safe.
Chrysalis was
telling the truth!
They really HAVE turned
ponies against each other!
Everypony's scared,
that's all.
We just need to
get to Ponyville
and find
Twilight pronto.
She'll know how to
set things right.
Please, stay calm.
I KNOW it seems bad.
But there's NO
need to panic!
GIVE US ONE GOOD
REASON NOT TO!
[angry shouting]
Ah..! Because Ponyville's
own heroes of Equestria
are here to save us!
Where'd all these
ponies come from?
Earth ponies been pourin' in
looking for somewhere safe.
We don't have unicorn
magic to protect us
or a city in the sky to hide in
like those cowardly pegasi...
Cowardly!?
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
They're blocking
Cloudsdale!
Said they didn't want
any "grounded" ponies
up in their business!
Listen up, buddy!
Don't! That's exactly what
Chrysalis and the others want!
More fighting.
We know you're scared.
We're here to help!
OH, YOU BETTER FIX THIS!
[shouts of agreement]
Twilight's probably as
worried as everypony else
and tryin' to find
somewhere safe.
That's why I was sure she'd be
waitin' for us in Ponyville.
Where else could she be!?
Oh! I know where Twilight is!
Oh! Thank Celestia
you're all allright.
She's upstairs.
It's.. not good.
[door opens abruptly]
You're here!? I was so worried!
Where are the princesses?
They put up a CRAZY fight so
we could escape and find you!
Mission Accomplished!
Now LET'S SAVE
EQUESTRIA! Woohoo, yeah!
They made a terrible
mistake. You all did!
From the second I got
away, I've been searching
every book, scroll and spell
for a way to rescue you
and stop Chrysalis,
Tirek and Cozy!
But I haven't found
anything! I've failed...
You'll come up
with something!
We can't save
Equestria without you!
You all escaped
without my help..
You didn't need me then, so
why would anypony need me now?
We know things look bad,
but we've been in tough
spots before and we always-
Look around! Nothing we've
EVER done has mattered.
Sombra? Returned and destroyed
the Tree of Harmony.
Chrysalis? Tirek?
Cozy Glow?
Returned and more
powerful than ever!
The School of
Friendship? Shut down.
Everypony in Equestria
is so blinded by fear,
they can't remember
what friendship IS.
NOTHING we do makes
any difference!
But, WE'RE still
free and together!
And it's not like things
could get any worse!
[screeching]
Haven't we learned NEVER
to say that by now?
[screeching]
THE WINDIGOS!
Pfft! That's just a
Hearth's Warming Eve Story.
Creatures made of wind that
spread cold and misery
across the land
to punish ponies!?
Seems pretty real to me! Let
the pegasi deal with this!
There's nothing we
CAN do except hide!
[screaming]
♪♪
That's enchanted wind!
We can't control it.
And we can't rely on those
snooty unicorns for any help.
Build up the cloudbank!
We'll try to block it!
What about everypony
down below?
They're on their
own. We all are..
♪♪
Fortify the shields around
the school of magic.
We need to protect ourselves.
It's all we can do.
[murmuring]
We have to do SOMETHING!
I've already
done enough.
You want the truth,
Twilight? Bad things happen.
No matter what you do,
there's NEVER gonna be a time
when everything's perfect.
But that don't mean
you quit trying!
WHAT IF I MAKE
THINGS WORSE?
Ever since Celestia told
me I was taking over,
I've been gaining
confidence.
Then I find out
it's all a lie.
Equestria's been
falling apart around us
and I didn't even notice!
What kind of princess does
that make ME? I'm scared.
I probably know more about
being scared than anypony,
but thanks to all of you, I've
learned I'm always LESS scared
when I'm with my friends.
If we're facing
impossible odds,
we're facing
them together!
It's what we always
do, darling!
But we're on our own and
we have no idea what to do!
That's true pretty much every
time something terrible
is about to happen.
We don't have the Elements
of Harmony anymore.
How can you all be
so calm about this?
Because, even if YOU don't
believe you can do this, WE do.
We believe in you. In us.
The truth is, all our
lives wouldn't be the same
if we hadn't met.
We're better off because
of our friendship with YOU.
So, when you say you
haven't made a difference,
that's just not true! You've
made a big difference.. to us.
Thank you. Sometimes even
the Princess of Friendship
needs a reminder that
there's more to the
Magic of Friendship
than rainbow lasers.
Although, that part
IS pretty cool.
♪♪
We STILL need a plan.
THAT sounds like the pony
I used to foal-sit for!
Count us in!
No. You need to stay here
and protect Flurry Heart.
If we don't... if
things don't work out,
she's Equestria's
last hope.
OK. Three of our worst
villains have taken over,
powered up by
ancient magic.
Everypony in Equestria
is so scared and divided
that the Windigos are circling
and it's up to us to fix it all.
What are we gonna
do, Twilight!?
The same thing we do
every time, Pinkie.
Try to save the world!
Every prisoner is
safely in their cells.
Now we can hunt down the
rest of the- ..Windigos?
I'm not hunting anypony
d-d-down in THIS weather!
Can't we magically get rid of
them and w-w-warm things up?
Chrysalis: I don't
think we should.
This could work out
quite well for me..
You mean US!
The harsh weather
is the final blow
to break the
ponies' spirits.
Once Equestria is
a frozen wasteland,
we'll use our magic to
destroy those windy beasts.
Ponies will be so grateful,
they'll do whatever I want.
The Windigos are
ancient magic.
It would be unwise to
leave them unchecked.
Best we deal
with them NOW.
We probably SHOULD deal with
Twilight and her friends
before anything else.
I thought it was too cold for
you to hunt anypony down.
We don't need to!
They're RIGHT there!
You think they
know we're here?
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
I'd say they have an idea.
[screeching]
That bell has Discord, Celestia
and Luna's magic inside.
If they use it
against us...
Discord's magic
is so chaotic,
he's the only one
who can use it.
You just can't accept
that you were beaten
before you even realized
there was a fight, can you?
You can't beat us
if we never give up!
As long as I have my
friends by my side,
I'll put my faith
in Friend--
Ugh! Can we get on
with this please!?
[zooming]
[explosion]
We need to get that bell and
get Discord and the princesses
their magic back! Rainbow
Dash, Pinkie, you're with me.
Sweet! I'll grab
that bell in ten seconds-
No. We're the distraction.
They're going to
get the bell.
[explosion]
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
THERE!
[scream]
[zapping]
Whoa!
♪♪
[cracking]
[zap]
[explosion]
[yell]
[thud]
♪♪
Step right up evil fillies
and gentlevillains!
Try your luck!
[zap]
Missed me!
Close, but no
cherry chimichanga!
[giggle] Thanks for playing!
[zap]
♪♪
Do they have to
be so ANNOYING?
Not annoying...
distracting!
[explosion]
♪♪
Agh!
[zap]
[crash]
[zapping]
[explosion]
♪♪
[grunting]
[snap]
Now, now Professor. We all
know you're not the fast one.
[zap]
ENOUGH! Or the dragon's
wings get plucked!
Agh!
PLEASE! Don't hurt him!
Don't worry about me!
Just save-Agh!
Turns out that the
"magic" of friendship
is your biggest
weakness.
A fitting end to
your PATHETIC story.
No matter what, we
face it together!
[screeching]
[blast]
Spike: What happened?
Can I open my eyes?
Applejack: You sure can!
Way to go, Twilight!
It's not me!
♪ [trumpet fanfare] ♪
♪♪
Don't let them escape!
Which ones!?
[thumping]
♪♪
Whoa!
[zap]
The changelings won't
fool them forever.
And I don't know how long the
unicorn's shield will hold!
Twilight: I don't understand.
How are you all here?
Gallus: That's kinda our fault.
You know those long
lectures about friendship
you gave at school?
[screeching]
[screaming]
[thud]
We all know the story of
Hearth's Warming Eve!
We can defeat the
Windigos TOGETHER!
You REALLY think if we
all sing a couple songs,
everything will be fine!?
It's not JUST
singing that saved
the founders of Equestria!
It's what it represented.
...earth ponies, unicorns and
pegasi becoming FRIENDS.
We learned at Twilight's
School that friendship
is the most powerful
magic there is!
Focusing on our differences
keeps us divided!
Villains and creatures
like the Windigos
use that division
against us!
Yaks strong.
Ponies strong.
But yaks and ponies
stronger TOGETHER!
Yaks must be LOYAL
to pony friends!
I know helping
other creatures
by being KIND and
GENEROUS sounds lame..
But I've SEEN how
powerful it can be!
Playing together,
singing together,
even LAUGHING
together.
THAT'S what real
heroes look like.
Were we really
happy by ourselves
at the bottom of the
ocean? Be honest!
It's the ponies that
showed us a better way!
They've taught us
how powerful love
and the MAGIC of
friendship truly is!
We can't let them
stand alone!
We're their friends.
They need us!
Applejack: How
'bout that?
It's just like you said the
day we opened that school.
The more creatures who
know about friendship,
the safer we'll be.
We TOLD you you had
it all figured out!
[thud]
[squeaking]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[shattering glass]
[crash]
♪ [music intensifies] ♪
[zap]
Twilight: ENOUGH!
Because of you,
I almost lost my way.
But every creature
here has reminded me
of the true power
of friendship.
There will always be
darkness in the world.
But there will also always
be those who find the light!
The Pillars knew this.
That's why they created
the Elements of Harmony.
The Elements showed
me and my friends
how strong our
friendship could be.
Together we worked to bring
harmony to Equestria.
But there will
ALWAYS be more to do.
Which is why we teach others
about the magic of friendship.
Others who will continue our
mission after we are gone.
Now I truly understand. The
elements were just symbols.
The real magic has
always been right here.
And the more who understand
how powerful friendship is,
the stronger we
will all be.
Together.
[zapping]
[high-pitched hum]
[explosion]
This is bad, isn't it.
♪ [majestic music] ♪
[whoosh]
[high-pitched hum]
[clang]
[thud]
Oh!
You think FRIENDSHIP
will save you!?
We will ALWAYS return!
NOTHING will EVER stop-
[crash]
[slurp]
Chocolate rain..?
[zap]
Don't look at ME!
Pinkie! You took Discord's magic
from the bell!? How do you feel?
Hm! Tingly. Itchy. Also like...
I COULD TRANSFORM
THE COSMOS
SO EVERYTHING IS
MADE OF ICING!
Perhaps maybe I should...?
[clang]
Waiter!? There's some
chaos in my soup...
[clang]
[snap]
There isn't a punishment
WORTHY of all you've done!
[whispering]
Oh! That DOES
seem fitting.
May I help?
Please..?
[zapping]
[explosion]
♪♪
[thud]
Together forever.
I can't think of anything
that they would want LESS!
[cheering]
Celestia: When I sent you to
Ponyville, I had high hopes.
When you became
Princess of Friendship,
I knew I made the
right choice.
But nothing could prepare me
for how proud I am right now.
Equestria is definitely
in the right hooves.
You.. are ready.
You know what?
I think I am!
Thank goodness! First
question, Your Highness,
what do we do with
all these creatures?
We're gonna need a LOT more
chairs for the coronation!
Actually, as ruler
of Equestria,
I'd like to postpone the
coronation for a while.
At least until the
castle's rebuilt.
Besides, there's something
WE need to do first.
Post apocalyptic
donuts!
Interesting choice.
I know. But there's gonna
be plenty of time for all
the challenges and struggles
and adventures to come.
For now, I just want to
spend a quiet moment
with the six best
friends I've ever had.
Well, mostly quiet..
[noisy eating]
It's like the
end of an era.
OR the beginning of an
even more AWESOME era!
All I know is whatever comes
next is going to be perfect.
How do you know that?
With you guys by my
side, how could it not?
[laughter]