♪ Looking forward to some fun
Knowing all our friends will come ♪
♪ 'Cause we're here to spend the day
Ev'rybody come and play ♪
♪ Let's all pick a meeting place
And we're gonna have to race ♪
♪ Ev'rybody follow me
This is where we're gonna be! ♪
♪ With my best friends ♪
♪ Though we're different ♪
♪ We feel like we still belong ♪
♪ And every day it makes
our friendship strong ♪
♪ Let's go find some games to win
Ev'rybody's joining in ♪
♪ 'Cause we're having such a blast ♪
Hey, did I just come in last?
♪ Doesn't matter win or lose
When we always are amused ♪
♪ My friends stand out in a crowd
Having fun and laughing loud! ♪
♪ With my best friends ♪
♪ We can depend ♪
♪ They will always follow through ♪
♪ It's a perfect day for fun
when I spend it with you ♪
♪ Taking photos with my friends
Never want this day to end ♪
♪ But the time is going fast
So come on and make it last ♪
♪ Get the band up on the stage
Doesn't matter what your age ♪
♪ Hear the music, now's your chance
Ev'rybody start to dance! ♪
♪ With my best friends ♪
♪ Though we're different ♪
♪ We feel like we still belong ♪
♪ And every day it makes
our friendship strong ♪
♪ With my best friends ♪
♪ We can depend ♪
♪ They will always follow through ♪
♪ There's a guarantee for fun
when I spend it with you ♪