♪♪
[coughing]
[grunting]
[muffled speech]
-[grunting]
-[gasping]
[all gasping and coughing]
And that's why
you don't scream
while sinking
in quicksand.
Webby, please
don't tell me how to die.
-[coughing]
-Don't worry.
I've read all about
the ancient pyramids.
I'll show you
the ins and outs.
[gagging] Would love
to focus on the outs.
[Scrooge]
[laughs] I was right!
The tomb of Toth-Ra,
Bringer of the Sun.
I've been searching
for decades and--
-[Launchpad chomping]
-Launchpad!
Mm.
Did you want a bite?
This is the last
of the lost pyramids.
Show some respect.
[chomping]
Sorry, Mr. McD.
[Dewey]
Oh, man!
What if there's a whole army
of mummies down here?
Unlikely.
Mummification was
an expensive process
meant for royalty.
It'd be rare for
more than one mummy...
Toth-Ra was pretty rich.
I bet there's
at least six.
Rich?
What are we talking?
Jewels, antiquities, what?
Pharaohs from this period
were typically entombed
with treasure, servants,
jars full of vital organs.
Ignoring the bad parts.
See you in the treasure room.
Wee!
Careful!
That was pretty
anti-climactic.
[all screaming]
-[all screaming]
-[Launchpad] Whoa!
Oh, ow!
-[all grunting]
-What?
[mummies groaning]
Mummies!
Behind me.
They could be dangerous.
Speak,
you ancient miscreants!
Hey! What's up?
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
Hey, if those are mummies
I'd hate to see daddies,
-am I right?
-Greetings, minions of Toth-Ra!
We are Scrooge McDuck
and family.
Hey, if you guys are mummies,
-then I'd hate to see--
-And associates
from the outside.
-[mummies murmuring]
-[gasps] Outsiders.
We mean you no harm.
If you could just
show us where your
-sacred treasure room is?
-Oh, shh, shh, shh.
You'll forgive the lad.
We're just used to the mummies
in pyramids being,
well, eh, dead.
[all laughing]
We are not mummies.
We merely dress
in this manner
to honor our powerful
and fashion-forward leader.
I am Amunet,
leader of the descendants
of the servants
of Pharaoh Toth-Ra.
For thousands of years,
our families have
served the pharaoh.
And our society
has thrived.
[cows mooing]
I give you good deal.
Buy my sand.
Buy from me!
-[chuckles]
-Aah!
"Thrived" isn't the word
I'd use.
Living mummies.
There's something
you don't see every day,
eh, Webbigail?
-[all gasp]
-Webby? Louie?!
They must've gone
down the other chute.
Into the pharaoh's
forbidden chamber!
-Forbidden?
-Oh, no!
Lucky!
The poor bairns
must be scared
out of their wits!
Wee! [laughs]
[Louie laughing]
Are we dead?
Oh, is this heaven?
The ruby ankh
of Neferhotep!
The ushabti army
of Xerxes the third!
[gasps]
A prophecy!
"To those who serve
the Pharaoh Toth-Ra,
he brings golden reward,
but beware all those
who cross him."
And then something
I can't quite translate.
Something about a curse?
Being stuck here
for all eternity?
Fine by me!
Mm, best not to
touch anything
until we find Mr. McDuck.
-Let's go.
-Or maybe we stay here.
It's a room
full of treasure.
Scroogey's gonna find it.
Good thinking.
Still, don't touch...
Well, hello.
[sighs] Anything.
And that's my hut,
and that's a public
waste hole.
They're awful close
to each other.
It does not
smell great,
but Almighty Toth-Ra decreed
this is where I am to live.
Oh, and here's the
Temple of Toth-Ra.
See here, Amunet.
My kids are trapped.
Now you take me
to the pharaoh this instant.
No need. The pharaoh
will be here soon.
Bless me bagpipes.
Your pharaoh is...
pleased.
He has accepted
our offering.
It is time for
our golden reward.
I give you
the sun!
-Aah!
-[gasps, sighs]
-That's it?
-Wait!
Get back here!
Great day, everyone.
If we skip meals
and start harvesting right now,
maybe he'll bring us
a full hour of sun tomorrow.
You know a mummy
doesn't actually
bring you the sun, right?
The Earth spins
on its axis, creating--
Aww, not the sharpest sickle
in the shed, are you, kid?
I got a Junior Woodchuck badge
in sickle sharpening
that says otherwise.
-[grunting]
-You should really
leave that alone.
Basic rule of
treasure hunting:
If it might be cursed,
don't touch it.
You said you weren't sure
what the prophecy meant.
No, but I am sure it said
the golden reward
is for those
who serve Toth-Ra.
I am serving him...
by cleaning up.
This place is a mess
of treasure.
[sighs]
I don't know.
-Maybe we better--
-Ooh!
What's in this
weird jar, huh?
[gasps, gags]
Do not look
in those jars.
Ooh, a kidney!
Intruders!
We brought that kidney
from home, I swear!
[grunts] Let me in,
you decomposing degenerate!
Those who enter
the pharaoh's chamber
never return!
-What?
-Oh, no!
Louie! Webby!
Sorry. Too much?
Isn't there some way
you can help us?
[chuckles] I suppose
we could just rise up
against the
all-powerful Toth-Ra,
-bringer of the golden sun.
-[mummies laughing]
Yes, that!
Do that!
Why?
We've got food, water,
fresh bandages
in lieu of pay,
a kind and merciful god-king.
What's the outside got
that we don't?
Toth-Ra has got you working
night and day,
but you barely got enough
to scrape by.
He doesn't
bring you the sun.
-He keeps it from you!
-[gasps]
Sorry, it's just not our way.
Don't you want to feel
the sun on your face?
Meh.
The wind in your hair?
Not really.
Don't you want freedom,
or glory?
-[Launchpad chomping]
-Launchpad!
[gulps loudly]
Oh, sorry.
I didn't want
my belly to grumble
and interrupt
your big speech.
Like I am right now.
It's bad enough
you goof around
during the greatest
archaeological find
of our time.
But, eh...
Oh, what is that?
Oh, this burrito?
Just rice, beans, cheese,
your choice of meat
wrapped in a
delicious tortilla.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Delicious!
Oh, where do we get
this bo-rrito?
Outside where freedom is.
Bo-rritos are outside?
We must have bo-rritos!
Rise up against
the mighty Toth-Ra!
Seriously, that's what--
oh, never mind.
Let's break into the temple!
-Yeah, burritos!
-[mummies clamoring]
Never should've
ignored a prophecy.
We crossed the pharaoh
and now we're doomed!
-Silence!
-Aah! But we didn't
cross the pharaoh.
It was just
some lowly guard.
Feels like a technicality.
As long as you could talk,
you could talk
your way out.
Trademark: Louie Duck.
I don't know,
this whole thing
is a silly mistake.
You were stealing treasure.
[gasps]
I would never!
I'm a new pharaoh in town.
Maybe you've
heard of me?
Lou-Rai,
master of all pharaohs.
Basically, your boss' boss.
You should just let us go
before I get angry.
He'll never buy that.
Pharaoh of pharaohs, huh?
There shall be none
above Toth-Ra!
[both screaming]
Into the pit
of eternal screams.
I never thought I'd die
in a pit of spikes.
I mean, I always hoped.
Prepare to scream eternally!
Or until you hit the bottom.
Wait a second!
You can't do that
because because I have
a really good reason...
and my reason is this--
Because
you've got to perform
the proper ceremony first.
I don't see any
mummification tools,
no book of the dead.
Are you even
a certified high priest?
Well, no, but I--
There has to be a high priest
in attendance.
Everyone knows that.
Wh--
I definitely knew that.
Just check the scroll
if you don't believe us.
-Bye!
-Hey!
Wow, that was quick thinking
on that phony
sacrifice stuff.
Oh, that was all real.
Wait, you were trying
to help him kill us?
If I'm gonna be sacrificed
I'm gonna do it right.
Pretenders,
get back here!
At least my thing helped.
Every time
you ignore the rules
and "pull a Louie",
we end up in more trouble.
Because the rules
of this place
are nonsense like this.
Bird, bird,
different bird,
snake, leaf.
Nonsense!
Just because
you don't understand it
doesn't mean it's--
Huh.
Actually,
this doesn't make sense.
This bird is facing
the wrong way.
Secret passage! Yes!
All right, troops.
It won't be easy,
but we'll whip you into shape.
Defeat that gauze-wrapped
reprobate Toth-Ra,
and save Louie and Webby.
Show 'em what
we got, boys!
[groaning]
Good, good.
Work on that
shamble, Horus.
Nice groan, Seth.
-What is this?
-What's more terrifying
than an army of mummies
limping towards you?
You realize
Toth-Ra is a mummy.
[mummies groaning]
-[mummy coughs]
-[Scrooge] Ugh.
All right,
back to one, people.
New strategy.
What do you know
about Frankensteins?
And then we come at Toth-Ra
from both sides.
But what about
his laser beam eyes?
You've seen
these laser eyes?
No, but he is
all-powerful.
Fine, we cause a diversion
and sneak around back.
But his scarab spies
will tell him we're coming.
Since when does he
have scarab spies?
Since whenever he wants
for he is Toth-Ra,
the almighty,
all-powerful--
Uh, yeah, yeah,
I get it.
[whistle shrieks]
One, two, three, and four,
-again.
-That's a boy, Launchpad.
Good to see
you're finally
taking things seriously.
Fill, fold,
roll, and tuck.
Real burrito fillings
are a lot messier
than these practice ones.
If you can't
tuck those ends,
how are you ever
gonna make it
through the
combination menu?
We're going to die
down here.
Now we just
follow this trail
and we are...
-back where we started?
-Louie's on it!
[grunts]
How was your day, darling?
[whispers]
I missed you.
[Louie grunting]
Stop touching
everything!
I'm trying to get out
the way we came in.
Plus, we get this
sweet souvenir.
Hey, I think I saw
a skeleton over there.
Really?!
Uh, no, no. No time.
The prophecy says
we'll be cursed if--
If we cross Toth-Ra,
but that can
mean anything.
Besides, the dumb pharaoh
isn't even here.
Who dares disturb my chamber?
Uh, ba-- I'm Webby.
[chuckles nervously]
-[mummies clamoring]
-Come on, let's go!
[clamoring continues]
Where are we going?
[mummies]
The Pharaoh's throne room!
And what are we
going to do?
[mummies]
Anything he asks!
No! You're gonna
stand up for yourselves
while I rescue my kids.
Right, but if we
attack Toth-Ra,
and he tells us
to surrender,
we should do that,
right?
We've spent our lives
blindly serving Toth-Ra.
Now we're trying to change
our whole way of life
for the promise of
a simple bo-rrito.
This is not just about
-a simple burrito.
-Huh?
It's about all kinds
of burritos.
-[mummies cheering]
-Wet burritos.
-[mummies] Yeah!
-Breakfast burritos.
[mummies]
Yeah!
Some people even put
french fries
in their burritos.
This is the dumbest rebellion
I've ever been part of.
[mummies cheering]
Great, we crossed Toth-Ra
by messing with his stuff
and now we're done for.
Oh, why do you always
have to work an angle?
-Good idea!
-No, wait!
Toth-Ra, Pharaoh Lou-Rai
from next door. Hey!
I am Toth-Ra,
commander of the sun.
Dooh, hate to
pull rank, Chief,
but, uh, I'm commander
of the whole universe,
which kind of includes
the sun, so...
Impossible.
Uh, come forth so that
I may smite you,
vile pretender!
No, you come over here
so I can smite you.
Never!
You come over here
because I'm going to
smite you...
so hard.
[Toth-Ra]
Get away from there!
Uh, I am ordering
that guard
to control me with my
awesome pharaoh powers.
Ah, fine, you got me.
How is this part
of the prophecy?
Webby, it's not a prophecy.
It's a con.
How long you been running
this pyramid scheme?
My ancestor was
Toth-Ra's personal guard.
He was supposed to protect him
till he awakened in here.
But he never woke up.
So to give everyone hope,
he set up this rig
so the pharaoh could
fulfill his promise to bring
the people their golden reward.
Wait, the golden reward
is just the sun?
That's lame.
And your family decided
to keep tricking the people
so they'd worship you
and do your bidding.
Ugh, but the prophecy!
-The mummy.
-All fake.
I'd really appreciate it
if you didn't tell anyone.
Aww, don't worry, Webbs.
You'll get ripped apart
by a real mummy some day.
[loud banging]
Pharaoh, Toth-Ra!
Your people
demand freedom!
To eat barbacoa!
But mostly
the freedom part.
Now release my family!
Hey, how did you--
I-- I mean,
you dare intrude
upon the pharaoh?!
[Toth-Ra]
Loyal followers,
the guard has crossed me.
Take him away!
Whoa!
Hey-a, Mr. McDuck.
Webby!
Where's Louie?
Be free, my people!
Ooh, and pack up
the treasure.
It is prophesied
that you will one day
give it to a young, handsome
duck dressed all in green.
Never mind.
I found him.
Or just give it to me.
And I shall give it to the
charming, young man myself.
A prophecy!
I know! I just couldn't
translate this last glyph.
It says, "Beware all those
who cross Toth-Ra...
past this point."
[growling]
Yes! The mummy's real!
[mummies shudder]
[both]
Aah!
Oh, great. Yeah,
that's a bad thing.
[growling]
[gasps]
-[groans]
-Louie!
I'll teach you to pick on my
family, you bandaged bampot!
Attack!
-Aah!
Mummy squad,
show him what you got!
-Yah!
-[hisses]
Hmm.
[growls]
Right, this was a bad plan.
I see that now.
Attack plan foxtrot!
[growls]
[indistinct whispers]
[mummies screaming]
-Told ya!
-A coincidence.
That beetle could've
said anything.
Enough flapping about,
you towering tattie bogle!
[Scrooge]
Let my children go-- aah!
-Mr. McD!
-[both grunt]
[groaning]
[both groan]
-Aah!
-[growls]
[Louie whimpering]
Help!
I'm coming, Louie!
Hmm.
Huey, Dewey,
stay here.
Launchpad,
Launchpad?
No, Launchpad.
-[mummies gasping]
-Is he okay?
Don't lose hope.
Remember the burritos.
When a burrito falls apart
you got to
put it in a bowl
and eat it with a fork.
Or, uh, grab
some tortilla chips
and make nachos, I guess.
Uh, is any of this
making sense?
This was never
about burritos.
-It wasn't?
-It's about freedom
to make a choice.
A choice bigger than
beef or veggies.
We've lived
our whole lives
toiling in the service
of the pharaoh.
Now we get to choose
for ourselves.
And what do we want?
[all]
Burritos!
Wow. Okay, then.
Charge!
I think we got off
on the wrong foot here.
I could help you,
you know,
with a little buzz
and some facetime
at the right crypts
I could make you
bigger than Tut, man!
Aah! Would you believe
that this is all a dream?
[growling]
Fine!
Look, I'm just a scared kid
who talked himself
into a problem
that he can't
get out of, okay?
No more rule bending.
Let's just do this your way.
I am your humble servant.
What can I do for you,
almighty Toth-Ra?
Die.
-Oh, man.
-[Webby] Louie!
If we can get him
back across the seal
maybe he'll stop trying
to destroy everyone.
How are we gonna get
a ten-foot mummy
back across the seal?
By offering him
a golden reward!
-Huh?
-[gasps]
[Scrooge]
Just like Launchpad taught you.
Fill, fold, roll, and tuck!
[Toth-Ra growling]
That's the biggest burrito
I've ever seen.
[Toth-Ra growling]
Aah! The sun god is angry!
Everyone back inside!
Oh... [chuckles]
Never mind.
So, what are you gonna do
now you're free?
We'll take 100 quesadillas,
55 tostadas,
and 200 burrito especiales,
please.
Oh, well, this is embarrassing.
This one's on me.
That will be $9,000.
-My money.
-Aww, thanks, Mr. McD.
I'll get you back.
Then we found
a secret tunnel.
Then we awoke
the cursed mummy.
And then we almost died again.
Hey, Webby, thanks
for saving my life
a bunch back there.
I'll try to listen
to you next time
and not, you know,
"pull a Louie."
Seriously, that's
a thing now?
It's all about branding.
Launchpad, bringer
of the bo-rrito,
as thanks
we bestow upon ye
the golden khopesh
of Toth-Ra.
Hey, thanks!
And Scrooge,
mighty warrior,
as thanks for helping us
see the light-- pun intended,
we give you this!
[sniffing]
Mm, you know,
this is actually
not bad at all.
-[mummies cheering]
-Delicious bo-rrito!