♪♪
[Huey] Precision. Excellence.
Men in funny hats.
Welcome to the Duckburg
Billionaire's Club
Golf Invitational,
the only golf tournament
to take place
on the world's most exotic
and expensive courses.
This year
sees Scrooge McDuck
facing off against
Flintheart Glomgold,
here at scenic Moorshire,
the birthplace of golf.
I'm Huey Duck, attempting
to earn my Junior
Woodchuck Merit Badge
for Sports Commentary.
I'll be here all day
providing nuanced analysis--
Are you ready
for some golf?!
[sighs] The badge does
require a co-commentator.
Two combatants.
One hole. No rules.
That's not actually--
Watch out!
Aah!
Get excited, kids.
Golf is in our blood!
Your ancestor,
"Black Donald" McDuck,
actually
invented the sport.
Of course,
he lost so badly
that the ensuing
temper tantrums
caused King James
to ban golf across
all of Scotland.
And we're...
proud of that in some way?
I dunno, man. Go-carts?
Hitting things
really hard with sticks?
Not being grounded
for said hitting?
Sounds kind of awesome.
It's a sport where you
try not to score points
to make it end sooner.
Hard pass.
Trust me, you'll love it.
The quiet strategy.
The intense focus.
The-- Aah!
[horn blows]
Semi-permanent
hearing loss.
Go Scrooge! Boo Glomgold!
Yay custom T-shirts!
[inhales]
[horn blows]
I'm glad you're excited, dear,
but this sport requires
a certain decorum.
[Huey]
Everybody move!
This lake will be used
for the swimming portion
of the competition.
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
-♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
-♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
All right,
Webbigail, care to--
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
I've never been
to a sport before.
But don't worry,
I'm gonna be the best fan!
Did you want
to give it a go?
I'm good. Golf clap!
Uh, how about you, lad?
Up for a--
Hm? No. Gross. No.
Not even a little.
Are you guys kidding me?
A chance to learn
the sport our family invented
from the greatest player
who ever lived,
I assume because
I don't follow golf?
-I want in.
-Atta boy!
Let's hone
that wildly misplaced
enthusiasm, shall we?
We'll start
with your swing.
Practice all you want,
McDuck!
You won't be
winning this year.
You say that
every year, Flinty.
And every year
you go home crying.
My eyes dry out very easily!
But this year I'll prove
that I'm the best Scottish
billionaire golfer!
I've hired
the world's best player...
to be my caddie!
Okay, if you want
to be a winner,
just follow
these three rules--
[gasps]
I'm already a winner!
Nobody tells
Flintheart Glomgold
what to do!
You're fired!
Oh!
[straining]
You there! Green one!
How would you
like the honor of caddying
under the great
Flintheart Glomgold?
Eh.
A chance to bask in
the collective glory of victory?
Blergh.
I tip by the hole.
Ehh,
if I'm gonna be bored,
I may as well
get paid for it.
Ha! Your own nephew's
abandoning you!
Soon, there'll be nobody
left to support you--
-[explosion]
-[all gasp]
Sorry.
Timer went off early.
[horn blowing]
Here we are, moments away
from the Classic's
opening coin toss.
Glomgold now very obviously
switching the official coin
for one that has
"heads" on both sides.
[Launchpad]
Very sneaky.
[Huey] He tosses
the double-headed coin,
-and Glomgold
has called tails.
-What? Aah!
Glomgold, clearly embarrassed,
now trying to throw the coin
into the ocean.
-[Launchpad]
He does not make it.
-[shouting angrily]
[Huey] Scrooge, desperate
to move things along,
-has agreed to let Glomgold
"win" the coin toss.
-[Glomgold] Ha!
Wow, what a game.
See ya next time,
everybody.
It hasn't even--
Launchpad!
That coin toss was only
the beginning, Scrooge!
The moment of reckoning
is at hand, and lo--
We've got another
ten minutes of gloating
before he takes a shot.
Let's work on your drive.
Hey, get back here!
I'll show you
how a real golfer
would play this hole!
All right, boy,
how would your uncle
play this hole?
Uh, just...
Why don't ya hit the ball
in the hole, I guess?
Hit the ball...
in the hole?
Of course!
I've been over-thinking it
this entire time!
Holy haggis!
It stayed on the course!
It went forward.
I'm not on fire.
That might be the best shot
I've ever taken!
Nice work, caddie!
Focus. Filter out
all distraction.
Go Scrooge!
Now remember:
Hips back. Shoulders down.
Tail tucked.
Controlled swing.
[grunting]
Was that okay?
Ha ha! You're a natural.
A little unpolished, sure,
but if we can focus
that swing,
you'll be almost
as good as me one day.
Really?
With a teacher
like you,
he could be
even better!
Really?!
Or, you know, nearly as good,
but not quite.
After years of hard work
and practice.
No need to get
the boy's hopes up.
[Glomgold] Scrooge!
Quit stalling! You're up!
Scrooge, the returning champion,
approaching the first hole.
[gobbling]
He's probably worried
Glomgold will use
his one free tackle
before the speed round
in the third quarter.
What do you think
is happening here?
One heck of a game!
Taking his time
with the shot...
Tell me about it.
Just hit the ball!
Aah! Ohh...
Ouch! And it's deep
in the rough.
Ha ha! Nice shot, Scroogey!
Decide to take a shortcut
through the weeds?
Unless... Boy!
Why didn't you
tell me about the shortcut
through the weeds?!
Oh, I can't believe it.
I haven't had a shot
that bad in 40 years.
What in the blazes...
[Launchpad and Huey screaming]
[Huey groaning]
Ah, yes. Scrooge
went for the classic
"magic forest stones"
bonus.
Risky, but it paid off.
Oooh, it wasn't a shortcut.
The great McDuck finally
hit a right clunker!
I did not!
I was simply getting
a lay of the terrain.
See, the key
to a good golf game--
Take the penalty
and let's get back
to the course.
A Scotsman plays it
where it lands.
[low humming noise]
[electricity buzzing]
Um, Mr. McDuck?
Heavenly hollyhock.
[Webby]
Mythical glowing stones.
Mysterious
teleportation circles.
[gasps] Do you know
what this means?
No more golf!
Whoo-hoo!
Does anybody see any clues
about where we are?
There are these two orbs.
Hmm, interesting.
And it looks like they'd fit
in that hole over there.
Hm. Okay.
Aah! Cannae touch
the blasted things.
-[zapping]
-[Glomgold] Aah!
-Aah!
Maybe we can use
these clubs.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Guys, it's golf.
It's still golf!
Okay, that's it,
I'm going home.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
Where did home go?
Welcome back to the
Billionaire's Club Classic,
where, in a bizarre turn
of events,
the players have become trapped
in some sort
of mystical faerie realm.
But they remain undeterred.
For more, we go
to two tiny horses.
What are you-- Aah!
[high-pitched]
Greetings!
We're Briar and Bramble,
the keepers of this realm.
Talking animals
wearing clothes?!
Oh, no,
did we die?
Are we
in Webby heaven?
Bet you're all wondering
what this place is.
It's a mystical
golf course, right?
Did ancient Scottish Druids
build a secret course
so they could
keep playing golf,
even after Black Donald
got it banned?
Uh, yep.
That's all correct.
Here, hop on our backs!
We'll give you a tour.
♪ Ohh! ♪
Wait.
Why are your manes wet?
[gasps]
You're kelpies, aren't you?
You tempt people
onto your backs,
then carry them off
into the sea!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We just got
out of the shower,
that's all.
Hmm? Hmm!
Fine. That
is generally our plan.
Come on, Bramble.
If they're sooo smart,
they must know
all about the treasure
at the end of the course.
Treasure?
First to complete
this course
will win
the priceless Druid's Cup.
Thus proving them
to be the finest golfer
in every plane of reality!
Ooh!
Uh-huh. Okay.
Well anyone else think
we should ignore
the murder ponies
and go home?
You'll all
be sent home safely
as soon as you finish
the course.
That is, if you
finish the course.
Um. Did we mention
the trophy has
custom engraving? Ooh!
Dewey, you've found
your calling.
Easy, lad. You can't
just flail that thing
at random anymore.
There's too much at stake.
If we lose the ball,
we don't go home.
We have got to play smart.
You might want
to get started.
It can be awful hard to play
once those mists roll in.
Come on,
we're wasting time!
Caddie! My clubs!
Caddie?
Ahem.
Hop on our backs.
We'll take you
to the next hole
and definitely
not to a watery grave.
You are the least fun
victims ever.
What the... ?!
Aw, shoulda
seen that coming.
How? How could he have
possibly seen that coming?
Give it back,
you overgrown puddle!
Aah! Caddie! Help!
Ohh! [straining]
Here!
Oh, it's like you don't
even want to be rescued.
-[zapping]
-[Glomgold] Aah!
Old golf tip: let
Flinty spring that trap,
the rest
is just patience.
Patience.
Patience!
Uh!
If you'd just let me--
Not the time
for a reckless clobber.
Come on,
ya blasted tentacle!
And besides,
you cannae just sub in.
It's against
the rules of golf.
[Briar]
It's okay!
Druid Golf
allows for twosomes!
Water's great,
by the way!
Oh, give it a go.
But don't get
too discouraged
if you don't make it.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uhh!
Go Dewey!
Good shot, lad.
Very proud of you.
You don't sound proud.
Yeah!
Scrooge and Dewey,
taking on the world,
one hole at time!
[Huey]
There you have it.
Another brash young upstart
destined to surpass
his aging mentor.
Is the commentary
still necessary?
It helps me feel
in control during
a frankly insane situation.
I like talking this way
'cause it makes everything
sound important.
Baloney trampoline.
[music playing]
[grumbling]
Nailed it!
Whoo-hoo, yeah!
Go Dewey!
Scrooge, still in the lead
on the 17th hole,
but Glomgold is closing in.
Hey, so is that weird mist.
Nice job. Nice job.
Aaand nice job.
Not nice enough.
Glomgold's
gonna pass us!
You bet your ballast I am!
I'll prove
once and for all
I'm the best golfer
in this or any other--
Aah! Caddie!
I'm pretty sure I can
get it to the hole
with one swing.
Let me go.
And risk dumping it
down into the water?
Absolutely not.
[Briar, imitating Webby]
Aw, give him a chance.
If he hits it in the water,
we can jump
on the kelpies to get it!
I'm the small girl duck.
You can trust me.
Oh, whoop!
[splash]
Come on.
I can do this!
Do what?
Whack the ball blindly?
Into the hole! Yes!
Like I've been doing
all day.
Why don't you trust me
to make this?
You don't have
the experience.
It takes time, effort--
-Hey!
-[grunting]
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
-[cheering]
[Dewey]
It's so easy!
No!
[growling]
I'm sorry. I just knew
I could, so I--
You pull a club
out of a Scotsman's hand,
you'd best be prepared
to knock him out with it!
Hey, I made the shot.
You disobeyed me
and risked the entire game
with your showboating!
I'm showboating?
This whole thing
has been about
how great you are.
You're so worried that
someone might actually
be better than you
at something
that you keep--
See here, I am
an inter-dimensionally
ranked golfer!
Whatever. I'm over
this dumb sport anyway.
Finish the course
so we can go home.
Now hold on.
I didn't mean to...
-[whack]
-[Glomgold]
Outta the way, McDuck!
Hah!
[Huey]
The last hole.
Looks like some
sort of Hall of Fame.
Well, your old Uncle
Scrooge will be joining
it soon enough, eh?
Let's get this over with.
Scrooge, lining up,
and none too soon.
Morale is not high.
Uh, Mr. McDuck?
Those mists are
getting really close.
Well, that's ominous.
[Huey] And he hooks it
onto the wall.
Nice work. How are you
going to get up there?
[Glomgold]
It's happening.
I'm one stroke away
from claiming the trophy
and beating Scrooge McDuck!
As soon as I take this swing,
I, Flintheart Glomgold,
will be the winner of
the Billionaire's Club Classic.
Sure, you may have won
the previous 27,
but I think
we can all agree
this one counts
more than the rest combined.
Uh, Flinty?
Stuff it, Scrooge.
I'm savoring the moment.
Caddie, savor with me.
Caddie?
[growls]
Um...
Oh. I see.
Curse you, McDuck!
Curse you and my love
of moment-savoring!
Aah!
The mist turns people
to stone!
Those statues used
to be real golfers!
[sinister laughter]
Oh, by the way,
the mists of Moorshire?
They turn mortals to stone.
Those statues are--
You just said all that,
didn't you?
So you're doomed.
Better to let us drown
you instead. Let's go!
[all] No!
You people are no fun.
We have to finish
the course.
Those hoofed hostiles
said it would get us home.
[grunting]
Everybody! We need
to support Scrooge!
Why? He hasn't
supported me all day.
No, we need
to support Scrooge.
Not everything
is a life lesson!
[all straining]
Louie! Hand me the club!
Oh, right, sure.
Nope, not the time.
Oh, my.
Scrooge, taking his time,
I'm not sure why.
There are lives at stake.
Wait, whose?
Oh, right.
[groans]
This has been Huey Duck,
signing off!
Man, I hate this sport.
[Webby]
Come on, Scrooge,
I know you can do it.
Webby! Guys! No!
What are you waiting for?
Take the stupid shot!
-Not me.
-What?
I cannae make the shot.
You can.
I know you can do it.
Okay, okay.
Filter out all distractions.
Hips back. Shoulders down.
Tail tucked.
Aah! Whack the ball!
Whack the ball!
[bell rings]
Yes!
-Aah!
-Oof!
You did it, lad!
I knew you could!
[Briar] Congratulations,
champions!
You are the first players
to ever complete
the Druid's Cup.
Go on. You earned it.
[Dewey]
"Scroge" and "Douise"?
Sorry.
It was a rush job.
We really didn't expect
you to make it.
Now, who's up
for a victory swim?
[all] No!
Yaah!
You! You let me
turn to stone!
You're the worst caddie ever!
You're fired!
As soon as you help me out.
Ahh!
-[whack]
-[Glomgold screams]
You know, we could use
another player
for next year's
Invitational.
I'd love someone
who actually gave me
a run for my money.
Eh, I think
my pro career is over.
I'm going out on top.
Still, I'd be up for
a friendly round now and then.
Sounds grand.
Whooo! Screwy for life!
In your face,
everybody who's not them!
Whoo-hoo!
Maybe just
the two of us.
Well, there
you have it, folks.
Scrooge let go of his ego
and learned that
a good teacher's pride
should be in his student,
not himself.
That's...
actually a good insight.
Wow, I'm impressed,
Launchpad.
And you're choking
on golf balls.
They look like tasty eggs!
I resisted for so long!