♪♪
Compass?
CB radio?
Sunscreen.
Hot dog costumes!
I'm sorry, what?
You know, in case
we get lost at sea
and one of us--
probably Louie--
goes mad with hunger,
we'll put these on!
Louie hates hot dogs,
so he probably won't eat us.
Are you saying that Louie
would rather eat us
than hot dogs?
I do hate hot dogs.
I think we'll be good.
[birds squawk]
So what do you
need me to do?
I think that's everything.
Louie's got the canteens,
Dewey's got the paddles...
Nautical leap! Yar!
-Oof!
-And nailed it.
[fighting noises]
Relax, we've taken
this old kayak
out dozens of times--
we got this.
Maybe I could be
in charge of the map.
Oh, Huey always
handles the map,
thanks to old
Captain Lost here.
Hey! That's Captain Lost, sir,
to you.
Captain Lost!
[laughing]
I don't know why we're laughing!
Ah, it's this whole crazy story
where we all went kayaking,
and Louie--
Got lost?
Yeah. You sorta had
to be there, I guess.
But now you will be!
Onward, to adventure!
-[all grunting]
-Pardon me.
Come on, why aren't we
"to adventuring"?
[gasps] Oof!
I guess we never had
to stick four people
in this thing.
Here, Webby, you can
take my spot.
-No, no, it's okay.
-Are you sure?
Yeah, I'll just go
when you guys get back.
Unless Captain Lost
gets us lost again!
Captain Lost!
It's just so fun
to chant!
[dramatic music]
[reading]
Looks like Webby's
going out to sea after all.
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring-do ♪
♪ Bad- and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring bad
and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
I'll save you,
noble sailor!
"Shipwrecked freighter crew
surrounded by dolphins?!"
Aw...
"...who are tearing us
limb from limb!"
Oh, no! I'll... what?
I'm here to save
either a sailor,
group of sailors,
or a shark
from a sea serpent/
pirate/M-agent/and/or scurvy!
What? N-no,
those are from me.
I'm just messing around,
you know, like a game?
Fun! Let me try!
"Please recycle
this bottle."
Okay, I don't think
you get this game.
Hi, I'm Webby.
Mm. Hey.
Is that a vintage
Sumerian talisman?
Dunno. Found it
at a thrift shop.
How-- ha! You got
some pink in your hair.
I-I think someone
pranked you.
It's supposed
to look this way.
Oh! Oh...
I like your shirt!
Mm, not my shirt.
Actually got it
off the lead singer
of the Featherweights
after a gig in Paris.
You've been
to Paris?!
You haven't?
Oh, you gotta go.
It's like here,
only fancier.
I've always wanted
to go to Paris,
crawl around
in the catacombs,
maybe touch a skull.
[giggles]
Welp, game over.
I got it!
[grunting]
Here!
That was actually
pretty cool.
Are you, like,
in the circus?
Circus acrobats
keep elephant hairs
in their pockets for good luck!
I don't know why
I just told you that,
or why I'm still talking,
or why I pointed out
the fact I'm still talking, or--
-Whoa, easy, Flippy.
-Webby!
Lena. Thanks
for the bottle.
[splashes]
Hey, you wanna come with me
to this blowout
on the edge of town?
Should be cool.
I've never actually seen
a proper explosion!
It's another name
for "party."
Yep! Totally knew that.
Could we just wait
for my friends
so I could let them know
where I'm going?
But the party could
be over by then.
Come on, it'll be
an adventure!
This is a party?
All the best parties
are at burnt-out junkyards.
So I'm gonna need you
to do your whole
pom-pom hardcore thing
up the wall, drop down
and open the door for
me. Cool?
Cool!
Wait, aren't you invited?
It's not an adventure
if you're invited.
[grunting]
[crashing]
-Got it!
-Nice.
Oh... yeah!
You want
to blow it up, don't you?
[imitates explosion]
[explosion dwindles]
[rock playing]
Wow! My first
costume party!
Oh, this isn't
a costume party.
-[gasps]
-And then...
What are
the Beagle Boys doing here?
Everyone here is
a Beagle.
It's a Beagle Boy party!
-[door slams]
-My boys!
[cheering]
Look around! You can see
the future of Duckburg is ours!
It warms my heart
to see all of you here together
as a family--
the Original Classics,
the Glam Yankees,
the Deju Vus,
the Sixth Avenue Meanies,
the Sixth Avenue Frendlies,
the Longboard Taquitos,
the Deju Vus,
the Tumblebums, ugh,
the Ugly Failures,
and the Deju Vus.
What do you all have
in common?
You love your mom!
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
dear Mom... ♪
This is Ma Beagle's
birthday party?
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
[cheering]
We've gotta get
out of here.
[grunts]
You're the brat
that got Ma busted!
Say what now?
Uh-uh, no way.
Ma said we're not supposed
to mess with them, remember?
That's the brat
that got me busted!
Bring her here!
Oh, every single time.
-Huh?
-Whaaa!
[laughing]
Run, Webby!
Thanks for the hospitality!
Sorry we have to go!
[spits] Get 'em!
[both panting]
We almost died!
[both gasp]
[angry growls]
[both] We're gonna die!
[screaming]
[honking]
Oh, come on.
Come on.
[frightened yells]
[back-up noise beeping]
[grunting]
-Hurry!
-Rwargh!
Real smooth moves
back there.
Ha! Thanks!
Wait, was that
sarcastic?
-Nope.
-Ha! Thanks!
Wait, was that?
What does Ma Beagle
have against you, anyway?
Oh, nothing!
She tried to kidnap me,
so I ensnared her
in an improvised
ball-pit man-trap.
All right,
where to now?
That's my house.
If we can make it there,
we'll be safe.
Whoa, you fight mob bosses
and you live in a mansion?
You're kinda something else,
aren't you, Pink?
-Aah!
-We're the Longboard Taquitos!
Wow, you guys
are so extreme!
What are you gonna do,
ollie all the way over here?
Shred the norm, brah!
Maybe we shouldn't
keep taunting them.
Taquitos got me
so ramped!
Foiled to the max!
In here!
[growls]
This is Ma Beagle
with a very special
birthday request.
Get those brats for me
before they make it
to McDuck Manor!
That'd be the best gift
a mother could get.
This is our shot, guys.
Maybe the Ugly Failures
might actually
become the Ugly Winners!
Couldn't we just
be the Winners?
Now, let's not get crazy.
They're blocking the exit!
Plan A.
We survey the area,
find another exit...
Plan B? Who needs a plan?
No, wait!
[British accent] Oi, mates!
Fancy seeing you lot
in this here warehouse!
Um, who are you?
Who are we?
We're the Beagle Birds,
Ma's adopted daughters
from across the pond, like.
Did Ma ever mention
a pond to you?
I don't think
she could swim.
I don't even think
she showers!
I smell a rat.
We're from England, guv,
just a little Cockney, innit?
Uh, meat pies,
bangers and mash...
Britty, darling,
oh, there you are!
Oh, thank you, gents!
My sister and I
will be certain
to tell
our dearest Mama Beagle
of the gracious hospitality
we've received here
in the Colonies.
This is Brittania,
and I'm, er...
Englabeth.
She talks fancy.
I trust her.
Well, they are family.
I mean, why would they lie?
Marvelous! Well, it was
wonderful to meet you.
-I'm taking this.
-Well, um...
A keepsake
of our serendipitous meeting!
Stupendous!
Ta-ta!
Wait, was that them?
You totally
clowned those jokers,
and we got a radio
so we can track them!
Where did you get
that tea-and-crumpets talk?
I live with my British granny
in a Scottish mansion.
I didn't hear an American accent
till I was, like, seven.
With my brains
and your weirdly
specific super-brains,
we could run this town!
Innit that right,
Englabeth?
Most indubitably,
Brittania!
Hah! Wait until the guys
hear my new nickname!
You mean those three nerds
who ditched you on a beach?
Yeah, they sound
real fun.
Oh, no, no!
There were only three spots
on the boat,
so I let them go.
We're cool like that.
It's a family thing.
Family, huh?
Not really my thing.
But family is the best!
You go on adventures together,
make inside jokes!
Like there was
this hilarious joke
where they went out boating
and Huey got them lost,
and since then, they call
him Captain Lost!
[laughter falls]
Yeah, I don't get it, either.
Uff! Sometimes
it's like they have
their own secret language.
It's just--
I don't know.
They have so much
history together.
Well, now
we have history.
-[rustling]
-[gasps]
-[screams]
-Lena, no!
These are the guys
I was talking about!
-Oh.
-[groans]
Lena, this is Huey,
Dewey, and Louie.
Webby, we've been looking
for you everywhere!
Cute, with the names
and the color-coded outfits.
Is that, like, your thing,
you're all exactly the same?
[all] Hah! No way!
We're all unique snowflakes!
Well, this usually
never happens!
This is really weird!
Okay, stop talking!
Antidisestablishmentarianism!
Seriously? Gah!
Seriously, Webby,
where have you been?
We've been worried
out of our minds!
Well, uh, Lena and I...
Right, you were so worried
that you left her on a beach
and didn't show up
for four hours?
We got lost!
Thanks to old
Captain Lost!
Why would you put me
in charge of the map again?
This is not on me.
Captain Lost!
Ooh, you change
the tone of that chant!
Yeah, they seem like
a real tight crew.
Guys, easy! We were
just having a little adventure.
[trees whistling]
[owl hoots]
What was that?
Shh!
-[grunts]
-Ma to the Tumblebums.
The rugrats have been spotted
in your turf.
Make 'em sorry
they crashed our party!
The Tumblebums?
They sound adorable!
[evil cackling]
Never mind.
-No way! You check!
-No, you check!
-Ohh...
-You go right now!
[indistinct arguing]
Why are the Beagle Boys
even after you?
Because we shoved
their mother's face in a cake.
Try to keep up, Louie.
Heh! Well, we've kind of
been having a girls' night.
[animalistic shouts]
We need a plan.
Okay, we've got a compass,
a half-empty canteen,
three old banana peels--
Wait, wait, three?
-Did you eat my banana?
-Yeah, it's called
stress eating, okay,
-and it's a stressful situation.
-[grunting]
Hey, I need
my potassium!
Let's make
a break for it.
-What?
-Let the boy band be bait
while we sneak out.
I can't leave them!
You mean like they left
you alone on that beach?
Come on, don't
you trust me?
[boys grunting]
Wait right here.
[scoffs] Whatever.
[all grunting]
Stop.
Think.
Okay, how do you get rid of
an evil clown?
[evil cackling]
Yah!
[boys cheering]
Lena, did you see that?
-Lena?
-[boys cheering]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's dumb.
I just--
I thought Lena and I
could maybe have
what you three have.
I promise we'll
never leave you
off the boat again.
We'll leave Louie.
He's bad at most things.
[both laughing]
"Webby, I've been kidnapped
by the Beagle Boys."
Wait, is this another prank?
"This is not a prank.
Lena."
She didn't ditch me!
She was captured!
Oh, wait,
she was captured.
[gasps]
Aah!
[grunts]
[radio static]
[Ma Beagle]
I'm on my way, boys.
I may not have gotten
to eat my birthday cake,
but at least I'll get
a little slice of revenge.
We have to help her!
We should go
get Uncle Scrooge
and Beakley
and a couple of tanks.
There's no time.
Look, me and Lena
fought a truck
and beat the Taquitos
and were British together.
I don't know what
any of that means.
Now you know how I feel
half the time.
You wouldn't leave
each other behind
and I'm not leaving her.
Now, come on!
And this time I'm getting
a spot in the stupid boat!
Uh, guys, I kind of got
a situation here.
A little help?
[grunting]
Rough day, huh?
Well, here.
Courtesy of the
Sixth Avenue Friendlies.
Sixth Avenue Meanies.
[glass shatters]
Psst, over here!
Webby, you came!
Like I would ditch you.
We're the Beagle Birds.
[Webby grunting]
You two ladies have given us
a lot of trouble tonight.
But it'll be worth it
when Ma sees her birthday gift.
And we got some early
Mother's Day shopping
-out of the way, too.
-[laughing]
Big Time to Ma,
what's your 10-20?
Seriously, your rescue plan
was to throw yourself blindly
into the middle of the
entire Beagle Family?
How is that any different
than what you did
at the junkyard?
I wasn't tied up
at the junkyard.
Now they have
what we have.
Now I remember
why I avoid family.
-All they do is--
-Fight?
Okay, Ma should be here
any second.
When Botched Job
gives the signal,
we all leap out
and yell surprise.
-Any questions?
-[Lena] Yeah, I got one.
Which one of you
gets to hand us over?
Say what, now?
I mean, you could
all hand us over
and share the credit,
or...
Well, obviously
we should do it.
I mean, we're, like,
the main guys, right?
-Give someone else a chance.
-Yeah.
We're, like,
anti-authority, bro.
We don't believe
in following.
Yeah, and I'm pretty sure
they was adopted.
Now that was uncalled for,
Mister.
Even if I have heard
the same rumor.
[whistling]
Oh, finally!
-[grunts]
-Hey, who threw that?
[Beagles chanting]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[Beagles clamoring and chanting]
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Whoa... [grunts]
Whoa!
[growling]
[Webby grunting]
[Beagles grunting]
[Beagle yells]
-Yah!
-Let go!
Whoa!
[grunts]
[Beagle yells]
[all grunting]
[tires screeching]
Hey!
[honks horn]
Where are the brats?
[all]
Um...
For the love of...
That's it.
None of you get birthdays
this year.
[all Beagles]
Aww.
That was awesome!
How you made
the Beagle Boys
fight each other
so we could escape,
and then--
Well, you shimmied up
that pillar like a pro.
You turned the entire
Beagle family
against each other
with a question.
You are my new favorite.
No big.
That's what family's
about, eh, Englabeth?
Oh, I knew you'd come through
in a spot, Brittania.
A lil Penny-come-quick
to get ya yet to be.
Fluff and nonsense.
[girls laughing]
You kinda
had to be there.
[buzzes]
Summoned spirit from the dark,
show thyself before this arc.
Free thy dread soul
from its prison,
Once more shall thee be risen!
Aunt Magica, I'm in.