♪♪
[Scrooge] Mount Neverrest,
the highest peak
in the world!
Most prized
of the seven summits,
Neverrest has claimed
the world's finest explorers.
It is said to be
completely unclimbable!
But now that smug stack
of stalagmites
has to deal
with Scrooge McDuck!
Okay, so instead
of spending Christmas
in a billionaire's mansion
waiting for Santa Claus...
That man is not allowed
in my home.
He knows what he did.
...we're following an old man
up Mount Certain Doom here?
Oh, Mount Neverrest
is three times deadlier
than Mount Certain Doom.
The mountain's summit
remains shrouded in mystery.
No one's ever seen the top,
which makes it
the perfect place
to earn my Junior Woodchuck
Cartography Badge!
Do you have any idea
how hard it is to find
a topographical landscape
that hasn't already been mapped?
-No?
-Well, very!
I've got a geographic
information system,
satellite radar detector,
thermal--
Yeah, you don't need
all that fancy doohickory.
All you need is your wits,
determination,
and these,
my old surveying tools.
Wow! They're rusty
with the wisdom of experience.
That's the spirit!
I'm gonna be
the first person to set foot
on the top of Neverrest!
And I'm gonna be
the first person
to draw a picture of it!
Ugh! This is
your captain speaking.
Flight doors
are now open.
[grunts]
Ah! Drink it in, kids.
Her deadly peaks,
her bottomless crevasses,
her flawless sheets
of brilliant white snow
betray a new hint
to the ancient secrets
hidden beneath,
completely untrod by man!
The untamed majesty
of Mount Neverrest!
[bloop]
[door bell rings]
Ooh, churros!
♪♪
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
What are all these people
doing here?
I thought this place
was supposed to be
uncharted territory!
And this map
isn't accurate at all!
Mountain goats aren't
native to this region,
and why is the sun
wearing sunglasses?
Is he looking
at another brighter sun?
Don't pay any attention
to these tourists, my boy.
Nothing but tchotchkes
and cheese puffs.
We are real explorers!
-Like George Mallardy!
-Who?
Only the greatest mountaineer
of the 20th century!
Legend has it
that Mallardy made it farther
up the mountain than anyone,
but was lost trying to rescue
a fellow incompetent climber,
famously known
as the Neverrest Ninnie.
George Mallardy.
He died as he lived,
freezing.
Ach, stop your hatering!
That's just a load of nonsense
to sell T-shirts to tourists.
We're gonna outdo
that quitter Mallardy
by making it
to the top.
You realize there's
a difference between quitting
and dying, right?
Not to me!
-[sheep bleats]
-[gasps]
[heavenly music plays]
Man. They never
have "Dewey."
Everybody, stand back!
I've been waiting
to do this my whole life!
Sledding!
Boo.
Huh. Well, okay.
Webby, Webby, you're
doing it all wrong.
If you want
the maximum sledding experience,
you need to wait for
the maximum opportune moment!
[gasps] We're gonna sled
down Mount Neverrest?!
And/or die trying!
[both] Whoo!
Hey, pal.
Looking to prove
your mettle up there
on the slopes
of old Neverrest?
Yep!
Big strapping guy like
you must be prepared
for ice fever, right?
You bet!
What is that?
[sighs] You don't have
any protection
against the deadly ravages
of ice fever?
It can strike even the most
experienced climber down
in mere minutes!
It could take several minutes
to climb Neverrest.
Maybe longer!
What do I do?
Buddy, I got
just the thing for you.
Wow, these are
pretty expensive.
You sure I need these?
That depends.
Do you want your eyes
to freeze out of your head?
That would make
flying harder.
You're also gonna want
this heat-reflecting blanket,
this oxygen tank
to keep your mind sharp
when the fever starts
killing off your brain cells
with a thousand
footwarmers Footcoolers
commemorative canteen,
Gore, Grip, Grop,
and these state-of-the-art
smart heating gloves
that get an ice fever
rating of eight!
Hmm...
Out of seven?
Ooh!
All right,
true explorers!
Now, this mountain
is gonna throw everything
she's got at us!
But it'll be worth it
when we find the treasure
of Mount Neverrest!
There is no treasure
of Mount Neverrest.
Nope, Louie out.
Already gone.
Have fun!
[bloop]
Let's go set foot
on the roof of the world!
And then throw
ourselves off it!
Yeah!
[Launchpad] First the ice fever
takes your vision.
Then it makes you feel
all warm and toasty,
even though
you're freezing to death.
Then it makes
your limbs all heavy.
Ach, it's just
a bit nippy.
How did you afford
all that gear, anyway?
Louie put it on his
corporate credit card.
Louie doesn't have
a corporate credit card.
Oh. Louie gave me
your credit card.
Now?
Not yet. We've only got
one shot at this.
Once you're down,
there's no coming back up.
Right.
Can't wait! [grunts]
Maximum opportune moment!
Ugh. Fine.
Point of no return,
this way to certain death,
this way to... cocoa.
Hmm.
[both] Certain death!
[Scrooge] That's the spirit.
-[clanks]
-[grunts]
Whoa!
Launchpad, hand me
my climbing spats, will ya?
Whoa! Ow! Ooh! Ow!
Launchpad?
[grunting, screaming]
Where'd he go?
He had half
of our equipment!
[screams] Oh!
[gibbers, screams]
Ugh. Where am I?
I've gone snowblind!
The ice fever's
setting in!
No!!!
[distant screaming]
Probably cozying up
with hot cocoa along with Louie.
Anyone else want
to check it out?
Last thing we need
on this trip
is a bunch
of Neverrest Ninnies.
I thought you said
that was a myth.
Just because it's a myth
doesn't mean it's not true.
Well, actually--
Don't you worry, kids.
It'll take more
than a pompous pile of pebbles
to slow your
old Uncle Scrooge down!
I promise, I won't let
anything bad happen to you.
-[cracking]
-[screams]
From now on!
Nothing bad from now on!
Heads down, knees up!
Let's go!
I'm gonna call
this Murder Ridge,
after Death Peak,
but before the Chasm
of Infinite Despair.
Aw. I'll call
that Bunny Rock.
[screaming]
Hmm. I'm still gonna
call it Bunny Rock.
Curse me kilts.
End of the line,
Uncle Scrooge?
Hmm.
[blooping]
[heavenly music plays]
Well, looks like
we'll have to settle
for a double luge-de-luge
and a moderate alley-oop
flatsmans 540.
Sledding!
-[ice pick clinks]
-[success noise dings]
Hey, hey!
Nice try, Neverrest!
[both] Yeah!
Aw. I mean... yeah.
[bangs]
So... hot.
Oh, no!
The next stage of ice fever!
I can't remove any of my gear,
or I'll freeze to death!
Ugh. Limbs heavy.
Movements lethargic.
-Watch it!
-Hey!
I can hear the shrill wail
of Neverrest's cruel wind
calling me.
Surrender...
No! This is not the end
of Launchpad McQuack!
It will be by plane crash
or not at all!
Aah! A yeti!
[Scrooge] Don't need this...
all this...
What even is this?
Certainly don't need this!
Um, the Junior Woodchuck Guide
suggests we need at least some
of this stuff.
We don't need anything
but grit, gumption, and--
And water!
Now?
I think that would technically
be more falling than sledding.
Ha-ha! Take that,
you mag-nelequent molehill!
What a rush!
I thought we were done for.
Nonsense, lad!
We're going straight
to the top.
We must've gained
some serious altitude
with that climb.
We should be closer
than ever, and--
Wait, is that Bunny Rock?
This can't be right!
Maybe we should backtrack
to figure out
where we went wrong.
Please! I'm sure that's
an entirely different
naturally occurring
demon-faced rock.
Okay, but it is snowing,
so the smart thing to do is--
Set up camp!
There's a cave
up about 500 meters ahead.
-See?
-Cool dark and foreboding cave,
Uncle Scrooge!
But this area's uncharted.
How did you know
this would be here?
Uh, guys, I don't think
we're the first climbers
to have this idea.
Whoa.
Where are their heads?
[Webby] Found 'em!
Uh, maybe we find
a slightly less deadly cave.
Wait, the entrance
was right here.
We must've gotten
turned around.
It's gotta
be here somewhere!
[gasp]
Is that...
George Mallardy.
Greatest mountaineer
of the 20th century.
Wait, he's written something
out on the wall here.
"Curse you, McDuck."
[bloop]
Ach, jinx. If I had a nickel
for every person
who cursed me
with their dying breath,
I'd be as rich
as I already am.
Junior Woodchuck
Rule 1118--
a Woodchuck chief
must always be honest
with his crew.
Fine. Ugh.
I was the Neverrest Ninny.
[all] What?
Seventy-five years
ago today,
I hired Mallardy
to lead me up the mountain.
I'd just made
my first million,
and I wanted to mark
the occasion
by doing something
no one had ever done.
I may have been
a little inexperienced,
but I didn't want
to leave anything to chance.
[laughs]
Mallardy mocked me
mercilessly.
He ordered me
to lighten my load,
but I was afraid to risk
my emergency supplies
and my sizeable money belt,
so he cut me loose.
I was weighed down
by doubt
and branded
the Neverrest Ninny.
[laughing]
Mallardy was never
heard from again.
But he became the man to make it
the farthest up the mountain!
Now he's the second farthest!
Uncle Scrooge!
What? He was
a backstabbing braggart
who almost
got me killed!
I think the mountain
got even for you.
And now we'll get even
with the mountain!
We will brave the new frontier,
chart the unknown!
How can I chart
the unknown if I don't know
what I'm charting!
I'm telling you,
this mountain doesn't
make any sense.
I think I hear the wind
coming from this way.
Webby, wait!
Good initiative,
Webbigail!
Thanks, Mr. McDuck!
[bloop]
Didn't you just--
Weren't you--?
I found an opening.
Lead the way!
-Whoo-hoo!
-We made it!
We should be closer
than ever now.
Is that Bunny Rock?
[Scrooge] Aw, come on!
The ice fever
in final stages.
Must stay warm.
Uh, Launchpad?
So warm!
Launchpad!
[screams]
Louie, is that you?
Stay calm,
little buddy.
We need to find a way
off this mountain
before ice fever
takes us both.
You know ice fever
is not a thing, right?
You're talking crazy.
You must have it, too.
Crazy talk is the third stage
of ice fever!
Who told you that?
The guy who sold me
this blanket.
Standard double snake oil.
I see how it is.
Well, no one cons
my family but me!
Our combined body heat
will save us both.
Soak in the wetness
of my sweat!
Ew! So much wetness! Ew!
At last!
After all these years,
the summit of Mount Neverrest!
We're in the clear
now, kids!
Ha-ha!
[squeaky, nervous laugh]
That's it!
I'm putting my foot down.
We can't go forward!
Of course we can.
The summit's right there!
We are violating every rule
of my Junior Woodchuck training!
We're out of supplies,
it's starting to get cold,
so even if we make it
to the top,
we'd freeze to death
before we get down.
Oh, and if we keep trying
to go up this way,
the whole thing
is gonna come crashing down!
This is all too risky!
Don't you go ninny
on me, lad!
You'll never get
your cartography badge
with that attitude!
I don't care!
We have to turn around now!
-[both] Now!
-[rumbling]
You already beat Mallardy.
Isn't that enough?
No! We'd be daft to give up
with the peak in our grasp.
It's not giving up.
It's just having common sense.
For the last time,
nothing bad is going to happen!
[both] Whoa!
-[screaming]
-Dewey! Webby!
-Kids!
-[yodeling]
How'd you guys
get up there?
I don't know.
Maybe Launchpad
was right about ice fever.
What are you--
Ow! What?
What the blistering bagpipes
is going on here?
Wormholes!
This mountain
is covered in some kind
of mystical
dimensional doorways
that have been randomly
zapping us around
the trail all day!
Between the fog
and the snow,
we didn't
even realize it!
That's why my map
didn't make sense!
Hoots, man!
A mountain protecting
its peak with portals!
Neverrest, you beauteous beaut,
you never cease to amaze.
And you wanted
to turn around!
What are you doing?
We're at the top
of a magical mystery mountain!
I gotta find my sled,
like, now!
-Yes!
-Whoa!
What?
Hmm...
Oh, that--
Whoa!
[laughs]
-Whoa-ho-ho!
-Whoo-hoo-hoo!
I'm getting nudges!
Are you getting nudges?
-[Webby laughing]
-My brain hurts!
You know what I mean?
[crackling]
Careful! The more
you zap around,
the less stable
this ice fall becomes!
Hey, my sled!
Hmm... [snaps]
I don't have
to climb the icefall.
I just to find the wormhole
that sled fell through.
Uncle Scrooge, no!
Ha-ha! I'm gonna do it!
Mount Neverrest,
consider yourself conquered!
Conquered!
[rumbling]
[gasps]
Just stop!
There's no way to reach the top.
The mountain won't let you!
Let this one go!
Look how far we've come!
Farther than anyone
has ever made it.
Isn't that enough?
I will not be
the Neverrest Ninny
for another 75 years!
Nobody has used the word
"ninny" in 75 years!
Junior Woodchuck Rule 727:
"Sometimes the bravest thing
an explorer can do
is walk away."
[screams]
-Now?
-Now!
-No!
-[grunts]
Hang on, kiddos!
Oh! Whoa!
[screams]
[screaming]
Whoo!
Aah! Whoo.
[screaming]
Ooh. Of course, if you
really want to survive in style,
you'll need something
from our Mallardy
Selects Collection.
You! Are you the man
who sold my friend
all this useless equipment?
Eh...
Look at him!
He's dying of ice fever!
All the overpriced junk
you sold him did nothing!
[groaning]
No, no,
that's impossible.
Tell that
to this poor man!
I see a bright light.
This is it!
Louie, marry me
among the clouds.
[gasps] He's delirious!
No, he's an idiot.
He's not dying
of ice fever.
Ice fever
isn't real!
[group growling]
Um, maybe just
sort of not real?
[overlapping yelling]
[laughs]
You saved me!
You carried me
down the mountain
singlehandedly,
then cured me
of ice fever!
Sure. Yeah. Why not?
[laughing]
We survived!
Take that,
Mount Neverrest!
You won't claim
our bodies today!
[all panting]
So, that's sledding, huh?
Meh.
Sorry we didn't make it
to the top, Uncle Scrooge.
Ah, tell you, buddy,
there's more to Neverrest
than just a mountain,
and there's more to us
than just a couple of ninnies
who couldn't climb it.
Plenty more adventures
where that came from, eh, lad?
Now, where the blazes
is that hot cocoa stand?
I am freezing!
♪♪