♪♪
[Scrooge] The Temple
of the Golden Cricket.
Every 50 years, at sundown,
the golden cricket emerges
singing its ethereal song.
Some say the song
holds the answer
to life's
greatest mysteries.
How did we get here?
What's our purpose
in the universe?
Wait, is that
a neon hot dog?
-Wow!
-So cool!
[Webby]
I'm hungry!
[Scrooge]
Yes, yes, the city of Macaw
is very exciting to look at,
but you'll only find
empty distractions there.
I can't believe
Uncle Gladstone is here!
-He's so charming.
-And funny.
He's, like,
the luckiest guy
in the world.
Uh, Uncle Donald
you must've had
the best time
growing up with him.
Hey, $20.
-Hey, 20--
-Dibs!
[alarm blaring]
He's the worst.
Just the worst.
Gladstone Gander is
a complete layabout.
I don't know why
we're responding
to his call.
It was a call
for help.
And like Uncle Donald says,
"Family always helps family."
Why did I say that?
Plus, he's easily
our coolest uncle.
-Hey!
-Sorry, coolest
non-trillionaire uncle.
[groans]
Hey, come on,
Uncle Donald
is kinda cool.
We're all gonna die!
I've wasted my life!
[chuckles]
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring bad
and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
We leave
for the temple
in an hour.
Launchpad,
I won't wait
another 50 years
to hear
that cricket sing.
Sure thing, Mr. McD.
I was just gonna swing over
and visit
an old girlfriend
from these parts.
See, she's had
some problems
with the local
crime family, and--
Yes, fine, whatever.
One hour.
I'm coming for you, Ziyi.
[elevator dinging]
Why did I wear green?
He always sees me
in green.
Take it easy.
Yeah, if Gladstone's
so great,
then why did he
call us for--
[Gladstone]
Help! No! Don't...
Stop... until you get that
last kink out, Pei Pei.
[massage blows landing]
[back cracks]
[sighs]
The worst.
Loose as a goose
and ready to gander.
Kids! Uncle Scrooge.
D-Money.
I was so relaxed
I didn't hear you come in.
Pei Pei here is
a miracle worker.
Anyway, welcome to Macaw.
Help yourself
to everything.
[Webby]
Guys, try this!
It feels like you're falling,
but you're not.
-[gasps]
-[laughs]
-Whoa!
-We're falling!
We're falling!
So, I thought
you needed help.
Oh, I do
need your help.
Spending all my winnings!
Oh, lighten up.
Hey, hey, guys,
who am I?
Haggis and top hats!
Bless me bagpipes!
[imitates flatulence]
[kids laughing]
[sighs] This place is for
no-account freeloaders
looking to get something
for nothing.
Ah, that's true,
Scroogey McBillions.
And I am the best at getting
something for nothing.
Best uncle!
Thank you, Gladstone,
for your inspiring message.
If you'll excuse us,
we have an improbably
enchanted insect
to inspect.
-To the temple!
-[kids laughing]
Oh, but I want to stay.
Show me everything.
Especially the stuff
you're not supposed to.
[laughs] I love this kid!
He's like me, but short
and with a cheaper haircut.
Now, you just gotta help me
convince your Uncle Donald.
Well, forget it, then.
Been nice seeing you,
Uncle Gladstone.
[Gladstone]
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
D-Squared, you came
all the way out here.
Let me show
you guys around.
It'll be good times.
Fine, you can stay.
-I can?
-And I'm coming with you.
-[Louie groans]
-Come on, kids.
Let them play pai gow
with a bunch of biddies.
We have a rip-roaring
adventure awaiting us.
[kids]
Adventure!
[elevator dinging]
[slot machines ringing]
[Scrooge]
Ah, ugh.
I can't make sense of this.
Where's the exit?
Is that "X"
hidden treasure?
The "X" is obviously
where we are,
-but where are we?
-Don't worry, kids.
I'll get us out of this
monument to moochers
-or my name isn't--
-Scrooge McDuck!
What good fortune to have
the highest of high rollers
in my humble establishment.
Luck has nothing
to do with it.
-Mister?
-Liu Hai.
Toad Liu Hai.
Please be my personal guest.
Anything you need,
just let me know.
At the House
of Lucky Fortune,
you are all kings.
Oh, good, street magic.
Well, thank you,
but we really
must be going.
At least stay
for the floor show.
Aquarioon:
The Sacred Waters of Aquarien.
The biggest indoor
water spectacle
in the eastern hemisphere.
Biggest waste of water
is more like it.
I mean, how many
million gallons
are you going through a day,
just for some dumb--
[announcer]
In a time before time...
the Earth lies
beneath a watery grave.
There is only light.
There is only ocean.
And among all the primal chaos
there lives Aquarioon.
Water dancing.
A calm washing over me.
[orchestral music playing]
Never felt... so at peace.
I suppose we have time
for one show.
But then it's right to the
Temple of the Golden Cricket.
[music continues]
This is the best
anyone has ever looked.
Well, Green Bean,
if you want to
be a winner,
you need to look
like a winner.
And you can bill my suit
to the room, please.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
Mr. Gladstone.
I cannot do this.
It would be such
a great honor for me
to know that you
are out in the world
wearing this suit.
[grunts]
$2,000, cash only.
Just like
the real thing,
only cheaper.
[tag beeping]
[Donald]
Ow!
Oh, man,
Uncle Donald's gotta be
the unluckiest duck
in the world.
Ow!
[Gladstone]
I'm counting on it.
[announcer]
And though noble Aquarioon
fell that day,
his soul lives on
for we are all Aquarioon.
Bravo!
We should really stay
for the 3:15 show.
You'll always be with me,
mighty Aquarioon!
-[guests clamoring]
-Thank you.
-Oh, you're too kind.
-[guests clamoring]
I love it, baby!
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
Hey, where's Donald?
Aah! [grunts]
There he is.
Try your luck,
Mr. Gander.
If I must.
[machine beeping, ringing]
[applause]
Do it again!
How about you give it a go,
Donaldo?
Easy, peasy... [grunts]
[machine winding down]
[Donald muttering]
Aah!
We've passed this gaming section
like three times.
Wait, didn't that gift shop
used to be over here?
Everything looks the same
in this blasted place.
They try to trap you here
so you'll spend
all your time and money
on cheap thrills.
But we're better than that.
Yeah, we need
some danger.
-Some--
-Tigers?
Ooh, where did you
come from?
And more importantly,
did you say "tigers"?
The majestic jade tigers
of Macaw.
Humanely raised in our natural
wildlife pavilion
and business center.
Actual tigers!
Do the number of stripes
tell you their age?
Is it true if you stare
at them in the eyes
they won't kill you,
or does that make them
want to kill you faster?
Oh, would you
like one?
[squeals]
You can't give a child
a tiger.
Especially not
this child.
Dewey Junior, you're coming home
with us.
Oh, and I already named him.
Oh, and I'm already
super emotionally attached.
Oh, fine.
But I am not changing
its litter.
Now, about that exit.
-[tiger growls]
-[man exclaims]
That guy at the mall
with the iguana
is gonna be so jealous.
Give her a spin!
-[game ringing]
-Whoo! Yeah!
[Louie laughing]
[laughs] Can't waste
all the luck on me.
[scoffs]
I got this.
[machine creaking]
[patrons screaming]
[items crashing, banging]
[announcer]
Attention, the 3:15 performance
of Aquarioon:
The Sacred Waters of Aquarien
-has been cancelled.
-[Dewey] No!
[chuckles]
-Eight?
-No.
-Five?
Twenty-seven?
No.
-Twenty-seven.
-No.
-Twenty-seven?
How does he think he's
holding up 27 fingers?
I don't know, Lou.
I just don't know.
I navigated myself out of
the Infinitaur's labyrinth.
Freed myself from the
Forever Fields of Fantoom.
Why can't I find
the blasted hotel exit?
[Webby]
Oh, don't worry.
I left a trail
of snacks behind us
to mark our path.
-[Webby groans]
-He's a tiger.
You tell him
not to eat something.
You look tired,
Mr. McDuck.
I implore you to
check in to a room.
Oh, no, we are
not interested.
At least stay for lunch
at our Buffet of Many Lands!
You can visit the entire world
on a single dinner plate.
Imagine taco dim sum.
Fettucine eclairs.
Why would I want
to imagine
any of that?
Sorry, sir,
but the only thing
we're hungry for
is adventure and--
is that a fountain
made of chocolate?
You can dip
positively anything
in it.
-Strawberries?
-Mm-hmm.
-What about my hand?
-Sure.
What about your hand?
Um, uh, fine.
Wait!
What about the Temple
of the Golden Cricket?
What about the mysteries
of the universe?
What about a nice, warm bed?
Fine, check me in.
Twenty-seven.
Twenty-seven!
Ugh, give it up,
Uncle Donald.
Please.
No, no, no, no.
Let it ride.
-You're about to--
-Two?
We have a winner!
Congratulations.
You won a brand-new
Thunderclutch sports car.
[laughs]
Great.
This is the second car
I've won for--
Four? [laughs]
You win again!
Seriously?
Wow, you really
can't lose.
Yeah, I know.
So close, Big D.
Hey, how about we play--
Oh, I give up.
I came to help you.
And instead you embarrass me
in front of the boys.
Wh-- I'm not trying
to embarrass you.
I just wanted to give
you and the fam
a taste of the good life.
By showing them
I'm a loser?
Ugh, winners, losers,
who cares?
If you want to
impress them,
keep playing.
Your luck is bound
to change.
[car horn honks]
Hey, Uncle Gladstone!
-[honks horn]
-I'm done.
Wait, no!
Uncle Donald's
taking a break, huh?
Well, then this is
the perfect time
for us to hit the
big winner's tables.
I don't need you.
I need him.
You'll feel so much better
after a night
in one of our luxury suites.
Maybe a week.
Perhaps a year.
You may never
want to leave.
I'll need a room
with a personal sauna,
a poolside view,
and a distraction.
A what?
[Scrooge]
Check-in is always
by the exit.
Thanks for the help, Liu Hai!
Come on, kids.
We can make it in time
for the Golden Cricket's
last chorus.
I'm with you.
Let's go.
Where you going, cuz?
There's tons more games.
Oh, and the buffet.
I get it.
You're the cool uncle.
I'm not.
Have fun!
[Gladstone grunts]
[laughing]
Oh, dang.
Did I not mention
I'm a prisoner here
and that's why
I called you for help?
What?
Why didn't you just tell us?
[Liu Hai]
Because I'd find out.
I am Liu Hai, ancient spirit
of chance and fortune.
Now, let's test your luck.
Finally, a proper adventure.
[evil laughter]
I sat through
The Waters of Aquanadon
three times when I could've been
fighting a demon?
It's Aquarioon.
[grunts]
Uh, yeah, you don't wanna
mess with Toad.
He's a luck vampire.
He's held me captive here
to feast off my
natural good luck.
I'm that delicious.
Are you bragging
about that?
I hoped Donald
would break
my lucky streak.
-You know, 'cause he's--
-Bad luck.
-A total jinx.
-The worst.
Gladstone's good fortune
has been satisfying,
but surely, as the
richest duck in the world,
Scrooge McDuck's luck must be
the most delicious feast of all.
Luck has nothing to do
with my success.
Oh, really?
I'll prove it.
One game.
If I win, you set us free.
If you win, we stay...
permanently.
Unless you think the spirit
of luck and fortune will lose.
Hmm, I can't resist
such a challenge.
Yes! Thank you,
Screwdriver
McDollarsigns.
I knew I could count on you.
Behold.
[Liu Hai]
First to the end wins.
Okay, Toad, let's do this.
[Liu Hai]
Unh-unh-unh.
My house, my rules.
Gladstone still
belongs to me.
So he is my champion.
You get--
Hmm, him.
[gulps]
The winner goes free.
The loser is doomed.
[evil laughter]
I don't even
get to be part
of the blasted challenge?
We came out here
to help you
and you put our family
in danger.
I'm sorry, Don.
I really am.
But I literally
just can't lose.
-Good luck.
-[groans]
There is only ocean.
[Huey]
There is only light.
And among the primal chaos
lives Aquarioon!
Oh!
Ow, ow, ow!
Aah!
[mutters]
[Donald screaming]
[panting]
Whoa!
[Donald screams]
Whew!
Ow!
Oh.
It's Dewey Junior!
[growling]
[Donald panting]
[panting continues]
Oh, come on!
[grunting]
Aah!
The Buffet
of Many Lands!
[muttering]
Man, I'm really sorry
about this.
I mean, obviously
not sorry enough
to sign up for a lifetime
of servitude, but...
Aww.
Huh? Huh?
[groans]
[low growling]
[evil laughter]
Oh, what's the point?
[Louie]
Come on, Uncle Donald!
So you have the worst
luck in the world.
Who cares?
No matter how bad
things get,
like really, really bad,
you keep going.
It's kind of ridiculous.
You never had the common sense
to give up before.
Why start now?
[growling]
[Donald growls]
[Donald grunting]
[muttering]
Hey, $20.
Where did that
come from?
[Donald grunts, mutters]
[panting]
-Whoa!
-[laughing]
What?
[kids cheering]
Well, at least I still have
the luckiest buffet on Earth.
Bad fortune, Mr. Gander.
Actually, Toad,
Gladstone lost to Donald
so technically, Donald is
the new luckiest guy on Earth.
It's really him
you should take.
Yeah!
Wait, no!
Hmm, a well-reasoned argument.
Donald Duck is my prize.
That wasn't the deal!
All bets are off.
Uh-oh.
Uncle Donald!
I can't believe
you just gave him up.
The kid's not wrong,
Uncle McDuncle.
What do we do?
Three, two, one.
[Donald muttering, grunts]
His luck, it's awful!
So awful!
[rumbling]
You did it, Uncle Donald!
You won!
That was pretty cool.
I mean, especially for you.
How the heck
did I win?
I guess you're not
so lucky, after all.
But if you think about it,
we're all free.
So, me losing is the luckiest
thing that could've happened.
Boom!
Still the luckiest guy on Earth
and a hero.
Huh?
Eh, luck's overrated.
[panting]
Whoa, Launchpad,
what happened to you?
Eh, you know,
tourist stuff.
Goodbye, Ziyi,
wherever you are.
Have I really just been
coasting on my luck,
charm, and ridiculous
good looks?
Who is Gladstone?
I need to get my hands dirty.
Do something meaningful.
A new, noble purpose.
[Woman]
Hey, handsome.
[yacht horn honks]
I need to get rid of my boat
for tax purposes.
I'll sell it to you for $20.
Gladstone is back, baby!
[chirping]
Okay, we can go now.