♪ We ♪
♪ Are the crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And pearl ♪
And Steven!
♪♪
♪ Mom was a diamond
who invaded Earth ♪
♪ Saw its beauty
and its worth ♪
♪ Mom made an army ♪
♪ And she fought herself ♪
♪ Did that even
end up mattering ♪
♪ When she faked
her own shattering? ♪
♪ Mom lived in hiding
by the name of Rose ♪
♪ With the friends she'd made ♪
♪ And the form she chose ♪
♪ Now all that's left
of her exists in me ♪
♪ And I think that
we can all agree ♪
♪ That is
a little bit upsetting ♪
♪ I'd rather think about ♪
♪ A wedding ♪
♪ Let's think about cake ♪
♪ Let's think about flowers ♪
♪ Let's think about dressing up
and dancing around for hours ♪
♪ There's an awful lot
of awful things ♪
♪ We could be thinking of ♪
♪ But for just one day,
let's only think about love ♪
Okay, Sapphire, I gotta
get dressed for our big day now,
so no peeking!
And no future vision,
either!
Sapphire:
[ Giggles ] Okay!
Oh, Steven, I just wish I could
have said something sooner
about Rose and Pink...
♪ We could think about lies
that we told in the past ♪
They took it so hard.
♪ Think about hurt feelings ♪
♪ And how long
they can last ♪
How can we move on?
♪ Or we could think
about hope ♪
Hope?
♪ You know I've
been hopin' ♪
About what?
♪ That everything's better now,
everything's out in the open ♪
Bismuth!
Is that what you're wearing
to the wedding?
It's the nicest thing
I own!
Lookin' sharp!
♪ We could think
about flowers ♪
about cake ♪
♪ We could think about
wonderful promises ♪
♪ We have the power to make ♪
♪ There's an awful lot
of awful things ♪
♪ We could be thinking of ♪
♪ But for just one day,
let's only think about love ♪
Maybe I shouldn't have
picked up roses.
Might be a little...
controversial.
♪ We could all rethink ♪
♪ How we feel
about Rose ♪
♪ When it comes to Pink
and the things that she did ♪
♪ In the past, I suppose ♪
Yeah.
♪ Or we could both
feel better ♪
♪ 'Cause we could
think about how ♪
♪ We could think about us,
and we could think about now ♪
Well, if we don't use these,
we're gonna need something else.
No worries! Peridot's gathering
more flowers right now.
I'll go get her!
[ Humming ]
♪ But for just one day ♪
♪ Let's only think
about... ♪
Peridot?
What if Lapis
was right?
Sooner or later, the diamonds
are going to come
for the cluster.
We're all gonna die here!
♪ We could think about war ♪
♪ We could think
about fighting ♪
♪ We could think about
long-lost friends ♪
♪ We wish
we were inviting ♪
♪ We could think about
the broken gems ♪
♪ In the cluster at
the planet's core ♪
♪ Or we could think about
the bubble we made ♪
♪ So that they can't be hurt
any ♪
♪ They can't be hurt
anymore ♪
♪ We could think
about joy ♪
about pain ♪
♪ We could think
about sunshine ♪
about rain ♪
♪ There's an awful lot
of awful things ♪
♪ We could be thinking of ♪
But for just one day
♪ Let's only think about ♪
♪ Just one day,
let's only think about ♪
♪ Lo-o-o-ve ♪
[ Guitar plays ]
You nervous?
I'm not!
[ Guitar continues ]
Flowers for you!
Wedding commander,
all flowers have been deployed!
Thanks, Peridot.
[ Guitar continues ]
[ Seagulls crying ]
♪♪
[ Guitar quickens ]
[ Clears throat ]
Dearly beloved...
gems, humans,
lions big and small...
living gourds, Onion --
we are gathered here today to
celebrate Ruby and Sapphire,
two of my favorite people
who combine into one of
my other favorite people.
You all probably know her
as Garnet.
She is their love, given form.
But now it's your turn
to talk about that.
I know this is all
kind of silly.
I mean, we've been together
for 5,750 years!
And eight months!
I used to feel like
I wasn't much good,
just one of me on my own.
But when we're together,
it feels like it's okay
to just be me.
So I want to be me
with you!
And -- and not even the diamonds
will come between us!
And if they try,
we'll beat 'em up!
[ Laughs ]
Ruby, my future used to look
like one single,
obvious stream,
unbending till
the end of time.
In an instant, you pulled me
from that destiny
and opened my eye
to an explosion
of infinite
possible futures,
streaking across
space and time,
altered and obliterated by
the smallest force of will.
What I mean is,
you changed my life.
And then,
I changed your life.
And now,
we change our lives.
Bismuth, the rings!
Hey, Bismuth,
that's your cue!
♪♪
Ruby, do you take this gem
to have and to hold,
on this and every other planet
in the universe?
I do!
And, Sapphire, do you --
Yes.
You didn't let me finish!
I'm just very excited.
Then,
by the power vested in me
by the State of Delmarva,
I now pronounce you Garnet!
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
Steven!
Hey, Garnet.
Thanks for everything.
[ Both laugh ]
I needed this.
What a wonderful idea.
Humans find a way to make a
moment's decision last forever.
I don't need future vision to
know I'll always remember this.
I'm so glad.
Aw, no. I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I guess seeing everyone together
has got me really choked up.
Wait a second.
You don't think...
Blue Diamond.
She's here?!
And she's not alone!
♪♪
[ All gasp ]
Oh, no.
It's the diamonds!
[ All screaming ]
Nanefua,
get on your Nanephone!
We've got a code blue
and a code yellow!
This is it!
We're over here,
you clods!
Wha?!
Where are they going?!
If they're not here for us,
they must be here
for the cluster!
Whoa!
What's the cluster?!
It's a huge earth-destroying
geo-weapon
that the diamonds made out
of a bajillion gem shards!
I gotta keep it calm
and in its bubble!
I can use my mind
to connect with it,
but only
when I'm asleep.
Asleep?
[ Rumbling ]
It's no use! How am I supposed
to sleep through this?
Maybe a lullaby
will help.
Uh, I'm not sure
this is gonna...
[ Snoring ]
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Gasps ]
The cluster!
Stay calm.
Try to keep from forming.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
It popped!
[ Rumbling ]
♪♪
[ Alarm blaring ]
Attention citizens
of Beach City --
Everyone head to your
designated shelters.
I repeat --
this is not a drill.
Get yourselves
over to the shelters!
♪♪
All right!
Looks like it's in control of
itself, and it's on our side!
♪♪
Go, cluster, go!
Blue Diamond.
Guess it's time to work
the old Universe charm.
All: No!
All right, I'll just be in here.
Rose Quartz...
so you escaped Homeworld
and crawled back here.
This is Pink's world!
How dare you use it
as your hiding place?!
Come!
Answer for what you've done!
This is bad, this is bad,
this is bad, this is bad!
Come on, you rocks,
let's put her in a bubble!
Right!
Wait! There's no
reason to fight.
Let me talk to her.
Blue Diamond,
please listen to me!
I didn't shatter Pink Diamond.
Pink Diamond's right here!
It's pretty interesting
when you think about it --
Enough!
Aah!
Ugh!
[ Roars ]
Wait!
You cannot fathom
how much I've mourned,
what thousands of years of grief
has done to me!
[ All grunt ]
What's going on!?
Guys?!
[ Crying ]
[ Whistles ]
[ Lion growls ]
Hold on, guys!
Connie!
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
I know this sword.
This is the sword
that shattered her!
[ Gasps ]
Aah!
[ People crying ]
You deserve this --
all of you!
Stop, please!
Steven!
What do we do?!
I don't know. She won't listen,
she just wants to fight.
Garnet: Blue Diamond!
Who are you
supposed to be?
I am the will of two gems
to care for each other,
to protect each other
from any threat,
no matter how vast
or how cruel.
You couldn't stop me 5,750 years
ago, and you can't stop me now!
It's you, that Ruby and Sapphire
that disrupted my court.
Ugh!
This is supposed to
be my day!
You hope to defeat me
by clinging to my feet?
I just needed to keep you from
taking three steps to the right.
♪♪
What?!
Whoo...
Lapis?!
[ Breathing heavily ]
You're really here.
Hey.
Lapis!
You came back -- again!
I couldn't stay away.
If they're gonna punish me
like a crystal gem,
I might as well be one,
right?
You got room
for one more?
Of course!
Save the hugs for
after the fight.
Look alive!
Lapis Lazuli!
Does every gem that comes
in contact with this planet
turn traitor?!
What?
I've felt worse.
Knock her off this beach!
Now's our chance!
♪♪
With all our strength together,
we can take her down!
That's right!
This is our home...
our planet...
our friends and family!
We are the Crystal Gems!
Pathetic!
You are nothing!
♪♪
[ Roars ]
Wah-ahh!
Hey, Blue diamond,
fight me!
You got guts, tiny!
Let me give you a hand!
Wha!
Everyone, group up!
♪♪
Yeah!
[ Electricity zapping ]
Uh, guys?
Run for it!
Aah!
The house!
Don't worry,
I can fix it!
My dad!
Uh-oh...
All right,
I'm stickin' with you guys!
[ Thud ]
Hup!
Did we do it?
[ All gasp ]
Cluster, you were amazing!
Are you okay?
Do you want to go back
in your bubble?
Okay, take it easy!
You're the best.
So, that is
a wedding reception.
Hmm. Nice job,
wedding planner.
Did ya see that?!
She couldn't lay a finger on me!
Hmm, but did you notice
how I perfectly managed
my trajectory --
right into her eyes?!
I'll demonstrate!
Launch me again!
[ Chuckles ] I like you,
Peridot. You don't quit.
[ Clanging ]
♪♪
Ha!
I told her off once.
I can do it again!
Hey, yellow clod!
Remember me?!
No.
Stop!
Don't do this!!
Listen to me --
I'm the one you're missing!
I'm Pink Diamond!
You!
Aah!
Steven!
Steven?!
Steven:
Connie, what's wrong?!
Come on,
please wake up!
I'm up, I'm up!
What's going on?!
Connie, I'm right here!
Come on, Steven,
we need you!
Aah!
What the hoo-hah?!
Huh.
Well, this is new.
What is this place?
♪♪
What else have you got?!
I've only just begun to fight!
Aah!
[ Gasps ] Lapis!
♪♪
Connie,
are you seeing this?!
Wake up! Please!
We're supposed to be in this
together, remember?
Uh, Connie, I'm o-kay?
Huh? Steven?!
Huh?
Connie, it's me!
W-where are you?
How are you doing...
I'm not sure, but I think
it's a classic psychic
ghost-type situation!
Ah, of course.
So, what's the plan?
The diamonds won't listen to me
out there,
but maybe I can get through
to them here.
They've gotta know Pink Diamond
wasn't shattered.
Please protect my body
while I'm gone.
Got it!
Good luck out there, Steven.
♪♪
This is it, I've got to
hold it together.
I've gotta hold
everyone together.
You can do it, Garnet!
Remember, you're made of love!
Steven?
Huh.
Always full of surprises.
[ Grunting ]
Amethyst:
Don't get shattered, don't get
shattered, don't get shattered!
You can do this, Amethyst!
I believe in you!
Steven?
I can do this! I can do this!
I can do this!
Pearl:
I won't give up! Everything
I do, I do it for her!
I do it for him!
Don't forget about yourself,
Pearl!
I do it for me!
I just got my friends back, and
now I'm gonna lose em again?
We can still do this --
together!
What am I thinking!
We haven't lost yet!
Hang in there, Peridot.
You, too, Lapis!
[ Grunts ]
♪♪
How miserable. I knew Pink
couldn't handle her own colony,
but I gave in.
And now I'm to blame
for her fate.
Aah!
Her thoughts are too strong!
What good
will any of this do?
The more I make these gems
suffer,
the more I long to see you
again, Pink.
Huh?
♪♪
Almost!
Blue Diamond, please listen!
Whoa, whoa!
What the...?
I felt something --
someone.
It worked!
I gotta get through to them!
Ahh!
Pink isn't gone!
I can explain everything
if you just stop
this fighting!
Aah!
There it is again!
What are you
jabbering about?
A presence!
It feels like...
Please, Blue,
you're being hysterical,
more so than usual.
Listen, Yellow, Pink's fate
is different than you think!
She faked her shattering!
This feeling,
I know it!
It must be a trick!
Show yourself, foe!
I'm not your foe!
Please just listen to me!
There! Aah.
Aah!
♪♪
Steven: Please,
the fighting has to stop.
We aren't enemies,
we're family.
Please, listen to me!
I need you to know
who I am!
Impossible!
This aura...
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
It's you!
Pink!
♪♪
♪ I always thought ♪
♪ I might be bad ♪
♪ Now I'm sure that it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause I think
you're so good ♪