>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ SEAGULL CRIES ]
>> Steven: HMMM...
HMMM...
HMMMM-HMMM...
>> YOU CAN DO IT, STEVEN.
>> Steven: THANKS SADIE.
IT'S JUST...
I COULD GET A DONUT, WHICH
WOULD BE TASTY.
BUT I ALWAYS GET DONUTS.
SHOULDN'T I BE LIVING LIFE TO
THE FULLEST AND TRYING NEW
THINGS?
SO TONIGHT, MAYBE I'M
THINKING...
SPICY PRETZELS?
>> WHY DON'T YOU ASK YOUR
LITTLE FRIEND?
>> [ SNIFFS ]
>> Steven: UGH, LION THOSE ARE
GROSS.
NO OFFENSE.
>> YOU KIDS BETTER HURRY IT UP.
LARS AND I ARE CLOSING UP --
>> [ HUMMING ]
[ CHOMPS ]
[ HUMMING CONTINUES ]
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]
I'M CLOSING UP FOR THE DAY.
>> Steven: HEY, SADIE!
THERE'S A SNACK NAMED AFTER YOU?
>> NAH, THOSE ARE ALL LUNCHES MY
MOM PACKED FOR ME.
>> Steven: AWW, THAT'S SO NICE!
>> EH...ACTUALLY, IT'S PRETTY
EMBARRASSING.
SHE'S BEEN DOING IT FOR YEARS.
I MEAN, I KNOW HOW TO FEED
MYSELF!
THEY JUST MAKE ME FEEL LIKE A
KID, YOU KNOW?
>> Steven: CAN I TRY ONE?
>> SURE.
BUT CHOOSE WISELY.
SOME OF THOSE HAVE BEEN IN THERE
FOR A FEW MONTHS.
>> Steven: ALRIGHTY, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE GOT HERE.
LOOK LIKE A CLASSIC PBJ SANDWICH
CUT INTO TRIANGLES!
VERY NICE!
IT'S THE ONLY SHAPE A SANDWICH
SHOULD BE.
MAMA SADIE, THIS LUNCH IS A
WIN!
AND FOR DESSERT WE HAVE...
>> [ GROWLING SOFTLY ]
>> Steven: WHOA! LOOK AT THIS!
LION! LION LOOK!
IT'S A COOKIE SHAPED LIKE A
STAR!
[ LAUGHS ]
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THIS
COOKIE IS...
OUT OF THIS WORLD.
EH?
>> [ SNORTS ]
>> Steven: [ MUNCHING ]
I WONDER WHAT KIND OF LUNCH
MY MOM WOULD'VE MADE ME?
[ GASPS ]
MAYBE ACTUAL SPACE COOKIES!
[ SIGHS ]
I JUST WISH...I KNEW A LITTLE
MORE ABOUT HER.
BLINK IF THIS MEANS YOU LOVE ME!
[ PUFFS ]
HE LOVES ME!
ALL DONE!
I MADE SURE TO MAKE IT EXTRA
SKOOSHY, JUST THE WAY YOU LIKE
IT!
WHA-- HEY!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: HEY, GET OUT OF
THERE!
LION, THIS IS THE STEVEN BED NOT
THE LION BED!
[ GRUNTS ]
COME ON!
WHOA! UGH!
HEY! THAT'S MINE TOO!
AND SIR BEARINGTON.
HUP! UGHH.
[ YAWNS ]
'NIGHT LION!
LOVE YOU...IN THE MORNING.
[ SNORES ]
[ Thinking ] WHOA...
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
[ GASPS ]
I CAN'T BREATHE!
>> Pearl: STEVEN! STEVEN!
STEVEN! STEVEN!
STEVEN! OH MY GOSH! OH MY GOSH!
>> Steven: [ MUFFLED YELLING ]
>> Pearl: HANG ON! I GOT YOU!
UGH, LION!
LET HIM GO!
[ YELLS ]
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
WHY WAS LION SLEEPING ON TOP OF
YOU?
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S BEING A LITTLE CLINGY
TODAY.
BUT THAT'S CAUSE I'M HIS
FAVORITE!
OH!
[ Muffled ] SEE?
WAIT...
[ Normal voice ] WHY ARE YOU
HERE, PEARL?
>> Pearl: ME? NOTHING.
I WAS JUST UH...
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW I ALWAYS
SAY...
UM, I JUST UH...
I LIKE TO WATCH YOU SLEEP
SOMETIMES.
AND BY SOMETIMES I MEAN OFTEN.
>> Steven: OKEYDOKEY, IT'S TIME
FOR EVERYONE TO LEAVE STEVEN
ALONE.
I'M A GROWING BOY AND I NEEDS MY
REST.
[ SIGHS ]
LION, THAT MEANS YOU TOO.
RAH! RAH! RAH! RAH! RAH!
AHHH.
HM!
>> I WIN.
>> Steven: W-WHAT?!
THAT WAS A GOOD MOVE.
>> THANKS.
>> Steven: DOGCOPTER, HOW DO YOU
DO IT?
>> HOW DO I DO WHAT?
>> Steven: I MEAN, WHAT'S YOUR
SECRET?
HOW'D YOU GET SO TALENTED?
>> DON'T FOCUS SO MUCH ON
TALENT, STEVEN.
MAKING ART IS ALL ABOUT
COMMUNICATION.
A PIECE OF ART IS A
CONVERSATION.
EVERY CHOICE YOU MAKE IS A
STATEMENT.
[ CHOMP! ]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT LABELS OR
CONFORMING TO A STANDARD.
JUST BE TRUE TO YOURSELF AND
PEOPLE WILL APPRECIATE YOUR
HONESTY.
[ GULPS ] AHH.
>> Steven: WHOA...
THANKS FOR THE ADVICE.
>> AND TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
>> Steven: WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ] HERE AGAIN?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS PLACE IS
BUT IT FEELS...FAMILIAR.
WHY CAN'T I BREATHE?
WAIT A MINUTE...
LION!
[ MUFFLED YELLING ]
UNGH!
LION, MY FACE IS NOT YOUR BED!
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
[ LION GROANS ]
>> Steven: YOU JUST WANTED A
BELLY RUB?
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YOU NEVER LET ME TOUCH YOUR
BELLY!
OH!
[ MUFFLED YELLING ]
IT'S A TRAP!
AN ADORABLE TRAP!
[ MUFFLED YELLING ]
OKAY YOU GOT ME!
[ PUFFS ]
WILL YOU LET ME GO?
COME ON NOW!
UGH!
AAH!
THAT'S IT!
LET'S GO LION, YOU'RE ON A TIME
OUT!
I SAID, YOU'RE ON TIME OUT!
YOU'RE GONNA STAY OUT HERE AND
THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU DID!
[ LION YOWLS ]
>> Steven: HMPH!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
HE LOVES ME!
AWW, I JUST CAN'T STAY MAD AT
YOU!
YOU'RE A WONDERFUL PINK HUMAN
BEING.
EXCEPT YOU'RE NOT.
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LION.
[ GASPS, PANTING ]
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ Thinking ] I'M INSIDE LION'S
MANE?!
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ LION GROWLS ]
SORRY, I COULDN'T RESIST.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ Thinking ] AM I...
SUPPOSED TO DO SOMETHING HERE?
WHA--?
MM...
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ Thinking ] FOR ME?
WHO WOULD PUT THIS HERE?
AND HOW DOES THIS HUGE PLACE FIT
INSIDE OF LION'S MANE ANYW--
MM...
[ STRUGGLING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: ...AND HE KEEPS
SLEEPING ON STEVEN'S FACE!
BUT STEVEN DOESN'T WANT ME
WATCHING HIM ANYMORE.
SO ONE OF YOU TWO HAS TO DO IT.
>> Steven: SADIE! SADIE!
>> STEVEN, YOU KNOW DONUTS
AREN'T READY FOR ANOTHER HOUR.
>> Steven: [ WHISPERING ]
>> REALLY? COME ON!
[ STATIC CRACKLES ]
[ WAVES CRASHING ]
>> [ Chuckling ] WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> STEVEN, THAT VOICE.
>> [ SNORING ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
GREG MADE A FRIEND.
[ SEAGULL CRIES ]
>> WHAT?! AH!
[ PANTING ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
GO ON...
>> SORRY, I'M GETTING STAGE
FRIGHT HERE.
>> TELL US ABOUT YOURSELF.
>> WELL, LET'S SEE HERE...
MY NAME IS GREG.
NO, NO, NO! THIS IS ALL WRONG!
OKAY, GO!
THEY CALL ME...
[ STRUMS GUITAR ]
MR. UNIVERSE!
GET READY BABY, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE THE COOLEST DAD THIS SIDE
OF THE COSMOS!
[ MIMICS GUITAR RIFF ]
PRESS THE BUTTON, ROSE!
>> OH, RIGHT!
WAS THAT THE RIGHT ONE?
>> UH...MAYBE?
>> OH, WHAT DOES THIS ONE DO?
ISN'T IT REMARKABLE, STEVEN?
THIS WORLD IS FULL OF SO MANY
POSSIBILITIES.
EACH LIVING THING HAS AN
ENTIRELY UNIQUE EXPERIENCE.
THE SIGHTS THEY SEE, THE SOUNDS
THEY HEAR.
THE LIVES THEY LIVE ARE SO
COMPLICATED...
A-AND SO SIMPLE.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU TO JOIN
THEM.
STEVEN, WE CAN'T BOTH EXIST.
I'M GOING TO BECOME HALF OF YOU.
AND I NEED YOU TO KNOW THAT
EVERY MOMENT YOU LOVE BEING
YOURSELF, THAT'S ME, LOVING YOU
AND LOVING BEING YOU.
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO BE
SOMETHING EXTRAORDINARY.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A HUMAN
BEING.
>> HEY, ROSE!
>> TAKE CARE OF THEM, STEVEN.
>> HEY, SADIE, COME ON WE GOT TO
OPEN UP!
WHAT IN THE WORLD DID YOU GUYS
WATCH?
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]
[ DIALING ]
HEY, MOM?
YOU KNOW HOW I SAID YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO MAKE ME THOSE LUNCHES
ANYMORE?
>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
WENT SO WELL.
>> Amethyst: THAT WAS KIND OF
GREAT WHEN YOU HIT IT WITH YOUR
SPEAR AND IT WENT LIKE BING
BOING -- PKWWW!
>> Pearl: AND THE WAY YOU WERE
CIRCLING AROUND IT...
ALMOST LOOKED LIKE STRATEGY.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, YOU KNOW, I CAN DO THAT
STUFF, TOO.
>> Steven: WAIT UP!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
SORRY I COULDN'T HELP MUCH.
I THINK THE FLOWERS ARE MAKING
ME --
AH-AHH...
AH-CHOO!
[ SNIFFLES ]
SORRY, GARNET.
>> Garnet: I'LL LIVE.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN, YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO SNEEZE INTO YOUR
ANTECUBITAL FOSSA.
>> Steven: MY WHAT?
>> Pearl: YOUR...
THIS THING.
>> Steven: [ GASPING ]
AH-AHH...
>> Amethyst: DO IT AT PEARL!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOUR FOSSA!
>> Steven: AH-CHOO!
>> Pearl: OH!
>> Steven: WAAH!
WHA?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHOA.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
HUH?
WAAH!
>> Pearl: CAREFUL!
IT'S DANGEROUS TO STICK YOUR
HEAD OUT OF THE STREAM!
>> Garnet: THERE'S NOT MUCH AIR,
AND IT'S VERY COLD.
>> Steven: YOU GUYS, I SAW
SOMETHING OUT THERE!
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> Steven: SOMETHING WARPING!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THAT'S NOT
POSSIBLE.
IS YOUR VISION BLURRY FROM THE
POLLEN?
>> Steven: I CAN SEE
PERFECTLY...PEARL.
I KNOW THERE'S SOMETHING OUT
THERE!
>> Garnet: THERE'S NOTHING OUT
THERE, STEVEN.
THERE HASN'T BEEN ANYTHING ELSE
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
UGH! UH...
[ REFRIGERATOR DOOR OPENS ]
AAH!
AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: [ MUNCHING ]
HEY, STEVEN!
WANT SOME MACARONI CHEESE?
[ MUNCHING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
W-WAIT!
I CAN'T SLEEP.
>> Amethyst: WHY?
ARE YOU SCARED OF THAT THING YOU
SAW WARPING RIGHT INTO THE HOUSE
AND ATTACKING YOU IN YOUR SLEEP?
>> Steven: NO.
>> Amethyst: OH! GOOD!
GOOD.
NIGHTY NIGHT!
DON'T LET THE WARP MONSTER BITE!
PBHT!
HA HA!
[ MUFFLED LAUGHING ]
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
LOOKS LIKE I'M NOT SLEEPING
TONIGHT.
[ BIRD SCREECHING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN...
WE'VE GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
>> Steven: AAH! AGHH!
>> Pearl: GAH!
>> Steven: OH, PEARL.
>> Garnet: NOW YOU'RE NOT
GETTING ANY COOKIES.
>> Amethyst: COOKIES?!
I'LL TAKE 'EM!
>> Garnet: [ WHISTLES ]
>> Amethyst: [ MUNCHING ]
>> Garnet: SLOW DOWN, AMETHYST.
>> Steven: I'M SORRY, PEARL.
I JUST...
I GUESS I DIDN'T...
>> Garnet: DIDN'T SLEEP.
>> Steven: [ YAWNS ]
MAYBE.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN!
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE THING YOU
THINK YOU SAW OUTSIDE THE WARP
STREAM YESTERDAY, IS IT?
[ CLANG! ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> Steven: BUT IT WAS REAL!
SOMETHING WAS WARPING SOMEWHERE
IN THE WARP!
>> Pearl: LISTEN.
NOTHING ON EARTH CAN USE THE
WARPS BUT US.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
STEVEN, NOD IN AGREEMENT IF YOU
UNDERSTAND.
NOD IN AGREEMENT --
>> Garnet: I'M CONFIDENT PEARL
IS RIGHT.
BUT IF IT'LL MAKE YOU FEEL
BETTER, WE CAN JUST GO CHECK.
NOTHING UNUSUAL.
>> Steven: AH-AHH...
AHH-CHOO!
>> Garnet: BLESS YOU.
>> Pearl: NOTHING HERE, EITHER.
AND THE GEODE IS HOLDING NICELY.
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
NOW THAT'S SOMETHING!
HEH. STEVEN JR.'s BEEN BUSY.
[ LAUGHING ]
THIS MAKES YOU A GRANDPA!
>> Garnet: CONGRATULATIONS.
>> Steven: HEY!
WE'RE GETTING OFF TASK HERE!
>> Pearl: WE'VE LOOKED ALL OVER!
THERE'S NOTHING OUT HERE TO
FIND!
>> Steven: BUT YOU'RE WRONG.
>> Pearl: EXCUSE ME?
>> Steven: I...I MEAN --
>> Pearl: NOTHING ON EARTH CAN
USE THESE WARPS BUT US!
>> Steven: WELL, WHAT IF IT CAME
FROM SPACE?
>> Pearl: I...DON'T APPRECIATE
YOUR TONE.
THESE ARE THE WARPS THAT ONCE
CONNECTED US TO OTHER PLANETS.
IF SOMETHING TRIED TO COME FROM
SPACE, IT WOULD BE THROUGH HERE.
BUT WAIT!
THIS WARP PAD IS BROKEN, MARKED
INACTIVE BY THE VERY DEPRESSED
CARTOON BREAKFAST STICKER YOU
PLACED HERE YOURSELF!
>> Amethyst: LOOK, PEARL'S
RIGHT, LIKE USUAL.
UGH!
YOU GET USED TO IT.
>> Garnet: WE'RE SAFE.
>> Steven: WELL...I GUESS SO.
>> Amethyst: OH, MAN! FINALLY!
THAT TOOK ALL DAY.
>> Garnet: IT WAS IMPORTANT TO
MAKE STEVEN FEEL SECURE.
>> Pearl: YES, STEVEN FEELS MUCH
BETTER NOW.
>> Steven: I'M A LITTLE TIRED...
OF YOU GUYS TELLING ME HOW I
FEEL!
I KNOW I SAW SOMETHING OUTSIDE
THE STREAM!
>> Pearl: AND I KNOW YOU DIDN'T!
YOU DON'T TELL ME WHAT I ALREADY
KNOW!
>> Steven: WHY IS IT SO HARD TO
JUST "LISTEN TO STEVEN?"
>> Amethyst: UH, THIS IS NEW.
I KIND OF LIKE IT.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU JUST DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> Steven: IT SOUNDS LIKE MAYBE
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT!
>> Pearl: UGH!
>> Garnet: OKAY, STEVEN, THAT'S
ENOUGH.
LET IT GO.
>> Amethyst: HEY, DUDE.
YOU STILL ON ABOUT THAT THING IN
THE STREAM?
UH, WHAT YOU EATING?
>> Steven: MACARONI AND NOTHING.
>> Amethyst: UGH. WHATEVER.
WE CAN HANG OUT AGAIN WHEN YOU
STOP BEING SUCH A SAD SACK.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
>> Steven: UGH!
WHY AM I DOING THIS?
FINE. I GIVE UP!
STEVEN WAS WRONG AND EVERYONE
ELSE WAS RIGHT!
NOTHING'S GOING TO COME THROUGH
THAT WARP PAD!
[ HIGH-PITCHED WHINE ]
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU WERE THE THING IN THE WARP
STREAM!
YOU DID COME FROM SPACE.
[ GASPS ]
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET TO THE WARP
PAD, AREN'T YOU?
AMETHYST, COME BACK!
OOF!
I KNEW IT!
I DID SEE SOMETHING!
GUYS!
I WAS RIGHT!
WAAH!
GUYS!
COME ON! CHECK THIS OUT!
OW!
UNH!
AAH! SORRY!
HUH?
OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
GARNET! AMETHYST!
PE-E-E-ARL!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
HUH?
Y-YOU'RE COMING FROM ALL OVER?
OW! HEY!
STOP IT!
WHOA!
UNH!
HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
I WON'T...
LET YOU...
UNH!
[ PANTING ]
[ SHUDDERED BREATHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
I WAS RIGHT.
[ CHUCKLES WEAKLY ]
AND NOW...
I'M GONNA DIE...
A TIRED, FROZEN LITTLE...
SAD SACK.
[ WARP STREAM ACTIVATES ]
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: TAKE DEEP BREATHS.
SO, THIS IS WHAT YOU SAW.
>> Steven: I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THAT!
>> Garnet: I DO.
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED TO YOU.
YOU'RE A CRYSTAL GEM, TOO.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, ARE YOU OKAY?!
AMETHYST HEARD THE WARP PAD
ACTIVATE, AND GARNET SAID YOU
WERE FLOATING OUTSIDE THE STREAM
AND --
UH...WHAT IS THAT?
>> Steven: YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> Amethyst: WHOA.
THAT THING'S FAR OUT.
>> Steven: IT'S SOME KIND OF
SPACE ROBOT.
THERE WERE TONS OF THEM!
AND IT LOOKED LIKE THEY WERE ALL
GOING TO THE SAME PLACE.
>> Amethyst: HUH?
>> Pearl: WHAT ARE THEY DOING TO
THE HOMEWORLD WARP?
>> Amethyst: THERE'S A MILLION
OF THEM!
THEY FIXED IT?
>> Steven: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
I...DON'T KNOW.
[ WARP STREAM ACTIVATES ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
HUAH!
>> HMM...
>> Pearl: WHO IS THAT?
>> Garnet: NO IDEA.
>> LOG DATE: 312.
THIS IS PERIDOT, PERFORMING
EARTH HUB MAINTENANCE CHECK.
>> Steven: PERIDOT.
HER NAME IS PERIDOT.
[ MUFFLED SPEAKING ]
>> WARP REPAIR A SUCCESS.
ALL 79 FLASK ROBONOIDS DEPLOYED
AND ACCOUNTED FOR.
PREPARING TO LOCATE AND MANUALLY
REACTIVATE KINDERGA--
[ GASPS ]
>> Steven: AWW.
THE LITTLE ONES ARE LIKE HER
BABIES.
[ CREAKING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> NOW TO ACCESS THE DOMESTIC
WARP.
HUH?
HUH.
THIS SITE MAY HAVE BEEN
COMPROMISED.
[ BEEPING ]
>> Pearl: THEY'RE COMING BACK.
I CAN'T DO THIS!
NOT AGAIN!
>> Amethyst: WE'RE DEAD!
WE ARE SO DEAD!
>> Steven: WAS THAT ANOTHER GEM?
WHERE DID SHE COME FROM?
WHAT WAS SHE TRYING TO DO?
HUH?
>> Garnet: IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> Steven: WHOA.
>> Amethyst: OH.
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
SHE'S NOT COMING BACK.