♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
OPEN THE DOOR, PERIDOT.
IF THIS "CLUSTER"
IS PUTTING US IN DANGER,
YOU NEED TO TELL US WHAT IT IS
SO WE CAN STOP IT.
NO! I HATE YOU.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU
ANYTHING ABOUT THE CLUSTER.
OH, COME ON.
IS IT LIKE A BIG,
UH, HUNK OF GRANOLA?
WHAT'S GRANOLA?
I'M SURE
IT'S NOT GRANOLA.
NOW, PERIDOT,
I'M SURE WE CAN REACH
SOME SORT OF AGREEMENT.
PERHAPS A TRADE
IS IN ORDER?
OH, SURE.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GIVE ME BACK
MY LEG ENHANCEMENTS
AND MY ARM ATTACHMENTS
WITH MY SCREEN AND MY LOG
AND ALL MY INFORMATION.
OH, WAIT,
YOU DESTROYED THEM!
SO, NO, I DON'T THINK WE CAN
REACH SOME SORT OF AGREEMENT!
[ ALL SIGH ]
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
OKAY, PERIDOT,
YOU CAN TURN AROUND NOW.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
SORRY FOR INTERRUPTING
YOUR INTERROGATION.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
STEVEN.
I SWEAR, PERIDOT IS GONNA CRACK
ANY SECOND NOW.
Peridot: I'LL NEVER CRACK
FOR THE LIKES OF YOU,
YOU...CRYSTAL CLODS.
[ LAUGHS ]
OOH, I GOT YOUR CLODS
RIGHT HERE, YOU LITTLE --
HOLD ON, PEARL.
IF SHE'S NOT GONNA BE
OF ANY HELP.
LET'S INVESTIGATE THIS THING
ON OUR OWN.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
SORRY, STEVEN.
WE'RE GONNA NEED YOU
TO STAY HERE
AND KEEP AN EYE
ON OUR...GUEST.
REALLY?
YEAH. MAKE SURE
SHE DOESN'T TRY ANYTHING.
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S HARMLESS
WITHOUT HER LIMB ENHANCERS
Peridot:
I'M NOT HARMLESS!
OH, HUSH UP!
OH, STEVEN!
THERE'S ONE MORE THING
I HAVE TO MENTION.
WHAT IS IT?
I LOVE YOU. BYE.
SEE YA LATER.
MM.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
THEY LEFT, YOU KNOW.
YOU CAN COME OUT NOW.
NO. I-I LIKE IT IN HERE.
OKAY.
WOW.
IT'S REALLY COMING DOWN.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
IT'S HAPPENING!
WHAT?
-THE CLUSTER!
-REALLY?
WHAT ELSE COULD BE MAKING
THAT HORRIBLE --
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
AAH! IT'S POUNDING ON THE EARTH
FROM THE INSIDE.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE END OF THE WORLD.
[ WHIMPERS ]
OH, THAT'S JUST THUNDER.
WHAT?
YEAH,
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
IT'S JUST THUNDER.
IT HAPPENS WHEN IT RAINS.
EH...HUH?
YOU DON'T KNOW
ABOUT RAIN?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
WITHOUT MY SCREEN.
IT'S OKAY.
HERE, PRETEND THIS SOUP
IS THE OCEAN.
WHEN THE SUN WARMS IT UP,
THE WATER EVAPORATES
INTO CLOUDS,
LIKE THIS STEAM.
AND WHEN THE CLOUDS
GET REALLY HEAVY, IT RAINS.
SO SCALDING LIQUID
POURS DOWN FROM THE SKY?
NO, NO, IT'S JUST WATER.
IT CAN'T HURT YOU.
HERE, WHY DON'T
I JUST SHOW YOU.
WHOO-HOO!
STEVEN, WAIT!
UH...OH...
COME ON!
[ LAUGHS ]
LOOK, I'M OKAY.
IT'S JUST WATER.
THIS IS JUST SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENS ON EARTH.
ISN'T IT COOL?
[ LAUGHS ]
WHOA!
WAH! [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH!
WHOO-HOO!
♪♪
YEAH, YOU DID IT!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ISN'T IT COOL?
[ LAUGHS ]
COOL.
THAT WAS FUN.
HUH?
IT WAS...SOMETHING.
HMM.
UH...
MM...
STEVEN?
HM?
I'M GOING TO SAY SOMETHING.
THANK YOU.
UH...WHAT FOR?
FOR EXPLAINING
THIS "RAIN" BUSINESS TO ME.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YES. YOU'RE A MUCH MORE
INTELLIGENT CREATURE
THAN I INITIALLY
THOUGHT.
UH, THAT'S GOOD.
YES.
MUCH MORE...USEFUL
THAN THOSE CLODS.
STEVEN,
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND!
ABOUT WHAT, EXACTLY?
I'VE DECIDED TO SHARE
SOME INFORMATION WITH YOU.
AH, I KNOW YOU USE
MY TOOTHBRUSH.
N-NO.
WELL, YES.
BUT IT'S ABOUT THE CLUSTER.
[ GASPS ]
YOU CRACKED.
I HAVEN'T CRACKED!
WAIT, YOU HAVE TO TELL THE GEMS.
THEY NEED TO KNOW THIS.
NO, I DON'T WANT
TO TALK TO THEM.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I NEED.
I COULD SHOW YOU NOW,
BUT I HAVE NOTHING.
MY ARM ATTACHMENTS,
MY FINGERS, MY SCREEN, MY LOG --
IT'S ALL GONE.
BUT ALL OF MY LOGS
UP TO DATE 652 STILL EXIST.
BACKED UP IN FACET 5
OF THE PRIME KINDERGARTEN.
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE YOU
TO THE KINDERGARTEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
STEVEN, DON'T YOU WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT THE CLUSTER?
MM...OKAY.
WE CAN GO
TO THE KINDERGARTEN.
OH, YES!
BUT...
NO, A CATCH.
FINE.
WHAT ARE YOUR DEMANDS?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HOLD
MY HAND THE WHOLE TIME.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, HERE WE ARE.
OKAY, GREAT.
LET'S GO.
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
THIS PLACE JUST GETS WORSE
EVERY TIME I COME HERE.
I KNOW.
IT'S BEEN SO POORLY MANAGED.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
IN WAY BETTER SHAPE
WHEN YOU FIRST EMERGED.
EMERGED?
YEAH, YOU'RE SOME KIND OF
QUARTZ, RIGHT?
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
MADE HERE.
UH...I CAME
FROM MY MOM AND DAD.
ARE THOSE SOME KIND OF ROCKS?
OR ANOTHER PLANET?
[ CHUCKLES ] NOPE.
MY DAD'S FROM EARTH,
BUT MY MOM'S A GEM.
YOU'RE SOME SORT OF HYBRID?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
THE ANSWER TO THAT
IS A STORY I LIKE TO CALL
"THE BALLAD
OF ROSE AND GREG."
I DON'T CARE.
LET'S JUST HURRY
TO THE CONTROL ROOM.
YOU SURE THIS IS SAFE?
THE LAST TIME I WAS HERE,
THERE WERE A BUNCH
OF FUSION MONSTERS.
YES, I WAS CHECKING
THEIR PROGRESS.
WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THOSE THINGS?
WHEN IT BECAME CLEAR
THAT THE EARTH WAS NO LONGER
A VIABLE COLONY,
HOMEWORLD DECIDED TO USE IT
FOR SOMETHING ELSE --
A SERIES OF EXPERIMENTS.
A GEM GEO-WEAPON.
OH, DID YOU HELP?
NEGATIVE.
I WASN'T LUCKY ENOUGH
TO BE AROUND FOR THAT.
BUT I READ OVER
A FEW HUNDRED YEARS OF REPORTS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THIS IS WHERE
YOU NEED TO BE, RIGHT?
YES. I'M GOING TO HAVE TO REMOVE
THIS PANEL
AND DO A BIT OF WORK
TO RESTORE POWER TO THIS ROOM,
SO...CAN I HAVE
MY HAND BACK NOW?
OKAY, BUT STAY
WHERE I CAN SEE YOU.
[ PANEL BEEPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ STRAINING ]
IT'S OVER.
I CAN'T SHOW YOU ANYTHING.
LET'S GO BACK.
MIND IF I TRY?
GO AHEAD.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA!
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS OVER HERE...
IT'S NOT PERFECT,
BUT IT'LL DO FOR NOW.
[ GROANS ]
COME ON.
WHAT'S UP, DOT?
I CAN'T QUITE
REACH THE --.
IT'S OKAY TO ASK FOR HELP,
YOU KNOW.
I HAD IT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THESE ARE THE EARLY ATTEMPTS
AT ARTIFICIAL FUSION.
THAT'S A LOT OF GEM SHARDS.
WE WERE GROWING THEM HERE
AT THIS VERY SITE.
BUT THESE WERE JUST PROTOTYPES
FOR THE FINAL PRODUCT,
A SINGULAR GIANT
ARTIFICIAL FUSION
COMPRISED OF MILLIONS
OF GEM SHARDS --
THE CLUSTER.
PERIDOT, YOU'RE SAYING
THERE'S A GIANT MUTANT GEM
THE SIZE OF THE EARTH
UNDER US RIGHT NOW?
OH, NO.
WHEN IT FORMS IT'LL BE MUCH,
MUCH BIGGER THAN THE EARTH.
RIGHT NOW IT LIES DORMANT,
INCUBATING IN THE EARTH'S CORE.
BUT WHEN IT EMERGES
AND TAKES ITS PHYSICAL FORM,
IT WILL DESTROY
THE PLANET.
THE PROTOTYPES
ARE ALREADY EMERGING.
THE CLUSTER IS NEXT.
IF WE CAN'T GET OFF THIS PLANET,
WE'VE GOT TO STOP THE CLUSTER.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE IMPOSSIBLE,
BUT NOW WE HAVE A CHANCE.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S YOU, STEVEN!
NOW THAT YOU'RE FILLED IN,
WE CAN GET TO WORK.
UH...HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO HELP?
WELL, YOU HAVE
ALL THE INFORMATION WE NEED
ABOUT EARTH
AND ITS ERRATIC BEHAVIOR.
PUT THAT TOGETHER
WITH MY EXPANSIVE KNOWLEDGE
OF THE CLUSTER,
AND WE JUST MIGHT
BE ABLE TO STOP IT.
NO, PERIDOT,
I DON'T THINK YOU GET IT.
JUST BECAUSE I KNOW
HOW CLOUDS WORK,
DOESN'T MEAN
I KNOW HOW TO STOP
A GIANT MUTANT
IN THE CENTER OF THE EARTH.
BESIDES, THE ONLY REASON I KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT CLOUDS AND RAIN
IS BECAUSE
MY DAD TOLD ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I USED TO BE REALLY SCARED
OF THUNDERSTORMS,
JUST LIKE YOU.
THEN DAD EXPLAINED HOW RAIN
AND ALL THAT STUFF WORKS,
THEN I WASN'T SCARED
OF RAIN ANYMORE.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU HAVE
OTHER KNOWLEDGE
ABOUT HOW
THIS PLANET WORKS.
SURE, BUT NONE OF IT'S
GONNA HELP US.
IF WE WANT TO STOP
THIS CLUSTER THING,
WE'LL NEED HELP
FROM THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
I SAID
I DON'T NEED THEM!
LET'S JUST WARP ME
BACK TO THE BATHROOM,
OR WHATEVER YOU CALL IT,
AND WE'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
IF IT LOOKS REALLY BAD,
THEN WE CAN JUST ASK
THIS DAD FOR HELP, RIGHT?
[ CREATURE SCREECHES ]
YIPE!
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, NO!
GEM MUTANTS!
[ SCREECHING ]
YAAH!
DO SOMETHING!
I AM DOING SOMETHING.
SOMETHING USEFUL!
UH, LET'S RUN.
OVER HERE.
NO, THE OTHER WAY.
NO, NOT THERE.
Both: AAH!
LET'S RUN
INTO THIS CORNER.
OH, NO!
WE'RE CORNERED!
Both: AAH!
AAH!
CAN'T YOU DESTROY IT?
NO, THIS IS ALL I CAN DO
ON MY OWN.
YAAH...
THAT'S IT.
WE ARE FINISHED.
[ ROARS ]
Garnet: HANG ON, STEVEN.
IT'S THE GEMS!
PERIDOT, THERE'S NO WAY
WE CAN STOP THIS THING
IN THE EARTH ON OUR OWN.
WE NEED THE HELP
OF THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
STEVEN,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?!
MOVE ASIDE, STEVEN.
PERIDOT?!
WHAT ARE YOU TWO
DOING HERE?!
STEVEN, I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO KEEP AN EYE ON HER.
I KNOW, BUT --
HE DID WHAT HE WAS TOLD.
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN UP, YOU CLO--
[SIGHS] CRYSTAL GEMS.
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
I HAVE SOMETHING TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE CLUSTER.
♪ I ALWAYS THOUGHT
I MIGHT BE BAD ♪
♪ NOW I'M SURE THAT IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I THINK YOU'RE SO GOOD,
AND I'M NOTHING LIKE YOU ♪
Peridot: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
AS IT SEEMS
I HAVE NO OTHER OPTIONS,
I HAVE CONCEDED TO REVEAL
SOME IMPORTANT INFORMATION
TO YOU CRYSTAL GEMS.
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
THIS...
WHOA!
...IS THE EARTH.
AT THE VERY CENTER
OF THE PLANET'S CORE
LIES THE CLUSTER.
ROTATE.
THIS IS THE CLUSTER --
A MASSIVE ARTIFICIAL FUSION
COMPOSED OF MILLIONS
OF GEM SHARDS.
IT HAS LAID DORMANT
FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS
WITHIN THIS PLANET'S CRUST.
WHEN THIS GEM ACTIVATES
AND TAKES ITS FORM,
THE RESULT WILL BE CATASTROPHIC.
NOW!
WO-WO-WO-WO-WO-WO-WO-WO-WO-WO
BWAAAHH!
[ ALL GASP ]
GRAH! GRAH! GRAH! GRAH!
WHAT IS THAT?!
IT'S THE CLUSTER.
IT DOES NOT
LOOK LIKE THAT.
BUT IT IS REAL, AND IT CAN
ACTIVATE AT ANY MOMENT!
[ Softly ] BWAAH...
WHAT A CLUSTER.
THAT ABOMINATION
MUST BE STOPPED.
BUT HOW?
WE'LL NEED TO BUILD
SOME SORT OF MACHINE
TO TAKE US
TO THE CENTER OF THE EARTH.
IT'LL HAVE TO --
Peridot: HEY!
I WASN'T FINISHED SPEAKING.
WHAT WE NEED
IS TO BUILD SOME SORT OF MACHINE
TO TAKE US
TO THE CENTER OF THE EARTH.
IT'LL NEED TO WITHSTAND UP TO
360 GIGAPASCALS OF PRESSURE
AND TEMPERATURES
OF 9,800 DEGREES.
WELL,
WE MUSTN'T WASTE TIME.
WE NEED TO START FINDING PARTS
FOR THIS MACHINE IMMEDIATELY.
YES, OBVIOUSLY.
WE'LL START BY DISMANTLING ALL
DEVICES INSIDE THIS DWELLING?
WHA?
[ GRUNTS ] THIS PRIMITIVE
RADIATION CONCENTRATOR
SHOULD COME IN HANDY!
NYAH!
THIS PRIMITIVE
VIBRATION TRANSMITTER
COULD POSSIBLY SERVE A FUNCTION.
[ PANTING ]
THERE'S A REMOTE CHANCE
SOMETHING USEFUL COULD BE INSIDE
THIS PRIMITIVE IMAGE CUBE.
WAIT!
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA
THAT DOESN'T INVOLVE
DESTROYING THE HOUSE.
CLASSIC STEVEN.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE
IN THE BARN
SHOULD BE ADEQUATE ENOUGH
FOR US TO GET STARTED.
FIRST, I RECOMMEND
WE ORGANIZE THE COMPONENT TYPES
AND ASSEMBLE A ROUGH BLUEPRINT
BASED ON WHAT WE HAVE AVAILABLE.
[ SIGHS ]
SORRY, STEVEN.
IT'S A LOVELY DRAWING,
BUT IT WON'T LOOK LIKE THIS.
HMM.
GOOD.
YES, THIS IS ADEQUATE.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN GO NOW.
UH, WHAT?
HMM?
UM...
THAT WILL BE ALL?
[ CLAPS HANDS ]
[ Through teeth ]
HOW DO YOU GET HER TO LEAVE?
EXCUSE ME,
I AM NOT LEAVING.
YEAH, SHE'S GOT TO STAY AND HELP
BUILD THE DRILL THING, RIGHT?
NO, NO.
YOU'RE CONFUSED.
A PEARL CAN'T BUILD
A THING LIKE THIS.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE PEARLS
AREN'T FOR THIS.
THEY'RE FOR STANDING AROUND
A-AND LOOKING NICE
A-AND, UH, HOLDING YOUR STUFF
FOR YOU, RIGHT?
THAT'S ENOUGH!
IF WE'RE GOING TO
WORK TOGETHER,
YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN TO YOU?
[ LAUGHS ]
DID YOU TEACH HER
TO TALK LIKE THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
SHE'S A PEARL.
SHE'S A MADE-TO-ORDER SERVANT
JUST LIKE THE HUNDREDS
OF OTHER PEARLS
BEING FLAUNTED AROUND
BACK ON HOMEWORLD.
WAIT.
THERE'S HUNDREDS OF PEARLS?
WELL, YES, BU--
AND SHE LOOKS LIKE A FANCY ONE,
TOO.
UGH!
HUNDREDS OF PEARLS.
SO, WHO DO YOU BELONG TO,
ANYWAY?
NOBODY!
THEN WHAT ARE YOU FOR?
WELL, YOU CAN BELONG TO ME
FOR NOW.
HA! A PERIDOT WITH A PEARL!
WHAT WOULD THEY SAY BACK HOME?
NOW, LISTEN HERE,
YOU LITTLE TINY TWERP.
IN CASE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN,
YOU'RE ON OUR TURF NOW,
AND I DIDN'T FIGHT
A 1,000-YEAR WAR
FOR THIS PLANET'S INDEPENDENCE
TO TAKE ORDERS
FROM THE LIKES OF YOU!
EXCUSE ME?
I AM NATURAL TECHNICIAN
AND A CERTIFIED KINDERGARTNER.
I WAS MADE FOR THIS.
YOU WERE MADE TO TAKE ORDERS,
NOT TO GIVE THEM.
WHOA, WHOA,
HANG ON, GUYS!
NOW, WE CAN ALL AGREE
THAT YOU'RE BOTH GOOD
AT BUILDING THINGS,
SO, CAN'T YOU JUST TRY
LISTENING TO EACH OTHER?
NO!
I'M AS GOOD AT BUILDING THINGS
AS YOU. BETTER, EVEN!
HA! NAME ONE THING
YOU COULD ENGINEER BETTER.
GO ON.
ROBOTS.
HMM?
YOU SHOULD BUILD ROBOTS --
GIANT ROBOTS.
I SEE A RACE --
A GIANT ROBO-RACE.
WITH PRIZES --
GIANT ROBO-PRIZES.
YOU MEAN
LIKE A COMPETITION?
YEAH, TO SEE WHO'S BETTER
AT BUILDING STUFF.
WHAT ARE THESE "RO-BUTTS"
YOU SPEAK OF?
THEY'RE LIKE THOSE FUNKY
MARBLE GUYS YOU WERE SENDING,
ONLY BIGGER
AND YOU CAN RIDE THEM.
[ IMITATES ROBOT ]
HA! BUILDING ONE OF THESE
"RO-BUTTS" WILL BE EASY!
WELL,
I CAN BUILD ONE FASTER!
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ DRILL WHIRS ]
AAH!
[ CLATTERING ]
YO, STEVEN. HOW ARE
THE WONDER NERDS DOING? WAH!
WH-WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE THEY BUILDING THE DRILL?
NO,
WE'RE BUILDING ROBOTS NOW.
[ WHIRRING ]
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I SAID...
GIANT ROBOT!
Peridot: HA! PATHETIC.
NOW, BEHOLD MY VISION
OF ULTIMATE POWER!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ GASPS ] HEY!
MINE'S TALLER.
I WIN.
LADIES AND GENTLEGEMS, WELCOME
TO THE FIRST ANNUAL ROBOLYMPICS!
WHOO!
POPCORN!
THIS COMPETITION WILL TEST
OUR ROBO-ENGINEERS' SKILLS
OF ROBO-CONSTRUCTION
AND ROBO-PILOTING.
WHOEVER WINS
WILL GET TO BE IN CHARGE
OF BUILDING
THE CLUSTER DRILL MACHINE THING.
LET THE GAMES BEGIN!
WAH!
UGH.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
OHHH!
[ CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMES ]
HUH?
[ Laughing ]
OH!
MM-HMM.
HMM.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THIS IS THE FINAL EVENT!
YOU GOT THIS, P!
GET IT, GIRL!
HMPH!
READY! SET! CHUCK!
[ Straining ] HYAH!
[ Groaning ] RAH!
All: WHOA.
YOU BOTH GET A POINT
ON THAT ONE.
HMM. HMM.
LOOKS LIKE OUR FINAL SCORE
IS...A TIE!
WELL, THAT SETTLES IT.
YOU BOTH GET TO LEAD THE PROJECT
TOGETHER!
NO!
THIS ISN'T OVER!
I DEMAND
WE HAVE A TIEBREAKER!
UGH,
LET'S JUST GIVE IT A REST.
THAT'S IT! WE TIED.
WE ARE THE SAME.
LET'S MOVE ON.
NO!
YOU'RE A PEARL.
YOU ARE BENEATH ME!
I'LL ALWAYS BE BETTER
THAN YOU,
AND NOTHING I'VE SEEN TODAY
WILL EVER CHANGE THAT!
WELL, HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A PEARL
DO THIS?
OOF!
[ ALL GASP ]
SO, YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
GOOD.
WE SHOULD HAVE DONE THIS
FROM THE BEGINNING!
[ GRUNTING, GROANING ]
STOP!
GIANT ROBOTS SHOULDN'T FIGHT!
FIGHT, FIGHT,
FIGHT, FIGHT!
[ GROANS ]
HA HA HA!
UGH.
PEARL!
IT'S ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I'VE GOT THIS.
BE CAREFUL!
KICK HER IN THE BUTT!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
THIS IS POINTLESS!
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE GONNA BEAT ME!
YOU'RE AN ACCESSORY,
SOMEBODY'S SHINY TOY!
WHERE DO YOU GET OFF
ACTING LIKE YOUR OWN GEM?
YOU'RE JUST A PEARL!
THAT'S RIGHT!
I AM A PEARL!
[ GASPS ]
WHOO-HOO!
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
MAY BE TRUE,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M STILL GONNA
KICK YOUR BUTT!
[ Laughing ] OH!
[ CHUCKLING EVILLY ]
UH-OH.
[ GRUNTING ]
All: PEARL!
[ MOANS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
VICTORY IS MINE!
NOW I'M THE ONE IN CHANGE.
PRAISE ME! PRAISE ME!
Steven:
PEARL, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, P!
OH, THAT WAS AWESOME.
YOU WERE HARD CORE!
OH, REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
HEY!
WHY AREN'T YOU LISTENING TO ME?
I WON!
I'M THE NATURAL LEADER HERE.
SHE'S JUST A COMMON PEARL!
Steven: YOU'RE WRONG!
IF PEARLS ARE REALLY
LIKE YOU SAY THEY ARE,
THEN PEARL ISN'T COMMON AT ALL.
SHE TRAINED HERSELF TO FIGHT,
SHE LEARNED HOW TO BUILD THINGS,
AND SHE WORKS HARD EVERY DAY TO
BE GREATER THAN SHE ALREADY IS!
THAT'S NOT COMMON.
THAT'S AMAZING!
COME ON.
LET'S CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
Amethyst:
PEARL [LAUGHS] YOU SHOULD
COME WRESTLING WITH ME.
Pearl: UH, I DON'T KNOW.
B-B-BUT I WON!
WHAT ABOUT THE RULES?
WELCOME TO EARTH.
[ BIRDS CAWING ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
IT'S REMARKABLE THAT A PEARL
SUCH AS YOURSELF
COULD BECOME SUCH A...
KNOWLEDGEABLE TECHNICIAN.
MM.
WHY DON'T WE GET STARTED?
[ DRILL WHIRS ]
YOU'RE HOLDING IT
UPSIDE DOWN.
YES. OF COURSE.
YOU KNOW, THOSE ROUND APPENDAGES
ON YOUR MACHINE
COULD BE USEFUL
FOR SOMETHING.
THEY'RE CALLED WHEELS.
[ SIGHS ]
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE WELL ON OUR WAY
TO STOPPING THE CLUSTER.
"YOU THINK YOU CAN STOP ME?"
AAH!
GRAH, GRAH, GRAH, GRAH, GRAH.
AAH! WE'RE DOOMED!
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]