Steven: [ As Lion ] I am Lion,
the host of this show,
"Cooking with Lion."
[ Roars ]
Hi, everyone.
Today we're going to
make snack sushi.
This is a great dish to make
if you're going to
have friends over
who don't like the taste
of raw fish.
[ As Lion ] Or if somebody has
already eaten all of your tuna.
Oh, Lion, that [chuckles] --
That was a lot of tuna.
And then you just threw it up
into my shoes.
But I found a surprise
replacement ingredient,
so let's get started.
First, use the spoon
to cut slices into
the flesh of the avocado.
Then run the spoon along
the inside of the skin
and transfer the slices
to a plate.
Next
let's make the spicy mayo.
In a bowl,
combine mayonnaise
and your favorite hot sauce
to taste.
I like it very spicy.
Let's prepare
the sushi roll.
On a bamboo rolling mat,
place a sheet of seaweed paper
rough side up.
Using a rice paddle or spatula,
spread the sushi rice
onto the seaweed paper.
Click here for the
"how to make sushi rice" video.
Line up your avocado slices
on top of the sushi rice.
Now for the secret ingredient --
cheese puffs.
Make sure to use
the smoother variety of puff
for the proper texture.
Line up your puffs
along the avocado slices.
Then use the bamboo mat
to roll up your sushi roll.
Now carefully slice your roll
into six equally sized pieces.
To finish,
place a dollop of the spicy mayo
on top of each piece of sushi,
and garnish the plate
with another dollop
'cause it's fancy.
Time to try one for myself!
Ugh!
Lion, no!
At least savor the flavors!
The ingredients in this
snack sushi are delicious.
Be sure to serve fresh
for maximum crunch.