♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ INSTRUMENTS TUNING ]
♪ THE SUN IS BRIGHT,
OUR SHIRTS ARE CLEAN ♪
♪ WE'RE SITTING UP
ABOVE THE SEA ♪
♪ COME ON AND SHARE
THIS JAM WITH ME ♪
♪ PEACH OR PLUM
OR STRAWBERRY ♪
♪ ANY KIND IS FINE,
YOU SEE ♪
♪ COME ON AND SHARE
THIS JAM WITH ME ♪
♪ I'LL DO MY BEST ♪
♪ TO GIVE THIS JAM
THE SWEETNESS IT DESERVES ♪
♪ AND I'LL KEEP IT FRESH ♪
♪ I'M JAMMIN' ON
THESE TASTY PRESERVES ♪
♪ INGREDIENTS IN HARMONY ♪
♪ WE MIX TOGETHER PERFECTLY ♪
♪ COME ON AND SHARE
THIS JAM WITH ME ♪
WHOO-HOO!
JAM BUDS!
NICE JAM SESSION.
DON'T FORGET
THE BEST PART.
[ SEAGULLS CALLING ]
UH...
[ SEAGULLS SCREECH ]
[ SHOUTS ]
HYAH!
HYAH! HYAH!
RUN BACK TO YOUR MASTERS!
TELL THEM WE'RE NOT AFRAID
OF YOUR KIND!
[ LAUGHS ]
THANKS FOR SAVING MY JAM SNACK.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT'S NOT SAFE
FROM ME. [ MUNCH! ]
[ Muffled ] YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD SWORD FIGHTER, CONNIE.
REALLY? I WAS JUST
SWINGING THIS THING AROUND.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
BUT I'D LOVE TO LEARN
HOW TO USE A REAL SWORD.
OH! STEVEN HAS AN IDEA!
YOU WANT ME TO DO WHAT?
YOU SHOULD TRAIN CONNIE
TO SWORD FIGHT.
SHE'S ALREADY SO GOOD.
STEVEN!
BUT YOU ARE. Y-YOU HELPED ME
FIGHT THE ROBOT FLOATY THING,
SHE TOOK DOWN THAT EVIL CLONE
OF HERSELF,
UH...THOSE MEAN SEAGULLS
JUST NOW.
YOU'RE AWFULLY YOUNG
TO BEGIN SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
BUT I SUPPOSE I WAS ONLY
A FEW THOUSAND YEARS OLD
WHEN I BEGIN FIGHTING
ALONGSIDE ROSE QUARTZ.
YES, CONNIE?
PLEASE, I WANT TO LEARN.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE.
BUT IF SOMETHING DANGEROUS
COMES ALONG,
I DON'T WANT TO BE A BURDEN.
I WANT TO HELP!
I WANT TO BE THERE FOR STEVEN,
TO FIGHT BY HIS SIDE!
THE EARTH IS MY HOME, TOO.
CAN'T I HELP PROTECT IT?
O-OKAY.
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL,
WE SHOULD GET STARTED.
WOO-HOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
WAIT, NOW?
[ ENERGY BUZZES ]
[ GRUNTS, LAUGHS ]
YOU OKAY?
IT CAN TAKE
SOME GETTING USED TO.
WHOO! [ LAUGHS ]
HEY, YOU TWO.
THIS WAY.
RACE YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHOA.
THIS IS AN ANCIENT SKY ARENA,
CONNIE,
WHERE SOME OF THE FIRST BATTLES
FOR EARTH TOOK PLACE.
IT WAS HERE
THAT I BECAME FAMILIAR WITH
THE HUMAN CONCEPT
OF BEING A KNIGHT,
COMPLETELY DEDICATED TO A PERSON
AND A CAUSE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU MUST BECOME,
CONNIE --
BRAVE, SELFLESS, LOYAL --
A KNIGHT.
WE BEGIN WITH A BOW.
FIRST TO ME, YOUR TEACHER.
AND NOW AGAIN
TO YOUR LIEGE.
OKAY. MY LIEGE.
MISS KNIGHT.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
I HOPE YOU TWO
ARE TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY.
YES, MA'AM.
MM-HMM. MM-HMM.
COOL.
HOLOGRAM PEARL.
TO BEGIN, THIS HOLO-PEARL
WILL BE YOUR OPPONENT.
LEVEL 0, BEGINNER SET.
DO YOU WISH TO ENGAGE
IN COMBAT?
YES!
STEVEN?
HMM?
OH!
UM, I'M SORRY.
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
REFLEX.
UH, YOU JUST BE CAREFUL,
AND I WILL GO OVER HERE.
ALL RIGHT. EVERYTHING BEGINS
WITH YOUR STANCE.
REMEMBER...
♪ YOU DO IT FOR HIM ♪
♪ AND YOU WOULD DO IT
AGAIN ♪
♪ YOU DO IT FOR HER ♪
♪ THAT IS TO SAY
YOU'LL DO IT FOR HIM ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR STANCE WIDE ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR BODY LOWERED ♪
♪ AS YOU'RE MOVING FORWARD ♪
♪ BALANCE IS THE KEY ♪
♪ RIGHT FOOT, LEFT FOOT ♪
♪ NOW GO EVEN FASTER ♪
♪ AND AS YOU'RE
MOVING BACKWARDS ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR EYES ON ME ♪
♪ KEEP MY STANCE WIDE ♪
GOOD.
♪ KEEP MY BODY LOWERED ♪
RIGHT.
♪ AS I'M MOVING FORWARD ♪
CONCENTRATE.
DON'T YOU
WANT HIM TO LIVE?
♪ RIGHT FOOT, LEFT FOOT ♪
YES, BUT PUT YOUR WHOLE BODY
INTO IT.
♪ EVERYTHING YOU HAVE,
EVERYTHING YOU ARE ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE
ON THE BATTLEFIELD ♪
♪ WHEN EVERYTHING
IS CHAOS ♪
♪ AND YOU HAVE NOTHING
BUT THE WAY YOU FEEL ♪
♪ YOUR STRATEGY
AND A SWORD ♪
♪ YOU JUST THINK ABOUT
THE LIFE YOU'LL HAVE ♪
♪ TOGETHER AFTER THE WAR ♪
♪ AND THEN YOU DO IT
FOR HER ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW YOU KNOW
YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU DO IT FOR HER ♪
♪ THAT IS TO SAY
YOU'LL DO IT FOR HIM ♪
♪ DEEP DOWN YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YOU WEREN'T BUILT
FOR FIGHTING ♪
♪ BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE NOT PREPARED TO TRY ♪
♪ WHAT THEY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ IS YOUR REAL ADVANTAGE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LIVE FOR SOMEONE
YOU'RE PREPARED TO DIE ♪
♪ DEEP DOWN, I KNOW
THAT I'M JUST A HUMAN ♪
TRUE.
♪ BUT I KNOW THAT I CAN ♪
♪ BUT YOU KNOW THAT YOU CAN ♪
♪ DRAW MY SWORD AND FIGHT ♪
♪ DRAW YOUR SWORD AND FIGHT ♪
♪ WITH MY SHORT EXISTENCE ♪
GOOD.
♪ I CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE ♪
YES, EXCELLENT.
♪ I CAN BE THERE FOR HIM ♪
♪ I CAN BE HIS KNIGHT ♪
♪ I CAN DO IT FOR HIM ♪
♪ YOU DO IT FOR HER ♪
♪ OKAY, NOW,
DO THAT AGAIN ♪
YES, MA'AM.
♪ YOU DO IT FOR HER,
AND NOW YOU SAY ♪
♪ I'LL DO IT FOR HIM ♪
CONNIE!
HEY, STEVEN.
CONNIE, WAIT.
HMM?
AH, RIGHT ON TIME.
CAN WE TALK FOR A MOMENT?
SURE. WHAT'S UP?
WE HAVE IMPORTANT TRAINING
TO DO, CONNIE.
YES, MA'AM.
SHE'S BEEN MAKING GREAT STRIDES,
STEVEN.
SHE'S GOING TO BE
AN ASSET TO YOU.
HMPH.
[ ENERGY BUZZES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WOW, GARNET.
THAT WAS THE FUNNIEST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD.
GARNET,
MASTER OF COMEDY.
[ LAUGHS ]
YO, STEVEN.
WHY ARE YOU STANDING THERE
ALL SAD LIKE THAT?!
W-WELL, CONNIE IS TAKING
SWORD-FIGHTING LESSONS
FROM PEARL.
BUT I THINK IT'S GETTING
A LITTLE TOO SERIOUS.
SHE WANTS CONNIE TO DO
ALL THIS DANGEROUS STUFF FOR ME.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
BACK DURING THE WAR,
PEARL TOOK PRIDE
IN RISKING HER DESTRUCTION
FOR YOUR MOTHER.
SHE PUT ROSE QUARTZ
OVER EVERYTHING --
OVER LOGIC, OVER CONSEQUENCE,
OVER HER OWN LIFE.
HYAH!
YOU OKAY, DUDE?
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING!
THANKS FOR TELLING ME THAT!
BYE!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
REMEMBER, CONNIE.
IN THE HEAT OF BATTLE,
STEVEN IS WHAT MATTERS.
YOU DON'T MATTER.
I DON'T MATTER.
HUH?
NOW, LET US BEGIN!
CONNIE?
[ SWORDS CLANGING IN DISTANCE ]
CONNIE, WHERE ARE YOU?
[ SHOUTING IN DISTANCE ]
CONNIE!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
TO SEE CONNIE, WOULD YOU?
UNREGISTERED COMBATANT
DETECTED.
[ GASPS ] CONNIE!
STEVEN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
CONNIE, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO DO THIS ANYMORE -- NOT ALONE.
NO, STEVEN.
I UNDERSTAND NOW.
YOUR LEGACY, YOUR DESTINY --
YOU ARE EVERYTHING!
AND I -- I AM NOTHING.
BUT I CAN DO THIS FOR YOU.
I CAN GIVE YOU MY SERVICE.
NO!
I DON'T WANT YOU TO.
STEVEN,
I'M DOING THIS FOR YOU!
HYAH!
I NEED TO BE ABLE
TO PROTECT YOU.
BUT IF YOU'RE THE ONE
PROTECTING ME,
THEN WHO'S THE ONE
PROTECTING YOU?
SOMEDAY SOON, WE MAY BE FIGHTING
SOME REALLY BAD GUYS.
AND WHEN THAT DAY COMES, I WANT
TO FIGHT WITH YOU, TOGETHER.
SO, PLEASE, WON'T YOU
SHARE THIS JAM WITH ME?
THIS IS MUCH EASIER.
THAT'S THE IDEA.
NO MATTER WHAT COMES,
WE DO THIS TOGETHER!
Pearl: STEVEN!
STEVEN, DON'T INTERFERE.
SHE NEEDS TO TAKE ME ON HERSELF.
WHY? WE'RE A TEAM.
SHE'S THE STRAWBERRY...
...AND HE'S THE BISCUIT!
AND THAT MAKES US JAM...
BUDS!
WHA...?
[ BOTH SHOUTING ]
[ GASPS ]
HYAH!
[ SHOUTS ]
ENOUGH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ] NO!
IN A REAL BATTLE, STEVEN
WON'T BE THERE TO SAVE YOU!
YES, I WILL!
STEVEN,
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
YES, I DO!
IF CONNIE IS GOING TO FIGHT,
WE'RE GOING TO FIGHT TOGETHER!
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ANYWHERE NEAR
THE FIGHT!
YOU'RE TOO IMPORTANT!
I AM NOT!
YES, YOU ARE!
NO!
WHY WON'T YOU JUST LET ME
DO THIS FOR YOU, ROSE!?
[ GASPS ]
I...I MEAN...
LET HER DO THIS.
WHY WON'T YOU LET CONNIE
DO THIS FOR YOU?
[ SWORD CLATTERS ]
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
HEY, PEARL...
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO MESS UP YOUR TRAINING.
BUT ALL THAT "YOU'RE NOTHING"
TALK WAS REALLY FREAKING ME OUT.
DID ROSE MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU WERE NOTHING?
HEH...
ROSE MADE ME FEEL LIKE
I WAS EVERYTHING.
I SEE NOW HOW DEEPLY
YOU CARE ABOUT EACH OTHER.
[ SNIFFLES ]
THAT WILL MAKE YOU
BOTH GREAT KNIGHTS!
CONNIE IS PRACTICALLY
AN EXPERT.
SO, STEVEN, YOU HAVE A LOT
OF CATCHING UP TO DO.
OH, I'M SO EXCITED.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE MIDAIR AND
UNDERWATER DUELING EXERCISES.
IT'S GOING TO BE BOODLES OF FUN!
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪
Ronaldo: BEACH CITY --
A SLEEPY SEASIDE TOWN.
FROM FAR AWAY,
IT LOOKS ORDINARY,
BUT TAKE A CLOSER LOOK,
AND YOU'LL START TO NOTICE
THE CRACKS IN THE FACADE.
[ NEWS THEME PLAYS ]
MY NAME IS --
UH...
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
MY NAME IS RONALDO.
FOR YEARS, I'VE RUN A BLOG
CALLED "KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD."
MY MISSION --
KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD!
AND ALSO TO EXPOSE THE TRUTH.
MOST PEOPLE CHOOSE TO IGNORE
MY MIND-BLOWING REVELATIONS.
BUT NO ONE COULD DENY IT
WHEN THE TRUTH
WAS POINTING RIGHT IN THE TOWN'S
COLLECTIVE FACE.
[ RONALDO GASPS ]
IT'S AN INVASION!
LOOK AT THAT THING!
IT'S RIGHT THERE!
BEACH CITY
NEEDED TO BE SAVED.
BUT FROM WHAT?
DUHM! DUHM! DUHM!
EH, I WAS JUST CLEANING UP
SOME FISH FOR A VERY BIG ORDER
WHEN IT HAPPENED.
I FELT
THIS VERY PECULIAR RUMBLING,
LIKE, "BOOM, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM!"
AND THEN A SONIC BOOM!
AND THE FISH I WAS PREPARING
FLEW UP INTO THE AIR
AND FELL ON THE GROUND.
I RAN OUTSIDE AND SAW
THIS GREAT BIG THING
IN THE SKY.
THE TOWN
WAS UNDER ATTACK!
WHAT IS THIS FOR, AGAIN?
IT'S A WEB-SCLUSIVE
FOR MY BL--
OH. UH, YES.
THAT DAY WAS CRAZY.
THE MAYOR SAID --
Ronaldo:
WERE YOU SCARED?!
WHAT?! NO!
I WASN'T --
I WAS JUST CONCERNED
THAT SOMETHING BAD
WOULD HAPPEN TO THE SHOP.
SO YOU CRIED A LOT?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
[ CRYING ]
LET IT GO!
DAD, NO!
[ CRYING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
PLEASE, NO!
I WAS UNDER A LOT OF STRESS
AT THE TIME!
[ GROANS ]
AWW. HEY.
WHAT?
I'M HERE FOR YOU,
BRO.
MMMM.
[ Muffled ] I'M FINE!
LET ME GO!
YOU CAN'T MAKE UP DRAMA
THIS GOOD!
Ronaldo:
WITH THE SPACE HAND CLOSING IN
FOR A HIGH-FIVE
OF THE THIRD KIND,
WE FLED THE TOWN.
BUT THEN, JUST AS MYSTERIOUSLY
AS THE SPACE HAND APPEARED,
IT EXPLODED INTO AN EXPLOSION.
[ EXPLOSION ]
WHAT IN BLUE BLAZES
WAS THAT?!
I THINK
IT WAS AN EXPLOSION.
Ronaldo: UNBELIEVABLE.
I MISSED IT!
THERE'S NO ACTUAL FOOTAGE
OF THE GIANT HAND THING
CRASHING INTO THE BEACH,
BUT HERE'S A LITTLE RE-ENACTMENT
FOR YOU.
WHOOOOOOOOOA!
PFFF! WHAH!
OUCH. OUCH, OUCH, OUCH.
AAAH! [ INHALES SHARPLY ]
MY HAND! AAH--
BEACH CITY WAS SAVED.
BUT BY WHOM?
Ronaldo: MISS!
HUH?
WHO DO YOU THINK
SAVED BEACH CITY
FROM THE GIANT HAND CRAFT?
OH. HEY, RONALDO.
WAIT.
A-- ARE YOU FILMING?
PLEASE ANSWER
THE QUESTION.
OH. OKAY.
UM, YEAH, SURE.
WHO SAVED US?
UM, WELL,
WASN'T IT STEVEN'S...FAMILY?
I-I THINK THEY PRETTY MUCH
KEEP TO THEMSELVES.
STEVEN SAYS THEY PROTECT
THE PLANET AND THE HUMAN RACE
[ STORE BELL CHIMES ]
AND THAT
THEY HAVE MAGIC POWERS.
IT SOUNDS HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT I'VE SEEN
SOME PRETTY WILD STUFF.
ONCE,
THEY MADE US HAMBURGERS,
AND WE WERE HAVING
A PRETTY GOOD TIME.
BUT THEN WE WERE ATTACKED
BY A HUGE CREATURE.
HEY!
YOU MAKING A MOVIE?
OH, LET HIM BE.
Ronaldo:
IT'S A DOCU-WEB-UMENTARY
ABOUT THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
[ SCOFFS ]
THEY ARE C-RA-ZY.
ONE OF THEM TRIED
TO KNOCK ME IN THE FACE.
I AIN'T MAD, THOUGH.
Ronaldo: MAYOR DEWEY,
WHO DO YOU THINK
SAVED BEACH CITY
FROM THE HAND CRAFT?
WHY, YOUNG MAN,
I CREDIT THE VOTERS
WITH SAVING BEACH CITY.
MY CONSTITUENTS KNOW
THEY'VE ELECTED A MAYOR
WHOM THEY CAN TRUST TO --
HUH? NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
W-WHY?
WELL,
I'M COVERING THE STORY.
COVER-UP?!
WHAT COVER-UP?!
BUT, MAYOR --
SECURITY!
H-HEY!
YOU CAN'T SUPPRESS THE TRUTH!
OBVIOUSLY, THE CRYSTAL GEMS
WERE INVOLVED,
EVEN AT THE HIGHEST LEVELS
OF LOCAL GOVERNMENT.
I DECIDED TO GO TO THE SOURCE.
Right now, I'm standi--
Peedee: SPEAK UP!
[ Echoing ] RIGHT NOW,
I'M STANDING DIRECTLY BELOW
THE FORTRESS
OF THE CRYSTAL GEMS!
I AM NOW GOING TO ATTEMPT
TO MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE MYSTERIOUS,
RECLUSIVE, AND --
AAH!
HI, RONALDO.
UH, HI, PEEDEE.
IS THAT A CAMERA?
Peedee: YEAH.
WE'RE MAKING A MOVIE ABOUT --
IT'S AN INVESTIGATIVE REPORT,
SHOT CAMERA VéRITé.
COOL!
SO...WANT TO PARTICIPATE
IN A GROUNDBREAKING INTERVIEW?
HMM.
ONLY IF YOU...
PARTICIPATE IN A GLASS
OF FRESH-SQUEEZED LEMONADE!
OHHH.
THAT GIANT HAND?
IT WAS A SPACESHIP
COMING TO GET US.
US?! I KNEW IT!
STEVEN,
WE KNOW TOO MUCH!
NO, NOT US US.
I-I MEANT ME
AND THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
WAIT. SO THE HAND WASN'T HERE
TO SNATCH UP HUMANS
FOR A HUMAN ZOO?
OR INTERFERE WITH OUR SUBSIDIZED
BEACH CITY WIND FARM?
OR THAW THE CRYOGENICALLY FROZEN
PETS OF THE ONE PERCENT?!
UH...
NO, I'M PRETTY SURE
IT CAME TO BEACH CITY
FOR ME AND THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
OH.
SO IF YOU AND THE CRYSTAL GEMS
WEREN'T HERE,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ATTACKED
BY THE GIANT HAND?
[ Chuckling ]
OHH. DEFINITELY NOT.
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
Ronaldo:
AND THERE IT WAS.
THE CRYSTAL GEMS
WEREN'T SAVING US.
THEY WERE PUTTING US IN DANGER.
[ BUZZER ]
I FELT I HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO LAY BARE THIS UGLY TRUTH
TO THE UNWITTING CITIZENS
OF BEACH CITY.
Ronaldo: MA'AM!
[ GASPS ]
ARE YOU AWARE
THAT THE CRYSTAL GEMS
NOT ONLY SAVED THE TOWN
BUT ALSO CAUSED THE INVASION
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
OH. WELL, NO MORE FISH ARE
GETTING KNOCKED OUT OF MY HANDS,
SO I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
Ronaldo: SIR! SIR!
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT THE CRYSTAL GEMS
ATTRACTING AN ONSLAUGHT
OF DANGEROUS SPACE BEINGS?
DO YOU FEEL SAFE?
[ GASPS ]
HEY! YOU CAN'T
KEEP QUIET FOREVER!
HOW CAN YOU POSSIBLY GO ON,
KNOWING THAT WE ARE UNDER SIEGE
BY FORCES MEANT TO DESTROY
THE CRYSTAL GEMS?
HOW CLOSE ARE YOU
TO BEING DONE WITH THIS PROJECT?
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION,
DAD!
[ SIGHS ]
I-I GUESS IT'S PRETTY BAD.
BUT WHAT'S A REGULAR GUY LIKE ME
SUPPOSED TO DO ABOUT IT?
I'VE GOT WORK TO DO.
AND SO DO YOU!
PUT DOWN THAT CAMERA!
Ronaldo:
EVERYONE WAS TOO AFRAID
TO REALIZE
THEY WERE ACTUALLY AFRAID.
BEACH CITY NEEDED A HERO.
AND THAT HERO
WOULD HAVE TO BE ME.
WHOA, WHOA --
OKAY, EVERYTHING'S READY
FOR OUR FULL-ON
NIGHTTIME STEALTH COVERAGE.
Peedee: IS IT REALLY OKAY
FOR US TO BE
LURKING AROUND HERE
LIKE THIS?
WE'RE NOT LURKING!
WE'RE INVESTIGATING!
THIS IS A MOMENT
OF TRUE BRAVERY.
ARE YOU BRAVE LIKE ME?
I'M SO BRAVE
TO BE DOING THIS.
COME ON!
Amethyst: AAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
Steven: AAAAH!
STAY BACK,
LITTLE BRO!
RACE YOU BACK
TO THE DANGER ZONE.
WAIT UP!
STEVEN!
UH, HEY, RONALDO.
HEY, PEEDEE.
YOU GUYS
SHOULD BE CAREFUL --
[ PEEDEE PANTING ]
CUT THE PLEASANTRIES!
YOU'RE ALL A DANGER
TO OUR CITY!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
Garnet:
PEARL! NOW!
Peedee: HOHHH, MY GOSH!
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?!
[ GROANS ]
PEARL! NOW!
HA!
AIM FOR THE EYE!
AYE-AYE,
GARNET.
WHERE'S
AMETHYST?
RIGHT HERE!
[ ROARS ]
LET'S FINISH
THE JOB.
THIS IS EXACTLY THE KIND OF
THING I'M TALKING ABOUT, STEVEN!
BUT THE CRYSTAL GEMS
ARE HERE TO HELP PEOPLE.
BUT ALL THE MONSTERS
JUST COME HERE TO GET YOU GUYS
AND THEN WRECK THINGS
AND PUT US IN DANGER!
BEACH CITY WOULD BE WAY SAFER
IF YOU GUYS WEREN'T HERE!
LISTEN, FRYBO.
MAGIC BEINGS
ARE INDEED DRAWN TO US,
BUT WE WERE HERE LONG BEFORE
BEACH CITY EVEN EXISTED.
WHO CARES
HOW LONG YOU'VE BEEN HERE?!
INNOCENT PEOPLE
ARE IN DANGER
AS LONG AS
YOU'RE HANGING AROUND!
YOU'RE RIGHT. I GUESS
WE'LL JUST LEAVE, THEN.
EXCUSE ME?
REALLY?!
BUT, GARNET --
PUT YOUR BUTS AWAY,
STEVEN.
WE'RE NOT WANTED HERE,
SO LET'S JUST LEAVE.
BUT, GARNET, WE'LL HAVE TO MOVE
ALL THE BUBBLES.
A-AND WHAT ABOUT
STEVEN'S THINGS?
MAN! UGH.
I KIND OF LIKED IT HERE.
UH...
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED!
UH, YOU CAN
TURN THE CAMERA O--
AHHHHH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I DID IT.
THANKS TO ME,
THE GEMS ARE GONE FOREVER.
MM.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
NOW YOU WON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO BLOG ABOUT ANYMORE.
COME ON, DUDE.
I'M TRYING TO FINISH THE MOVIE.
WELL, THIS RELATES
TO YOUR MOVIE.
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF --
THE GEMS CAUSE ALL
THE WEIRD STUFF IN BEACH CITY,
SO NOW THAT THEY'RE GONE,
THERE'LL BE NO MORE WEIRD STUFF.
NO.
NO!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
Ronaldo:
WHAT HAD I DONE?
I DONE BAD.
I MADE A TERRIBLE MISTAKE.
[ PEEDEE PANTING ]
THIS -- THIS IS --
[ PANTING ]
THIS IS A MATTER
OF WEIRD AND DEATH!
Peedee: I'M GOING...
AS FAST AS I CAN!
[ PANTING ]
CRYSTAL GEMS!
YOU HAVE TO STAY!
EVERY MESSED-UP CONSEQUENCE
OF YOUR PRESENCE
GIVES ME REASON
TO WAKE UP IN THE MORNING!
WITHOUT YOU,
MY BLOG DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE!
I'M TOO LATE!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
I'VE MADE BEACH CITY...
NORMAL!
[ SOBBING ]
I'VE BROKEN MY PROMISE
TO THE CITY!
AND TO MYSELF!
[ SOBBING ]
[ MOANS ]
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE STILL HERE!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE!
I WAS WRONG!
STAY
AND KEEP THIS TOWN WEIRD!
Ronaldo: I HAD NO IDEA
HOW THIS CRYSTAL GEM
WOULD RESPOND TO MY PLEA.
THE ANSWER WILL SHOCK YOU.
OKAY.
HAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
THANK YOU! THANK YOU!
THANK YOU!
[ SOBBING ]
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
I HAD SKILLFULLY NEGOTIATED
FOR THE GEMS TO STAY.
PERHAPS I HAVE A FUTURE IN...
INTERGALACTIC DIPLOMACY?
[ LAUGHS ]
IN THE END,
I SUPPOSE THE GEMS
REALLY DO SAVE BEACH CITY --
FROM BEING NOT WEIRD!
OKAY, PEEDEE, I THINK
THAT ABOUT WRAPS IT UP.
GOOD JOB
WITH THE CAMERA, BRO.
Peedee: OH. THANKS.
[ DIGITAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
THAT WAS
VERY POORLY EDITED.
WERE WE REALLY GONNA LEAVE
BEACH CITY?
NO. I JUST WANTED HIM TO GET
THAT CAMERA OUT OF MY FACE.
I WONDER HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAVE SEEN THIS THING.
OH. [ LAUGHS ]
I THINK WE'RE THE ONLY ONES.
SEE?
HMM.
CLICK.
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪