♪ We
♪ Are the crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And pearl
And Steven!
♪♪
[ Seagulls squawking ]
[ Door chimes ]
Thanks for coming.
Hey, Sadie!
Hey, Steven.
What'll it be?
Sorry to be a pain,
but I got
kind of a long order.
I hope it's not
too much trouble.
What trouble?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm a professional
doughnut girl.
Okay...
I'll have one jelly doughnut
with powdered sugar on the side,
three chocolate frosted,
one frosted chocolate,
two chocolate-frosted
chocolate,
one dog-nut --
medium well --
one coffee with milk and sugar,
hold the coffee.
I also have
several methods of payment
I'd like you to split
this order across evenly.
Uh,
what's all this for?
Band practice.
You're in a band?!
Kinda.
I started jamming with Jenny,
Buck, and Sour Cream!
Whoa!
That's so cool!
Aw, man!
I bet you guys
sound amazing!
We're still trying
to figure out our sound,
but it's been fun just
playing music with other people.
It's also nice
to have an outlet
that doesn't involve space
and gem stuff
and everything else
going on.
Um...
You doing okay?
Well, I worry about Lars
being in space,
and I hope he's safe
and all but...
[ Sighs ]
Working all these shifts
by myself has been a huge drag.
I'm totally used to
doing his work,
but I'm used to at least
having him here to talk to.
Now I got to
do  th myself, too.
Oh, come on, Sadie,
you missed a spot!
Oh, no, sorry.
Well, we'll all be practicing
at Sour Cream's place tonight.
Feel free to stop by
if you have time.
I'll try!
Hopefully I can finish
restocking napkins early.
We're always running out,
for some reason.
Hmm, weird.
Well,
see ya, Sadie!
Bye, Steven.
[ Electronic beats playing ]
What do ya call
that style?
Beach core.
Buck: Hey.
What's up,
Buck?
Guess who's got a gig
at Delmarva's number-two
music and seafood festival
this weekend?!
Chuji
and the Woo Woos?
Jack
and the Frosted Tips?
7-Force?
No, us!
What?!
What?!          What?!
We don't even
have a name yet!
Or a set list!
Or even one single song
to  p on a set list!
[ Sighs ]
Guess we got
a lot of work to do.
What if we went for
a more of a rap-a-billy style?
No, thanks.
How about
something like...
♪ Here we are
♪ Our hearts combining
♪ Music and friends,
our souls aligning ♪
Buck:
Hold on, Steven.
You got a really cool sentiment
going on
that can resonate
with a wide audience.
I just feel like
this seafood festival
needs to hear something
challenging and provocative.
Check this out.
[ Guitar strumming ]
♪ Doo-doo
♪ Butt
♪ The government
♪ Corrupts
Jenny: Hold on there,
Bucky D.
I'm all for
being socially conscious
and waking people up
inside,
but people are gonna be at
this seafood fest to have fun!
Let's give them something
they can dance to!
Sour Cream,
give me a beat!
A what?
A beat!
[ Echoing ] ♪ Beat ♪
Oh, yeah!
Let's spice it up!
[ Funky riff plays ]
Cool!
Yeah!
And then how about some...
[ Screeching tones play ]
What the heck,
Sour Cream?!
What?
Can't let your audience
get too comfortable.
Maybe we should just call it
a night and try again tomorrow.
Agreed.
Sadie:
Oh, hey, guys!
Sorry I'm
so late.
Took longer to close up
than I thought it would.
Y'all still practicing?
Oh, sorry, Sadie,
we just wrapped up.
We were
getting nowhere.
Aw, shoot!
I really wanted
to hear you guys.
Well, let me know if
you have another band practice
when I'm not working.
See ya, guys.
Bye, Sadie!
Later.
Bye, Sadie.
See ya, girl.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Sprinkler whirring ]
Steven:
Hi, Sadie!
S'up?
Hey, how's it goin'?
Hey, girl.
Whoa!
Hey, guys!
I just got home from work.
[ Chuckles ]
We know.
We followed you.
Sorry if
that's weird.
We know how busy
your schedule is,
so we decided
to bring the jam to you.
Aw, shucks, guys!
But...
[ Groans nervously ]
My room
is such a mess right now.
Okay, ah, okay, just give me
a moment to tidy up!
Dang, Sadie!
You've got
so much space in here!
Yo, Sadie, do you have
any free outlets to plug into?
Oh, yeah,
check over by the TV.
Let's get
serious now.
The show
is this weekend!
Wait...
I can't really feel the music
in this cramped spot.
This looks comfy.
No, wait!
[ Crunch ]
Aw, doo-doo.
I think
I broke your bed.
[ Grunts ]
Sour Cream: Whoa!
Scary movies!
Hey, Sadie,
you've got a dark side.
It's more of
a dork side.
Jenny: Hey,
is that "The Lurch"?
You know this one?
Yeah!
It's a classic!
I can't believe
you have a copy!
Guys,
we have to watch this.
Brains!
[ Groaning ]
[ Screams ]
I can't believe
you like this one.
Not everyone appreciates
Bulgarian horror.
Uh, guys, don't we need
to find our sound?
I kind of like
this sound.
[ Eerie music playing ]
[ Dark electronic beat plays ]
Ooh. I like that.
[ Bass playing ]
And then,
we can do this.
[ Guitar strumming ]
Now we just need
some provocative lyrics.
♪ Tired
♪ From work
Nice.
[ Chuckles ]
♪ Hate
♪ My job
[ Guitar playing ]
♪ I really oughta be
in mourning ♪
♪ But I've got another shift
this morning ♪
♪ Everyday feels like
it's never-ending ♪
♪ What's the point
of all this time I'm spending ♪
♪ Here
♪ At this
♪ Dead-end job
♪ Oh
♪ We are the working dead
♪ And we lurch
for minimum wage ♪
♪ But I'd really rather be
♪ Eating your brain
♪ Look at you --
you seem so bright and healthy ♪
♪ And your minds are full of joy
and wonder ♪
♪ Stay a thousand miles
from the condition ♪
♪ That I've got
from all the stress I'm under ♪
♪ Don't come near me
or you might encourage ♪
♪ All these terrifying
sudden urges ♪
♪ Seeing you makes skipping work
so tempting ♪
♪ Don't you know
that in the night, I'm temping ♪
♪ Here
♪ At this
♪ Dead-end job
♪ Oh
♪ We are the working dead
♪ And we lurch
for minimum wage ♪
♪ But I'd really rather be
♪ Eating your brain
[ Woman screaming ]
Whoa!   Whoa!
Whoa!           Whoa!
Sadie,
that was awesome!
Yeah, girl, yeah!
That was so rad!
You're not Sadie Miller,
you're Sadie Killer.
This is it!
This is our sound!
Sadie, you should be
our frontman!
Really?!
[ Chuckling ] Wow, I...
Uh, wait, no,
I can't.
Ugh, I've got to
work tomorrow.
Actually, you guys
should probably pack up.
I got to get some rest
before my shift.
Aw, doo-doo.
[ Seagulls squawking ]
[ Door chimes ]
Hey.
What're you doing here?
I was just wondering
if I could get some advice.
We've been trying
to write
some more spooky songs
without you, but...
they sound so phony
coming from me.
Rawr,
I'm a bad, bad boy!
Yeesh.
I don't know.
I can't do it like you.
You got any tips?
Let's see.
First, lose your youth
to your boring job.
Then lose the only person
you've ever felt truly close to.
And then lose your mind
working all his shifts.
I don't think I can do all that
before the show tomorrow.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Are you sure
you can't come?
I'm the only employee
at the shop.
I can't just leave.
Singing is fun,
and being in the band
would be really fun --
like the most fun ever.
But -- But a lot of things
could be a lot of things.
This job is a drag,
but at last I know
it's a drag.
It's normal.
There's something nice
about that, you know?
Hanging out,
singing and stuff,
it feels
so not normal.
It's like --
you ever feel so bad
that you feel good?
Like when you get so cold
that it burns.
Sometimes I just want
to scream my guts out.
Well,
no not my guts,
but whatever thing
is squirming around in my guts.
Wow!
That -- That's poetry!
You're such a natural
at this.
All right,
I'll try my best.
How's this?
♪ Hate my job,
hate my job ♪
♪ Obligations
♪ No vacations
♪ Kinda sa-a-a-d
Do I really
sound like that?
No, no, y-you sing it like
it's really a problem for you.
Don't worry, I'll get it,
I promise.
♪ Squirming in my guts
♪ I got to sell doughnuts
♪ Big doughnut
[ Humming ]
[ Insects chirping ]
I can't believe your car
can hold all these amps.
Hey, guys.
Hey,
it's Steven Universe.
Is that the scariest jacket
you could find?
Mm-hmm.
Hope it doesn't scare anyone
too much.
So,
no Sadie Killer, huh?
'Fraid not.
She's just...
too busy with work.
Aw, man!
This gig won't be the same
without her.
All right, Steven,
you're gonna have to
up your scary game
to fill Sadie's shoes.
Got it!
Rawr!
You can't help
being cute,
no more than I can help
being cool.
Let's go.
[ Engine starts ]
Okay.
Jenny:
Buckle up, y'all.
Hope the seafood
at this thing is good.
So where is
this place exactly?
Buck: I gave you
the directions.
Oh, that tiny
piece of paper?
Where'd I put it?
Did it fall
under the seat?
I don't see it
back here.
Yo,
what if this...
was all a dream?
[ Groans ]
This is not --
Sadie: Hey!
Wait up!
[ Panting ]
Sadie!          Sadie!
I can do it!
I can do the show!
I can come!
All right!
Yeah!
Oh, thank goodness!
And I can come
to practice,
and I can come
to the next show
and the show
after that!
But, Sadie,
don't you have work?
Ha! I quit!
If you see him,
call me right away.
He's my only inter-dimensional
gateway to space,
and I love him.
Okay, I think I have
enough fliers left to --
Aah! Aah!
[ Tires screech ]
♪♪
What are you doing
Saturday night?
Hey! Listen! Little kid!
Beat it, Kevin.
I'm throwing a party
at my parents' palatial estate.
All the coolest teens
in Delmarva have RSVP'd
except one --
the only one cooler than I am.
Are you talking about me?
What? No! Ew!
I'm talking
about Stevonnie.
W-What?!
You can't just --
[Grumbles]
This is the last thing
I need right now.
Look, Stevonnie is better
than me, okay?
Better dancer,
better driver.
Stevonnie truly does not care
what anyone thinks.
That's why
they're the coolest.
If I can't be the coolest,
I at least got to be seen
hanging with the coolest.
Stevonnie only exists
when Connie and I are together,
and we're...
I'm not coming.
[ Sighs ] Great.
So I invited that other kid
for nothing.
Wh--
Connie's going?!
[ Panting ]
Of course she's going.
No one turns down an invitation
to a Kevin party.
But she can't stand you.
Why would she --
[ Gasps ] Wait.
Did you say
all of this to her, too?
Does she think I'm --
[ Grunts ] --
I'm gonna be there?
[ Engine revs ]
Is it too late to RSVP?
Yes.
But I'll make an exception...
for Stevonnie.
[ Tires squeal ]
[ Tires screech ]
Wait. What's your number?
I'll text you the address.
Oh. Yeah, uh, 301-555...
Here, you enter it.
Okay, uh, how do I...?
You roll the little ball
to navigate.
The screen is so tiny.
Here.
Huh, your name's Steven?
Weird.
I thought it was Clarence.
See you at the party Saturday,
Steven.
[ Tires squeal ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Mid-tempo music playing ]
Steven!
What took you so long?!
I-I got lost
coming up the driveway.
Derrick: Yo, Kev,
who invited the 7-year-old, bro?
Hey, shut your mouth,
Derrick!
I thought I told you
to go buy more ice!
Ugh. You just come
from picture day at
school or something?
I brought snacks?
Wha...? Aah!
This party is lame enough
as it is.
Look at these people.
♪♪
This is forgettable.
But not for long.
Every time Stevonnie shows up
on the scene,
everybody's
talking about it.
And when Stevonnie shows up
at my party,
everyone's gonna be
talking about this night
until they're
old grandparents,
and their last words
to their grandchildren will be,
"Kevin throws
the best parties."
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Um...
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
Lion?!
Wait, you're the one
who had him the whole time?!
What? Ugh!
No, I'm allergic to dogs.
Then what's he
doing here?
[ Gasps ]
Connie!
-Hey!
I haven't seen her
in so long.
She looks so different.
Ugh!
I thought she'd be here
to see me,
but maybe she's just here
to have a good time.
Maybe she's moved on.
She's moved on?
Wait,
did you guys break up?
Can 7-year-olds
even do that?
I'm 14.
You didn't tell me
you guys broke up.
You got a free ticket
to what would have been
the best teen party
in Delmarva.
But now it's just
some sad kid party
getting crashed
by a couple of sad kids!
All right, okay.
I'm -- I'm leaving.
[ Inhales ] No.
When did this happen?
A few weeks ago.
Hmm.
You been texting her?
Several dozen times.
[ Sighs ]
She text you back?
Um, no.
Hmm, but she knew
you'd be here.
Right! Right.
I'll -- I'll just go
talk to her.
[ Voice breaking ] I'll --
I'll just go tell her
how sorry I am.
I-I really messed up.
[ Sniffles ]
I-I was an idiot! And I --
Whoa! No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, kid, listen.
I wouldn't normally do this
because you're a pitiful kid
with snot coming out
of your nose...
[ Sobs, sniffles ]
...but I need
those old people
to whisper my name
when they die.
And if you don't
pull it together,
you're gonna regret it.
And it'll be Sabina
all over again!
Wh-- Who's [sniffles]
Who's Sabina?
♪♪
You can't just dump
your emotional honesty face
all over her.
You're gonna freak her out.
[ Sniffles ]
I-I just want us
to talk again.
Exactly.
But look what she's doing.
Life is good.
She's got a dog now.
[ Sighs ]
And a haircut.
Right.
But your life is good, too.
You don't need
to talk to her, either.
You've got new stuff going on --
new friends, new shirt.
She gave this to me
for my birthday.
Ugh.
Derrick!
Gimme your jacket.
Derrick: What? No.
Dude! Aah!
-Derrick! Give me the --
-Come on!
Here. Put this on.
Your friend looks
kind of mad, though.
He's not my friend.
Put it on. Collar up.
Hmm, not quite
cool enough.
I got it.
Nice.
It's almost like
you have style.
Why do I need the scarf?
It's not even cold out.
When you put on a scarf
like this, it's always cool.
Let's show her
what a great time you're having.
♪♪
Hey, kid,
you should say hi to Connie.
So I can tell her
about my feelings?
No. Be casual.
You're showing her
how you have it together.
You're not dying
to talk to her
because you're not dying
at all.
You're living.
Make her want
that life with you.
Kevin, that --
that's kind of moving.
So move already.
Walk over, be cool,
and walk away.
Got it.
Okay. Be cool.
Be cool, yeah. Be cool.
Hey!
-Hi.
[ Coughs ]
Nice weather
you're wearing.
-Uh, I got your texts.
-Oh, yeah.
I forgot about those
because I've been living.
Wha...?
Well,
back to my great life.
Uh, chowzers.
[ Whimpers ]
That was terrible!
This is all wrong,
Kevin!
No way.
Look, little man.
Your girl's making her way
back for more.
Steven!
What is going on?!
I came here
hoping we could talk,
but it seems like you only want
to talk to Kevin.
I guess Kevin
is your best friend now.
-What? No, no, no!
[ Sighs ] Anyway,
I'm glad you're doing well.
That's all
I really wanted to know.
No, no! But --
But you're my best friend!
Best friend?! What are you kids
even talking about?
I thought she was your ex.
Great.
Now what am I gonna do?
Think, Kevin.
How do people
treat their friends?
Connie!
Wait, wait, Connie.
Don't go.
Steven, I wasn't trying
to ignore you.
I was going to
text you back.
I-I wrote, "I can't talk to you
right now,"
but then I realized
if I sent it,
that would be
talking to you.
And it didn't make any sense.
I wasn't making any sense.
If we were
going to talk,
I thought
it's got to be in person.
So I rode Lion to your house,
but there was a note that said,
"Gone vacationing,"
and then I ran into Kevin
and he said you'd be here,
but, uh,
maybe this is still too soon.
I-I don't even know
what to say to you.
I'm angry.
I miss you.
I feel like
I'm out of my mind.
No, you're not.
I surrendered myself
to Homeworld.
I let them take me away,
maybe forever,
and then I came back and I tried
to act like it was no big deal.
But it was a big deal.
I couldn't stand
the thought
of you being taken away
on that spaceship,
but then I did that to you.
I promised you we'd always be
a team, and I let you down.
I'm sorry.
Jam buds?
Jam buds.
It's so good
to talk to you.
I've been wanting to see you
so bad
I accepted a party invitation
from Kevin.
[ Chuckles ]
I know.
I took his advice.
[ Chuckles ]
I think he got is heart broken.
I-It's actually really sad.
[ Chuckles ]
Of course he did.
Hey, nice shirt.
Nice hair.
[ Chuckles ] Thank you.
All right! Hey, everybody,
are you having fun?
Together: Yeah!
Liars!
You're all so fake.
You make me sick.
But get ready.
I'm gonna introduce you
to somebody so real
you'll all feel
as sick as me!
This party starts now!
Children! Go!
♪♪
It's pretty late.
We should head out.
Thanks for all your help,
Kevin.
What?
[ Microphone thuds ]
You got to do the thing.
What did I help you for
if you're not gonna elevate
my party?
Wha...? Hey!
Don't you walk away from...
[ Water splashes ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Derrick laughs ]
Shut up, Derrick!
If it helps, Kevin, I think
you threw a very nice party.
Mm-hmm.
Good night!
-[ Roars ]
-No! Wait!
[ Partygoers cheering ]
[ Groans ]
[ Pop! ]
♪♪