>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY
THINK PUNCHING A BLOOD POLYP WAS
A GOOD IDEA?
LOOK AT ALL THE GUNK YOU GOT ON
ME!
AND LOOK AT STEVEN.
>> Steven: IT'S NOT SO BAD ONCE
YOU GET USED TO IT.
>> Amethyst: SEE?
HE LIKES IT!
>> Pearl: HE CERTAINLY WON'T
LIKE IT WHEN IT HARDENS.
>> Steven: UH...WHAT?
I'M GONNA GO WASH.
>> Pearl: HE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
SO CLOSE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> Amethyst: HOW WAS I SUPPOSED
TO KNOW THEY'D POP?
>> Steven: UH, GUYS?
>> Pearl: YOU'RE ALWAYS PUTTING
US IN DANGER WITH YOUR LITTLE
OUTBURSTS!
OH, YOU ARE JUST...SO...
CHILDISH!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YEAH.
DON'T FORGET "RECKLESS,"
"VULGAR," "LOUDMOUTH," AND
THAT'S JUST WHAT MAKES ME SO
AWESOME, RIGHT, GARNET?!
>> Garnet: AMETHYST, YOU ARE A
CRYSTAL GEM.
YOU NEED TO ACT LIKE IT.
>> Amethyst: FINE.
>> Pearl: I THINK WE REALLY GOT
THROUGH TO HER.
>> Garnet: [ SIGHS ]
>> Pearl: RIGHT, GARNET?
>> Steven: GUYS?
[ SNORING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HUH?
WHA?
[ GRUNTING ]
AMETHYST?
>> FOR THOSE OF YOU BEFUDDLED BY
THE EVENTS OF ATHLETICISM,
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE
THE PURPLE PUMA [GROWLS] IS THE
SINGLE, MOST-HATED WRESTLER IN
BEACH CITY UNDERGROUND'S
HISTORY!
[ CROWD BOOS ]
>> Steven: WHAT?
[ BOOING CONTINUES ]
>> ALL RIGHT, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN.
LET'S INTRODUCE HIS OPPONENT --
OR SHOULD I SAY VICTIM?
[ LAUGHS ]
THE LOCHNESS BLOGSTER!
>> I'M [LAUGHS NERVOUSLY] GOING
TO END YOUR REIGN OF TERROR!
[ BELL DINGS ]
YAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BELL DINGS ]
>> Steven: UGH.
>> WELL, NOW, THAT -- THAT WAS
QUICK.
>> Amethyst: [ YAWNS ]
>> YEAH, YEAH, I DON'T LIKE IT,
EITHER, BUT HEY, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> Amethyst: [ SCREAMS ]
[ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> Steven: ARE YOU A SECRET
WRESTLER?
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
BUT HOW?
BUT WHEN?
BUT WHY?
>> Amethyst: COME HERE.
LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO YOU.
IN THE RING, NOBODY CAN TELL ME
WHAT TO DO!
AND IF THEY TRY, I HIT 'EM IN
THE FACE WITH A CHAIR!
>> Steven: AND PEOPLE...LIKE
THAT?
>> Amethyst: LIKE IT?
THEY LOVE IT!
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, THEY HATE IT, BUT IT'S ALL
PART OF THE FUN, YOU KNOW?
E-EVERYONE HERE...GETS THAT.
[ GROANS ]
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
HAVING PEARL AND GARNET ON YOUR
BACK ALL THE TIME!
>> Steven: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
[ As Pearl ] OH, STEVEN, I TOLD
YOU BEFORE NOT TO TAKE PEANUT
BUTTER ON MISSIONS!
[ As Garnet ] I'M NOT GOING TO
SAY ANYTHING, BUT I EXPECT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND THAT THAT WAS
WRONG.
> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
> Steven: LET ME BE A WRESTLER
WITH YOU!
I'M SO STIFLED!
>> Amethyst: WELL, I HAVEN'T WON
THE TAG-TEAM BELT YET, BUT YOU
CAN'T TELL PEARL AND GARNET.
>> Steven: DEAL!
>> Amethyst: [ SNORING ]
>> Steven: ARE YOU READY?!
PRESENTING...
TIGER MILLIONAIRE -- RICH,
FELINE INDUSTRIALIST FROM
JUNGLE ISLAND!
ONCE THE SINGLE CHILD OF THE
WEALTHY TIGER FAMILY, HE CLAWED
OUT HIS OWN DESTINY MAKING MONEY
IN THE COCONUT MINES.
>> Amethyst: WOW!
YOU JUST CAME UP WITH ALL THAT?
>> Steven: WELL, YEAH.
WHAT'S YOUR BACK STORY?
>> Amethyst: PUMAS ARE COOL.
>> Steven: UH...W-WE'LL WORKSHOP
THAT LATER.
>> TWO LOCAL HEROES IN THE RING
TONIGHT.
THEY BUILD HOSPITALS FOR THE
SICK, AND THEY BUILD MUSCLES
THAT LOOK SLICK.
GIVE IT UP FOR CONCRETE HEAT AND
CHUNK TRUCK!
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
FACING OFF AGAINST
THE PURPLE PUMA AND OUR NEWEST,
MEW-EST COMPETITOR...
TIGER MILLIONAIRE!
[ CROWD BOOS ]
>> THAT LITTLE GUY'S GONNA GET
CREAMED.
>> FROM HERE, HE KINDA LOOKS
LIKE STEVEN.
>> [ SCOFFS ] YEAH, RIGHT.
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, WAIT.
I'M JUST USING YOU TO GET THE
TAG-TEAM BELT.
I'LL DO ALL THE ACTUAL FIGHTING.
>> Steven: DO I STILL GET TO
WEAR THE COSTUME?
>> Amethyst: I DON'T CARE.
>> Steven: OKAY!
[ BELL DINGS ]
>> Amethyst: [ GROWLS ]
[ ROARS ]
>> OOH, A DEVASTATING MOVE BY
PUMA!
>> Steven: U-UH,
PURPLE -- PURPLE PUMA!
LOOK OUT!
[ SPECTATORS GASP ]
>> WHAT A GROSS MISUSE OF SAFETY
EQUIPMENT AND YOUR TAX DOLLARS.
>> Steven: THAT'S NOT FAIR.
>> IT MAY NOT SEEM FAIR, BUT
HEY, ANYTHING GOES IN WRESTLING.
>> Steven: IT DOES?
>> OH, YES, IT DOES!
>> Steven: LOOKS LIKE THIS
TIGER'S GOT TO TURN CHEETAH!
HEY, CHUNK TRUCK!
I'LL GIVE YOU A MILLION JUNGLE
BUCKS TO THROW THE MATCH!
>> WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS LIKE TIGER MILLIONAIRE
IS OFFERING A BRIBE!
>> WHY, WE COULD FILL 1,000
POTHOLES WITH --
[ GRUNTS ]
>> OH, SNAP!
DID YOU SEE THAT?!
>> [ GROANING ]
OH-H!
[ BELL DINGS ]
>> OH!
I MEAN, JUST, WOW.
>> Amethyst: WAY TO GO, TIGER!
[ CROWD BOOS ]
[ BELL DINGING ]
>> YE-EAH!
[ CROWD BOOS ]
>> RECORD-BREAKING HEAT TONIGHT,
FOLKS.
COULD IT BE?
TIGER MILLIONAIRE HAS BOUGHT OUT
OUR SODA STAND.
MAYBE HE'LL SHARE WITH HIS
THIRSTY FA-- OH!
[ CROWD GASPS ]
NOW THERE'S NO SODAS FOR
ANYBODY.
[ CROWD BOOS ]
WHA-- AND NOW HE'S PUTTING ON
GALOSHES?!
WOW, FOLKS.
THIS IS REALLY HARD TO WATCH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
CLASSIC.
TIGER! HEY, TIGER!
W-WOULD YOU SIGN THIS?
IT'D BE SO RAD!
>> Steven: YOU COULDN'T AFFORD
IT!
[ CROWD BOOS ]
>> WHO-O-O-A.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D LIVE TO SEE
THE DAY WHEN A CONTENDER TURNED
ON HIS OWN FANS.
>> Steven: I THOUGHT WE WERE
JUST HAVING FUN!
>> TIGER MILLIONAIRE, YOU ARE
THE CRUELEST CREATURE ON THE
PLANET!
>> Amethyst: HEY, TIGER!
ARE YOU READY TO WIN OUR FINAL
MATCH?!
>> Steven: AMETHYST, AM I...THE
CRUELEST CREATURE ON THE PLANET?
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
OH, STEVEN.
THOSE ARE JUST WORDS PEOPLE USE
TO DESCRIBE HOW THEY FEEL ABOUT
YOU.
LISTEN, STEVEN.
YOU CAN'T LET ANYONE MAKE YOU
FEEL LIKE GARBAGE.
>> Steven: IS THAT HOW YOU FEEL?
>> Amethyst: I ONLY FEEL HOW I
WANT TO FEEL.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, FANS OF
WRESTLING, WELCOME TO THE
TAG-TEAM CHAMPIONSHIP!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
IN THE RING TONIGHT -- THEY'VE
STOMPED THEIR WAY THROUGH THE
TOURNAMENT AND INTO OUR HEARTS.
GIVE IT UP, Y'ALL.
GIVE IT UP FOR
DASHING DAVE DOOBER AND
HANDSOME HANK HACKLESCHMIDT!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
ONLY ONE THING WOULD MAKE THESE
MEN LOOK BETTER, FOLKS -- IT'S
THE TAG-TEAM BELTS!
BUT...STANDING IN THEIR WAY, THE
RUTHLESS KINGS OF THE JUNGLE.
THEY'LL EAT YOUR KIDS AND FIRE
YOUR PARENTS!
OOOH!
YES, IT COULD ONLY BE...
THE PURPLE PUMA...
[ CROWD BOOS ]
...AND TIGER MILLIONAIRE!
>> DON'T YOU DARE HURT THOSE
MEN, YOU MONSTERS!
>> MAN, PEOPLE ARE REALLY
HATING ON TIGER M.
>> HE'S AWFUL BECAUSE HE HURT ME
SPECIFICALLY!
[ CROWD GASPS ]
>> Steven: PEARL? UH, GARNET?
>> Amethyst: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> Pearl: WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> Steven: I THOUGHT WE COULD
USE SOME PROMOTION.
>> LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE SOME NEW
OPPONENTS!
>> Pearl: NO, YOU DON'T!
THIS MATCH IS CANCELLED.
>> WHAT?
[ CROWD GRUMBLES ]
>> Steven: WHAT? WHY?
>> Pearl: WHY?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'VE BEEN
SNEAKING OFF TO THIS -- THIS --
CIRCUS OF VIOLENCE!
AND YOU!
USING YOUR GEM POWERS ON HUMANS?
>> Amethyst: IT'S NOT ENOUGH
THAT YOU'RE ON MY CASE ALL THE
TIME?
YOU HAVE TO RUIN THIS FOR ME,
TOO?
>> Pearl: WE'RE NOT HERE TO
FIGHT.
>> Together: FIGHT! FIGHT!
FIGHT! FIGHT! FIGHT! FIGHT!
>> Garnet: STEVEN, AMETHYST...
>> Amethyst: WHAT?!
>> Garnet: ...GO BACK TO THE
TEMPLE.
>> Amethyst: I DON'T WANNA!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Both: [ GASP ]
>> Garnet: DON'T DO THIS.
>> Steven: GUYS! STOP!
>> AAH!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ FEEDBACK ]
WAIT!
I WANT TO TELL YOU PURPLE PUMA'S
BACK STORY.
HE WAS THE WILDEST CAT IN THE
JUNGLE -- SO WILD, THE OTHER
CATS COULDN'T TAKE IT.
SO SHE -- I MEAN, HE -- WENT TO
LOOK FOR SOMEWHERE HE FIT IN --
SOMEWHERE WITH OTHER PEOPLE WHO
FELT MISUNDERSTOOD.
>> THAT REALLY SOUNDS LIKE
STEVEN.
>> SHH!
>> Steven: THAT'S WHY WE'RE ALL
HERE -- TO BE WILD AND FREE AND
BODY-SLAM EACH OTHER AND WEAR
COOL COSTUMES AND MAKE UP
NICKNAMES, AND -- AND -- UH,
SO...CAN'T WE JUST...HAVE THIS?
CAN'T WE JUST...WRESTLE?
>> Garnet: NO.
[ ALL GASP ]
BECAUSE...WE ARE...THE NOTORIOUS
O-ORDER OF...WRESTLING HATERS.
>> Pearl: THAT'S RIGHT.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
UM [CHUCKLES] WE WANT TO STOP
ALL WRESTLING EVERYWHERE!
YOU'RE GOING TO LET US DESTROY
ALL WRESTLING?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> YOU GOT TO SAVE WRESTLING!
COME ON!
TIGER! PUMA!
>> Together: TIGER! PUMA!
>> Steven: WE'LL STOP YOU!
>> WHAT A STUNNING TURNAROUND!
THE JUNGLE DUO ARE FIGHTING
BACK!
AND THEY'VE TAKEN DOWN
CAPTAIN SQUARE.
BUT WAIT. WAIT.
IT'S THE -- IT'S THE
GOOD-LOOKING GANG WITH A LADDER!
A-ARE THEY PLANNING TO STEAL THE
BELT?
NO!
OOH, THEY'RE ACTUALLY HELPING
TIGER UP!
HE'S CLIMBING AN ACTUAL...
>> Amethyst: SORRY FOR, UM...
SORRY.
>> Garnet: SAME HERE.
>> TIGER MILLIONAIRE HAS CLAIMED
THE TAG-TEAM BELTS!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
TIGER AND PUMA HAVE WON THE
CHAMPIONSHIP AND SAVED
WRESTLING!
>> LARS, I'M REALLY CONFUSED.
>> [ Voice breaking ] I LOVE
YOU, TIGER MILLIONAIRE.
>> Steven: W-WATER.
UH...SO THIRSTY...FOR WATER.
>> Pearl: IT'LL BE SAFER IF YOU
STAND UP AND WALK.
>> Steven: YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS IS HOW...YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
ACT...IN THE DESERT.
[ PANTING ]
[ GROANS ]
IS THIS THE THING?
THE PLACE?
>> Garnet: YES, STEVEN.
THE POWER IN THIS STRUCTURE HAS
TURNED AIMLESS.
>> Pearl: IT'S BUILDING COLUMNS
WITH NO ROOFS -- STAIRS THAT GO
NOWHERE.
THIS IS OUT OF CONTROL.
>> Amethyst: THEN I GUESS WE
BETTER...
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Amethyst: WHOOPS!
...ROLL ON OVER THERE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Pearl: THAT WAS A BIT
UNNECESSARY.
>> Amethyst: NAN NANI NI
NUN-NANI NANI!
>> Pearl: EXCUSE ME?
[ CREATURE ROARS ]
>> Steven: WHAT WAS THAT?
>> Amethyst: LET'S GO!
>> Garnet: IT'LL BE BEST IF YOU
STAY HERE, STEVEN.
>> Pearl: WE'LL BE QUICK.
>> Steven: WHAT IF SOMETHING
EATS ME?
>> Garnet: DO NOT WORRY, WET
ONE.
THERE'S NOTHING OUT HERE THAT
CAN HARM YOU.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> Steven: OKAY.
[ PANTING ]
UGH!
WHEW!
IT'S...SO...DESERT.
[ GROANS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
NOTHING CAN HARM ME.
I AM THE WET ONE.
AAH!
[ PANTING ]
GOOD THING THIS COLUMN WAS HERE.
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
NO, NO, NO!
[ GASPS ]
NO! NO!
HUH?
>> [ YAWNS ]
>> Steven: HUH.
AAH!
DON'T BITE.
AWW.
YOU JUST WANTED ATTENTION.
DIDN'T YOU?
YOUR MANE -- IT'S SO SOFT.
SO YOU FROM AROUND HERE?
I'M JUST HERE ON BUSINESS.
I REALLY LIKE YOUR PINK FUR.
YOU'RE LIKE THE COTTON CANDY OF
THE JUNGLE!
WAH! UHH!
[ GROANING ]
I ALWAYS WANTED AN ANIMAL
FRIEND, BUT I THOUGHT -- OOH! --
IT WOULD BE LIKE A GOLDFISH OR A
DINOSAUR!
BUT I GUESS FATE HAD OTHER PLANS
FOR STEVEN UNIVERSE -- UHH! --
AND HIS BEST FRIEND LION.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, BUBBLE IT
AWAY!
>> Amethyst: NO!
QUIT BEING JEALOUS, PEARL.
MY KILL, MY KEEP.
>> Pearl: I'M NOT JEALOUS.
JUST BE CAREFUL!
IF YOU DROP IT ON THE SAND,
IT'LL REBUILD EVERYTHING!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
GARNET, AMETHYST, AND PEARL ARE
COMING.
QUICK, PUT MY HEAD IN YOUR
MOUTH.
>> Pearl: STEVEN! WHAT IS THAT?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> Steven: UH...STOP!
IT'S OKAY!
LOOK, HE'S TOTALLY TAME!
>> Pearl: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> Steven: NO, IT ISN'T.
I TAUGHT HIM TO SAY "I LOVE
YOU."
I LOVE YOU.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S SO SWEET!
I-I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ]
GET YOUR HANDS OUT OF THAT
THING'S MOUTH.
WE HAVE TO GET THE DESERT GLASS
OUT OF THE DESERT!
>> Amethyst: I GOT IT.
>> Garnet: LET'S GO, STEVEN.
>> Steven: OKAY. GIVE ME A SEC.
HEY, LION, I GOT TO GO.
I HAD A LOT OF FUN.
I FEEL LIKE YOU REALLY GET ME.
SHHHH.
THIS IS ALREADY TOO HARD FOR THE
BOTH OF US.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, THAT PILLOW
NEEDS TO BE CONTAINED!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, YEAH.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
[ SNORING ]
[ SCRATCHING ]
>> Steven: WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
>> Amethyst: ALL I HEAR IS YOUR
MOUTH.
>> Steven: I THOUGHT GEMS DON'T
NEED SLEEP.
>> Amethyst: WE DON'T.
[ SIGHS ]
FEELS GOOD, THOUGH.
>> Steven: [ MUMBLING ]
PROBABLY SOME KID TRYING TO SELL
ME LAVA INSURANCE.
HOLD YOUR BRITCHES!
[ GASPS ] LION!
OH! OH, MY GOSH!
THIS IS SUCH A SURPRISE!
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY TO SEE
LITTLE OLD ME?
WHOA!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE FRESH.
YOU CAN'T GO IN THERE.
AMETHYST IS PRETEND SLEEPING.
BUT WHATEVS.
WE'RE TOGETHER AGAIN.
NOW WE CAN DO EVERYTHING BEST
FRIENDS DO!
OKAY, HERE I COME!
I'M GONNA JUMP!
GET INTO POSITION!
READY?!
AND...CATCH ME!
I'M JUMPING!
CATCH ME!
I'M FALLING!
DO IT! CATCH ME!
I'LL DIE!
EEE!
OKAY, OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE NOT INTO
THIS -- WAH! UHH! OOH! -- GAME.
OKAY!
GONNA THROW THIS BALL!
HERE IT COMES!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAAAAT?!
THAT THROW WAS SO GOOD!
LION, ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS CATCH
IT IN YOUR MOUTH.
SEE?
AWW.
PFFT! UGH.
YOU DON'T LIKE THAT ONE, EITHER?
OKAY, WAIT!
I'VE GOT SOMETHING YOU'VE GOT TO
LIKE!
FISH STEW PIZZA!
CATS LOVE FISH.
EVERYBODY LOVES PIZZA.
SO YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS!
WHOA!
THIS PLACE IS JUMPIN'!
WAIT HERE.
WE'RE GONNA BLOW SOME MINDS.
HEY, GUYS!
I'M DOING OKAY, YOU KNOW?
JUST GETTING SOME PIZZA.
KOFI.
KIKI.
>> WHAT ARE YOU HAVING, STEVEN?
>> Steven: LARGE PIZZA, PLEASE.
EXTRA FISHY.
>> YOU MUST BE HUNGRY!
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
I'M ORDERING FOR TWO.
>> [ SPITS ]
STEVEN'S PREGNANT?!
>> Steven: I DON'T THINK SO.
BUT I HAVE A GIANT PET LION
RIGHT OUTSIDE!
>> YOU'RE NOT LYIN', ARE YOU?
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S FUNNY!
BUT I'M NOT.
>> I BELIEVE IT!
LOT'S OF WEIRD STUFF HAPPENS IN
BEACH CITY.
YOU'D KNOW IF YOU READ MY BLOG
"KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD"!
I ALSO HAVE BUTTONS!
>> Steven: JUST GO OUTSIDE, AND
SEE FOR YOURSELVES!
>> THIS IS AMAZING!
>> Steven: MM-HMM!
>> IT'S INVISIBLE!
>> Steven: HUH? WHAT?
HE'S NOT INVISIBLE.
HE'S PINK.
>> PINK?
HOW CAN HE BE INVISIBLE AND
PINK?
>> THERE'S NOTHING OUT HERE,
RONALDO.
STEVEN WAS LYIN'.
SORRY FOR USING THE SAME PUN
TWICE.
>> BET YOU'RE NOT EVEN PREGNANT.
>> Steven: NO, I'M TELLING THE
TRUTH!
HE'S REAL!
ONION, YOU BELIEVE ME, RIGHT?
>> [ SCOFFS ]
>> Steven: HUH?
[ GASPS ]
HEY! HEY! LION!
YOU LEFT ME AT THE PIZZA PLACE!
I LOOKED LIKE A FOOL!
I HAD TO EAT A WHOLE PIZZA BY
MYSELF!
LION!
LION, NO!
>> Amethyst: [ SNORING ]
>> Steven: LION?
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Amethyst: UHH!
AHH.
KEEP IT DOWN, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
THE PILLOW?
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANTED?
THIS PILLOW?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO PLAY WITH
YOU AND FEED YOU 'CAUSE I
THOUGHT WE WERE BEST FRIENDS.
DID ALL OF THAT MEAN NOTHING TO
YOU?
AAH!
FINE!
I DON'T CARE!
IF YOU WANT IT, YOU CAN HAVE IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
THE DESERT GLASS!
IT'S REBUILDING ITS CASTLE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU BUBBLE IT
EARLIER?
>> Amethyst: WELCOME TO
SHRUG CITY, P.
>> Pearl: DON'T MOVE!
WE'RE COMING!
>> Steven: OKAY!
UHH!
HUH?
THERE IT IS -- THE PILLOW!
I HAVE TO GET IT OFF THE SAND.
HUH?
AAAAH!
UNH!
>> Garnet: HYAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
THIS WALL'S NOT MOVING!
>> Pearl: WE GOT TO GET THROUGH
BEFORE THINGS GET ANY --
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
WAH!
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
[ GASPS ]
UHH.
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
[ GASPS ]
NO!
AAAAAAAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
LION!
WAAA-AAA-AAH!
YOU DIDN'T COME HERE TO STEAL
THE PILLOW.
YOU CAME HERE TO PROTECT US FROM
IT!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
IT'S THERE!
IT'S PUTTING UP DEFENSES!
HOW ARE WE GONNA GET UP THERE?!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: YUP. SOUNDS GOOD.
LET'S GO.
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: NOW, LION!
>> Steven: WHOO!
ROAR!
AAH!
UHH! UHH!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
>> Pearl: WE SHOULD HAVE DONE
THIS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> Amethyst: IN MY DEFENSE, I
FORGOT.
>> Steven: SO I GUESS THIS IS
GOODBYE.
WE HAD SOME GOOD TIMES.
BUT I'M SURE YOU HAVE OTHER
MAGICAL STUFF TO SMASH WITH
OTHER MAGICAL BOYS.
I LOVE YOU, STEVEN.
I WANT TO STAY WITH YOU FOREVER.
[ GASPS ]
REALLY?!
GUYS, YOU HEAR THAT?!
>> Pearl: ARE WE REALLY GOING TO
LET HIM KEEP THAT?
>> Garnet: WE KEPT AMETHYST.
>> Pearl: OH!
[ Laughing ] "KEPT AMETHYST."
OH, GARNET!
THAT'S PRICELESS!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YAY! LION!
WINK!