Connie: I'm recording.
Thanks, Connie.
Okay, it's 5-6-3-8-3.
5...6...3...8...3.
Come on.
Play the song, "P."
I can'ts waits
no mores.
Amethyst, I'm trying.
Steven, are you sure
that's the right number?
I keep typing it in, but it
doesn't seem to be playing.
Oh,
you need to hit "start."
Ah, I see.
Yes!
Connie, the song's starting!
Connie: Actually,
you guys just go on ahead.
-Are you sure?
-It's fine.
Someone's got to
hold the camera, right?
Oh. All right.
♪ I can't help it
if I make a scene ♪
♪ Stepping out of
my hot-pink limousine ♪
Yeah, boy!
♪ I'm turning heads,
and I'm stopping traffic ♪
♪ When I pose they scream,
and when I joke they laugh ♪
♪ I've got a pair of eyes
that they're getting lost in ♪
♪ They're hypnotized
by my way of walkin' ♪
♪ I've got 'em dazzled
like a stage magician ♪
♪ When I point they look, and
when I talk they listen, well ♪
♪ Everybody needs a friend, and
I've got you and you and you ♪
♪ So many
I can't even name them ♪
♪ Can you blame me?
I'm too famous ♪
Connie?
Connie, come on.
The best part's coming up!
Connie: Oh, it's fine.
You guys are already
doing a great job.
Come on, it's your turn.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. Go on. Have fun.
Okay.
Thanks, Garnet.
♪ Haven't you noticed
that I'm a star? ♪
♪ I'm coming into view as the
world is turning ♪
♪ Haven't you noticed
I've made it this far? ♪
♪ Now everyone
can see me burning ♪
[ Laughter ]
-Whoo-hoo-hoo!
-All right.
-Awesome.
Connie, what a finale!
Thanks, Pearl.
You're a karaoke beast!
Aww. Thanks, you guys.
I really...
Uh, Pearl, how many times
did you enter the song number
before hitting "start"?
Probably
about 15 times.
-Encore!
-Yeah!