>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ INSECTS CHIRPING,
DOOR CREAKS ]
>> SADIE, BETTER HURRY UP!
I'M GONNA LOCK YOU IN!
>> HEY, JUST A SEC.
AAH!
>> Steven: DON'T BE TOO SCARED.
IT'S JUST ME.
I'M ON MY WAY OVER TO A
SPOOKY-MOVIE PARTY.
YOU WANT TO COME?
>> PARTY?
WHO'S THROWING IT?
>> Steven: RONALDO, THE FRENCH
FRYMAN.
>> UGH! THAT SOCIAL NAPALM?
DO WHAT YOU WANT, MAN.
I GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO THAN
WAX WEIRD WITH BEACH CITY'S
BIGGEST BOZO, RONALDO.
>> OKAY.
OH, HA! NICE TIMING, STEVEN.
HEY, SHOULD WE HEAD OVER TO
RONALDO'S?
>> Steven: YEAH!
I'M-A GET SO SCARED!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
NIGHT, LARS.
>> Steven: NIGHTY-NIGHT.
>> HEY! WAIT UP!
[ GASPING ]
SO, WHERE'S THIS THING AT?
>> Steven: IT'S RIGHT UP THERE.
>> STEVEN! WELCOME TO MY
BEACH CITY HORROR CLUB.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
MORE LIKE COMEDY CLUB.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> LARS?!
OH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UM...
UH, C-C-C-COME IN.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
I'm scared already.
>> RONALDO, RIGHT? YEAH.
I'M SADIE.
NICE TO FINALLY OFFICIALLY MEET
YOU.
>> BOO!
>> AAH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> STEVEN, YOU'RE FRIENDS WITH
LARS?
>> Steven: YEAH.
ISN'T EVERYBODY?
>> [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
OH, BOY!
>> Steven: YEAH!
>> OUR FIRST FILM TONIGHT IS A
RARE CLASSIC THAT HARDLY NEEDS
INTRODUCTION -- "EVIL BEAR 2:
BEARLY ALIVE."
>> WHAT? I'VE SEEN THAT.
IT'S BORING.
AND THAT STUPID FAKE C.G. BEAR!
HARDLY LOOKS LIKE IT'S REALLY
KILLING ANYBODY.
>> C.G.?! BLASPHEMER!
YOU SAW THE REMAKE!
I HAVE THE ORIGINAL.
A TRUE FAN WOULD ACCEPT NOTHING
LESS.
>> WHOA, MAN.
TAKE IT DOWN A NOTCH.
>> WHOA, WAIT.
HOW DID YOU GET A COPY OF THAT?
CAN I SEE THE BOX?
WHOA! IN THIS CUT, YOU ACTUALLY
SEE EVIL BEAR EAT THE HERMIT'S
LEG.
HO!
OH, IS THIS GONNA BE A BIT MUCH
FOR HIM?
>> Steven: I CAN HANDLE IT!
[ BEAR GROWLS, WOMAN SCREAMS ]
>> YO, STEVEN, ARE YOU SURE YOU
CAN SEE WITH THE COUCH IN YOUR
WAY?
>> YOU'RE...EATING MY...LEG!
>> OH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> OH, DID I MISS THE PART WHERE
YOU CAN SEE THE SOUND GUY?
>> HEY!
IT WAS JUST GETTING GOOD!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> PROBABLY JUST A FUSE.
>> OR MAYBE IT'S A GHO-O-ST?
>> [ CHUCKLES ] GOOD ONE.
>> NO, REALLY.
WHAT IF IT'S A GHO-O-O-O-ST?
AS A SKEPTIC OF MORTALITY, I'VE
LONG SUSPECTED THAT THIS PLACE
MIGHT BE HAUNTED.
AHA!
SPIRIT, I BESEECH YOU!
>> DUDE, CUT IT OUT.
YOU'RE BEING SUPER-WEIRD.
>> WE WISH TO MAKE CONTACT!
PLEASE, SPIRIT, SEND US A SIGN.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] WHOA!
>> WHOA!
>> OW!
>> SPIRIT, THAT WAS A GOOD SIGN.
BUT COULD YOU SEND A COUPLE MORE
LIKE THAT, JUST TO BE SURE?
[ INDISTINCT WHISPERING ]
WHOA!
AAH!
THAT'S -- THAT'S OKAY, SPIRIT.
YOU CAN REIN IT IN A LITTLE!
>> HOW IS THIS HAPPENING?!
>> Steven: THIS...IS AMAZING!
A REAL-LIFE HAUNTED HOUSE!
[ ALL SCREAM ]
>> LOOK OUT!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
>> IT WON'T OPEN!
[ ALL GASPING ]
I'M SO SORRY!
I HAD NO IDEA THERE WAS THIS
VIOLENT OF A PRESENCE HERE.
>> Steven: IT HAPPENS.
>> NO, IT DOESN'T!
IT'S NOT A GHOST!
>> WHO CARES WHAT IT IS?
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE!
>> YOU KNOW, I DEAL WITH THIS
KIND OF STUFF ON A REGULAR
BASIS, BUT, UH, YOU, UH, LOOKED
PRETTY COOL BACK THERE.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH! YOU REALLY TOOK CHARGE.
>> WHEN STUFF GETS HAIRY, I JUST
KEEP MY EYES FORWARD, YOU KNOW?
>> ONCE THE CIVILIANS ARE SAFE,
I'M GONNA COME BACK TO
INVESTIGATE.
IF YOU WANTED TO HELP...
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> IS SOMETHING WRONG, LARS?
>> OH, SHH!
[ CHILDREN LAUGHING ]
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> OH, IT'S NOTHING!
WE'RE ALL JUST HEARING THINGS
AND SEEING THINGS AND FEELING
THINGS THAT AREN'T REAL!
[ ALL GROWLING ]
>> [ GASPS, SCREAMS ]
[ BOTH STRAINING ]
AAH!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> AAH!
>> HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A HAUNTING
THIS BAD?!
>> THIS IS NO RUN-OF-THE-MILL
HAUNTING!
IT'S A POLTERGEIST!
A "GHOST" ONLY HAUNTS A HOUSE.
A POLTERGEIST HAUNTS A PERSON!
THEY'RE USUALLY ATTRACTED TO THE
TERRIFYING INNER WORLD OF THE
EMOTIONALLY DISTURBED!
>> YOU THINK STUFF IS COMING
AFTER ME?!
HOW CAN YOU LISTEN TO THIS WEIRD
GUY?
HE PRACTICALLY LIVES IN A
HAUNTED HOUSE.
DON'T YOU THINK MAYBE HE HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT?
>> Steven: I THINK YOU CAN STOP
BEING SUCH A DINK TO RONALDO.
>> [ GROANS ]
SADIE, YOU'RE NOT AN IDIOT!
>> Both: HEY!
>> DO YOU BELIEVE ALL OF THIS?!
>> I...
>> ALL THIS STUFF -- THEY'VE
GOT TO BE DOING IT SOMEHOW.
WE'VE GOT TO DITCH THESE GUYS.
COME ON.
>> I'M NOT DITCHING ANYONE.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT ME, HUH?!
SADIE, COME ON. YOU ALWAYS --
>> HUH? AAAAH!
>> SADIE?
>> THE SPIRIT TOOK HER!
YOU'RE GONNA DRAG US ALL DOWN
WITH YOU!
DON'T YOU EVEN CARE?!
>> [ Weakly ] LARS!
>> THE BASEMENT!
>> I DON'T SEE HER ANYWHERE!
>> SPIRIT, SHOW YOURSELF!
>> Steven: IT'S CLOSE.
I CAN FEEL IT.
IT'S HURTING AND...OBSESSED.
>> [ SHUDDERS ]
>> IT SHOULD'VE BEEN YOU!
>> WH-WHAT?
>> IT TOOK HER, BUT IT SHOULD
HAVE BEEN YOU, LARS!
>> Steven: WHOA!
H-HOLD ON, RONALDO.
>> [ Echoing ] Lars.
[ CREAKING ]
>> HEY! LET GO!
>> Steven: WAIT! STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> SPIRIT, I DELIVER THE PACKAGE
OF DARKNESS!
RETURN TO US THE INNOCENT SADIE!
>> Lars!
>> C-COME ON, MAN.
WE USED TO BE FRIENDS.
>> AND YOU THREW ME AWAY!
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> Steven: LARS!
>> NO, STEVEN!
HE'S NOT WORTH IT!
>> WHY DOES EVERYTHING BAD
HAPPEN TO ME?
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> [ GASPING ]
>> All: SADIE!
>> [ COUGHS, GASPS ]
>> Steven: IT'S A GEM.
[ ALL GROAN ]
>> THIS IS THE PERFECT CLUBHOUSE
FOR THE BEACH CITY
EXPLORER CLUB!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> SECRET CLUBHOUSE, RIGHT,
RONNY?
ZIP!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
>> [ GROANS ]
LARS, YOU'RE A RIOT!
[ SCRAPING ]
>> DUDE!
>> JUST CARVING OUR NAMES IN!
PRETTY METAL, HUH?
[ RUMBLING ]
>> WEIRD.
HOLY SMOKES!
THE CLUBHOUSE IS POSSESSED!
>> [ GROANS ]
>> LARS! LARS!
WHEN YOU TURN ON THE TV
TOMORROW, THIS IS WHAT'S GONNA
BE ON EVERY STATION!
>> B-B-BUT -- BUT YOU SAID THIS
WAS SECRET.
>> OUR FIRST PARANORMAL
DISCOVERY!
WE'RE GONNA TAKE ON THE WORLD
TOGETHER!
>> UM...LET ME JUST -- UH, I'LL
JUST, UH...
>> [ GASPS ] NO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
>> I'M JUST TEARING MYSELF OUT.
>> STOP!
[ STRAINS ]
LET ME...SEE!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT DID YOU DO?
OH!
>> OH, COME ON.
RONNY, KNOW I CAN'T LET PEOPLE
SEE ME LIKE THAT.
>> WHAT?!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?!
DON'T YOU KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
THIS WAS?!
AAH!
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH ABOUT
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK?!
>> YOU WOULDN'T SAY THAT IF YOU
KNEW WHAT OTHER PEOPLE SAY ABOUT
YOU!
>> LARS?
>> Steven: AAH!
OKAY, SHH. I'VE GOT YOU.
WHEN YOU WERE STUCK IN THE WALL,
WAS THE HOUSE LIKE YOUR BODY?
YOU MUST HAVE FELT LIKE YOU WERE
UNDER ATTACK, BACK WHEN
CARVED HIS LARS CARVED HIS NAME
IN YOU.
>> CAN I SEE THAT?
>> Steven: UH, SORRY.
WE SHOULD LET IT REST.
>> SO, ALL THAT LASHING OUT WAS
JUST FROM FEELING HURT AND
TRAPPED FOR SO LONG.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO RIP IT UP,
OKAY?
YOU CAN STOP TALKING ABOUT ME
NOW.
>> WAIT!
OH, SADIE, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> UH, YEAH. I'M FINE.
>> OH, YEAH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WE WERE BOTH WORRIED ABOUT -- I
MEAN, I RAN DOWN HERE FASTER.
>> CAN WE GET OUT OF HERE?
>> Steven: SADIE, YOU CAN COME
WITH ME.
I THINK THESE TWO HAVE A LOT TO
TALK ABOUT.
>> I BET.
>> I WASN'T TRYING TO MAKE YOU
LOOK BAD.
>> AH, WHATEVER.
IT DIDN'T MATTER.
I DON'T CARE!
>> HEY, LARS...
TAKE IT DOWN A NOTCH.
>> AAH!
>> Steven: MMM.
YOU'RE ROASTING GOOD!
AND...
[ BLOWS ]
>> GOOD JOB NOT SETTING THAT ONE
ON FIRE.
>> Steven: MM-HMM.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT MARSHMALLOWS
THAT MAKE THEM SO...
GOOD?
>> IT'S PROBABLY THE ANIMAL
BY-PRODUCT.
>> Steven: YOU MEAN LIKE...
POOP?
>> [ Chuckling ] NO.
STUFF LIKE HOOVES, BONE MARROW,
COLLAGEN...
AND LOTS OF SUGAR AND CORN
SYRUP.
>> Steven: CORN SUGAR!
>> SUGAR SYRUP!
MMM!
[ Muffled ] BONE MARROW!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
HELLO?
>> Have you been watching
World Weather News?
>> UM...NO.
STEVEN'S STILL GROUNDED FROM
WATCHING TV.
>> I see.
Well, there's a snowstorm on
its way to Beach City, and I
don't want you getting snowed
in.
You need to get a ride home this
instant.
Otherwise, your father is gonna
try to pick you up.
>> OH, NO. DON'T SEND DAD.
I'LL BE HOME SOON.
LOOKS LIKE I GOT TO GET GOING.
>> Steven: OH, NO!
>> THERE'S A SNOWSTORM COMING
THROUGH, AND MY PARENTS DON'T
WANT ME GETTING STUCK HERE.
>> Steven: MAN! THAT STINKS!
>> [ SIGHS ]
WOULDN'T IT BE FUN IF WE GOT
SNOWED IN TOGETHER?
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
WE COULD STAY UP ALL NIGHT AND
WATCH THE SNOW FALL!
>> Garnet: HELLO, YOU TWO.
>> Steven: HI, GARNET.
>> HI, GARNET.
>> Pearl: YOU ALL HAVING A NICE
TIME?
>> Steven: YEAH, BUT CONNIE HAS
TO GO SOON.
THERE'S A SNOWSTORM A-COMIN'.
>> MAYBE THE STORM WILL MISS US.
SOMETIMES THE FORECAST IS
COMPLETELY WRONG.
>> Garnet: NOPE.
IT'S DEFINITELY GOING TO SNOW.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S THE 411, YO.
>> Garnet: TRUST.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
GARNET HAS FUTURE VISION.
>> Garnet: YOU KIDS BETTER GET
YOURSELVES TO GREG'S.
>> Steven: WAIT -- WE CAN'T GO
YET.
I'VE GOT TO SHOW YOU THIS
TUBE-TUBE VIDEO REALLY QUICK.
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
>> Steven: IT'S ONLY, LIKE, ONE
MINUTE LONG.
>> Garnet: I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT
TO GO, BUT YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE
RIGHT CHOICE.
MWAH!
>> Steven: [ GIGGLES ]
THAT TICKLES!
WOW!
AAH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
GOTCHA, STEVEN!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> COME ON, KIDS.
WE GOT TO GET GOING IF WE'RE
GONNA BEAT THE STORM.
I'LL START THE VAN.
♪ CARABINER ♪
♪ CARABINER! ♪
>> Steven: AW! DO WE GOT TO GO?
>> YES.
THE MAHESWARANS THINK I'M A
RESPONSIBLE PARENT, AND I'VE GOT
TO MAINTAIN THAT IMAGE.
>> [ SIGHS ]
GUESS THIS IS IT.
>> Steven: WELL, DAD, IF YOU
WANT TO LOOK RESPONSIBLE, YOU
SHOULD PROBABLY CHANGE OUT OF
THAT SWEATSUIT.
>> BUT IT'S CHERRIES.
EVERYBODY LIKES CHERRIES.
I'M A CHERRY MAN!
OKAY, I SEE YOUR POINT.
JUST GIVE ME A SECOND TO CHANGE.
>> STEVEN, ARE YOU
PROCRASTINATING?
>> Steven: NAH.
I'M JUST KILLING TIME.
>> AHA!
YOU CAN PRACTICALLY SMELL THE
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> Steven: ISN'T THAT THE
TURTLENECK YOU WORE THE FIRST
TIME YOU MET THEM?
THEY'RE GONNA THINK YOU ONLY
HAVE ONE FANCY SHIRT.
>> I DO ONLY HAVE ONE FANCY
SHIRT.
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY, DAD.
WE'LL HELP YOU FIND THE
PERFECT, MOST RESPONSIBLE
OUTFIT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T WORN ANY OF THIS STUFF
IN YEARS.
OHH!
OKAY, HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
>> Steven: I CAN'T LIE.
THAT IS THE BEST OUTFIT I HAVE
EVER SEEN.
>> OKAY, GREAT! LET'S GO!
HOLY MOLY!
THAT SNOW IS REALLY COMING DOWN.
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
>> All: AAAAAH!
[ SCREECHING CONTINUES ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
>> W-WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
>> UHH...
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO WALK.
>> Both: WHAT?!
>> A RESPONSIBLE PARENT DOESN'T
LET TWO KIDS STRAND THEMSELVES
IN A VAN IN THE MIDDLE OF
NOWHERE.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
A RESPONSIBLE PARENT ESCORTS
THOSE KIDS THROUGH WIND, SLEET,
AND SNOW TO AVOID MAKING THE
OTHER PARENTS ANGRY!
[ KNOCKING, DOORBELL RINGING ]
>> H-HI, MOM. HI, DAD.
>> Steven: H-HELLO, DR. AND
MR. MAHESWARAN.
>> SORRY WE'RE LATE.
>> MOM, DAD...
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
...YOU REMEMBER MR. UNIVERSE AND
STE--
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
TIME IT IS?!
>> WHY ARE THE CHILDREN BLUE?!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DO--
>> AH...AH...CHOO!
>> SHE'S SICK!
YOU'RE GOING STRAIGHT TO BED,
YOUNG LADY!
THAT'S THE LAST TIME I LET YOU
OUT DURING FLU SEASON.
>> I THINK YOU KNOW WHERE THE
DOOR IS.
SINCE YOU'RE...STANDING IN IT.
>> UHH, I KIND OF CRASHED MY
RIDE.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
>> YES.
>> [ GROANS ]
I'LL GO SET UP THE PULL-OUT
COUCH.
>> UHH...OKAY.
SO MUCH FOR BEING RESPONSIBLE.
[ SIGHS ]
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE WORN THE
FLORAL PRINT.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ CRASH ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
IS EVERYONE OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> Steven: W-WAIT.
WHAT -- W-WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WE WIPED OUT.
>> Steven: NO, I MEAN, WHY ARE
WE IN THE VAN?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE GOT TO GET OUT THERE AND
START WALKING IF WE WANT TO GET
CONNIE HOME.
>> Steven: DAD! NO!
WE SHOULD STAY PUT.
IT'LL BE WAY SAFER THIS WAY.
>> MY PARENTS ARE ALL ABOUT
SAFETY.
>> HEH.
YOU CAN'T ARGUE WITH SAFETY.
>> Steven: IT'LL BE LIKE
CAMPING.
>> BUT IN COZY BUCKET SEATS.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
THANKS FOR DINNER, MR. UNIVERSE.
ITADAKIMASU.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: ANY REQUESTS?
>> HMM.
LET'S HEAR A SONG ABOUT...
A SNACK MONSTER THAT LOVES...
ANIMAL BY-PRODUCTS!
OM-NOM-NOM!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> HELLO?
>> Connie, are you still at
Steven Universe's house?
I'm on my way.
>> DAD, NO!
YOU KNOW HOW BAD YOU ARE AT
DRIVING IN THE SNOW!
IT'S WAY TOO ROUGH OUT HERE!
>> I'm almost at Beach City, so
start putting on your shoes.
>> Steven: I SEE SOME
HEADLIGHTS.
IS THAT HIM?
[ ENGINE REVS ]
>> Don't worry.
I got it this time.
Oh, wait.
Ohh!
Aaaaah!
>> DAD, STOP THE CAR!
YOU'RE RIGHT IN FRONT OF US!
[ HORN BLARING ]
>> I-I got it. I got it! I --
Ohh! Aah!
I-I don't got it!
I don't have anything!
[ CRASH ]
>> Steven: UGH!
AAAAAAAAH!
>> WHOA. SORRY, STEVEN.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Steven: CONNIE, WHAT'S GOING
ON?!
EVERYTHING KEEPS REPEATING!
>> HEY, COME ON, KIDS.
WE GOT TO GET GOING IF WE'RE
GONNA BEAT THE STORM.
I'LL START THE VAN.
♪ CARABINER ♪
♪ CARABINER! ♪
HEY! WHAT THE --
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
>> MY KEYS!
I'M NOT GONNA FIND THOSE TILL
SPRING!
>> Steven: COME ON, CONNIE!
>> WHAT?
>> HEY!
>> Steven: LET'S GO BACK TO MY
PLACE.
>> BUT MY PARENTS --
>> Steven: NO, CONNIE!
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME!
IF WE LEAVE BEACH CITY, BAD
THINGS ARE GONNA HAPPEN!
I'VE SEEN IT! BAD THINGS!
SEVERAL BAD THINGS!
>> UM...OKAY.
LET ME JUST CALL MY MOM AND TELL
HER.
MOM, THIS IS CONNIE.
I'M STAYING AT STEVEN'S
OVERNIGHT.
>> Oh, no, you're not, young
lady!
You're coming home right now!
>> Steven: DR. MAHESWARAN, YOU
CAN'T LET YOUR HUSBAND LEAVE THE
HOUSE!
HE CAN'T DRIVE IN THE SNOW!
>> What?
Yes, I can!
>> Steven: PLEASE TRUST ME!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> HEY!
[ BOTH PANTING ]
>> Garnet: HOLD IT STEADY.
WE HAVE TO SEND THIS TO THE
GALAXY WARP WITHOUT WARPING
OURSELVES.
>> Pearl: THIS IS TOO RISKY.
>> Amethyst: NO, IT'S NOT.
GET OVER IT.
>> Pearl: IF THE SHOOTING STAR
GOES OFF MID-WARP, IT COULD
EXPLODE FOREVER IN WARP SPACE.
AND EVEN IF WE DO MANAGE TO
DESTROY THE ENTIRE GALAXY WARP,
THEY COULD STILL FIND ANOTHER
WAY TO GET HERE.
>> Steven: UHH, WHATCHA DOIN'?
>> Pearl: STEVEN?!
>> Garnet: PEARL! NO!
MWAH.
>> Steven: UHHHH...
WHAT?
GARNET, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Garnet: I PASSED MY ABILITY
TO YOU FOR JUST A MOMENT.
>> Steven: YOU MEAN...
I HAD FUTURE VISIONS?
>> Garnet: TELL ME WHAT YOU SAW.
>> Steven: I SAW...SOME GOOD
THINGS, BUT MOSTLY BAD THINGS.
>> Garnet: AND NOW YOU CAN MAKE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
>> Steven: HMM.
CONNIE, WE HAVE TO GO RIGHT THIS
INSTANT.
>> WOULD YOU LOOK AT THIS?
AN ENTIRE INCH OF SNOW.
>> Steven: DAD, THERE'S NO TIME!
WE GOT TO GO NOW!
>> WHA-HUH?!
>> CONNIE!
OH, THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE SAFE.
>> NICE SWEATSHIRT, GREG.
>> OH, THANKS.
>> Steven: WELL, WE BETTER GET
GOING.
BYE, CONNIE.
SORRY WE CAN'T STAY AND WATCH
THE SNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S STARTING TO GET PRETTY
BAD OUT THERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU UNIVERSES
SHOULD BE DRIVING IN THIS
WEATHER.
>> WHY DON'T YOU BOTH STAY HERE
TONIGHT?
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Both: REALLY?!
>> WOW, MOM.
THAT'S...REALLY COOL.
>> IT'S...JUST SAFER THAT WAY.
WE MAHESWARANS ARE ALL ABOUT
SAFETY.
>> I'LL MAKE UP THE COUCH.
>> A COUCH?
OOH LA LA!
CHâTEAU MAHESWARAN!
[ SNORING ]
[ SNORING CONTINUES ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]