♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ STATIC ]
Marty: ♪ FROM THE MOMENT
THE MEAT HITS THE FLAME ♪
♪ MY STOMACH IS GROWLING
WITHOUT ANY SHAME ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IN MY GUT,
IT'S BEEN WORTH THE $5.95 ♪
♪ WOULD YOU LIKE A BURGER ♪
♪ FROM PEPE'S BURGERS? ♪
Steven: WHOA.
YOUR SONG IS ON TV!
YEAH. APPARENTLY, MARTY SOLD
MY SONG AS A BURGER JINGLE,
AND NOW
I'M FILTHY-STINKING RICH.
[ SIGHS ]
THE SWEET STENCH OF SUCCESS.
WHAT IS THIS?
YOU KNOW, WHEN ROSE CAME
TO MY CONCERT THE NIGHT WE MET,
I WAS PLAYING THIS SONG.
THIS IS WHAT DID IT --
BURGERS?
IT WASN'T ABOUT BURGERS
BACK THEN.
SHE PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
LIKED THIS, THOUGH, RIGHT?
AH, SHE WOULD HAVE LOVED IT.
[ GROANS ]
[ TV SHUTS OFF ]
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH ALL THE MONEY?
I DON'T KNOW.
♪ BRIGHT, SUNNY DAY ♪
♪ DON'T COST NOTHIN' ♪
♪ LIGHT, SUMMER BREEZE ♪
♪ WHAT DO I DO ♪
♪ WITH ALL THIS MONEY ♪
♪ WHEN THE ONLY THING I WANT
IS YOU? ♪
♪ PALLIN' AROUND ♪
♪ DON'T COST NOTHIN' ♪
♪ SINGIN' A SONG ♪
♪ HOW DO I SPEND ♪
♪ ALL THIS MONEY? ♪
♪ I'D RATHER JUST SPEND TIME
WITH YOU ♪
♪ YOU COULD BUY A HOUSE ♪
♪ AND A CAR ♪
♪ I GUESS THAT I CAN ♪
♪ BUT I'VE ALREADY
GOT A VAN ♪
♪ I COULD PUT YOU
THROUGH COLLEGE ♪
BUT I'M WITH THE GEMS
ALL THE TIME.
♪ I COULD BUY YOU
ALL THE FINEST COURSES ONLINE ♪
♪ WHAT IF WE TOOK A TRIP? ♪
HEY, YOU THINK?
YEAH, I DO.
♪ WE COULD TAKE A VACATION ♪
WE COULD GO
SOMEWHERE NEW.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ I KNOW A PLACE
THAT'S ALWAYS EXCITING ♪
♪ THE SHOWS AND THE SIGHTS AND
THE LIGHTS THAT ARE BLINDING ♪
♪ EMPIRE CITY ♪
♪ I'M TALKIN' EMPIRE CITY ♪
♪ THE STREETS AND THE SOUNDS
AND THE BUILDINGS TOWERIN' ♪
♪ SUBWAYS THAT RUNS FROM
BROOKLYN TO THE BOWERY ♪
♪ EMPIRE CITY ♪
♪ LET'S GO TO EMPIRE CITY ♪
♪ WE DON'T NEED MONEY ♪
♪ I KNOW A PLACE
THAT'S ALWAYS EXCITING ♪
♪ BUT COULD BE FUNNY ♪
♪ THE SHOWS AND THE SIGHTS
AND THE LIGHTS SO BLINDING ♪
♪ SO LET'S GO TODAY ♪
♪ THE STREETS AND THE SOUNDS
AND THE BUILDINGS TOWERING ♪
♪ JUST POINT ME THE WAY TO ♪
♪ SUBWAYS THAT RUN
FROM BROOKLYN TO THE BOWERY ♪
♪ EMPIRE CITY ♪
♪ AND LET'S BRING PEARL ♪
WHAT?!
I DON'T KNOW.
PAST EXPERIENCES HAVE TAUGHT ME
THAT THREE IS A CROWD.
STEVEN, ME AND PEARL
HAVEN'T GOTTEN ALONG THAT WELL
SINCE, UH -- WELL, SINCE
I STARTED DATING YOUR MOTHER.
AW, COME ON!
WE'RE ALL A BIG FAMILY.
IT'LL BE GREAT.
JUST YOU, ME, PEARL,
AND DON'T FORGET MOM.
-UGH.
-HUH?
[ ORCHESTRA PLAYS FANFARE ]
[ PIANO PLAYING ]
[ BELL DINGS ]
[ KA-CHING! ]
-HEY, SHAKE A LEG!
-IT'S MR. GREG!
AND HE'S HERE TO SPEND HIS DOUGH
ALL OVER THE TOWN!
-HE'S GOT THE BUCKS.
-I'VE GOT THE BUCKS!
-IT'S ALL DELUXE.
-IT'S ALL DELUXE!
WHEN YOU'RE DINING OUT WITH ME,
IT'S THE FINEST STEAK AND BRIE.
♪ AND IF I BREAK A TABLE,
IT AIN'T NO -- ♪
WHOA!
JUST BILL IT TO MY BANK.
A HUNDRED BUCKS?!
GEE, THANKS!
[ ELEVATOR BELL DINGS ]
[ DING! ]
♪♪
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
-I MUST ADMIT...
-YOU MUST ADMIT.
-...IT'S A PERFECT FIT.
-YOU LOOK GREAT IN IT.
AND THOSE FOUNTAINS
I FOUND WASTEFUL
ARE ACTUALLY QUITE TASTEFUL.
THIS CITY'S GOT ITS CHARM,
UNLIKE THAT TERMITE-RIDDEN BARN.
AND ANY TIME WITH STEVEN
MAKES FOR A DELIGHTFUL EVENIN'.
-YOU'RE HAVING FUN!
-MORE OR LESS.
SO DANCE WITH ME.
JUST SAY --
NO!
I --
I MEAN...
MAYBE LATER.
BOO!
YOU RUINED THE SONG!
SORRY, GUYS.
THANKS FOR SINGING WITH US.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, KIDDO.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN THIS WAY.
[ BOTH SNORING ]
[ SIGHS ]
♪♪
♪ I WAS FINE WITH THE MEN ♪
♪ WHO WOULD COME INTO HER LIFE
NOW AND AGAIN ♪
♪ I WAS FINE 'CAUSE I KNEW ♪
♪ THAT THEY DIDN'T REALLY
MATTER, UNTIL YOU ♪
♪ I WAS FINE WHEN YOU CAME ♪
♪ AND WE FOUGHT LIKE
IT WAS ALL SOME SILLY GAME ♪
♪ OVER HER, WHO SHE'D CHOOSE ♪
♪ AFTER ALL THOSE YEARS,
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D LOSE ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT OVER? ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT OVER? ♪
♪ YOU WON, AND SHE CHOSE YOU ♪
♪ AND SHE LOVED YOU,
AND SHE'S GONE ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ WHY CAN'T I MOVE ON? ♪
♪ WAR AND GLORY, REINVENTION ♪
♪ FUSION, FREEDOM,
HER ATTENTION ♪
♪ OUT IN DAYLIGHT,
MY POTENTIAL ♪
♪ BOLD, PRECISE, EXPERIMENTAL ♪
♪ WHO AM I NOW IN THIS WORLD
WITHOUT HER? ♪
♪ PETTY AND DULL
WITH THE NERVE TO DOUBT HER ♪
♪ WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
IT'S ALREADY DONE ♪
♪ NOW I'VE GOT TO BE THERE
FOR HER SON ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT OVER? ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ ISN'T IT OVER? ♪
♪ YOU WON, AND SHE CHOSE YOU ♪
♪ AND SHE LOVED YOU ♪
♪ AND SHE'S GONE ♪
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
♪ WHY CAN'T I MOVE ON? ♪
[ GASPS ]
GREG!
YOU WERE AWAKE.
NOTHING'S GONNA FIX THIS,
IS IT?
GREG!
I'M SORRY
YOU HAD TO BE AROUND ME.
DAD!
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
COME ALONG.
NO. THIS IS EXACTLY
WHY I BROUGHT YOU.
♪♪
[ GROANS ]
CHERRY MAN.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ RAGTIME MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GASPS ]
OOH!
♪ ROO-DOO-DOO-DOO,
ROO-DOO-DOO-DOO ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU TALK
TO EACH OTHER? ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU
TALK TO EACH OTHER? ♪
♪ JUST GIVE IT A TRY ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU TALK
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED? ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU'RE TRYING
TO AVOID IT ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T KNOW WHY ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT NOT BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT NOT
BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ BUT YOU'VE GOT
A LOT IN COMMON ♪
♪ YOU REALLY DO ♪
[ BOTH SIGH ]
♪ YOU BOTH LOVE ME,
AND I LOVE BOTH OF YOU ♪
Greg: LOOK, IF I WERE YOU,
I'D HATE ME, TOO.
Pearl:
I DON'T HATE YOU.
BUT I KNEW
HOW YOU FELT ABOUT ROSE,
AND I STAYED ANYWAY.
THAT WASN'T THE PROBLEM.
THEN WHAT WAS?
SHE FELL IN LOVE WITH YOU.
WELL, YOU KNOW ROSE.
-SHE ALWAYS DID WHAT SHE WANTED!
♪ I KNOW YOU BOTH NEED IT ♪
♪ I KNOW
YOU BOTH NEED IT ♪
♪ SOMEONE WHO KNOWS
WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH ♪
♪ AND YOU MIGHT NOT BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT NOT BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ BUT YOU'VE GOT
A LOT IN COMMON ♪
♪ YOU REALLY DO ♪
♪ YOU BOTH LOVE ME,
AND I LOVE BOTH OF YOU ♪
♪ YOU BOTH LOVE ME ♪
♪ AND I LOVE BOTH OF YOU ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Man: HURRAY!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
Ricky: LE BILL.
UGH!
♪ TAILOR-MADE SUITS ♪
♪ THOSE COST SOMETHIN' ♪
♪ ROOM WITH A VIEW ♪
♪ DANCING WITH YOU ♪
♪ DON'T COST NOTHIN' ♪
WHY'D WE EVEN COME?
WE COULD HAVE DONE THIS AT HOME.
[ LAUGHING ]
♪ SINGIN' A SONG
DON'T COST NOTHIN' ♪
OR WAS IT PALLING AROUND DON'T
COST NOTHIN'?
♪ GETTING IT WRONG ♪
♪ DON'T COST NOTHIN' ♪
I TRIED.
I'M SURPRISED
YOU REMEMBERED ANY OF IT.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
IT'S CATCHY.
♪ IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT? ♪
[ POP! ]
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO ♪
♪ I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪
Steven:
SPECIAL DELIVERY.
OH. WOW.
THANKS.
IT'S A...
A RECTANGLE.
AND A TABLET.
MY DAD BOUGHT IT, BUT HE DECIDED
HE DIDN'T NEED IT.
HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
OVERSATURATION OF MEDIA
BEING A PLAGUE
TO ONE'S MIND.
SO I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
LIKE IT.
HERE.
[ GASPS ]
YOU USE YOUR FINGERS
TO WORK IT.
LIKE
MY OLD FINGER SCREENS.
BUT NOW YOU HAVE THE WHOLE
WORLD WIDE WEB TO HANG OUT ON.
WORLD WIDE? HA.
I HAD THE ABILITY TO SEARCH
AND RETRIEVE DATA
FROM ACROSS MULTIPLE
STAR SYSTEMS.
HMM, IMPRESSIVE.
BUT I CAN DO YOU ONE BETTER --
TUBETUBE.
[ CAT YOWLING ]
WHY WAS THIS DOCUMENTED?
YOU CAN LOG YOUR THOUGHTS
ON THE INTERNET, TOO.
YOU JUST HAVE TO KEEP IT
UNDER 140 CHARACTERS.
THAT'S SO MANY PEOPLE.
[ CLATTERING ]
I'LL MAKE YOU AN ACCOUNT
SO YOU CAN START LOGGING
AS SOON AS YOU WANT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I REALLY,
REALLY LIKE THIS,
BUT IT'S A SHAME IT DOESN'T
COME ATTACHED TO YOUR BODY.
[ GASPS ]
OH, WAIT.
I'M GONNA LEAVE THE PROFILE
STUFF BLANK FOR YOU
TO FILL IN LATER.
THERE.
GIMME.
[ LAUGHS ]
BEHOLD MY INNOVATION.
CHA-CHA-CHA-CHA-CHA-CHA-CHA.
HAAAAA.
SHING. SHING.
HAAAAAAA.
SHING, SHING!
I'VE HARNESSED THE POWER OF
YOUR INTERLOCKING FABRIC STRIPS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
GOOD THING I GREW OUT
OF THOSE SHOES.
[ SIGHS ]
TO HAVE TECH AGAIN.
IT FEELS SO GOOD WHEN EVERYTHING
IS AT YOUR FINGERTIPS.
YO. YOU GUYS LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE HAVING FUN.
OH, AMETHYST.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU LOOK LIKE A SQUARE.
IT'S A RECTANGLE.
HEH, TRUTH.
ANYWAY,
YOU TWO READY TO GO OR WHAT?
GO?
YEAH.
AMETHYST AND I WERE GONNA GO
HANG OUT,
AND WE WANTED YOU TO COME,
TOO.
HANG OUT?
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S A FRIEND THING TO DO.
SO, WHERE ARE WE HANGING OUT,
FRIENDS?
TA-DA!
WELCOME TO FUNLAND!
YOU'VE BROUGHT ME
TO A SIGN!
NAH, NAH.
YOU GOT TO GO INSIDE.
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
A SPEED PATTERN
TRANSPORTATION CIRCUIT.
AND A ROLLER COASTER.
YOU GOT TO DO THE MOST FUN THING
IN FUNLAND FIRST.
HMM. BOLD.
LET'S FOLLOW THIS LOGIC!
[ BELL DINGING ]
THREE, PLEASE.
SURE.
WE GOT SOME NEW RULES, FIRST.
[ DING! ]
UH...
UGH.
[ DING! ]
HMM.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLS ]
HA-HA!
SORRY, GUYS.
LOOKS LIKE THIS SQUAD
HAS SOME GROWING TO DO
BEFORE YOU CAN RIDE.
I DO NOT HAVE TO GROW.
THIS HEIGHT IS INDICATIVE
OF MY RARITY AND IMPORTANCE.
I DEMAND ENTRY,
YOU CLOD!
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
YOU KIDS WANT ANOTHER
LIFETIME BAN?
NO, THANKS, MR. SMILEY.
SHORTY SQUAD OUT.
WELL, THAT STINKS.
[ SIGHS ] WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
MAINTAIN A HEALTHY LIFESTYLE
IN HOPES WE GROW BEFORE THE END
OF THE SEASON.
UGH. OF COURSE.
LET'S JUST GROW.
[ GASPS ]
SHAPE-SHIFTING!
HMM.
[ GRUNTING ]
UH, PERIDOT?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
UH, I --
I MUST BE A LITTLE RUSTY...
WHY DON'T YOU TWO JUST GO?
AW, WHAT?
WHAT.
YOU SURE?
SURE I'M SURE.
I CAN JUST LOOK UP WHAT
A ROLLER COASTER FEELS LIKE.
JUST HURRY UP AND GO SO YOU CAN
HURRY UP AND COME BACK.
OH, OKAY.
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
SO GOOD.
WHAT NEXT?
YES. WHAT NEXT THAT DOESN'T HAVE
A HEIGHT RESTRICTION?
UH, THERE!
OOH. [ GIGGLES ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
HA,
THIS PLACE IS FUN.
YEAH. IT TOTALLY DOES LIVE UP
TO ITS NAME.
[ SIGHS ]
LET'S SEE WHO CAN EAT
THE MOST CHILI DOGS
BEFORE WE GO ON
THE TILT-A-WHIRL.
♪♪
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN, AMETHYST!
LOOK AT THIS BEING.
ITS LARGE HEAD,
SWOLLEN WITH THOUGHTS!
THOSE COMPASSIONATE EYES.
IT UNDERSTANDS.
I NEED IT. NOW!
PERIDOT, THAT'S A PRIZE.
YOU HAVE TO WIN IT FIRST.
[ DINGS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY, THERE, STEVEN.
MR. SMILEY, YOU'RE WORKING
THE RING TOSS, TOO?
YEAH. YOU COULD SAY WE'RE
A LITTLE "FUN-DERSTAFFED."
[ CHUCKLES ]
I GET IT.
I'M GLAD YOU SEEING THE HUMOR
IN IT, STEVEN,
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T SEEN A BED
IN SIX DAYS!
OH.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
HYAH!
[ CLATTER ]
I WIN!
UM, WELL...
YOU HAVE TO LAND THE RINGS
FIRST, BROSKI.
SHORTY SQUAD THROW!
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
OKAY, LAST CHANCE.
WE GOT THIS.
[ ALL SIGH ]
THIS BIZ IS RIGGED!
I DIDN'T SAVE EARTH
FOR THIS.
SORRY, PERIDOT.
HMM. NO.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU THAT PRIZE.
HEY, MR. SMILEY.
IS THAT ONION TRYING TO LIGHT
THE ROLLER COASTER ON FIRE?
I'M NOT FALLING
FOR THAT ONE AGAIN.
[ SCREAMING IN DISTANCE ]
OH!
NO! I'M STILL PAYING OFF
THE LAST LAWSUIT!
HEH.
GOOD OLD ONION.
ALL THIS RUNNIN' AROUND.
I'M NOT EVEN IN A UNION.
Amethyst: YO, MR. S.
WHILE YOU WERE GONE,
PERI GOT A RING.
I DID?
We're lying.
OH, UH, YES,
I DID LAND THE RING.
I ALSO DO NOT STEAL STEVEN'S
CLOTHES WHEN HE'S NOT LOOKING.
Steven: WHAT?
HUH.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
AND I THOUGHT THIS THING
WAS RIGGED.
HERE YOU GO, KID.
IT'S A LITTLE SISTER.
[ LAUGHS ]
UM, EXCUSE ME,
BUT YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M SUPPOSED TO WIN
THAT ONE.
YOU MEAN THE BIG GUY?
SORRY.
THAT ONE'S 10 RINGS.
FIND CUTE ROOMMATES
IN YOUR AREA.
I'M ALL SET, THANKS.
THAT TOY YOU WON IS REALLY COOL,
PERIDOT.
YOU MEAN THAT AMETHYST WON
WITH SHAPE-SHIFTING.
MAYBE THEY SHOULD CALL IT
SHAPE-SHIFT LAND,
BECAUSE IT'S A LAND
WHERE YOU GO TO SHAPE-SHIFT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
SHAPE-SHIFTING, BRO?
YOU MEAN BESIDES BEING AN INSULT
TO YOUR INTENDED FORM?
OKAY, WHAT'S REALLY WRONG
WITH IT?
I CAN'T DO IT...
AT ALL.
WELL,
WE CAN HELP YOU TRY.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T EVER THINK I COULD USE
MY POWERS, EITHER,
BUT THEN THE GEMS
HELPED ME OUT.
WE CAN HELP YOU, TOO.
YEAH, MAN.
[ MUNCHES ] MMM!
WE'LL GIVE YOU THE
SHAPE-SHIFTING LOWDOWN.
[ GRUNTS ]
SHORTY SQUAD STYLE.
♪♪
AH? MM.
TA-DA!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CAT YOWLS ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
HUP!
WHOA.
[ GROANS ]
UH, OKAY.
MAYBE WE JUST HAVE
TO ACTIVATE IT MANUALLY.
YOU GRAB HER FEET.
I'LL GRAB THE ARMS.
OKAY.
READY? PULL.
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
OW.
IS IT WORKING?
I THINK SO.
OW.
PULL HARDER!
I THINK I JUST HEARD
A CRACK.
OW.
THAT'S HER POWERS OPENING,
STEVEN.
OW, OW, OW.
OW, OW, OW, OW, OW, OW.
DROP ME NOW.
[ GRUNTS ]
THIS ISN'T GOING TO WORK.
MAYBE IF WE KEEP TRYING...
NO.
MY LACK OF SKILL
IS AN OBJECTIVE FACT.
I'M AN ERA-2 PERIDOT.
I'M NEW.
RESOURCES ARE DWINDLING
ON HOMEWORLD.
THEY CAN'T MAKE GEMS
LIKE THEY USED TO.
THAT'S WHY THEY GIVE
ERA-2 PERIDOTS
TECHNOLOGICAL ENHANCEMENTS.
BECAUSE WE...
DON'T HAVE POWERS.
PER, I'MMA BE REALLY REAL
WITH YOU FOR A SEC.
THIS WHOLE TIME
WE'VE BEEN HERE,
YOU'VE JUST BEEN FOCUSING
ON WHAT YOU CAN'T DO.
OF COURSE YOU'RE NOT HAVING
ANY FUN.
YOU THINK THAT ALL YOU ARE
IS WHO YOU COULD BE,
BUT WE DON'T HANG OUT WITH YOU
BECAUSE OF WHO YOU COULD BE.
WE LIKE YOU.
I KNOW YOU JUST HEARD ME.
STOP PLAYING
WITH THAT THING.
UGH.
GIMME THAT!
NO!
YOU DON'T NEED IT!
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT!
YES...I...DO!
WAIT.
W-W-W-W-W-W-WAIT.
NO!
IT'S ALL THAT I AM!
PERIDOT.
METAL POWERS!
DUDE.
[ GIGGLES ]
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
YOU CAN OPEN
REALLY TIGHT JARS.
YOU CAN REMOVE STAPLES
WITHOUT A STAPLE REMOVER.
YOU CAN OPEN DOORS WITHOUT
HAVING TO TOUCH THEM
AFTER YOU WASH YOUR HANDS.
NO.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT I CAN DO.
[ SNORES ]
10!
THAT'S 10!
WAH!
THAT'S 10, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS YOU WON
FAIR AND SQUARE,
OR FAIR AND TRIANGLE.
[ MR. SMILEY LAUGHS ]
BECAUSE YOUR HEAD
LOOKS LIKE A TRIANGLE.
HERE YOU GO, KID.
YOU DID IT, PERIDOT.
GIVE IT UP
FOR PEA-POD!
NO, GIVE IT UP
FOR THE SHORTY SQUAD.
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO ♪
♪ I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪