>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: OUTSIDE, DUDE.
>> Steven: HAVE YOU SEEN
RANGER GUY?
>> Amethyst: EXCUSE ME?
>> Steven: RANGER GUY.
ONE OF MY GUYS.
YOU KNOW...GUYS?
G.U.Y.S.!
GUYS UNDER YOUR SUPERVISION.
THERE'S NINJA GUY,
CONSTRUCTION GUY, COP GUY,
EYE GUY, INVISIBLE GUY,
JAGGED GUY, CAT GUY, APPLE GUY,
AND MY MAIN MAN RANGER GUY, THE
BEST OF ALL THE GUYS.
HE'S GONE MISSING.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
>> Pearl: WHAT'S THAT I HEAR?
YOU CAN'T FIND YOUR LITTLE MEN
IN THAT SUPER JUNKY ROOM OF
YOURS?
>> Steven: IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
>> Pearl: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
>> Steven: HOW'D THAT GET IN
THERE?
>> Pearl: YOU LEFT YOUR WINDOW
WIDE OPEN FOR THINGS TO JUST FLY
IN AND OUT.
>> Amethyst: AWW, GIVE HIM A
BREAK, P.
MY ROOM'S MESSY, BUT I ALWAYS
FIND WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
>> Pearl: THEN WHY HAVEN'T YOU
FOUND MY MAGIC AX?
>> Amethyst: I HAVEN'T LOOKED
FOR IT YET.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, GO AND FIND
IT RIGHT THIS SECOND.
>> Amethyst: HEY, FEEL FREE TO
GO LOOK FOR IT YOURSELF.
>> Pearl: THERE'S NO WAY I'M
GOING INTO THAT DUMP.
>> Amethyst: PEARL, ALL YOUR
NAGGING'S MADE STEVEN DEPRESSED.
>> Pearl: IS EVERYTHING OKAY,
STEVEN?
>> Steven: YEAH. I'M FINE.
JUST HAVE TO BREAK THE BAD NEWS
TO MY DAD.
>> Steven: DAD!
DAD!
AAH! I'M SO SORRY!
>> YEAH, YOU'RE SORRY.
SORRY YOU WALKED THROUGH THAT
DOOR WITHOUT A HOSE IN YOUR
HAND, READY FOR BATTLE!
AAAAAAH!
>> Steven: WAIT!
>> MAN, YOU LOOK SAD AND WET.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR LIFE,
LITTLE GUY?
>> Steven: I...LOST SOMETHING.
SOMETHING PRECIOUS.
>> [ GASPS ]
YOUR INNOCENCE?
>> Steven: I LOST RANGER GUY.
ONE OF MY GUYS FROM OUR SPECIAL
DAY AT THE BEACH LAST SUMMER.
YOU BOUGHT HIM FOR ME AT THE END
OF THE DAY.
HE WAS ONE OF A KIND.
HE HAD A MISCOLORED HAT.
HOW COULD YOU NOT REMEMBER?
>> OH.
WAS THIS THE SAME DAY WE ATE
THAT AWESOME FUNNEL CAKE?
>> Steven: UH, HUH?
>> YEAH, MAN.
THAT FUNNEL CAKE...
[ CHUCKLES ]
I EVEN KEPT THE PLATE.
COME ON!
>> Steven: COOL BALLOONS.
>> UH, LET'S SEE HERE.
GOT CANS, NAPKINS, OH, A YO-YO,
A BOOK ABOUT YO-YO TRICKS, A
SANDWICH I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
CATCH UP ON...
OW, MY BUTT!
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> WAIT.
WHAT'S YOUR STORY AGAIN?
>> Steven: I LOST MY SPECIAL
RANGER GUY, AND I'M QUITE UPSET
OVER IT.
>> HUH.
WELL...HERE'S A BAG FULL OF
QUARTERS.
NOW YOU CAN GET ALL THE GUYS YOU
WANT.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
Thank you.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> Steven: THANK YOU!
>> Steven: WE'LL BE REUNITED
SOON, RANGER GUY.
HERE WE GO.
[ BEEPING ]
AND...
>> DAVE GUY!
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> LUCKY!
>> Steven: NOT LUCKY!
HE'S, LIKE, THE WORST GUY.
MAYBE HE COMES WITH SOMETHING
COOL.
TAXES?
COME ON, DAVE GUY!
IS THIS ALL YOU HAVE TO OFFER --
A BUNCH OF PAPERWORK?
ANSWER ME!
THANK GOODNESS I HAVE ALL THESE
QUARTERS.
>> DAVE GUY!
>> Steven: NO!
>> STOP IT!
>> DAVE GUY!
>> Steven: [ Sobbing ] RANGER
GUY!
>> THIS MACHINE IS OUT OF GUYS.
PLEASE TRY AGAIN ANOTHER TIME.
>> Steven: IT'S OVER.
[ RATTLING ]
HUH?
OH.
ONION.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[ GASPS ]
HE'S GOT A RANGER GUY?!
ONION!
WAIT UP!
LET'S TRADE!
WHICH WAY DID HE GO?
OH!
I GUESS HE NEEDS A SUITCASE.
IS HE HAGGLING WITH THAT GUY?
HE'S A TOUGH CUSTOMER.
LOOKS LIKE THEY WORKED SOMETHING
OUT.
HUH?
DID HE GET THAT GUY'S LUNCH?
I WONDER HOW THIS IS GONNA PLAY
OUT.
OH, MAN.
HEY, GOOD LOOKING.
WHAT THE HECK IS HE DOING?!
HE'S NOT EVEN HUNGRY?!
[ GASPS ]
NOT THE TOMATOES!
[ HORN BLOWS ]
HUH?
HEY.
IS THAT ONION'S DAD?
>> [ MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> Steven: I GUESS THEY DON'T
NEED WORDS.
HUH?
HE'S LEAVING SO SOON?
[ HORN BLOWS ]
DOES ONION JUST...SIT AROUND AND
WAIT FOR HIS DAD ALL DAY?
[ GASPS ]
RANGER GUY!
OKAY. LET'S DO THIS.
HEY, ONION.
HOW ARE YOU?
THAT'S GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE THAT
YOU'RE A GUYS FAN.
YOU KNOW, GUYS?
THE LITTLE MAN IN YOUR BACK
POCKET?
YEAH, RANGER GUY.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRADE THAT
BORING OLD RANGER GUY FOR A
BRAND-SPANKING-NEW, MINT-IN-BOX
DAVE GUY!
PRETTY NICE, RIGHT?
OH.
I SEE WHERE THIS IS GOING.
YOU'RE GETTING QUITE THE DEAL
HERE...
WITH TWO DAVE GUYS!
YEAH!
WHAT?
YOU WANT MORE?
LIKE...TWO MORE?
FIVE MORE.
10 MORE?
20 MORE.
THIS WHOLE BAG?
ALL 30 OF THESE DAVE GUYS FOR
JUST ONE RANGER GUY.
BUT THERE AREN'T ANY MORE.
THE MACHINE'S EMPTY.
I BOUGHT THEM ALL.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY!
LET'S WORK SOMETHING OUT.
RANGER GUUUUUUUY!
>> Steven: UGH, STUPID DAVE GUY.
GOT NO FUTURE, YOUR HAIRCUT'S
GROSS, YOU SMELL BAD...
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU TALKING ABOUT PEARL?
>> Steven: NO.
I'M TALKING ABOUT DUMB, OLD
DAVE GUY.
I MEAN, JUST LOOK AT HIM.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE HIS LIFE IS
GOING ANYWHERE?
>> Amethyst: AH, CUT HIM A
BREAK.
MAYBE THIS IS THE YEAR HE GETS
HIS LIFE TOGETHER.
MAYBE HE'LL GET A COOL
INTERNSHIP.
>> Steven: [ SCOFFS ]
I DOUBT IT.
I CAN'T EVEN TRADE 30 DAVE GUYS
WITH ONION TO GET ONE
RANGER GUY.
>> Amethyst: SO, YOU NEED MORE
OF THAT LITTLE MAN TO GET SOME
OTHER LITTLE MAN.
>> Steven: YEAH.
AND THE MACHINE IS SOLD OUT OF
THEM.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> Amethyst: PEARL'S REPLICATOR
WAND.
YOU CAN USE IT TO MAKE COPIES OF
STUFF.
YOU'RE MAGIC.
I'M SURE YOU CAN FIGURE OUT HOW
TO USE IT.
>> Steven: HAVE YOU BEEN SITTING
HERE ALL DAY WITH THIS IN YOUR
HAIR?
>> Amethyst: NAH.
I GOT UP TO LOOK FOR PEARL'S
DUMB AX BUT FOUND THAT INSTEAD.
THEN I REPLICATED A BUNCH OF
GARBAGE AND STUFFED IT ALL IN
PEARL'S ROOM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
>> Steven: HEY, ONION!
[ WARBLE! ]
[ ZAP! ]
THAT MAKES 31!
YOU WANT MORE?
HOW ABOUT 32?
[ ZAP! ]
33?
34?
[ ZAP! ]
35?
36.
[ ZAP! ]
37.
38.
[ ZAP! ]
39.
40!
ENOUGH!
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?!
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
YOU MEAN...YOU WANT THIS?
FOR RANGER GUY?
[ WAILING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: WE ARE ON THE SCENE
WITH RANGER GUY ON BEACH PATROL.
[ High-pitched ] THINGS ARE
LOOKING JUST GREAT OUT HERE,
STEVEN.
[ Normal voice ] YEP.
EVERYTHING IS GREAT.
GREAT.
WERE YOU ALWAYS THIS BORING,
RANGER GUY?
[ High-pitched ] I USED TO BE A
DOCTOR.
[ Normal voice ] MAYBE YOU'RE
JUST MORE FUN AROUND OTHER --
[ GRUNTS ]
GUYS?
DAVE GUY?
I THOUGHT I SAW THE LAST OF --
UH.
HEY!
WHAT'S THE BIG I...DEA?
[ GASPS ]
ONION!
[ ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ]
>> Pearl: THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
HOW DID HE GET MY REPLICATOR?
>> Garnet: THAT CHILD SHOULD NOT
BE IN POSSESSION OF SUCH AN
ITEM.
>> Amethyst: AREN'T THESE
STEVEN'S LITTLE MEN?
OH!
>> Steven: THEY'RE CALLED GUYS!
>> Pearl: CAN YOU PLEASE EXPLAIN
THIS MESS?
>> Steven: I TRADED THAT
REPLICATOR FOR RANGER GUY.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST REPLICATE RANGER GUY?
>> Steven: DANG IT!
>> Garnet: LET'S GO BEFORE THIS
GETS ANY WORSE.
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
UH.
HOW DO YOU MOVE IN THIS STUFF?
>> Steven: TRY AND ACT LIKE A
RICH DUCK.
>> Amethyst: WHAT DOES THAT
MEAN?
>> OH, MY GOSH!
I JUST WANTED SOME ICE CREAM.
>> Amethyst: HI, GREG.
>> WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON OUT
HERE?
>> Amethyst: UH, YOU KNOW, JUST
DOING OUR THING.
[ WARBLE! ]
>> Garnet: HAND IT OVER.
IT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU.
[ ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ]
>> Pearl: AAH!
>> Garnet: THIS IS NOT A GAME.
[ WARBLE! ]
>> Pearl: WHAT DID HE SHOOT?
[ ZAP! ]
>> Garnet: GO UNDER!
>> AT LEAST IT STOPPED RAINING
TOYS.
>> Amethyst: AH! RICH DUCK!
>> Steven: OOOOOOOOONION!
ONION, PLEASE STOP.
LET'S TRADE BACK.
YOU TAKE RANGER GUY.
HE'S THE BEST.
HE EVEN HAS A MISCOLORED H--
[ GASPS ]
YOU TRADED ME MY OWN GUY!
OUR TRADE DIDN'T COUNT.
[ GRUNTS ]
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
>> Pearl: I'M NEVER LETTING
AMETHYST BORROW ANYTHING AGAIN.
[ CRACKS ]
GARNET!
>> Garnet: I'M NOT CLEANING UP
THIS MESS.
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
[ POP! POP! POP! ]
>> Steven: I THINK I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU TOOK MY RANGER GUY,
ONION.
I BET YOU GET PRETTY LONELY
WAITING FOR YOU DAD ALL DAY.
YOU WERE PROBABLY REALLY BORED,
TOO.
AND 'CAUSE YOU MISSED YOUR DAD,
YOU TOOK MY RANGER GUY, WHICH IS
A SYMBOL OF THE RELATIONSHIP I
HAVE WITH MY DAD.
NO?
WELL, HERE.
YOU NEED HIM MORE THAN I DO.
>> Garnet: LET'S GO.
>> Amethyst: SO, ALL THE STUFF
THAT GOT COPIED TURNED INTO
NOTHING?
>> Pearl: YEP.
>> Amethyst: RATS.
>> THAT WAS REALLY COOL WHAT YOU
DID BACK THERE.
>> Steven: THANKS, DAD.
>> BUT YOU WENT THROUGH ALL THAT
TROUBLE FOR A TOY?
>> Steven: IT WAS MORE ABOUT THE
MEMORIES THAN THE TOY.
NOW WE HAVE NEW MEMORIES --
HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE MEMORIES.
>> AWW.
>> [ YAWNS ]
>> [ SPEAKING JAPANESE ]
>> Steven: OH, LONELY BLADE, YOU
SO LONELY.
>> [ SPEAKING JAPANESE ]
>> Steven: WHAT?!
THE JANITOR IS THE EVIL SAMURAI
PRESIDENT?!
THAT'S BANANAS.
>> Pearl: OH, COME ON.
IT WAS SO OBVIOUS.
HE'S BEEN MOPPING IN THE
BACKGROUND OF EVERY FIGHT SCENE.
LOOK. HERE HE IS ON THE COVER OF
THE BOX.
>> Steven: OH, YEAH!
>> [ SPEAKING JAPANESE ]
HYAH!
>> Steven: GO, LONELY, GO!
DO THE BOOMERANG BLADE AGAIN!
>> Pearl: OH, COME ON.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
JUST LOOK AT THEIR FORM.
THIS IS NOTHING LIKE REAL
SWORD-FIGHTING.
>> Garnet: SHH!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
IT'S JUST A MOVIE, PEARL.
>> Pearl: WELL, IF YOU EVER WANT
TO SEE A DEMONSTRATION OF PROPER
SWORD TECHNIQUES, I'D BE HAPPY
TO SHOW YOU.
NOW?
ALL RIGHT.
IN ORDER TO GIVE A PROPER
DEMONSTRATION, I'M GOING TO NEED
A SPARRING PARTNER.
LUCKILY, I HAVE THE PERFECT
CANDIDATE RIGHT HERE.
[ PING! ]
[ BEEPS ]
>> Steven: COOL! HOLOGRAM PEARL!
>> Amethyst: AH, GEEZ.
[ SHING! ]
>> DO YOU WISH TO ENGAGE IN
COMBAT?
>> Pearl: LET THIS BE THE
PERFECT BATTLE.
>> YOU'VE ALREADY MADE A MISTAKE
BY CHALLENGING ME.
>> Pearl: [ LAUGHS ]
WE SHALL LET OUR SWORDS DECIDE.
>> Amethyst: NERD!
>> Both: SHH!
>> COMMENCING DUEL.
[ SHING! ]
[ CLANG! ]
[ THUD! ]
DEFENSE RANK "S."
ZERO OPENINGS DETECTED.
>> Steven: GO, PEARL, GO!
>> Amethyst: GO, HOLO-PEARL!
[ SHING! ]
>> OPENING DETECTED.
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
[ SHING! ]
>> Pearl: HAH!
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
>> MATCH. SET.
CHALLENGER WINS!
>> Steven: WHOO-HOO! YAY, PEARL!
>> DO YOU WISH TO BATTLE AGAIN?
>> Steven: PEARL!
THAT WAS AMAZING!
YOU WERE SO COOL!
>> Pearl: [ Chuckles ] OH, WELL.
ONE DOES TRY THEIR BEST.
>> Steven: WILL YOU TEACH ME TO
SWORD-FIGHT LIKE YOU?
>> Pearl: [ Laughing ] ALL
RIGHT, BUT WE SHOULD START WITH
THE BASICS.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
INITIATE TRAINING MODE.
>> TRAINING MODE INITIATED.
LEVEL 1. BEGIN!
>> Pearl: I WANT YOU TO STAND
BACK, STEVEN, AND WATCH ME
CAREFULLY, OKAY?
>> PARRY! PARRY! THRUST!
PARRY! PARRY! THRUST!
>> Pearl: DO YOU SEE WHAT I'M
DOING WITH MY FEET, STEVEN?
>> PARRY! PARRY! THRUST!
>> Pearl: NOTICE WHERE I KEEP MY
CENTER OF GRAVITY.
>> Steven: AWW.
CAN YOU SHOW ME SOMETHING COOL,
LIKE THE BOOMERANG BLADE?
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU KNOW
THAT'S NOT A REAL SWORD
TECHNIQUE.
>> Steven: BOOMERANG BLADE!
BOOMERANG BLADE!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THESE ARE REAL
SWORD TECHNIQUES, NOT THOSE
SILLY THINGS FROM YOUR MOVIE.
IT'S ABOUT WAITING CAREFULLY FOR
THE PERFECT MOMENT TO --
>> THRUST!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: WHOA.
>> Garnet: OH, NO.
>> Steven: PEARL?
>> Pearl: WHOOPSY-DAISY.
STEVEN, IT'S OKAY.
I'M GONNA BE JUST --
[ CLATTERS ]
>> Steven: NO!
PEARL? PEARL!
>> CHALLENGER DEFEATED!
LEVEL 1 FAILED.
>> Both: STEVEN!
>> Steven: I-I WAS JUST --
AND -- AND SHE WAS TRYING TO --
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, IT'S OKAY.
PEARL'S GONNA BE JUST FINE.
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> Garnet: SOMETIMES IF OUR
BODIES ARE BADLY DAMAGED, WE
RELEASE OUR PHYSICAL FORMS AND
RETREAT TO OUR GEMS TO
REGENERATE.
>> Steven: SO, SHE'S GONNA BE
OKAY?
>> Amethyst: DON'T WORRY, BUD.
THIS KIND OF THING JUST HAPPENS
SOMETIMES -- USUALLY TO ME.
>> Garnet: ALWAYS TO YOU.
>> Amethyst: HEY, I'M SCRAPPY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
SO, HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE HER TO
REGENERATE -- 5 MINUTES,
10 MINUTES?
[ GROANS ]
WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
[ TWINKLE! ]
>> Amethyst: WHAT UP?
>> Steven: HE-E-E-Y.
>> Amethyst: SHE'S STILL NOT
DONE?
MAN, SHE'S REALLY TAKING HER
TIME WITH THIS ONE.
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
>> Amethyst: GOT TO TELL YOU,
THOUGH, LOVE WHAT YOU'VE DONE
WITH THE PLACE.
>> Steven: PEARL USUALLY HELPS
ME TIDY UP.
>> Amethyst: AH, I SAY LEAVE IT.
>> Steven: HEY, IF REAL PEARL
CAN'T BE HERE, THERE'S ALWAYS
THE NEXT BEST THING!
>> DO YOU WISH TO ENGAGE IN
COMBAT?
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, COVER THAT
THING BACK UP.
>> Steven: BUT IT'S LIKE PEARL!
LOOK AT IT!
>> Amethyst: YE-E-E-AH.
THAT AIN'T PEARL.
>> Steven: WELL, MAYBE I CAN GET
IT TO ACT LIKE HER.
HERE WE HAVE...A MESS.
ORGANIZING MESSES IS ONE OF
PEARL'S FAVORITE HOBBIES.
HERE. PEARL LIKES TO ORGANIZE
THEM BY TYPE -- ANIMAL,
HUMANOID, MISCELLANEOUS.
NOW YOU TRY.
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
>> YOU'VE DRAWN YOUR SWORD IN
VAIN!
>> Steven: WHAT?! AAH!
>> CHALLENGER DEFEATED!
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
MAYBE WE NEED TO TRY SOMETHING
ELSE.
[ SEA GULL CRIES ]
>> Amethyst: I'M GONNA DO IT.
>> Garnet: GO ON, THEN.
>> Amethyst: [ CHOMPS ]
[ MUNCHING ]
[ GULPS ]
[ POOF! ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
PEARL ALWAYS LIKES TO TEASE
AMETHYST WHEN SHE DOES FUNNY
STUFF LIKE THIS.
>> I WON'T GO EASY ON YOU THIS
TIME!
>> Steven: THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
WHAT ARE YOU RASCALS DOING OVER
HERE?
>> DRAW YOUR WEAPON, CHALLENGER!
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
[ POOF! ]
>> Amethyst: UGH.
STEVEN, WHY ARE YOU STILL
HANGING OUT WITH THAT THING?
IT'S GROSS.
[ BELCHES ]
>> Steven: I JUST REALLY MISS
SPENDING TIME WITH PEARL.
>> Garnet: PEARL WILL COME BACK
TO US IN TIME, STEVEN.
HAVE PATIENCE.
AND STOP HANGING OUT WITH THAT
THING.
IT'S CREEPY.
>> Amethyst: WH-O-O-O-O-OA!
>> Garnet: HMM.
>> Steven: YOU HAD FUN AT THE
BOARDWALK, RIGHT?
>> PARRY!
>> Steven: AW, COME ON.
YOU GOT TO WORK WITH ME HERE.
THIS IS PEARL'S FAVORITE TREE.
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE IT?
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
COME ON. DON'T HOLD BACK.
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
>> CHALLENGE ACCEPTED!
>> Steven: WHAT?!
OH, NO! THE TREE!
>> CHALLENGER DEFEATED!
>> Steven: REAL PEARL WOULD
NEVER DO THAT!
RAH! YOU'RE HOPELESS!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
IT'S TOO BAD YOU'RE STILL NOT
BACK, PEARL, BECAUSE I JUST
FOUND A COPY OF THE FIFTH
"LONELY BLADE" MOVIE!
[ SIGHS ]
HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA MAKE ME
WAIT, PEARL?
[ BEEPING ]
OH, THE POPCORN'S DONE.
STAY RIGHT THERE.
[ GASPS ]
>> DO YOU WISH TO TEST YOUR
SKILLS AGAINST ME IN A DUEL?!
>> Steven: NO!
NO SWORD-FIGHTING!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> DRAW YOUR SWORD AND FULFILL
YOUR DESTINY!
>> Steven: HUH? NO!
LEAVE REAL PEARL AND ME ALONE!
GO BACK UNDER YOUR SHEET.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> BROTHER, IS THAT YOU?
>> YES, IT'S ME --
YOUR...BROTHER.
YOUR TECHNIQUE IS...
>> Steven: WHOA!
THIS DUB IS REALLY GOOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, PEARL?
>> PARRY!
>> Steven: AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
[ MUNCHING ]
>> BROTHER!
>> JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE NOT MY REAL BROTHER!
AAH! BOOMERANG BLADE!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> YOUR TECHNIQUE IS IMPRESSIVE.
BUT IT WON'T BE ENOUGH.
>> Pearl: IT'S ABOUT WAITING
CAREFULLY FOR THE PERFECT MOMENT
TO --
>> Steven: [ GROWLS ]
>> THRUST!
>> Steven: AAH! THE TV!
WHY MUST YOU DESTROY THE THINGS
I LOVE?!
>> CHALLENGER DEFEATED!
CONTINUE?
>> Steven: I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU!
YOU'RE NOTHING LIKE PEARL!
PEARL IS SMART, AND SHE ALWAYS
WANTS TO PROTECT ME FROM DANGER!
ALL YOU WANT TO DO IS FIGHT ME!
>> CHALLENGE ACCEPTED!
>> Steven: [ GROWLS ]
ALL RIGHT, FINE!
>> BASIC ATTACK MODE INITIATED.
PARRY! PARRY! THRUST!
PARRY...
>> Steven: DON'T SAY THAT!
>> PARRY! PARRY! THRUST!
BASIC ATTACK MODE DEFEATED!
NOW INITIATING ADVANCED MODE!
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! SHING! ]
>> Steven: AAH! WAH!
UGH!
AAH!
WALRUS SHIELD.
[ SHING! ]
AAH!
SNACKS, PILLOW, FUZZY FLOWER,
BOOMERANG?
BOOMERANG!
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
AAH!
[ GASPS ] AAH!
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
AAAH! AAAH!
AAH! PEARL!
I SHOULD HAVE JUST WAITED FOR
YOU TO COME BACK!
I SHOULD HAVE WAITED FOR...
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
...THE PERFECT MOMENT!
BOOMERANG BLADE!
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! THWACK! ]
>> UGH!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
>> CHALLENGER WINS!
DO YOU WISH TO DUEL AGAIN?
>> Steven: N-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN, WE HEARD
FIGHTING.
>> Amethyst: OW!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> Steven: OH, JUST MOPPING.
[ GASPS ] DIE!
YOU KNOW, I MIGHT MISS PEARL A
WHOLE LOT, BUT SOMETIMES YOU
JUST HAVE TO ACCEPT THINGS THE
WAY THEY ARE BEFORE YOU --
[ WARBLE! WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ TING! ]
NEVER MIND! PEARL'S BACK!
>> Pearl: [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
OHH! HEY! MISS ME MUCH?
>> Steven: OH, MAN!
I HAD THIS WHOLE THING PLANNED
OUT FOR WHEN YOU CAME BACK!
>> Pearl: UH, STEVEN, WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOUR ROOM?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU.
>> Amethyst: I GOT HIT BY A
AIRPLANE!
>> Steven: PEARL'S BACK!
PEARL'S BACK! PEARL'S BACK!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
>> Steven: PEARL'S BACK!
>> Amethyst: [ BELCHES ]
>> Pearl: UGH. I CAN'T LEAVE YOU
GUYS ALONE FOR A SECOND.
>> Steven: PEARL'S BACK!