Pearl: GUH! THIS ISN'T
GETTING US ANYWHERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
PEROGIE?
YOU TIRED?
I DON'T GET TIRED.
I GET RESULTS.
[ GURGLING ]
WAS THE SIGN FOR "PULL ME UP"
ONE WIGGLE OR TWO?
AMETHYST, STAY FOCUSED.
FOR ALL WE KNOW,
LAPIS AND JASPER'S FUSION
COULD BE
RIGHT UNDER OUR NOSES.
[ GASPS ]
THIS IS WHY
WE WEAR LIFE JACKETS.
ARE -- ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
NOTHING.
[ GURGLING ]
OH, IT FEELS LIKE
WE'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR LIGHT YEARS.
UH, LIGHT YEARS
MEASURES LIGHT.
[ GAGS ]
NOT YEARS.
[ GROANS ]
AND I'M SICK
OF THESE...LIFE DIAPERS.
SAFETY IS NO PUNCH LINE,
PEARL.
SAFETY IS OUR JOB.
WE MUST FIND
JASPER AND LAPIS.
AS IT STANDS,
THEIR FUSION
IS A TICKING TIME BOMB.
IS LAPIS GONNA BE OKAY?
SHE HAD CONTROL
WHEN SHE USED HER POWER
TO DRAG THEIR FUSION
INTO THE OCEAN,
BUT A FUSION LIKE THEIRS
IS UNSTABLE,
BOUND TOGETHER
BY ANGER AND MISTRUST.
IF THAT BOND SNAPS,
THEIR ANGER WILL TAKE OVER
AND DESTROY.
DON'T WORRY, LAPIS.
WE WON'T LET YOU
SLEEP WITH THE FISHES.
[ YAWNS ]
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO KEEP LOOKING.
BUT FIRST,
LET'S BRING STEVEN HOME.
HUH? WHAT? WHA?
NO. I'M --
I'M -- I'M FINE.
LET'S -- LET'S
GO FISHING.
FIRST ONE
TO CATCH SOMETHING WINS.
I WIN.
Pearl: WE SHOULD BE
OUT THERE SEARCHING,
NOT IN HERE
NOT SEARCHING.
SLEEP IS A CURSE, AND YET
A CURSE I NEED TO LIVE.
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
STEVEN ISN'T
LIKE US.
HE NEEDS REST.
DON'T YOU GUYS
NEED REST, TOO?
YOU LOOK EXHAUSTED.
WE LOOK AWESOME.
LOOK, YOU CAN'T REALLY
KNOCK SLEEP
UNTIL YOU TRY IT.
AND MAYBE WE CAN THROW
A LITTLE FUN INTO THE MIX
WITH A SLUMBER PARTY!
F-FUN?
YEAH.
ALL OF US TOGETHER,
PEACEFULLY DOZING OFF.
IT'LL BE LIKE THERE ISN'T
A VENGEFUL FUSION
BOILING THE OCEAN WITH HATRED.
STEVEN'S RIGHT.
YOU SHOULD STAY HERE AND RELAX,
BUT I'M GOING.
'CAUSE I'M ALWAYS RELAXED.
BUT GARNET,
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
SEARCH THE OCEAN
BY YOURSELF.
LET ME --
LET US HELP YOU.
WE'RE A TEAM.
NO.
RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE A PARTY --
A SLUMBER PARTY.
STEVEN,
PUT THESE GEMS TO BED.
DON'T STAY UP
TOO LATE.
THERE'S SNACKS
IN THE FRIDGE.
BYE.
NOW, BEFORE WE
GET THIS SLUMBER PARTY STARTED,
WOULD EITHER OF YOU
CARE FOR A SLUMBER COMPANION?
I'M GOOD.
[ SNORING ]
[ HUMS ]
PEARL?
I'LL PASS
ON THE SLUMBER PALS.
OKAY.
SLEEP IT UP, THEN.
OH, RIGHT.
IS THIS RIGHT?
NO, YOU SHOULD LAY DOWN.
I GET IT NOW.
AM I DOING IT?
WELL, THAT'S WAY BETTER
THAN BEFORE.
BUT CLOSE YOUR EYES
ALL THE WAY.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
I'M SLEEPING NOW.
I'M SLEEPING.
YOU CAN'T TALK
WHILE YOU SLEEP.
HOW'S THIS
EVEN SUPPOSED TO WORK?
IT'S EASY.
YOU JUST LIE DOWN,
GET NICE AND COMFY, DON'T MOVE,
AND DON'T THINK
ABOUT ANYTHING.
Greg:
STEVEN UNIVERSE WAS FILMED
BEFORE A LIVE STUDIO AUDIENCE.
OH, MY GOODNESS,
CONNIE'S GOING TO BE HERE
ANY SECOND NOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOUR FIRST
SCHOOL DANCE.
LET ME JUST FIX YOUR TIE
AND --
Amethyst:
STOP FUSSING OVER STEVEN
LIKE A BABY.
AMETHYST,
WHAT DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT RIDING THAT THING
IN THE HOUSE?
HAVE FUN
AT YOUR DANCE, DUDE.
OH!
BUNGACOWA!
AMETHYST,
I'M GONNA GET YOU!
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
JUST A SECOND,
CONNIE.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
WHAT AMETHYST JUST -- HUH?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
CAN I HELP YOU?
CHILLE TID.
OH, HI, GARNET.
HEY, STEVEN.
YOU GOT TO COME
TO THE BEACH TONIGHT.
THERE'S GONNA BE
THIS HUGE BONFIRE PARTY THING.
I CAN'T
GO TO THAT.
I'M GOING TO THE BIG DANCE
WITH CONNIE.
WOW.
THE BIG DANCE.
DON'T DO ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL --
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
[ GASPS ]
SHE'S HERE!
OKAY, I'M READY
FOR THE BIG DANCE CON--
HUH?
LAPIS?
[ GRUNTS ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
AH! UGH!
OH, MAN...
I FEEL ASLEEP
AND HAD THIS WEIRD DREAM.
I OPENED THE DOOR
AND LAPIS WAS THERE, AND --
WELL, THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
LAPIS IS FUSED WITH JASPER
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN.
YOU'VE NEVER HAD
A DREAM BEFORE, HUH?
UH...I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL, PEARL, DREAMS
DON'T ALWAYS MAKE SENSE.
WHEN YOU DREAM,
THE THOUGHTS IN YOUR HEAD
GET ALL MIXED UP
INTO A WEIRD MOVIE.
AND THEY'RE
REALLY HARD TO EXPLAIN,
WHICH IS WHY
THEY'RE BORING TO LISTEN TO.
LIKE [SIGHS]
THIS ONE TIME,
I HAD A DREAM WHERE,
LIKE, THESE THINGS
WERE BEING SOLD
AT THE BIG DONUT, RIGHT?
BUT THE FRONT DOOR
OF THE BIG DONUT SHOP
LED TO THE BACK
OF MY DAD'S VAN.
SO, I GO INTO THE VAN,
AND LION IS DRIVING
FOR SOME REASON, BUT...
[ YAWNS ]
...HE'S DRIVING
REALLY WELL.
AND -- AND THEN I SAY TO HIM,
I SAYS, "LION --"
[ YAWNS ]
"LION, HOW DID YOU LEARN
TO DRIVE YOU A V-VAN?
YOU CAN'T EVEN...
YOU...YOU CAN'T
BRING...ME...MY...
WHOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
DOGCOPTER!
MR. COPTER, SIR,
I'M ONE OF YOUR BIGGEST FANS!
CAN I PLEASE
HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
[ MEOWS ]
MR. COPTER, PLEASE --
HEY, WAIT!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I HOPE THE RUMORS
ABOUT DOGCOPTER IN THE TABLOIDS
AREN'T TRUE.
HUH?
OH, HEY, PEARL!
WAIT...DON'T EAT ME!
[ CHOMP! ]
PTOO!
OOH! OH, MAN.
THANKS FOR THE UPGRADE,
PEARL!
NOW I CAN CATCH UP
WITH DOG--
WHOA.
AMETHYST?
HMM.
THIS IS
GETTING REALLY WEIRD.
Lapis:
THIS IS WEIRD.
HEY, THAT SOUNDS
A LOT LIKE --
STEVEN!
LAPIS LAZULI!
STEVEN, WH-WHAT
ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
UH, I KNOW IT'S WEIRD,
BUT I'M JUST DREAMING,
SO DON'T EVEN
WORRY ABOUT IT.
WHAT? NO!
STEVEN, I'M TRYING
TO CONCENTRATE.
[ GASPS ]
HOW ARE YOU HERE?
OH, MY GOSH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
STEVEN, PLEASE, I --
[ WARBLING, LAUGHING ]
[ AMETHYST LAUGHING ]
UGH... [ GASPS ]
LAPIS!
AMETHYST?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?
[ PEARL LAUGHING ]
OH, ROSE!
THIS IS WONDERFUL!
I'M JUST HAVING SO MUCH FUN
SPENDING TIME WITH YOU, ROSE!
FORGET ABOUT GREG.
LET'S GO TRAVEL THE GALAXY!
PEARL,
THANK YOU SO MUCH...
FOR FIXING MY VAN!
OH! UGH!
BLEGH...
GAH!
[ MUMBLING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
PEARL?
UH...
YES, STEVEN?
I HAD ANOTHER DREAM
ABOUT LAPIS.
OH...THAT'S OKAY!
DREAMS AREN'T REAL!
THEY'RE JUST
MIXED-UP MOVIES!
BUT I -- I THINK
I WAS TALKING TO HER.
WAIT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
I DON'T,
BUT I COULD JUST FEEL IT.
SHE WAS YELLING,
AND SHE
WAS REALLY FREAKED OUT.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
IS SHE STILL IN CONTROL?
I...I DON'T KNOW.
STEVEN, YOU COULD BE USING
YOUR DREAMS
TO CONNECT
WITH HER MENTALLY.
CAN YOU DO IT AGAIN?
MAYBE LAPIS CAN JUST
TELL YOU WHERE THEY ARE.
I GUESS I HAVE
TO GO BACK TO SLEEP.
QUICK, PEARL,
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DREAM
SO I CAN FALL ASLEEP.
M-MY DREAM?
COME ON, PEARL!
IT'S FOR THE GREATER GOOD!
HA, HA!
[ SIGHS ]
IF I MUST.
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
SO, IN MY DREAM, I WAS --
[ STEVEN SNORING ]
WHAT?
[ LAUGHS ]
WOW!
HE BEEN SLEEP.
OH! I KNOW
THIS IS A DREAM NOW,
SO I CAN IMAGINE
ANYTHING I WANT.
UH...MASHED POTATO.
HMM.
NOW HOW DO I FIND LAPIS?
NOT LAPIS.
UGH! LION?
WAIT.
YOU'RE NOT LION.
WHOA!
AAH! UGH!
OW.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
[ GROANING ]
LAPIS!
STEVEN!
WHY DO YOU
KEEP COMING BACK?
I CAN'T
GET DISTRACTED!
I-I'VE GOT
TO HOLD US DOWN
WITH THE WEIGHT
OF YOUR PLANET'S OCEAN.
[ Straining ] I'VE GOT
TO KEEP HER...
[ GROANS ]
WAIT, LAPIS, TELL ME
WHERE YOU ARE.
WE CAN HELP YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
I TOLD YOU!
NO!
AAH!
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU!
JASPER!
YOU! YOU!
GAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
OHH! NO!
[ GASPS ]
LAPIS!
CAN'T YOU SEE?
I CAN'T STOP,
NOT FOR A SECOND.
DON'T LOOK FOR ME.
I DON'T WANT YOUR HELP.
B-BUT --
JUST LET ME DO THIS
FOR YOU!
LAPIS...
NO!
I'M NOT LAPIS ANYMORE.
WE'RE MALACHITE NOW.
LAPIS, NO!
[ CHAINS RATTLING ]
[ GASPS ]
OOORAGH!
GO!
LAPIS!
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
STEVEN, IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE HERE.
DID YOU SEE HER?
YEAH.
SHE'S STILL FUSED.
AND SHE'S STILL IN CONTROL,
BUT I DON'T KNOW FOR HOW LONG.
AND --
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
THIS IS A WEIRD PARTY.
GARNET! MM.
STEVEN, YOU'RE STILL AWAKE.
AMETHYST WAS
ON A SKATEBOARD.
AND THEN DOGCOPTER
MEOWED AT ME
AND WAS JUST NOT INTERESTED
IN WHAT I HAD TO SAY AT ALL!
AND I MIGHT HAVE SOME ISSUES
I NEED TO WORK OUT...
BUT LAPIS, SHE'S OUT THERE,
AND SHE'S STILL --
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
I KNOW YOU'RE WORRIED,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO
RIGHT NOW.
SO LET'S TAKE IT EASY.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
THAT'S
PRETTY CONVINCING.
GARNET?
[ SNORES ]
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪