>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: AND I REALLY LIKE THE
ONES THAT SHOOT UP KIND OF
SPIRALLY WITH THE LONG TAILS.
>> STEVEN, I'M SLIPPING.
HOLD THAT END UP A LITTLE MORE.
>> Steven: OH. SORRY!
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I'M NOT SURE THE
"SUMMER WAX SPECIAL" SIGN WAS
THAT EFFECTIVE ANYWAY, BUT I
CAN'T BRING MYSELF TO THROW
MYSELF OUT.
MIGHT AS WELL STORE IT FOR THE
REST OF THE WINTER.
>> Steven: SO, WHICH FIREWORK IS
YOUR FAVORITE, DAD?
>> OH. UH, I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST LIKE WATCHING THEM
TOGETHER WITH YOU.
>> Steven: YEAH, ME, TOO!
I CAN'T WAIT FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE
TOMORROW.
IT FEELS LIKE I'VE WAITED A
WHOLE YEAR!
>> WELL, YOU FEEL THAT WAY FOR A
REASON.
MM.
HMM.
[ RUMBLE! RUMBLE! CRASH! ]
WHOA!
I HAVEN'T REALLY CLEARED THIS
PLACE OUT SINCE YOUR MOM --
[ COUGHS ]
MAYBE THIS IS GOOD TIMING --
A NEW YEAR COMING UP.
I SHOULD JUST GET RID OF ALL
THIS STUFF.
>> Steven: I COULD TAKE THESE
OFF YOUR HANDS.
>> THAT'S A START, BUT I'LL NEED
A LITTLE MORE HELP THAN THAT,
AND THIS GUY'S NOT GONNA DO IT.
WHO WOULD ORGANIZE A MESS THIS
BIG, THOUGH?
>> Steven: AH!
I KNOW JUST THE GEM!
HERE'S AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: SURPRISE.
>> OH.
>> Steven: SOMETHING WRONG?
>> WELL, NO.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU MEANT PEARL.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: WHAT?!
I'M NOT LETTING PEARL SEE THIS!
AMETHYST'S ROOM IS FULL OF JUNK.
SHE KNOWS HOW TO HANDLE A MESS.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
>> Amethyst: HEY, MAN, IT'S
COOL.
I'VE SEEN YOUR JUNK BEFORE.
WHAT YOU NEED HERE IS A
SYSTEM -- SOMETHING TO SEPARATE
THE TRASH FROM THE GARBAGE.
>> Steven: WELL, HOW 'BOUT THIS?
>> Both: HUH?
>> Steven: I MADE ORGANIZATIONAL
BOXES.
THIS WAY WE CAN SORT EVERYTHING
INTO EASY CATEGORIES -- KEEP,
SELL, BURN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WE SHOULD
BURN ANYTHING.
>> Amethyst: AH, COME ON, GREG!
WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF?
>> FIRE?
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
KEEP. KEEP. KEEP.
>> WHOA! HOLD ON.
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO BE
THROWING STUFF AWAY?
>> Amethyst: ARE YOU CRAZY?!
YOU'VE GOT SOME SERIOUSLY GOOD
JUNK IN HERE, MAN, LIKE...
>> Steven: BOOKS!
>> AH. SO, BOOKS ARE COOL AGAIN.
>> Steven: YEAH, EVER SINCE YOU
GUYS GROUNDED ME FROM TV FOR A
THOUSAND YEARS.
>> WE DID WHAT, NOW?
>> Steven: CAN I HAVE THESE?
>> UH, HOLD ON.
LET ME SEE SOME OF THOSE FIRST.
YEAH, I THINK YOU'LL LIKE THIS
ONE AND THIS ONE, AND, UH, MAYBE
WE'LL SAVE THIS ONE FOR WHEN
YOU'RE A LITTLE OLDER.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
UGH!
>> Amethyst: HA!
YOU BOUGHT THIS?!
HA!
>> UH...I GUESS I DON'T NEED
THESE OLD DUMBBELLS.
>> Amethyst: AH, COME ON.
DON'T YOU WANT TO GET YOKED?!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
>> COME ON, AMETHYST.
KNOCK IT OFF.
OH, NO.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> Steven: A PHOTO OF YOU AND
MOM.
>> AH, IT'S -- IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST THE FRAME.
>> Amethyst: HE-E-E-E-E-Y!
I FOUND SOMETHING THAT
DEFINITELY DOESN'T BELONG WITH
ALL THIS THIS JUNK.
>> IS IT THE DEED TO MY UNCLE'S
MANSION?
>> Amethyst: EVEN BETTER.
>> IS THAT..."LI'L BUTLER"?
OH, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN ALL
THESE YEARS?!
>> Amethyst: ♪ LI'L BUTLER,
THAT'S YOU ♪
>> Steven: AMETHYST, WHAT'S
"LI'L BUTLER"?
>> OH, MAN.
STEVEN, WE USED TO WATCH THESE
ALL THE TIME WHEN YOU WERE
LITTLE.
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS!
>> Steven: HEY!
I-I'M STILL GROUNDED, YOU KNOW!
>> Amethyst: COME ON.
JUST ONE, FOR OLD TIMES' SAKE.
>> OKAY, BUT JUST ONE.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> ♪ AN ORPHANED BOY WITH SASS
AND PEP GOT DROPPED OFF ON OUR
MANSION STEP ♪
♪ LI'L BUTLER ♪
♪ WE WASHED HIS FACE OF DIRT AND
LEAVES, AND NOW HE WORKS HERE AS
OUR JEEVES ♪
♪ LI'L BUTLER ♪
♪ OH, LITTLEST BUTLER ♪
♪ OH, YOU'RE THE BUTLER WHO
BUTLERS OUR HEARTS ♪
♪ SO MOP THE FLOOR AND DUST THE
SHELVES AND TEACH US LESSONS
'BOUT OURSELVES ♪
♪ LI'L BUTLER ♪
♪ LI'L BUTLER, THAT'S YOU ♪
>> YOU PEOPLE HAVE TOO MUCH
MONEY.
[ TWINKLE! ]
>> Steven: WHOA.
AH, NO! GROUNDED!
SH-SH-SHOULDN'T WE FINISH
CLEANING THE STORAGE UNIT?!
>> Amethyst: [ Laughing ] OH,
MAN!
IS THIS THE PILOT?
THEY DIDN'T EVEN HAVE THE DOG
YET.
>> OH, YEAH!
THEY JUST HAD A CAT NAMED
"MONEY"!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
HEY, STEVEN, IT'S GETTING PRETTY
LATE.
WHY DON'T WE JUST CALL IT A DAY?
WE CAN PICK THIS UP AGAIN
TOMORROW.
>> Steven: UH...OKAY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW, DAD!
>> DID ANY OF YOU ORDER A BABY?
>> Steven: HEY.
I'LL TAKE TWO BREAKFAST-ONLY
BREAKFAST SPECIALS, PLEASE.
>> SURE.
RONALDO! CAN I GET A DOUBLE
ORDER OF HASH BROWNS?
>> Steven: YEAH.
MY DAD AND I GOT A BIG DAY
CLEANING THE STORAGE UNIT.
GOT TO START THE YEAR OFF RIGHT,
YOU KNOW
>> WOW! THAT'S REALLY PRACTICAL
OF YOU, STEVEN.
MY DAD AND I ARE RESTOCKING ALL
THE CONDIMENTS.
I GET TO CLEAN THE BOTTLES.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO WASH THEM
TWICE, BUT I ALWAYS WASH THEM
THREE TIMES.
ODD NUMBERS JUST FEEL CLEANER.
>> Steven: HEY, ARE YOU GOING TO
THE NEW YEAR'S FIREWORKS
TONIGHT?
>> YEAH! IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
PRETTY DARN SPECTACULAR!
MAYOR DEWEY'S BEEN SETTING UP
ALL MORNING.
THERE ARE GONNA BE BLUE ONES!
I LOVE THE BLUE ONES.
>> Steven: IT'S GONNA BE SO
AWESOME.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU GUYS?
DAD?
>> I'LL LOOK LIKE A FOOL IF I
SHOW UP TO SCHOOL ON JUST ONE
PONY!
>> Both: YOU PEOPLE HAVE TOO
MUCH MONEY!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Amethyst: WHAT A SURPRISE.
LI'L BUTLER DOES IT AGAIN.
>> YOU CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON
LI'L B.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ] YEAH.
EVERYTHING'S ALWAYS RIGHT WITH
HIM.
ONE MORE?
>> DO IT!
>> Steven: HEY!
>> OH, STEVEN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING COMING OVER
SO LATE?
>> Steven: IT'S...MORNING.
>> OH, WOW.
I GUESS WE LOST TRACK OF THE
TIME.
>> Steven: YOU NEVER STOPPED
WATCHING "LI'L BUTLER"?!
UGH!
>> Amethyst: WHEN YOU GET TO
SEASON 3, IT REALLY STARTS
GETTING GOOD.
THAT'S WHEN THE UPTIGHT
NEIGHBORS, THE RICHINGTONS, MOVE
NEXT-DOOR.
HA! THEY'RE A RIOT!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> WELL, I NEVER!
>> WELL, I ALWAYS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Steven: WELL, YOU WANT TO GET
STARTED?
>> OH, YEAH. [ GROANS ]
>> Amethyst: OOH, THIS PART IS
SO GOOD.
[ HORSE NEIGHS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Steven: I GUESS THE STORAGE
UNIT CAN WAIT.
>> YEAH, BUDDY.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
>> Amethyst: ALL RIGHT! SNACKS!
>> Steven: WANT TO JUST MEET AT
THE FIREWORKS?
>> SURE.
>> Steven: OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
>> Pearl: LIKE THIS?
>> Steven: YEAH!
YOU GUYS ARE KILLIN' IT!
AND HERE ARE SOME POTS AND PANS.
WE GOT TO MAKE LOTS OF NOISE.
DAD AND I DO THIS EVERY YEAR.
I BROUGHT SOME FOR AMETHYST,
TOO.
THEY SHOULD BE HERE ANY SECOND.
>> Pearl: WHY WOULD SHE COME
WITH GREG?
[ GASPS ]
ARE THEY HANGING OUT AGAIN?
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"AGAIN"?
>> Garnet: THEY'D BETTER NOT BE
WATCHING THAT DUMB SHOW.
>> Steven: "LI'L BUTLER"?
>> Garnet: [ SCOFFS ]
>> Pearl: UNBELIEVABLE!
THEY REALLY ARE!
THEY USED TO DISAPPEAR FOR DAYS,
WATCHING THOSE OBNOXIOUS TAPES
OVER AND OVER AND OVER, UNTIL...
>> Steven: UNTIL WHAT?
>> Pearl: I DON'T KNOW.
ONE DAY, THEY JUST STOPPED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HAPPY NEW YEAR, STEVEN.
HOW'S MY VOLUME?
[ TAPS SOFTLY ]
>> Garnet: IT'S LOW.
[ CLANGS LOUDLY ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ WHIRS ]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
I'M MISSING THE FIREWORKS!
IT'S PAST MIDNIGHT!
HOW DID I GET SO SUCKED IN TO
THIS SHOW AGAIN?
IT'S LIKE EVERYTHING ELSE JUST
DISAPPEARS!
[ GROANS ]
>> Amethyst: WHOA, WHOA.
DON'T GO.
WE'RE HAVING A REALLY GOOD TIME!
HERE. LOOK.
I'VE GOT THE 2-PART HAWAII
SPECIAL.
>> BUT STEVEN REALLY WANTED ME
TO DO NEW YEAR'S.
>> Amethyst: HE'LL BE FINE.
HE'S STEVEN.
HE'S TOUGH.
>> I WANTED TO BE THERE!
>> Amethyst: HERE. HERE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN LIKE THIS.
WHOA! FIREWORKS!
[ LAUGHS ]
HEY, DAD, COME ON!
NOW LET'S WATCH SOME
"LI'L BUTLER"!
>> AMETHYST, YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT SHAPESHIFTING.
>> Amethyst: GEEZ. SORRY.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO CHEER YOU
UP.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT -- I FORGOT.
YOU'RE SO SENSITIVE.
>> I KNOW YOU LIKE MAKING ME
UNCOMFORTABLE, BUT IT'S NOT
FUNNY.
I CAN'T STAY HERE AND HUMOR YOU.
I HAVE TO BE THERE FOR MY SON.
>> Amethyst: WELL, WHAT ABOUT
ME, HUH?
I HAD SOMEONE WHO WAS ALWAYS
THERE FOR ME UNTIL SHE STARTED
HANGING OUT WITH YOU!
>> DON'T DO THIS, AMETHYST --
SERIOUSLY.
>> Amethyst: I BET YOU'D STAY
FOR HER.
>> YOU WOULDN'T.
>> Amethyst: WHAT?
DO THIS?
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING AFTER
HAWAII?
>> Amethyst: HEY, GREG
[CHUCKLES] TURN AROUND.
CHECK IT OUT!
>> I KNOW YOU'RE DOING IT!
I WANT TO BE FRIENDS AGAIN.
I REALLY DO.
BUT I CAN'T LET YOU DO THIS TO
ME AGAIN!
>> Steven: STOP!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ STATIC ]
WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?!
I GET IT.
IT'S HARD TO DEAL WITH STUFF
FROM THE PAST.
YOU WANT TO PUT IT OFF BECAUSE
THERE'S TONS OF IT AND IT'S
REALLY HEAVY AND IT MEANS A LOT
TO YOU, SO IT'S HARD TO LET
ANYTHING GO.
BUT YOU GOT TO, BECAUSE THIS
THING IS FULL!
SERIOUSLY, WHEN DID YOU EVEN
HAVE A CAT?!
[ STATIC CONTINUES ]
>> OKAY.
WE'RE FINISHING THIS TODAY.
>> Steven: RIGHT.
WHAT? PEARL?
>> Pearl: HELLO, GREG.
NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
>> Steven: WAS THIS...YOUR IDEA?
>> Pearl: WELL...
>> Garnet: IT WAS AMETHYST'S
IDEA.
>> Amethyst: I-I JUST THOUGHT WE
COULD TAKE ALL THIS STUFF BACK
TO THE TEMPLE.
IT CAN FIT IN MY ROOM.
THAT WAY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
THROW ANYTHING AWAY.
BUT -- BUT YOU CAN KEEP THIS.
UH...THANK YOU, AMETHYST.
[ SEA GULLS CRYING ]
>> Steven: CAN I LOOK YET?
>> OKAY.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
BOOKS!
WHOA! COOL COVER.
>> IT'S MY FAVORITE SERIES.
IT'S ABOUT THIS GIRL NAMED LISA,
AND SHE'S A WITCH.
I MEAN, SHE DOESN'T KNOW SHE'S A
WITCH AT FIRST.
AND SHE HAS A FAMILIAR, WHICH IS
SORT OF LIKE THIS SPIRIT
COMPANION THAT EVERYONE IN THE
WORLD HAS, AND HERS IS A TALKING
FALCON NAMED ARCHIMICARUS.
ANYWAYS, SHE GOES ON THIS QUEST
TO FIND HER FATHER AFTER HE'S
KIDNAPPED BY A MYSTERIOUS
ONE-EYED MAN.
>> Steven: WHOA! MYSTERY!
>> HERE, LET ME GET YOU STARTED.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
"CHAPTER ONE: THE MORNING THIEF.
LISA AWOKE WITH A START, THE
ECHOES OF HER DREAMS STILL
DANCING IN HER MIND.
THE LOW RUMBLE OF THUNDER
MURMURED THROUGH THE QUIET
HOUSE."
[ RUMBLE! ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
THIS IS A REALLY GOOD BOOK.
>> UH...OKAY.
"THE HOUSE WAS DEATHLY STILL.
THE ONLY SOUND LISA COULD HEAR
WAS HER OWN HEARTBEAT POUNDING
IN HER EARS.
THE HAIRS ON HER NECK TINGLED
WHEN SUDDENLY..."
>> Steven: WHAT THE...
>> Both: AAH!
>> Amethyst: WHAT WAS THAT?
[ BUBBLE! ]
[ WHIR! ]
>> Steven: IT'S ONE OF THE
MARBLE ROBOTS!
>> WHAT?
HUH?!
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
AMETHYST! PEARL!
>> Both: HYAH!
>> Steven: YOU OKAY?
>> I LOVE HANGING OUT AT YOUR
PLACE.
>> Steven: PEARL, DO YOU THINK
THIS WAS --
>> Pearl: ONE OF PERIDOT'S
MACHINES?
YES, I THINK SO, ONLY [SIGHS]
WE'VE NEVER SEEN ONE THIS BIG
BEFORE.
>> Amethyst: OR THIS GOOEY.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, WE NEED TO
BE CAREFUL.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS STUFF
IS.
>> Amethyst: [ SNICKERING ]
>> Pearl: OH, NO.
DON'T YOU DARE GET THAT STUFF ON
ME!
>> Amethyst: GOOP HUG!
COME HERE, PEARL!
I LOVE YOU, PEARL!
>> PERIDOT.
IS THAT THE GEM YOU TOLD ME
ABOUT -- THE ONE THAT'S TRYING
TO COME TO EARTH?
>> Steven: YEAH, WE STOPPED HER
BEFORE, BUT I GUESS SHE CAN
STILL SHOOT STUFF HERE FROM
SPACE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK IT WAS
HERE TO DO?
>> Garnet: WE DESTROYED IT.
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
>> Steven: HMM.
[ SQUISHY FOOTSTEPS ]
>> Amethyst: GOOP HUG!
>> CONNIE!
THE STEVEN UNIVERSE BOY WOULD
LIKE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
[ FOOTSTEPS ON STAIRS ]
I SWEAR THAT'S NOT HIS REAL
NAME.
>> HI, STEVEN. WHAT'S UP?
HAVE YOU READ MORE
"UNFAMILIAR FAMILIAR"?
>> YEAH, BUT I'M --
>> [ SQUEALS ]
ISN'T IT AMAZING?
HOW FAR DID YOU GET?
>> Steven: I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF
ONE OF THEM, BUT I'M REALLY
CONFUSED.
THEY KEEP TALKING ABOUT THIS
PLINKMAN GUY WHO DIED.
AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW WHO HE IS?
>> PLINKMAN?
BUT THAT'S LISA'S DAD.
STEVEN, YOU'RE READING THEM IN
ORDER, RIGHT?
>> Steven: THERE'S AN ORDER?!
AW, MAN.
I JUST STARTED WITH THE ONE WITH
THE COOLEST COVER.
Hello?
CONNIE?
[ RUMBLE! ]
WHAT THE...
>> Garnet: SOMETHING ENTERED THE
ATMOSPHERE.
[ BOTH PANTING ]
>> Amethyst: UP THERE!
>> Pearl: IT'S ANOTHER ONE OF
THOSE THINGS!
>> Garnet: IT LANDED ON
MASK ISLAND.
COME ON!
>> Steven: CONNIE, I'M GONNA
CALL YOU BACK!
[ RUSTLING ]
>> Pearl: IS IT LOOKING FOR A
WARP?
>> Garnet: WE HAVE TO STOP IT!
[ WHAP! ]
[ WAR CRIES ]
>> Steven: YEESH.
WHAT ARE THESE THINGS TRYING TO
DO?
>> Pearl: [ Hesitantly ] WE'RE
NOT REALLY THAT SURE.
>> Garnet: IT'S NOT TRYING TO DO
ANYTHING NOW.
>> Steven: MM.
>> OKAY, SO, YOU READ THE FIRST
THREE BOOKS IN ORDER.
DO YOU...LIKE THEM?
>> STEVEN: Of course!
THEY'RE AWESOME!
I REALLY LOVE LISA'S FAMILIAR.
HE'S MY FAVORITE.
I'M JUST CONFUSED ABOUT ONE
THING, THOUGH.
>> MM, WHAT'S THAT?
>> Steven: WHAT IS A FAMILIAR?
>> NOOO.
[ GROANS ]
[ RUMBLE! ]
Was that another one of those
marble things?
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> Amethyst: GRRR!
WHAT IS WITH THESE THINGS?!
THIS IS LIKE THE FIFTH ONE THIS
WEEK.
>> Garnet: WE'LL FIND IT IN THE
DESERT.
>> Steven: CONNIE, TALK LATER.
WAIT, YOU GUYS! WAIT FOR ME!
[ WAR CRIES, BLOWS LANDING ]
>> Pearl: [ Deliberately ] STOP
COMING HERE, YOU STUPID BALLS!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, LET IT OUT!
GET CRAZY!
WAH!
>> Steven: GUYS, GUYS, GUYS!
STOP!
HOW MANY MORE OF THESE THINGS
ARE YOU GONNA HAVE TO FIGHT?
>> Pearl: WE DON'T KNOW!
THEY JUST KEEP COMING AND
COMING, AND WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THEY ARE!
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
>> Steven: TH-THAT'S OKAY.
I-I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ALL THE
TIME.
IT'S LIKE MY WHOLE LIFE.
BUT I'VE GOT YOU GUYS TO TELL ME
ABOUT GEM STUFF, CONNIE CAN
EXPLAIN WHAT FAMILIARS ARE, AND
DAD TELLS ME WEIRD DAD STUFF.
>> Pearl: BUT NOBODY KNOWS WHAT
THESE THINGS ARE HERE TO DO.
>> Steven: WELL...
IT PROBABLY DOES.
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> Steven: WE COULD FOLLOW IT
AND SEE WHERE IT GOES.
>> Amethyst: ARE YOU NUTS?!
>> Pearl: WHO KNOWS WHAT COULD
GO WRONG?!
>> Garnet: WE CAN'T FIGHT THESE
THINGS FOREVER.
WELL, WE CAN, BUT I DON'T WANT
TO.
LET'S DO IT STEVEN'S WAY.
>> Steven: YEAH!
♪ LET'S FOLLOW THE FUNKY
FLO-O-O-W♪
>> Amethyst: WE'RE DEAD.
[ TAPPING ]
[ ALL GRUNT ]
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT, BIG GUY.
MUSH.
>> Pearl: OH, OH, OH!
>> Amethyst: UGH.
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
WHOO-HOO!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Garnet: KINDERGARTEN.
>> Pearl: OH, WHY HERE?
THIS SITE HAS BEEN DAMAGED
ENOUGH BY THE GEMS THAT WERE
INCUBATED HERE 6,000 YEARS AGO.
[ BREATHES SHAKILY ]
THAT'S IT! IT'S CONFIRMED!
THIS THING IS UP TO NO GOOD.
>> Steven: WAIT!
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT IT'S
DOING HERE.
CAN'T WE JUST SEE WHERE IT WANTS
TO GO?
>> Pearl: GARNET.
>> Garnet: MM...
STEVEN'S WAY.
>> Pearl: UGH.
[ WHIR! ]
>> All: AAH!
>> Pearl: WHAT DOES IT WANT
HERE?
>> Steven: MAYBE IT JUST WANTS
TO SEE WHERE AMETHYST WAS MADE.
>> Amethyst: MAYBE IT SHOULD
MIND ITS OWN BUSINESS.
>> Pearl: I DON'T LIKE THIS AT
ALL.
>> Steven: BUT --
>> Amethyst: I'M KIND OF WITH
PEARL ON THIS ONE.
>> Steven: AW, COME ON.
CAN'T YOU FEEL THIS GUY'S FUNKY
FLOW?
HE'S A FUNK MASTER.
>> Pearl: I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
DOING THIS.
>> Steven: WHY'D YOU STOP,
LITTLE BUDDY?
>> Garnet: SOMETHING'S
HAPPENING.
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: YES!
SEE?
I KNEW WE'D FIND SOMETHING
COOL!
LET'S GO.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
HEY, GUYS. GOIN' DOWN?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Pearl: WHAT IS ALL THIS?
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ LIQUID SQUISHING ]
>> Steven: WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
[ SQUISHING CONTINUES ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ ZAP! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
AAH!
>> ESTABLISH GEM-PROJECTION
LINK WITH CONTROL ROOM.
PLUG ROBONOID HAS SUCCESSFULLY
LANDED ON PLANET EARTH AND
ENTERED PRIME KINDERGARTEN
CONTROL ROOM IN FACET 5.
WE'LL PROCEED TO PERFORM
STATUS-CHECK OF KINDERGARTEN.
>> Amethyst: IT'S PERIDOT.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
IS SHE TRYING TO RE-ACTIVATE THE
KINDERGARTEN?
DOESN'T SHE KNOW IT'LL DESTROY
ALL LIFE ON EARTH?
>> Steven: WHY DON'T WE ASK HER?
>> Garnet: SHH!
STEVEN, WE'RE FACING AN ENEMY
WE DON'T KNOW, A TECHNOLOGY WE
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS ISN'T THE TIME TO BE ASKING
QUESTIONS.
>> Steven: REALLY SOUNDS LIKE IT
IS.
>> Garnet: OKAY, HERE'S THE
PLAN -- WE CAN'T LET HER SEE US,
SO WE WAIT FOR AN OPENING.
WHEN SHE'S DISTRACTED, WE
DESTROY THE POWER SOURCE ON THE
FAR WALL.
STEVEN STAYS HERE.
>> Pearl: HMM.
>> Amethyst: HMM.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
>> ALL: Steven!
>> NOW ACCOUNTING FOR ALL
OPERATIONAL INJECTORS.
CHECKING FOR ABERRATIONS IN
PERIMETER.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ SCOFFS ]
THIS GEM TECH IS SIMPLY
ARCHAIC.
>> Steven: UH, I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT LOOKS PRETTY COOL.
[ WHIRRING ]
HI. I'M STEVEN.
>> THERE APPEARS TO BE AN
INFESTATION OF..."STEVENS" IN
THE KINDERGARTEN.
>> Steven: AW, I'M NOT SO BAD
ONCE YOU GET TO KNOW ME.
>> AND HOW MANY MORE STEVENS
ARE PRESENT IN THIS AREA?
>> Steven: OH.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
JUST ME.
>> AH, THAT'S A RELIEF.
SO, TELL ME, HAVE STEVENS
REPLACED HUMANS AS THE DOMINANT
SPECIES ON EARTH?
>> Steven: OH, NO, THERE'S LOTS
OF HUMANS.
THERE'S MY DAD, CONNIE, LARS,
AND SADIE, THE MAILMAN, ONION --
I THINK.
LOTS OF PEOPLE!
>> HMM.
>> Steven: NOW I GET TO ASK A
QUESTION.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MM.
JUST PICKING UP WHERE WE LEFT
OFF.
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
>> A GEM?!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> AAH! MORE?
BUT THE RED EYE DIDN'T REPORT
THE PRESENCE OF ANY GEMS ON
THIS PLANET.
>> Pearl: THAT'S BECAUSE WE
DESTROYED IT.
>> YOU WHAT?
BUT THE RECORDS SAY THAT GEMS
WERE WIPED OUT ON EARTH.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE THE ONES THAT HAVE BEEN
DESTROYING MY PLUG ROBONOIDS!
ARE YOU THE REASON THE
HOMEWORLD WARP IS DOWN AGAIN?
IS THIS YOUR BIZARRE ICON?!
OHH!
WHY DO YOU KEEP DESTROYING MY
THINGS?!
>> Pearl: BECAUSE WE ARE THE
CRYSTAL GEMS!
WE'RE STILL ALIVE, AND WE'RE
STILL THE GUARDIANS OF THIS
PLANET AND ALL ITS LIVING
CREATURES!
>> THE CRYSTAL GEMS?
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
AAH! STOP!
HOW DARE YOU?!
I'M DOING THIS ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER.
[ Straining ] YOU'RE JUST MAKING
IT REALLY DIFFICULT!
>> Garnet: AMETHYST, NOW!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
DESTROY!
>> I'M REPORTING THIS!
[ ZAP! ]
>> Amethyst: IS IT OVER?
>> Steven: OKAY.
I-I MIGHT HAVE GONE A LITTLE TOO
FAR THIS TIME.
>> Garnet: WELL, STEVEN, YOU
WEREN'T COMPLETELY WRONG.
WE LEARNED SOMETHING NEW BECAUSE
OF YOUR DECISIONS.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT!
>> Garnet: BUT, YEAH, THIS WAS A
PRETTY BAD IDEA.
>> Steven: AW, MAN.
[ WHIR! ]