♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ ALL GASP ]
RUBY? AAH!
[ GRUMBLES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
HA! HOO-WHOO!
HOW-OOH!
HIYA!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ] WHAT A LOVELY PLANET!
[ HUMMING ]
WAIT! SO WE JUST GET OUT
AND WALK AROUND?
OOH!
NOW, WHERE'S THE GEM
THE SCANNERS LOCKED ONTO?
LET'S FAN OUT
AND SEARCH THE AREA.
WHOA,
LOOK AT THEM ALL.
I KNEW IT.
THEY'RE AFTER ME.
THIS IS THE END
OF THE LINE.
YOU REALLY
WEREN'T KIDDING.
I DISOBEYED A DIRECT ORDER
FROM YELLOW DIAMOND,
AND I CALLED HER A CLOD...
TO HER FACE.
OH, HONESTLY,
YOU CALL EVERYONE A CLOD.
YES, BUT NOT EVERYONE
HAS COMMAND OVER ALL THE ARMIES
OF HOMEWORLD,
WAITING FOR THE WORD
TO SHATTER ME!
PERIDOT,
WE WON'T LET THEM GET YOU.
BUT HAVEN'T I CAUSED YOU
ENOUGH TROUBLE?
DON'T WORRY, PERIDOT.
IT'S OUR SWORN DUTY
TO PROTECT ANYTHING
THAT CALLS THIS PLANET HOME.
AND THAT INCLUDES
CLODS LIKE YOU.
THAT'S MY WORD.
LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
I HAVE A PLAN.
OR SHOULD I SAY
WE HAVE A PLAN?
HELLO, EVERYONE.
Both: RUBY! SAPPHIRE!
HU-U-U-GS!
HELLO, STEVEN.
SO, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-YOU GOT THIS.
JUST ACT CASUAL.
YEAH, CASUAL.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
FOCUS, RUBIES!
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT MISSION
FROM YELLOW DIAMOND,
SO WE CAN'T MESS IT UP.
EH, HEY, HEY!
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH, WHAT ARE WE ALL DOING
OVER HERE?
YEAH, WHAT ARE WE ALL
DOING HERE?
WE'RE HERE TO RETRIEVE
THE LEADER OF THE EARTH MISSION!
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE ARE MORE
OF US THAN USUAL.
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE FIVE
OF US.
FIVE RUBIES!
ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE.
-[ CHUCKLES ] NEVER MIND.
-PHEW!
THE LEADER OF THE EARTH MISSION
MUST BE AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
WELL, SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT
IN THAT BARN.
WHOA!
I DIDN'T SEE THAT BEFORE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD LOOK AROUND
IN THERE.
I'LL GO...BY MYSELF.
GAH!
BYE-BYE!
THEY WANT TO SEARCH
THE BARN.
-WE HEARD.
-WE SAW.
I'M SCARED.
LET'S AMBUSH THEM!
NO.
NO ONE NEEDS TO GET HURT.
LET'S BE SENSIBLE.
WHAT DO I DO?
[ WHIMPERS ]
JUST GO OUT THERE
AND TELL THEM THIS IS A PLACE
WHERE HUMANS LIVE.
[ SIGHS ]
I DON'T WANT TO GO ALONE.
OOH! I'LL COME.
I'LL BE YOUR BACKUP.
AND HERE'S SOME BACKUP
FOR YOUR BACKUP.
I CHECKED THE BARN, AND
I JUST FOUND A BUNCH OF HUMANS.
YEP! NOTHING IN THERE
BUT US HUMANS!
REALLY?
LOOKS LIKE WE FAILED.
TIME TO GO BACK HOME.
I THINK
WE BETTER DOUBLE-CHECK.
YOU REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
LAST TIME.
LAST TIME?
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, RUBY,
YOU'RE SO FORGETFUL.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SEARCH THE BARN!
Together: YES, RUBY!
WAIT!
YOU CAN'T BEC--
BECAUSE, UH...
YOU HAVE TO, UH,
PLAY BASEBALL.
YEAH,
IT'S A HUMAN THING.
IF YOU WIN,
YOU CAN GO INSIDE.
AND IF YOU LOSE,
YOU GOT TO LEAVE FOREVER.
BASE...BALL.
All: BASEBALL?
I SAW THAT THIS
WAS A POSSIBILITY,
THOUGH I AM SURPRISED THAT THIS
IS THE PATH WE'RE TAKING.
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
ALL RIGHT,
MY HUMAN BASEBALL KNOWLEDGE
WILL LEAD US TO VICTORY.
LET'S JUST GO OUT THERE
AND PRETEND TO BE HUMANS,
EXCEPT PERIDOT.
YOU STAY HERE IN THE BARN
AND HIDE.
OKAY.
EVERYBODY IN?
LAPIS?
[ CHUCKLES ]
THIS PLAN SUCKS.
WE'RE THE HUMANS!
STEVEN!
EARL!
AMY!
BOB!
AND SOPHIE!
UNDERSTOOD.
OUR TEAM IS THE RUBIES,
CONSISTING OF RUBY!
-RUBY!
AND RUBY!
HERE'S THE RULES OF THE GAME --
WE TAKE TURNS THROWING THE BALL
AT EACH OTHER.
THE BATTER TRIES TO HIT THE BALL
WITH THE BAT,
AND THEN THEY RUN
AROUND THE BASES.
WHOEVER GETS THE MOST RUNS WINS.
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
AH!
YOU GET THREE TRIES
TO HIT THE BALL.
IF YOU MISS...
STRIKE ONE!
WHAT?!
STRIKE TWO!
[ GRUNTS ]
STRIKE THREE!
THREE STRIKES,
AND YOU'RE OUT.
OH, DARN.
MM, GUESS I'M OUT.
OHH!
YOU SWUNG TOO SLOW!
DO IT LIKE THIS!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHACK! ]
HUT, HUT, HUT!
[ WHISTLE! ]
HUT!
AND THAT'S CALLED
A HOME RUN.
IF THE BALL GETS CAUGHT,
YOU'RE OUT.
AND IF YOU GET TAGGED,
YOU'RE OUT!
[ GROANS ]
UH, AND AFTER THREE OUTS,
WE SWITCH SIDES.
[ GROANS ]
[ POP ]
[ WHACK! ]
WHOA-HO-HO!
[ WHOOSH! ]
NICE!
WOW! THAT PURPLE HUMAN'S
REALLY GOOD!
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
US HUMANS --
WE'RE FULL OF SURPRISES.
Amethyst, be careful!
HEY, RUBY.
[ LAUGHING ]
Doc: STRIKE ONE!
HUH?
HAVEN'T I SEEN YOU
SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T GET OFF PLANET MUCH.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
STRIKE TWO!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
FLIRTING.
UH-OH.
STRIKE THREE!
[ POP ]
UH...        UH...
[ BOTH LAUGH NERVOUSLY ]
♪♪
WHAT?!
YEAH! [ GRUNTS ]
♪♪
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ]
[ BAT WHACKS BASEBALL ]
[ SMACK ]
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CRACK ]
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
ARE WE WINNING?
UM...
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS LEAD WITH YOUR HIPS.
YEAH.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
LET ME SHOW YOU AGAIN.
WELL [LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
WE'RE DOING JUST FINE.
EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE A-OKAY.
YOU'RE LYING TO ME!
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER!
THANK YOU!
Steven: ALL RIGHT, IT'S
THE BOTTOM OF THE NINTH.
WE'VE GOT LAPIS ON SECOND,
BUT ONE MORE OUT
AND THE GAME'S OVER FOR US.
WE NEED TO HIT A HOME RUN.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
WAIT! I CALL A TIME-OUT!
LISTEN, YOU TWO,
I KNOW IT'S HARD
BEING SEPARATED,
BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP THEM
OUT OF THE BARN
OR THEY'RE
GONNA FIND PERIDOT.
REMEMBER?
RUBY, STOP BEING CUTE,
AND, SAPPHIRE,
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL.
PUN INTENDED?
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
WHAT DID I JUST SAY?
[ GRUNTS ]
Doc: STRIKE ONE!
[ BIRD CAWING IN DISTANCE ]
COME ON!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT!
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Doc: STRIKE TWO!
JUST LOOK AT THE BALL.
I'M TRYING,
BUT ALL I WANT TO LOOK AT
IS YOU.
DON'T WORRY, YOU CAN LOOK AT ME
WHEN YOU'RE RUNNING FOR HOME.
[ FOOSH! ]
[ GRUNTING ]
WHOO-AH-AH!
AAAH!
[ WHACK! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
[ MAJESTIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
YEAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
COME TO ME!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
[ LAUGHING ]
WHOOPS.
THEY'RE GEMS!
WE'VE BEEN TRICKED!
WHAT A TURN OF EVENTS!
UH...
HUH? W-WHAT?
SORRY, GUYS. GAME IS OVER.
THAT'S IT!
RUBIES, COMBINE!
[ WARBLE! ]
[ GROUND RUMBLES ]
[ ROARS ]
[ Screaming ] WAIT!
UH, WAIT! STOP!
DON'T HURT THEM!
OOF! OOF!
[ PANTING ]
WAIT.
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE!
IT'S ME YOU'RE AFTER,
RIGHT?
I'M NOT GONNA STAND BY
AND LET MY FRIENDS
FIGHT MY BATTLES!
AWW! PERI LOVES US.
ARE YOU THE PERIDOT ASSIGNED
TO THE FAILED EARTH MISSION?
NOT SURE IF "FAILED"
WOULD BE THE RIGHT WORD TO --
WHERE IS JASPER?
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR JASPER?
CORRECT!
WAIT, BUT I'M THE ONE
WHO BETRAYED THE MISSION,
WHO CALLED YELLOW DIAMOND
A CLOD,
THE NEW LEADER
OF THE CRYSTAL GEMS?
WHAT?
TELL US
WHERE JASPER IS NOW!
[ GASPS ]
JASPER -- UM,
WE KNOW WHERE JASPER IS.
WELL?!
UH...
NEPTUNE!
SHE'S ON
THE PLANET NEPTUNE.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SO?
[ SIGHS ]
[ WARBLE! ]
WE ALL HERE?
1...2...3...4...
AND -- HA! -- 5.
TO THE PLANET NEPTUNE!
LET'S MOVE OUT,
SOLDIERS.
WHAT A LOVELY-SOUNDING
PLANET.
BUT WE
JUST GOT HERE.
LET'S GO, NEWBIE!
Thank you.
[ WARBLE! ]
[ ZAP! ]
[ WHOOSH! ]
MAN,
RUBIES ARE DUMB.
NOT ALL OF THEM.
[ POP! ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
♪♪