>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: HOW CAN YOU LIVE LIKE
THIS?!
>> Amethyst: IT WAS FINE TILL
YOU GUYS STARTED WHINING.
>> Pearl: WHINING?!
THE WHOLE TEMPLE REEKS!
>> Steven: I FOUND IT!
>> Pearl: WHAT MANNER OF MAGICAL
ALLOY IS THIS?
>> Garnet: IT'S A BURRITO.
>> Amethyst: IT'S THE TUNA
BURRITO FROM AQUA-MEXICAN!
>> Steven: THAT PLACE CLOSED
LIKE 5 YEARS AGO.
UGH!
HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
IT KIND OF LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS
AND MY MOM.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN, THAT IS
US!
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> Garnet: THE HARD PART WAS
GETTING THE SHARK TO POSE.
>> Steven: WHY'S EVERYONE
DRESSED LIKE OLD-TIMEY PEOPLE?
>> Pearl: THEY ARE OLD-TIMEY
PEOPLE.
>> Steven: W-WAIT.
BUT THAT WOULD MEAN...
HOW OLD ARE YOU GUYS?
>> Pearl: MUCH OLDER THAN ANY
HUMAN.
>> Steven: DOES THAT MEAN YOU'LL
LIVE FOREVER?
>> Pearl: NO, NO.
WE DON'T AGE, BUT WE CAN STILL
GET HURT AND DIE.
>> Amethyst: [ GROANING ]
[ COUGHS ]
>> Pearl: BUT NOT FROM FOOD
POISONING.
>> Steven: I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS ARE LIKE A BAZILLION
YEARS OLD!
HOW DO YOU FIND A CAKE BIG
ENOUGH FOR ALL THOSE CANDLES?
>> Garnet: WE DON'T REALLY
CELEBRATE BIRTHDAYS.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
WHY NOT?!
>> Garnet: IT'S NOT OUR WAY.
>> Steven: WELL, I CAN'T JUST
IGNORE THIS TRAMESTY OF
UNJUSTICE!
I PLEDGE THAT YOU WILL HAVE
YOUR BIRTHDAYS!
WITH ALL THE CANDY, CAKE, AND
ICE CREAM YOU'VE BEEN DENIED!
>> Amethyst: [ VOMITS ]
>> Steven: AND THE BIRTHDAY
QUEEN IS...AMETHYST!
I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
DAD MADE ME THIS OUTFIT AND IT
BRINGS ME SPECIAL BIRTHDAY LUCK
EVERY YEAR!
♪ IT MIGHT AS WELL BE YOUR
BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ SO WHY DON'T WE HAVE A
PARTY? ♪
♪ EVEN IF YOUR AGE ISN'T REAL ♪
♪ AND YOUR BODY'S AN ILLUSION ♪
HEY!
IT GOES LIKE THIS.
LION, YOU'RE KILLIN' ME.
>> Pearl: UM, STEVEN...
I KNOW YOU PUT A LOT OF EFFORT
INTO...PUTTING FACES ON
THINGS, BUT COULD IT BE WE'RE
JUST A TAD...MATURE FOR THIS
RITUAL?
>> Amethyst: BOOP!
>> Pearl: OH!
YOU WILL REMOVE THAT THIS
INSTANT!
>> Steven: WAIT!
HERE!
>> Amethyst: AWW!
I'LL USE IT ALL THE TIME!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] NO!
IT'S FOR THE PIÑATA!
THE PIÑATA IS AN ARTIFACT FROM
ANCIENT AQUA MEXICO.
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Steven: AAH, AAH, AAAAAH!
>> Amethyst: AM I...GETTING...
CLOSE?
>> Garnet: HIGHER.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT NEXT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: WELL, YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO GET DELICIOUS CANDY
WHEN YOU BROKE IT OPEN...
>> Amethyst: WAIT.
YOU HAD CANDY YOU DIDN'T JUST
GIVE IT TO US?
>> Steven: THERE WILL BE MORE
SWEET TREATS AT PEARL'S PARTY.
I PROMISE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
HONK!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, THAT IS A
BRAVE LOOK.
>> Steven: NO, IT'S FUNNY!
>> Pearl: HOW?
>> Steven: UH...
OH, GEEZ, I'M BREAKING
CHARACTER.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I WROTE SOME JOKES!
WHY DID PEARL THROW BUTTER OUT
THE WINDOW?
>> Amethyst: YOU DID WHAT?
>> Steven: TO SEE A BUTTERFLY!
>> Pearl: I NEVER DID THAT.
STEVEN, ARE YOU TELLING LIES?
>> Steven: N-NO!
OH! I KNOW.
PEARL, DO YOU LIKE PIE?
>> Pearl: I DO LIKE PIE.
>> Steven: WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK!
I BAKED YOU A PIE!
I SURE HOPE NOTHING HAPPENS
TO IT!
>> Pearl: YES, ME TOO.
>> Steven: WH-WHOOPS!
>> Pearl: WHOA, STEVEN!
I'VE GOT YOU!
BE CAREFUL.
YOU ALMOST FELL RIGHT ON THAT --
[ GASPS ]
>> Steven: SEE, PEARL?
IT'S FUNNY!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Pearl: [ WHISPERING ]
>> Garnet: PEARL SAYS SHE'S ALL
PARTIED OUT AND SHE'S READY TO
GO HOME.
>> Steven: THIS ISN'T GOING AT
ALL LIKE IT SHOULD.
I'VE GOT TO PULL OUT THE
ULTIMATE BIRTHDAY.
OKAY, THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE NOT
GONNA LOVE THIS!
IT'S KAZOO RACERS!
YOU GET IN A CAR, YOU PLAY A
KAZOO -- [ KAZOO HUMS ]
WHAT MORE COULD YOU WANT?
DAD USED TO DO THIS FOR ME EVERY
YEAR.
>> Pearl: I THINK THIS IS WHY
AGING MAKES HUMANS DIE.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, THANK YOU FOR
THE BIRTHDAY PARTIES, BUT I
DON'T THINK WE'LL NEED ANY MORE.
>> Steven: WHY NOT?
>> Garnet: OUR AGE IS ONLY AN
ILLUSION.
AND PEARL'S PRETTY SURE THIS
RITUAL IS MORE FOR HUMAN
CHILDREN.
>> Pearl: NOTHING AGAINST
CHILDREN!
>> Steven: CHILDREN?
EVERYONE GETS TO HAVE BIRTHDAYS!
SERIOUSLY. GIVE IT A TRY!
YOU'RE NEVER TOO OLD!
>> Garnet: WE'RE JUST TOO BIG.
>> Steven: YOU'RE NOT TOO BIG.
Y-Y-YOU JUST GET IN AND THEN,
UH...
>> Amethyst: I CAN FIT!
WHICH WAY TO THE BABY WAR?
EAT TREAD, DIRTBAGS!
>> Steven: WHAT IF BIRTHDAYS ARE
JUST FOR LITTLE KIDS?
WHAT IF EVEN I'M TOO OLD?
>> Amethyst: NO WAY.
YOU TOTALLY FIT!
OH, MY BAD.
YOU ARE TOO OLD.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> Pearl: ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Steven: I JUST NEED TO THINK.
KAZOO RACERS SUDDENLY SEEMS
UNDIGNIFIED.
I NEVER REALIZED BIRTHDAYS MEANT
LEAVING THINGS BEHIND.
ALL THESE PARTIES...
UGH! SO EMBARRASSING.
[ SIGHS ]
[ Deep voice ] OH, ONION...
SO YOUNG, SO INNOCENT.
WHACKERMAN JR.!
AWW...
I CAN'T BE SEEN PLAYING CHILDISH
GAMES LIKE WHACKERMAN JR.
I BETTER STICK TO SOPHISTICATED
GAMES LIKE REGULAR WHACKERMAN.
>> IT'S WHACKIN' TIME!
YOU'RE GONNA GET WHACKED!
OHH!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
THAT WAS FUN, BUT A BOY ON THE
CUSP OF MANHOOD CAN'T SPEND THE
WHOLE DAY WHACKERING.
I NEED TO TAKE CONTROL OF MY
LIFE.
IT'S TIME TO GET A PROPER JOB!
BUT WHICH ONE?
SURF MASTER?
NO.
LOVE DOCTOR?
I'M TOO SQUEAMISH.
AH!
NOW THIS IS THE JOB FOR ME.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
HA. THIS DAY WENT SO FAST.
I NEED A PICK-ME-UP!
[ BELL JINGLES ]
TWO OF THE USUAL, PLEASE!
I'VE HAD QUITE A DAY.
>> YOU MUST BE CONFUSED, PAL.
I WORK HERE EVERY DAY AND I'VE
NEVER SEEN YOUR MUG BEFORE.
>> Steven: OH, HARDY-HAR, LARS!
>> HUH?
>> Steven: I USED TO MAKE JOKES!
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE HAD A LOT OF TIME TO THINK
TODAY, AND SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO
SMARTEN UP, ACT LIKE AN ADULT.
'CAUSE ONE DAY, IF YOU DON'T,
EVERYONE YOU KNOW IS GONNA GROW
UP WITHOUT YOU!
AND YOU WON'T HAVE LITTLE STEVEN
TO PICK ON ANYMORE BECAUSE I'LL
BE A GROWN-UP, TOO!
>> STEVEN WHO?
>> Steven: STEVEN QUARTZ
UNIVERSE!
AND I WANT THAT DOUGHNUT, RIGHT
THERE!
OH!
AAH!
>> SIR! A-ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Steven: I'M OLD!
>> YEAH, AND NUTS.
>> Steven: I'M GONNA HAVE TO EAT
FIBER CEREAL.
ALL MY TEETH ARE GONNA FALL OUT.
AND THEN I'LL HAVE TO EAT
OATMEAL, AND IT'LL BE
SUGAR-FREE!
SUGAR FRE-E-E-E!
I NEED TO REVERSE THIS!
I NEED...A REVERSE BIRTHDAY!
THE KING COSTUME.
WILL YOU HELP ME INTO MY
BIRTHDAY SUIT?
>> YEAH, YOU BETTER RUN!
>> Steven: AAAAAAH!
[ BONE CRACKS ]
OHH!
I'M...TOO OLD...
FOR THIS.
UNH!
[ GROANS ]
LION!
[ LION GRUMBLES ]
>> Pearl: YOU KNOW --
[ GRUNTS ] -- STEVEN WAS RIGHT.
THIS IS FUN.
>> Amethyst: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
KEEP WEARING THAT STUFF.
>> Garnet: IT MAKES ME FEEL...
IMPORTANT.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
>> Amethyst: HE'S OKAY!
HE'S JUST REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY, REALLY OLD.
>> Pearl: GEMS CAN'T DIE FROM
AGING...BUT HE'S HALF HUMAN.
>> Amethyst: CAN'T WE FIX HIM?
>> Steven: MY BIRTHDAY SUIT
MIGHT HELP.
>> Amethyst: GOOD AS NEW!
RIGHT?
>> Steven: THANKS, GUYS.
BUT I GUESS THIS SUIT'S ALL OUT
OF BIRTHDAY MAGIC.
WE HAD A GOOD RUN, HUH?
[ WHEEZES ]
>> Garnet: [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
MORE BIRTHDAYS...NOW.
>> Amethyst: CHECK IT OUT,
B-DAY BOY!
HEH, I'M A TINY CAR!
>> Garnet: BEEP BEEP.
>> Steven: KIDS...
STUFF...?
>> Amethyst: EH, PIÑATA TIME!
>> Steven: [ GROANING ]
>> Garnet: IT'S NOT WORKING!
>> Amethyst: PEARL, GET OVER
HERE!
>> Pearl: I CAN'T!
>> Amethyst: FOR STEVEN!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ LABORED BREATHING ]
>> Pearl: OH, LOOK...
I HAVE WHAT, UH -- WHAT APPEARS
TO BE...
A DELICIOUS PIE!
I SINCERELY HOPE THAT...
NOTHING HAPPENS TO...
OH, STEVEN!
[ SOBBING ]
>> Amethyst: ARE YOU TRYING TO
KILL HIM FASTER?!
>> Pearl: [ SOBBING CONTINUES ]
>> Amethyst: PEARL!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GROANS ]
>> Both: GARNET!
[ BOTH SHOUTING ]
>> Amethyst: GARNET, STOP!
>> Garnet: I THOUGHT VIOLENCE...
WOULD BE THE ANSWER.
>> Pearl: [ Muffled ] I THINK
THE PARTY APPROACH WAS WORKING.
[ HEART BEATING ]
>> Steven: WOULD YOU GUYS
JUST...PLEASE...
CONTROL YOURSELVES?!
UH...
OH, NO.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE YELLED.
BUT I CAN'T STAND TO SEE YOU
FREAKING OUT LIKE THIS!
>> Pearl: WHA...?
>> Garnet: STEVEN, YOU'RE
CHANGING!
>> Pearl: YOUR AGE IS
FLUCTUATING!
I THINK YOUR GEM IS REACTING TO
YOUR STATE OF MIND!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, STOP
FEELING OLD!
>> Steven: BUT I WASTED YOUR
TIME.
WE ALL HAVE SUCH LITTLE TIME...
>> All: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: YOU HAVE TO FEEL LIKE
YOURSELF -- SWEET AND
CONSIDERATE AND ONLY
OCCASIONALLY OBNOXIOUS.
>> Steven: DO YOU REALLY THINK
I'M ALL THOSE THINGS?
>> Garnet: YES!
>> Amethyst: WHY ELSE WOULD YOU
THROW US ALL THOSE PARTIES?
>> Steven: OH, MY GOSH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM PRETTY GREAT.
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN!
STEVEN!
>> Garnet: WE'LL WORK ON THE
REST LATER.
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
>> Pearl: THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD
AT ALL.
>> Steven: WHOA! COOL!
>> Both: NO, STEVEN!
>> Pearl: DON'T GET NEAR THAT
STUFF!
>> Steven: WHOA!
STEVEN'S HERE!
>> Pearl: YOU HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL, STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHY?
>> [ QUACKS ]
>> Steven: WHAT IS THAT STUFF?
>> Garnet: IT'S THE MOSS THAT
ROSE QUARTZ RAISED ON THE HILL.
>> Steven: MY MOM PLANTED THIS
STUFF?
>> Pearl: ROSE QUARTZ USED TO
CLIMB THAT HILL EVERY SPRING AND
TEND TO THE MOSS AT THE TOP.
BUT NOW THAT ROSE IS GONE, THE
MOSS IS ON THE MOVE.
>> Steven: IT'S LOST.
>> Amethyst: IT'S NOT LOST.
IT'S GROSS.
>> Pearl: YES, BUT ROSE LOVED IT
ANYWAY.
SHE SAW THE BEAUTY IN
EVERYTHING, NO MATTER HOW GROSS.
FORTUNATELY, I KNOW JUST WHAT TO
DO IN THIS SITUATION.
HA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-H!
HA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-H!
>> Steven: THIS IS WHY I GET UP
IN THE MORNING.
IS THIS...POLICE TAPE?
>> Pearl: ISN'T THIS GREAT?!
THIS WAY WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TO
USE MAGIC.
HUMANS WILL JUST SEE THIS AND
WALK AWAY.
>> Garnet: DON'T HOLD BACK.
>> Amethyst: I NEVER...DO!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SIGHS, GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: ♪ FA LA-LA LA-LA ♪
♪ PERFECT! ♪
NOW WE CAN COME UP WITH A PLAN
TO MOVE THE MOSS BACK TO ITS
HILL.
>> Steven: WHO WANTS TO GET SOME
LUNCH?
JUST ME, THEN?
NICE.
♪ GETTIN' ME A P,
GETTIN' ME A ZA ♪
♪ GETTIN' ME A P-P-P-P-PIZZA ♪
♪ GETTIN' ME A P,
GETTIN' ME A ZA ♪
[ HUMMING ]
HEY, IS THAT LARS?
LARS!
>> [ GROANS ] WHY NOW?
>> Steven: GOT A HIGH FIVE FOR
YOU FROM WA-A-A-Y
DOWNTO-O-O-O-WN!
OHHHHHH!
>> NO, STEVEN! NO HIGH FIVES!
>> Steven: MMMMM, OKAY.
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
SO...HOW COME YOU'RE NOT AT
THE BIG DONUT?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I DON'T SPEND MY WHOLE LIFE AT
WORK.
I DO...OTHER THINGS.
>> Steven: LIKE STANDING AGAINST
THIS WALL?
>> WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?!
>> Steven: LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
DOING A LOT OF NOTHING.
>> THAT'S THE PLAN, STE-VAN.
JUST PLAYING IT COOL TODAY, YOU
KNOW?
>> Steven: WE ARE SO MUCH ALIKE.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> Steven: YOU WANT TO GET A
FRESH PIZZA RIGHT OUT OF THE
OVEN, BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO SEEM
TOO DESPERATE, RIGHT?
WELL, THERE'S NO NEED TO BE
ASHAMED.
JUST WALK RIGHT IN AND ASK.
THAT'S WHAT I ALWAYS DO.
>> STEVEN, DON'T GO IN THERE
RIGHT NOW!
>> Steven: OH, HEY!
>> HE OPENED THE DOOR, AND THERE
WAS DOGGY DOO EVERYWHERE.
>> THAT'S NASTY.
I DON'T LIKE NASTY STUFF.
>> Steven: ISN'T THAT KIKI'S
SISTER AND HER FRIENDS?
>> JENNY, SOUR CREAM, AND
BUCK DEWEY.
>> Steven: OH.
YOU KNOW THOSE GUYS?
>> NOT QUITE, BUT I'M SURE WE'LL
HANG AT SOME POINT.
>> Steven: YOU SHOULD GO IN AND
TALK TO THEM.
>> THAT'S NOT HOW THESE THINGS
WORK, STEVEN!
THE PLAN IS TO KEEP IT COOL AND
LET THEM COME TO ME.
>> Steven: HERE THEY COME.
>> AAH! STEVEN, TURN AROUND!
ACT NATURAL!
>> TELL DAD I'LL BE BACK LATER.
>> Steven: I DON'T THINK THEY
SAW YOU.
>> STEVEN, YOU WERE BLOCKING ME
WITH YOUR...BIG HAIR!
AAAH!
>> Steven: SORRY!
I'LL GO TELL THEM TO LOOK OVER
HERE!
>> STEVEN, NO!
DON'T GO OVER THERE!
I HATE YOU!
>> MUFFINS THAT ARE LIKE THIS
BIG.
>> THOSE THINGS ARE TOO SWEET
FOR ME.
>> Steven: HI! MY NAME'S STEVEN.
>> BUCK DEWEY.
>> THEY CALL ME "SOUR CREAM."
>> I'M JENNY.
>> AAH, HE'S GONNA WRECK
EVERYTHING!
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
I CAN'T HEAR THEM!
UGH! WHY IS HE DANCING?!
NO! MY LIFE IS HORRIBLE!
>> Steven: HEY, LARS!
>> YO.
>> Steven: THEY INVITED US ALONG
FOR A RIDE.
>> HUH?
W-WAIT A MINUTE.
THEY? YOU?
STEVEN, YOU GOT LUCKY.
SO, DON'T RUIN THIS WITH ANY OF
YOUR LAME SHTICK.
>> Steven: PYOO, PYOO!
YOU GOT IT!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> HOP ON IN, GUYS.
>> Steven: OH, YEAH!
MIDDLE SEAT!
>> WHERE'D YOU GET THAT RAD
SHIRT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
ANY OF MY CLOTHES COME FROM.
>> YEAH, MAN.
LIVIN' FREE.
I LIKE IT.
>> HEY, CHECK OUT MY SHIRT.
>> OH. THAT SNAKE IS NASTY.
>> OH. [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH. I HATE SNAKES.
>> OH, WHAT? THAT'S TOO BAD.
SOME SNAKES ARE PRETTY COOL.
>> Steven: SOUNDS LIKE IT'S TIME
TO BUCKLE UP!
>> QUIT BEING LAME, STEVEN.
>> HEY, MAN, THERE'S NOTHING
LAME ABOUT SEAT-BELT SAFETY.
>> CAR DOES NOT MOVE TILL WE'RE
ALL BUCKLED UP.
>> YEAH. NOW LET'S GET SOME
SPACED-OUT BEATS UP IN HERE.
YEAH. I CAN RAVE TO THIS.
>> HEY, THIS CAR'S REALLY COOL,
JENNY.
>> IT'S JUST A DELIVERY CAR FOR
MY DAD'S LAME SHOP.
MAKES ME SMELL LIKE PIZZA.
WHERE TO, Y'ALL?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
>> Steven: OH, CAN WE STOP BY
THE BIG DONUT?
>> THAT OLD PLACE?
>> MAN, THAT PLACE IS A DRAG.
>> Steven: BUT THAT'S WHERE LARS
WORKS.
>> [ COUGHS ]
QUIT IT, STEVEN.
[ COUGHS ]
>> Steven: YOU NEED SOME WATER?
FUNLAND ARCADE IS THE BEST!
LET'S DO THAT!
>> MAN, I BEAT ALL THE "G's" IN
THERE LIKE 3 MILLION TIMES.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
NO WAY!
>> YEAH. ME TOO.
>> Steven: NO WAY!
>> HONESTLY, THOUGH, I'M JUST
EXAGGERATING TO SOUND COOL.
>> Steven: I APPRECIATE YOUR
HONESTY.
>> HEY, BUCK, ISN'T THAT YOUR
DAD?
>> ANOTHER REASON YOU SHOULD
RE-ELECT ME -- I LOVE BABIES!
WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT? A BABY!
GONNA KISS IT.
[ SMOOCHING ]
[ LIGHT APPLAUSE ]
>> Steven: HMM.
I LIKE HIS POLICIES ON BABIES.
>> MAN. HE NEVER KISSES ME LIKE
THAT.
>> THAT'S ROUGH, BRO.
>> IT'S NOT ROUGH.
THE LACK OF DADDY KISSES IN MY
LIFE MADE ME WHO I AM.
>> OH, MY GOSH, GUYS.
WE SHOULD CHECK OUT
DEAD MAN'S MOUTH.
>> Steven: WHAT'S
DEAD MAN'S MOUTH?
>> OH, IT'S THIS LAKE WHERE SOME
DUDE DIED OR IT LOOKS LIKE A
MOUTH.
I FORGET THE SPECIFICS.
>> DEAD MAN'S MOUTH, HERE...
WE...COME.
>> Steven: SOUNDS GOOD TO ME!
>> WE'RE HERE.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
Y-YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW THIS PLACE MAY SEEM COOL,
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY A LOT LESS
COOL THAN YOU THINK.
WHY DON'T WE JUST GO HAVE SOME
MORE FUN AT THE BOARDWALK?
>> STEVEN, STOP BEING LAME.
LET'S CHECK THIS PLACE OUT.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
OH, YEAH.
>> Steven: OH! PFF!
THE POLICE TAPE!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> HUH. POLICE TAPE?
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> AWESOME.
>> I'M ABOVE THE LAW.
>> WHO WANTS TO GO FOR A SWIM?
[ BUBBLING ]
>> Steven: AAH!
>> PANTS BECOME SHORTS.
>> AAH!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ EXHALES ]
>> Steven: LARS, DON'T GO IN
THERE!
IT'S DANGEROUS!
>> STEVEN, YOU TRYING TO SCARE
US?
>> BUILD AN ATMOSPHERE.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> OOOOOOOOH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Steven: WAIT!
>> I'M NOT THAT SLOW.
>> [ GRUNTS ]
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MAN?!
>> Steven: [ Sobbing ] DON'T!
>> STEVEN...WHAT...IS...YOUR...
DEAL?!
[ GASPS ]
>> UGH. EW!
OHH! AAH!
>> AAH!
>> Steven: OH, NO!
UGH! AAAAH!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?!
>> Steven: IT'S SOME KIND OF
MAGIC MOSS MY MOM PLANTED!
>> WAIT. YOUR MOM?
[ BUBBLING CONTINUES ]
[ ALL GASPING AND GROANING ]
>> GUYS, HANG ON!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
LARS, I KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO!
>> THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
[ GROANS ]
I KNEW IF SOMETHING WENT WRONG
TODAY, IT WOULD BE BECAUSE OF
YOU!
NOW I'M NEVER GOING TO BE
FRIENDS WITH THESE GUYS, ALL
BECAUSE OF YOUR WEIRD MOM!
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT MY MOM?!
I DIDN'T EVEN GET TO KNOW MY
MOM!
BUT I DO KNOW SHE SAW BEAUTY IN
EVERYTHING, EVEN IN STUFF LIKE
THIS AND EVEN IN JERKS LIKE YOU!
[ SIGHS ]
NOW HELP ME GET THEM TO THE CAR.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> HEY!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
>> Steven: LARS, HURRY!
THIS MOSS BELONGS ON THE TOP OF
THAT HILL.
COME ON, LARS!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?!
>> UH, STEVEN, I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO DRIVE A STICK SHIFT!
>> Steven: I'LL WORK THE STICK.
YOU JUST KEEP US ON THE ROAD.
>> OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THIS.
IGNITION!
>> Steven: STICK PROBLEM!
>> STEVEN, NO!
PUT IT IN REVERSE!
>> Steven: IS THAT THE ONE WITH
"R" ON IT?
AAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> JENNY'S GONNA KILL ME!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN WHEN WE
GET TO THE TOP OF THAT HILL?
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW!
>> YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> Steven: THAT'S JUST WHERE THE
MOSS WANTS TO BE!
AAH!
>> HUH? AAAAAAH!
IT'S GETTING EVERYWHERE!
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Steven: WE MADE IT!
>> WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
>> Steven: WE GOT TO GET UP
THERE!
[ GROANING ]
HURRY!
>> YEAH!
I'M...GETTING...STUCK.
OHH!
>> Steven: OH! DON'T GIVE UP!
>> STEVEN?
>> WHAT?
THIS SUCKS.
OHHHHH!
>> Steven: LARS!
[ WIND BLOWING ]
>> [ GASPS, COUGHS ]
>> Steven: [ COUGHS ]
THE MOSS WAS JUST TRYING TO
BLOOM.
>> UGH. WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I THINK I DIED.
>> GUYS, LOOK!
>> WHOA!
>> YOU CAN SEE ALL OF BEACH CITY
FROM UP HERE.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
HOW DID WE EVEN GET UP HERE?
>> WELL, STEVEN THOUGHT THAT --
>> Steven: LARS DROVE US HERE.
>> YEAH, LARS.
SUPERCOOL.
>> YOU'RE COOL, LARS.
>> I CAN TOTALLY RAVE TO THIS.
>> GO! GO! GO! GO!
SOUR CREAM! SOUR CREAM!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH!
>> OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.