♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
HOW MUCH LONGER TILL
WE CAN USE THE DRILL?
WELL, WITH THE NEW COORDINATES
WE GOT FROM THE MOONBASE,
WE SHOULD BE READY TO GO.
BUT WE REALLY SHOULD PERFORM
A FEW TESTS FIRST.
OH!
STEVEN.
PERIDOT.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
UH, YEAH.
SURE.
WHY ARE WE IN
THIS BROKEN-DOWN VEHICLE?
I WANTED TO ASK YOU...
ABOUT THE DIAMONDS?
OH!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE OTHERS
HAVE TOLD YOU,
BUT THERE'S A REASON
THEY'RE IN CHARGE.
WHY'S THAT?
THEY'RE OBJECTIVELY BETTER
THAN US.
EVERY GEM HAS THEIR STRENGTHS
AND WEAKNESSES --
BUT NOT THEM.
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY, TOTALLY,
COMPLETELY FLAWLESS BEINGS!
ESPECIALLY MY DIAMOND --
YELLOW DIAMOND.
THE MOST PERFECT,
THE MOST REASONABLE, RATIONAL,
EFFICIENT DECIDER EVER TO EXIST
IN THE UNIVERSE.
YOU'RE REALLY LOYAL TO HER,
AREN'T YOU?
HOW COULD I NOT BE?
WE MIGHT HAVE
OUR LITTLE TRUCE,
BUT I'LL NEVER FORSAKE
THE GEM I WAS MADE FOR.
THAT'S GOOD,
BECAUSE SHE'S RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
AAH, NO!
AAH!
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH!
YOU'RE UP AGAINST
ONE OF THE EARTH'S GREATEST
TRAPPING TECHNOLOGIES --
THE CHILD SAFETY LOCK!
[ GASPS ]
NO! NO!
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME --
THE GREAT AND LOVABLE PERIDOT?!
I THOUGHT WE WERE FINALLY
FRIENDS, LIKE YOU WANTED!
I SAW YOU SNEAK THIS
OFF THE MOON BASE
WHILE NO ONE ELSE
WAS LOOKING!
WHAT IS IT?
TELL ME!
IT'S NOTHING SPECIAL...
AND DEFINITELY
NOT IMPORTANT AT ALL!
HMM.
THEN WHY DON'T
I JUST SMASH IT?!
NO, NO, NO, NO,
WAIT!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I HAVE A PLAN.
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
IT'S...
A COMMUNICATOR.
MEANT FOR
THE EXPRESS PURPOSE
OF CONTACTING THE DIAMONDS
BACK ON HOMEWORLD.
YOU'RE STILL TRYING TO CONTACT
HOMEWORLD?
YES. OF COURSE!
I FIGURED IT OUT!
YOU SIMPLE CLODS KEEP
TRYING TO PROTECT THE EARTH,
BUT YOU CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT!
I LET MYSELF GET CARRIED AWAY,
TOO --
LAUGHING, SINGING,
BUILDING OUR LITTLE MACHINE!
BUT DON'T YOU SEE?
NONE OF THAT MATTERS!
ALL THAT MATTERS IS THAT
I'M OF USE TO YELLOW DIAMOND!
THIS PLANET CAN BE OF USE
TO YELLOW DIAMOND!
I MUST CONTACT HER --
TO REVEAL WHAT I'VE DISCOVERED!
BUT THE DIAMONDS
ARE BAD!
THEY DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE EARTH.
THEY WANTED TO HOLLOW IT OUT,
AND NOW THEY WANT TO BLOW IT UP
WITH THE CLUSTER!
YES, YES!
THAT'S THE POINT!
UGH!
WHY DO I KEEP STICKING MY NECK
OUT FOR YOU!
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA BE
ON OUR SIDE!
GARNET, AMETHYST, PEARL!
STEVEN, NO --
DON'T GET THEM!
STEVEN!
RELEASE ME!
[ ALL GASP ]
SHE TOOK A DIRECT LINE
TO THE DIAMONDS
FROM THE MOON BASE?!
WHAT WAS SHE THINKING?!
MAN, AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE GONE THROUGH,
SHE'S STILL OUT TO GET US.
OH, I'M TAKING BACK
ALL MY COOL NICKNAMES FOR HER.
SO LONG "PERRY" AND "P-DOT."
HELLO, P...
AAH!
I'M TOO MAD!
I'LL THINK OF SOMETHING LATER!
[ HORN HONKING ]
Steven: [ SIGHS ]
I SEE SHE KNOWS
WHAT A HORN IS NOW.
YOU OFFERED HER
A LOT OF YOUR TRUST.
I DID!
AND IT BLEW UP IN MY FACE.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN PROTECTING
THE EARTH
FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS!
SHE COULD HAVE DESTROYED
ALL OF THAT --
THE WHOLE EARTH!
WHY DID I THINK
I COULD CHANGE HER MIND?
UGH.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
BUT I GUESS YOU CAN'T, LIKE,
GET INTO OTHER PEOPLE'S HEADS
AND CHANGE WHAT THEY THINK.
OH, MAYBE WE CAN?
YEAH!
IF WE JUST SHRINK DOWN
REALLY LITTLE,
WE CAN GET IN --
NO, NO, NO!
I DON'T WANT TO TELL HER
WHAT TO DO.
SHE SHOULD JUST KNOW,
SHOULDN'T SHE?
IT'S GOOD YOU BELIEVE
IN EVERYONE, STEVEN.
LIKE YOUR MOTHER,
YOU SEEM TO HAVE A LITTLE MORE
PATIENCE THAN THE REST OF US.
BUT THE TRUTH IS NOT EVERYONE
DESERVES THAT PATIENCE.
LOOK ON
THE BRIGHT SIDE --
AT LEAST YOU GOT THIS THING
AWAY FROM HER
BEFORE SHE DID
ANY REAL DAMAGE.
YEAH.
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
[ LAUGHING ]
FREE, FREE!
HOW DID SHE
ESCAPE?!
OH!
FOOLS!
YOUR INVISIBLE ROTARY SHIELD
WAS NO MATCH FOR ME --
ONCE I APPLIED LOGIC!
[ GROWLS ]
NOW I'M GONNA DO THIS RIGHT!
UGH! SEE?
NONE OF YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
OH-HO HO-KAY!
I BEEN READY FOR THIS!
GET IN.
WHERE'S STEVEN?
STUPID PERIDOT!
STUPID GIANT ROBOT!
OH, WHY, OH, WHY
DID I HAVE TO ENCOURAGE HER?
THERE'S NO TIME
FOR FEELING HORRIBLE.
WE HAVE TO CATCH PERIDOT BEFORE
SHE CONTACTS YELLOW DIAMOND!
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN FEEL HORRIBLE ALL YOU
WANT BACK AT THE TEMPLE.
[ SCREAMING ]
Peridot: [ GRUNTING ]
WHAT'S UP, PERI-SNOT?
GOOD ONE, AMETHYST!
[ GROANS ]
[ GASPS ]
HUH!
DOG PILE!
NO, NO!
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY
WITH IT!
I TRUSTED YOU!
I SPENT ALL THAT TIME
BONDING AND HOPING
AND CARING ABOUT YOU!
YOU DON'T GET IT,
EITHER!
THIS IS YOUR WHOLE...
[ STRAINING ]
...PROBLEM!
YOUR EMOTIONS
RULE OUT REASON!
I WILL DO
WHAT HAS TO BE DONE!
[ DIAMOND ACTIVATES ]
HUH?
Peridot: [ LAUGHING ]
SHE'LL SORT THIS OUT.
[ ALL GASPING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
THIS IS THE YELLOW DIAMOND
CONTROL ROOM.
IS THAT ANOTHER PEARL?
WHO IS SHE?
NOT ALL PEARLS KNOW
EACH OTHER, STEVEN.
WHO AUTHORIZED YOU
TO MAKE THIS CALL?
NO ONE.
B-BUT IT'S AN EMERGENCY!
THAT'S NO EXCUSE TO USE
THE DIRECT DIAMOND
COMMUNICATION CHANNEL!
Yellow Diamond:
PEARL?
YES, MY DIAMOND?
WHY IS THERE SOMEONE
ON THE DIAMOND LINE?
I DON'T KNOW!
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TELL HER
THAT --
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
[ ALL GASP ]
IS THAT...
YELLOW...
DIAMOND.
MY DIAMOND!
PERIDOT REPORTING IN!
WHICH PERIDOT?
F-FACET 2F5L, CUT 5XG.
I'M SORRY TO CONTACT YOU
THIS WAY,
BUT ALL OTHER FORMS
OF COMMUNICATION
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED
AND --
THIS SAYS YOU'RE BEHIND SCHEDULE
ON YOUR MISSION TO...
HOW IS THE EARTH?
IT'S FULL OF LIFE!
ORGANIC LIFE.
AND WHERE IS THE JASPER
I ASSIGNED YOU?
AND WHY AREN'T YOU CALLING
FROM THE SHIP?
OH, HMM...
THE SHIP WAS DESTROYED.
BY WHOM?
IT -- IT --
IT WAS DESTROYED BY...
NO ONE!
THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT...
WHILE WE WERE LANDING.
I'LL INFORM YOUR MANAGER
OF YOUR INCOMPETENCE.
AND WHAT IS THE STATUS
OF THE CLUSTER?
THE CLUSTER
WILL EMERGE SHORTLY!
GOOD.
WE'LL FINALLY GET SOME USE
OUT OF THAT MISERABLE PLANET.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR REPORT,
PERIDOT.
THERE'LL BE A SHIP HEADING
TO YOUR LOCATION
TO TAKE YOU
TO YOUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT.
WAIT!
I -- I WOULDN'T HAVE CALLED
JUST TO WASTE YOUR TIME
WITH A REPORT!
YOU ALREADY HAVE.
NO, I MEAN,
THE REASON I'VE CALLED,
THE REAL REASON IS...
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD TERMINATE
THE CLUSTER!
WHY?
THE ORGANIC ECOSYSTEM CREATES
RESOURCES UNIQUE TO THIS WORLD.
WE CAN'T SACRIFICE
ALL THAT POTENTIAL
JUST FOR ONE GEO-WEAPON!
I'D LIKE TO TELL YOU
SOME PLANS I CAME UP WITH
TO UTILIZE THE PLANET
WITHOUT DISRUPTING THE LOCAL --
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT POTENTIAL AND RESOURCES.
WHAT?
I WANT MY CLUSTER,
AND I WANT THAT PLANET
TO DIE.
JUST MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
NO!
HUH?!
ARE YOU QUESTIONING
MY AUTHORITY?
I'M QUESTIONING
YOUR OBJECTIVITY, MY DIAMOND.
WELL!
YOU ARE OUT OF LINE.
I JUST THINK --
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN THE PUNY THOUGHTS
OF A PERIDOT.
BUT --
YOU HAVE DISRESPECTED
THIS CHANNEL AND MY TIME
WITH YOUR PRESENCE,
AND YOU WOULD DO WELL TO --
BUT --
SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
YOU HAVE FAILED
AT EVERY STAGE OF THIS MISSION.
YOUR ONLY CHANCE
TO REDEEM YOURSELF
IS TO OBEY
THIS SIMPLE ORDER --
YOU ARE TO LEAVE
THE CLUSTER TO GROW!
IT WILL TEAR APART
THE EARTH,
AND I WILL TAKE
IMMENSE SATISFACTION
IN ERASING
THAT HIDEOUS ROCK
OFF OF OUR STAR MAPS!
IS THAT CLEAR?!
I WON'T DO IT!
I CAN TELL YOU WITH CERTAINTY
THAT THERE ARE THINGS ON
THIS PLANET WORTH PROTECTING!
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE EARTH?!
APPARENTLY MORE THAN YOU,
YOU CLOD!
HMM?!
UH, PERIDOT, OUT!
[ CHEERING ]
THAT WAS AMAZING!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST DID THAT.
I WAS SO WRONG ABOUT BEING
SO WRONG ABOUT YOU!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST DID THAT.
YOU THOUGHT
YOU COULD CHANGE HER MIND.
YELLOW D GOT TORN DOWN
BY THE PERIDACTYL!
UGH!
CAN ONE OF YOU TAKE THIS?
WHY?
BECAUSE IT CAN BE
REMOTELY DETONATED.
[ GASPS ]
HOW DO WE STOP IT?
JUST GET RID OF IT!
UH, HERE, AMETHYST!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH IT?!
[ GASPS ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
I THOUGHT I COULD REASON
WITH HER.
YEAH,
YOU REALLY MADE HER MAD.
AND THEN YOU INSULTED HER
TO HER FACE.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
I'M A TRAITOR TO MY HOMEWORLD.
YOU'RE A CRYSTAL GEM!
MMM!
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT
OR NOT.
OH!
[ GROANING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
LOG DATE 7-1-5-2.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I JUST DID THAT.
I DISOBEYED MY ORDERS AND WENT
AGAINST YELLOW DIAMOND'S WISHES.
I'M A TRAITOROUS CLOD!
I NEVER WANT TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT I'VE DONE AGAIN!
[ TAPE REWINDS ]
I'M A TRAITOROUS CLOD!
[ LAUGHS ]
I NEVER WANT TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT I'VE DONE AGAIN!
AND I CALLED YELLOW DIAMOND
A CLOD RIGHT TO HER FACE!
I CALLED YELLOW DIAMOND A CLOD
RIGHT TO HER FACE.
UH, PERIDOT,
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
[ TAPE RECORDER REWINDS ]
I'M A TRAITOROUS CLOD.
[ TAPE REWINDS ]
TRAITOROUS CLOD.
NO.
IT'S ALL GONNA WORK OUT.
YOU'RE WITH US NOW!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M PROTECTING A PLANET
I WAS ONCE TRYING TO DESTROY.
I USED TO FOLLOW EVERY ORDER --
EVERY RULE.
NOW I'M A TRAITOR.
A REBEL!
A CRYSTAL GEM-M-M-M-M.
[ CHUCKLES ]
CLOD! CLOD! CLOD!
WELL, THAT TAPE RECORDER
SEEMS TO BE HELPING.
NO, IT'S NOT!
IT'S A CHRONICLE
OF MY DESCENT INTO MADNESS!
YOU DROPPED THIS.
GET IT AWAY FROM ME.
GIVE IT TO STEVEN.
RETURN MADNESS
TO ITS SOURCE!
ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT IT?
WHATEVER.
IT'S YOURS NOW. YOURS.
NOT MINE. NOT MINE.
YOURS. YOURS.
LET'S CALM DOWN.
OKAY.
SO, AM I GONNA HAVE TO
WEAR A STAR?
WHERE AM I GONNA PUT
THE STAR?
THEY SEEM TO BE
GETTING ALONG WELL.
I WONDER WHEN THAT HAPPENED.
[ TAPE REWINDS ]
LOG DATE 7-1-1-2.
THE STEVEN HAS GIVEN ME
THIS EARTH MACHINE
TO REPLACE MY COMMUNICATOR LOG.
IT LOOKS...
EXTREMELY PRIMITIVE.
HE ALSO SAID HE WANTED ME TO
STOP CALLING HIM "THE STEVEN."
IT'S JUST "STEVEN."
I SAID I'D CALL HIM
WHATEVER I WANT!
[ HISSES ]
HE TOLD ME THAT WAS RUDE.
RUDE.
I GUESS
I'LL CALL HIM "STEVEN."
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
THE ORGANIC LIFE FORMS OF EARTH
HAVE FASCINATING TRAITS
DESPITE THEIR POOR CHOICE
OF RESIDENCE.
I WONDER IF ALL OF THEM HAVE
FLIGHT CAPABILITIES?
[ HAMMERING ]
OH, YOU MUST BE PERIDOT.
[ WIND GUSTS ]
WHOA!!
AAAAAAH!
PERIDOT!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU CAN'T JUST SHOVE SOMEONE
OFF OF A ROOF!
WHY NOT?
THIS IS A HUMAN!
HE ISN'T LIKE US!
HE'S FRAGILE AND SOFT!
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE
A SIX PACK IS GONNA SAVE YOU
FROM THAT HEIGHT.
YOU COULD HAVE
SERIOUSLY HURT HIM.
WELL, HOW WAS I SUPPOSED
TO KNOW THAT?
HM.
GREG, YOU'LL HAVE TO
EXCUSE PERIDOT.
SHE'S FAR FROM HER HOMEWORLD,
AND SHE STILL HAS A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT OUR PLANET.
NO, I DON'T!
YES, YOU DO!
UH, HEY, YEAH.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
UGH!
Peridot: IN CONCLUSION,
NOT ALL OF THE ORGANIC BEINGS
HERE CAN FLY.
ADDITIONALLY,
IT IS, WITHOUT QUESTION,
THAT THE PERMAFUSION, GARNET,
IS THE WORST.
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
TODAY, I WAS ASSIGNED
A "CHORE" -- CLEANING DUTY --
LIKE I'M THE PEARL.
THESE CLUMPS DON'T KNOW
HOW LUCKY THEY ARE TO HAVE ME.
ALTHOUGH, WHILE DOING "CHORE",
I DID HAPPEN UPON
A CONTAINER CONTAINING MANY...
SHIRTS.
IMAGINE -- APPEARANCE MODIFIERS
THAT AREN'T
MELDED TO YOUR BODY.
OOOH! [ CHUCKLES ]
NICE SHORTS.
AAH!
HOW --
HOW DID THESE GET HERE?
AAH!
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
LOG DATE 7-1-2-2.
TODAY MARKS THE 30th
EARTH ROTATION SINCE MY CAPTURE.
HAPPY ONE MONTH
CAN-AVERSARY!
CYLINDERS?
THEY'RE STILTS.
YOU TIE THEM ON YOUR FEET,
AND THEY MAKE YOU TALLER.
I TRIED TO
SPRUCE THEM UP A BIT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS ABOUT FLAMES,
BUT THEY JUST MAKE
EVERYTHING COOLER.
WHY ARE YOU GIVING ME THESE?
BECAUSE
I WANT YOU TO FEEL NICE.
THAT'S WHAT GIFTS ARE FOR.
YOU GIVE THEM TO YOUR FRIENDS
TO SHOW YOU CARE.
AND THEY GO, "WOW, THANKS!"
[ SCOFFS ]
AS IF I'D STOOP SO LOW
AS TO TIE YOUR EARTH TRASH
TO MY BODY.
LEAVE ME!
GO, GO, GO, GO...
GO!
AND, WOW, THANKS!
[ OWL HOOTING ]
WHY, YES, PEARL,
I DID GET TALLER.
HOW CORRECT OF YOU TO NOTICE.
OF COURSE, AMETHYST,
I WILL ACQUIRE
THOSE CHEESY CHAPS FOR YOU
OFF THAT VERY HIGH SHELF.
HYAH! WHOA.
[ LAUGHS ]
THEY EVEN FUNCTION IN REVERSE!
UGH!
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
"JOKES."
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
"WHY DID THE CHICKEN
CROSS THE ROAD?"
"THE CHICKEN WANTED TO GET
TO THE OTHER SIDE OF THE ROAD."
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT'S A CHICKEN?
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
IT SEEMS THE EARTH ONES
ARE CONSTANTLY
FILLING THE VOIDS OF THEIR LIFE
WITH MEANINGLESS DISTRACTIONS.
Paulette: ON THE LAST EPISODE
OF "CAMP PINING HEARTS"...
I DON'T CARE THAT YOU'RE ON
THE YELLOW TEAM, PERCY.
WE CAN MAKE THIS WORK!
[ Canadian accent ]
IT'S COOLOR WAR, PAULETTE.
DOESN'T THAT MEAN
ANYTHING TO YOU?
WHAT IS THIS STRANGE RITUAL?
UH, THAT'S UMM...
ARE THEY ATTEMPTING FUSION?
NO, WELL, MY DAD TOLD ME
DURING CERTAIN STAGES
IN YOUR LIFE--
HOW COULD ANYONE INDULGE
IN THIS BASELESS DRIVEL?
I'LL HAVE NO PART OF IT!
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
Peridot: HOUR 78 OF
"CAMP PINING HEARTS".
Percy: IT'S THE COOLOR WAR,
PAULETTE.
IT'S THE COOLOR WAR,
DOESN'T THAT MEAN
ANYTHING TO YOU?
UH, YOU'VE BEEN HERE
FOR A FEW DAYS.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
I'VE JUST BEEN WATCHING
YOUR PREVIOUSLY RECORDED
ENTERTAINMENT.
IS THAT THE SAME EPISODE
FROM THREE DAYS AGO?
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE?
MMM...
NAH.
OH.
YOU MADE A PICTURE.
PICTURE? THIS ISN'T JUST
A PICTURE, STEVEN!
IT'S A COMPLEX CHART
CATALOGING THE COMPATIBLE
CHARACTERISTICS BETWEEN CAMPERS.
SOMEHOW THE REJECTS AT CAMP CLOD
FAIL TO RECOGNIZE
THE SUPERIOR PAIR
THAT IS PIERRE AND PERCY.
WELL, THAT'S 'CAUSE
PAULETTE LIKES PERCY.
PAULETTE. HA!
PAULETTE HAS NO PLACE
IN THE CAMP'S HIERARCHY.
NOW PIERRE --
PIERRE IS A BRUTE!
PIERRE LAID WASTE
TO THE THREE-LEGGED RACES.
PIERRE AND PERCY PRESENT
THE STRONGEST BATTLE FORMATION.
THEY'D DESTROY THE CAMP!
YOU GOT ALL THIS
FROM ONE EPISODE?
IT'S SUBTEXT, STEVEN.
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
Peridot: WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
[ GROANS ] I REMEMBER THIS PART.
PERCY & PIERRE ARE BOTH
ON THE YELLOW TEAM --
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
AND THAT'S WHY
PERCY AND PIERRE
ARE OBJECTIVELY
THE BEST FOR EACH OTHER!
GAH!
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
Peridot:
LOG DATE 7-1-3-2.
PROGRESS ON THE CLUSTER DRILL
IS GOING OPTIMAL, SURPRISINGLY.
THOUGH I HAVE A FEW COMPLAINTS
ON THE WORK ETHIC OF --
HEY!
[ LAUGHS ]
AMETHYST, REALLY.
THIS IS NO TIME
TO BE FOOLING AROUND.
AW, COME ON, P.
I'M JUST TRYING TO
LION THE MOOD.
[ GROANS ]
DO YOU ALWAYS USE SHAPE-SHIFTING
LIKE THIS?
YOU MEAN TO BE REALLY COOL?
PRETTY MUCH.
BUT IT'S SUCH A...
Both: SIGNIFICANT USE OF ENERGY
COMPARED TO THE OUTPUT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I'VE BEEN PRACTICING
MY PERRY-PHRASING.
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE
IN MY OPINION,
BUT IT'S HARD TO BEAT
THE ORIGINAL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, CAN YOU SHIFT INTO
ANYTHING?
SURE.
GOT A REQUEST?
BOK BOK!
I'M A CHICKEN!
[ LAUGHS ]
I GET THE JOKE NOW!
HA! YES, WELL, AT LEAST
SHE ISN'T LION AROUND ANYMORE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ LAUGHS ]
Peridot: PEARL REALLY TRIES
FOR SOME REASON,
AND I CAN APPRECIATE THAT.
AMETHYST'S COMPANY IS
ENTERTAINING, AS WELL.
BUT, THE FUSED ONE...
...ELUDES ME.
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
OKAY, WE CAN ADD
MORE SUPPORT AS WE GO,
BUT FOR NOW, WE JUST HAVE TO
PICK IT UP AND PUT IT ON TOP.
NO SWEAT.
[ Deep voice ]
LET'S DO THIS!
YOU'VE GOT THE RIGHT IDEA,
BUT WE MIGHT WANT TO BE
A BIT MORE CAREFUL.
GOTCHA.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
SHALL WE?
HUH? AAH!
[ SIGHS ]
THAT LOOKS GREAT.
LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, I'M AT MY LIMIT!
EVENING, PERIDOT.
EXPLAIN IT TO ME, FUSION.
I CAN AT LEAST MAKE SENSE
OF YOUR EXISTENCE
IF IT'S FOR
A FUNCTIONAL PURPOSE.
BUT YOU?
YOU'RE NOT USING YOUR COMBINED
SIZE AND STRENGTH
TO DO ANYTHING!
I'M DOING SOMETHING.
AND WHAT'S THAT?
STARGAZING.
ICH.
YOU CAN DO THAT ALONE.
DON'T WANT TO.
HM.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU CAN SEE
HOME WORLD'S GALAXY FROM HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'RE VERY DIFFERENT.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
REALLY?
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO UNDERSTAND
FUSION, I CAN HELP YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LET'S FUSE.
OH, MY STARS!
[ THUD ]
I GET IT, YOU'RE NOT READY.
THAT'S FAIR.
ANOTHER TIME THEN.
NO!
NO-NO-NO.
JUST -- JUST GIMME A SEC!
[ MID-TEMPO DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
YEAH.
GET READY.
AAH!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
I CAN'T DO IT.
THAT'S FINE.
PERIDOT, I'M PROUD OF YOU.
WHY?!
BECAUSE YOU'VE MADE AN EFFORT
TO UNDERSTAND ME.
BUT I STILL
DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU!
WHY ARE YOU FUSED
ALL THE TIME?
I'M PERCY AND PIERRE.
OH!
[ TAPE FAST FORWARDS ]
Peridot: OKAY, GO.
Garnet: LOG DATE 7-14-2 --
[ GASPS ]
Peridot: NO, YOU SAY IT
"7, 1, 4, 2".
UGH, LOG DATE 7, 1, 4, 2.
I HAVE ATTEMPTED A FUSION
WITH THE FUSION GARNET.
I HAD HOPED TO GAIN A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF FUSION.
INSTEAD I GAINED A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF GARNET.
Garnet:
WAIT, KEEP IT ON A MOMENT.
STEVEN, YOU PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T HAVE LISTENED
TO PERIDOT'S LOGS,
BUT I KNOW YOUR CURIOSITY
COMES FROM A PLACE OF CARING.
YOU SHOULD GIVE THE RECORDER
BACK TO HER NOW.
SHE'S GOING TO WANT TO KEEP IT.
Peridot: WAIT, WHAT?
HERE, PERIDOT,
TAKE THIS BACK.
WOW. THANKS.