♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ TIMER TICKING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
[ DING! ]
YES! PERFECTLY TIMED
AFTERNOON SANDWICH COMPLETE.
WAIT, I CAN'T EAT
SUCH A PERFECT SANDWICH
ALL ON ITS OWN.
IT NEEDS A SIDE.
BUT WHAT?
OH, HEY, AMETHYST.
I MADE LUNCH.
YOU WANT TO EAT
THIS EMPTY CONTAINER?
NO, THANKS.
O-OKAY.
YOU SEEN
GARNET OR PEARL?
NOPE.
ANY IDEA
WHERE THEY MIGHT BE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMEWHERE NOT TALKING
TO EACH OTHER.
HMM.
WAIT, I KNOW
WHAT THIS MEAL NEEDS.
A BAG OF...
[ GASPS ]
ONION?!
WHAT THE...
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
ONION!
WE JUST PUT THAT SCREEN IN!
COME BACK HERE!
THOSE WERE GOING TO COMPLETE
MY PERFECT LUNCH!
IT'S A SPECIAL FLAVOR
THAT'S ONLY IN STORES
FOR A LIMITED TIME!
I KNOW HOW YOU ARE
WITH FOOD!
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
GONNA EAT THEM!
AT LEAST LET ME HAVE
JUST ONE!
THIS IS IT, ONION.
NOWHERE TO HIDE.
NOW JUST --
JUST DROP THE BAG AND --
UH...ONION?
UH...
[ GASPS ]
AMETHYST?
UH...THAT'S REALLY WEIRD!
UM, SO...I ALWAYS KNEW
ONION WAS WEIRD, BUT...
I THINK
HE'S OBSESSED WITH YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
AMETHYST?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
Woman: WHO'S IN THERE?
NOW, I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU GOT PAST THAT TARP,
BUT THIS IS
PRIVATE PROPERTY.
VIDALIA?!
AMETHYST?!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
IT'S BEEN YEARS!
MAN, YOU'VE CHANGED.
YOU LOOK TERRIBLE!
YOU LOOK THE SAME...
TERRIBLE!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WAIT, WHAT?
WHO'S SHE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW EACH OTHER?
OH, WE BOTH KIND OF
HUNG AROUND YOUR DAD,
BUT VIDALIA'S
COOLER THAN YOUR DAD,
SO WE STARTED HANGING OUT
WITHOUT HIM.
IS THAT STEVEN?
LOOK AT HIM.
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE GREG.
THAT'S GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
HE USED TO BE SUPER HOT.
[ BOTH SNICKERING ]
UH, SO DID YOU PAINT THESE
WHEN YOU USED TO HANG OUT?
YEAH, SOME OF THEM.
SOME ARE NEW, THOUGH.
AMETHYST
WAS MY FAVORITE MODEL.
CAN YOU STILL
TURN INTO ANYTHING?
[ CHUCKLES ]
ANYTHING BUT RESPECTABLE.
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, MAN, WE USED TO GET INTO
ALL SORTS OF TROUBLE.
NOW TELL ME, STEVEN,
AREN'T WE JUST
THE SPITTING IMAGE OF MISCHIEF?
[ SCOFFS ] HARDLY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE WEARING SLIPPERS.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT I'VE DONE
IN THESE SHOES.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
IT'S GREAT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
SORRY
IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
I GUESS
WE'VE BOTH BEEN BUSY.
OH, YEAH.
I GET IT -- KIDS.
WHAT ABOUT KIDS?
OH, HERE'S ONE NOW.
YOU'RE ONION'S MOM?!
[ LAUGHS ] YEP.
HE'S MY LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER.
AND, STEVEN,
HE LOVES TALKING ABOUT YOU.
[ MUMBLES ]
OH, THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA!
STEVEN, AMETHYST,
ONION WANTS TO KNOW
IF YOU'D LIKE TO
STAY FOR DINNER.
UM [CHUCKLES]
WE'D LOVE TO. [ CHUCKLES ]
RIGHT, STEVEN? ONION'S, LIKE,
YOUR BEST FRIEND.
NOW, TELL ME WHAT YOU DID
IN THOSE SHOES, GIRL.
MM, I CAN'T EAT
ANOTHER BITE OF
[CHUCKLES]
WHATEVER THAT WAS.
OH, IT'S JUST
A LITTLE DISH
I LIKE TO CALL
NOODLES AND BUTTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LONG IT'S BEEN.
I MEAN,
CHECK THIS GUY OUT.
I USED TO BE
BIGGER THAN HIM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
DO YOU EVER HEAR FROM
OLD FARTY MARTY?
HM? [ LAUGHS ]
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THAT FOOL IS.
DON'T CARE, EITHER.
IT'S JUST BEEN ME
AND YELLOWTAIL FOR A WHILE NOW.
WHAT?!
YELLOWTAIL?
YEAH, THINGS JUST
KIND OF HAPPENED.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
I'M LIVING WITH A FISHERMAN.
[ LAUGHS ] YOU SHOULD SEE
YOUR FACE RIGHT NOW.
HEY, SOUR CREAM.
I JUST DIDN'T EXPECT
ANY OF THIS.
WELL, THAT'S JUST
HOW IT IS NOW.
SO WHERE'S
OLD FISH TAIL AT?
UH, IT'S YELLOWTAIL.
HE SPENDS A LOT OF TIME
OUT AT SEA.
HEY, IT'S ME.
DUDE, YOU USED TO
COMPLAIN SO MUCH
ABOUT THE SMELL
AT THE DOCKS.
IT USED TO BE
SO GROSS OVER THERE.
NOW THERE ARE ALL THESE FANCY
BOATS HANGING AROUND.
REMEMBER WHEN WE SNUCK ON TO
THE MAYOR'S BOAT AND TRASHED IT?
WHY DO YOU HATE FOOD?
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
AMETHYST?
HUH?
YOU HAVEN'T SAID A WORD
ABOUT YOURSELF ALL NIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
MY LIFE IS BORING.
ALL RIGHT,
HOW ARE THE GEMS?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE BORING, TOO.
OKAY, THANKS FOR DINNER.
TIME TO GO, RIGHT, AMETHYST?
WHAT'S THE HURRY?
WE GOT NOTHING TO DO.
'SIDES, AN AMETHYST/VIDALIA
PARTY DON'T END
TILL THE SUN COME UP.
Onion: MA-MA.
WHAT'S THAT?
[ MUMBLING ]
OH, THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA!
STEVEN, ONION WANTS TO
SHOW YOU AROUND THE HOUSE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
CAN ONION TOTE YOU AROUND?
[ TECHNO MUSIC PLAYS ]
UH...
W-WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, WHENEVER SOUR CREAM
STARTS DEEJAYING,
IT USES ALL THE ELECTRICITY
IN THE HOUSE.
GOOD THING
YELLOWTAIL'S NOT HERE --
IT DRIVES HIM NUTS.
DUDE,
YOUR HOUSE IS JACKED.
WHAT CAN YOU DO?
KIDS GOT TO EXPRESS THEMSELVES.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU TOO, ONION.
VERY EXPRESSIVE.
LOOKS LIKE HE'S READY
FOR YOU, STEVEN.
UH...
COOL SHOPPING CART.
[ GASPS ]
WHY DON'T YOU JUST JUMP UP
AND DOWN ON THAT TRAMPOLINE?
I MEAN, IT'S, LIKE,
RIGHT THERE.
BUT IT'S YOUR ROOM...
[ SQUEAKING ]
...SO DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
[ GASPS ]
YOU HAVE A LITTLE
MOUSY ROOMMATE FRIEND!
AWW!
OH.
[ SQUEAKING ]
IS THAT YOUR PET?
OH, THAT MUST BE
WHERE HE LIVES, RIGHT?
LET ME HELP YOU
PUT HIM IN HIS HOME.
THIS IS A PRETTY LARGE CONTAINER
FOR A LITTLE BABY --
SNAKE!
ONION, YOU WANT ME
TO FEED OUR LITTLE FRIEND
TO THIS SNAKE, HUH?
OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
OH.
SORRY,
BUT WE ALL GOT TO EAT.
[ SQUEAKING ]
I...
CAN'T!
UGH!
JUST TAKE HIM FROM ME!
I-I'LL BE OVER HERE.
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ CAGE DOOR SHUTS ]
UH...
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY MORE WEIRD
PETS TO SHOW ME, DO YOU?
YOU GONNA
PUT ON A MOVIE?
THAT'D BE NICE --
AND NOT CREEPY AT ALL.
COOL HOSPITAL SETTING.
Vidalia: OKAY, I'M READY.
HEY, THAT'S YOUR MOM.
I'M READY!
WHAT'S
SHE GETTING READY FOR?
OH.
OH, YELLOWTAIL, I THINK...
OH, IT'S HAPPENING!
UGH, WAIT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
HERE HE COMES!
HUH?
"HAPPY BIRTHDAY ONION."
IS THIS YOU
BEING BORN?!
OH, I AM NEVER
DOING THIS --
AAH!
I CAN'T TAKE
MUCH MORE OF THIS.
WHERE?
OKAY, I'M OUT.
CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
NEED TO GO HOME.
AMETHYST, I'M SORRY,
BUT IT'S TIME TO --
EVEN GARNET, LIKE, I'VE NEVER
SEEN GARNET THIS UPSET.
IT'S AWFUL AT HOME.
I FEEL TRAPPED.
THAT'S CRAZY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN, THOUGH.
YOU DO?
HEY, WE DON'T ALWAYS GET ALONG
IN THIS FAMILY.
YELLOWTAIL AND SOUR CREAM ARE
ALWAYS AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS.
IT MAKES ME NUTS.
ACTUALLY,
WHEN I GET LIKE THAT,
I THINK ABOUT YOU
AND HOW YOU COULD
ALWAYS JUST ROLL WITH IT.
WHAT?!
NO! THAT WAS YOU!
YOU WERE SO...COOL.
I WAS JUST LIKE...A DUMB SPONGE
FOLLOWING YOU AROUND.
BUT YOU WERE DOWN FOR ANYTHING,
NOT AFRAID OF ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
I WANTED TO BE LIKE YOU?
UGH.
I STILL THINK ABOUT IT.
TO BE HONEST, THAT'S WHY
I STARTED PAINTING YOU AGAIN.
I'M -- I'M INSPIRED BY YOU,
AMETHYST.
OH, LOOKS LIKE
I'M GONNA NEED MORE TEA.
YOU WANT TO EAT THIS BAG?
YEAH, MY FAVORITE.
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
GOOD THING THE KIDS
ARE KEEPING THEMSELVES BUSY.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, ONION, LET'S DO THIS.
WHATEVER WEIRD OR HORRIBLE THING
YOU HAVE PLANNED FOR ME,
I CAN TAKE IT.
HEY, SLOW DOWN.
OH, BOY.
THIS IS GONNA BE BAD.
UH, UH, ONION,
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT'S THIS ROOM?
[ GRUNTS ] OH!
WHAT'S IN THERE?
SOMETHING HORRIBLE?
[ GASPS ]
ONION!
IT'S FULL OF GUYS!
WOW!
I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS RED VARIANT
OF NINJA GUY BEFORE.
YOU HAVE GALS, TOO?!
HARD HAT GAL!
TRIANGLE GAL!
ORANGE GAL!
KAREN!
KAREN...
HOW'D YOU GET A HOLD OF --
NO, DON'T TELL ME.
HMM?
NO WAY!
IT'S EXPLORER GAL!
SHE'S SO COOL-LOOKING!
THANKS FOR SHOWING HER
TO ME --
YOU -- YOU SHOULD
TAKE YOUR EXPLORER GAL BACK.
ARE YOU GIVING THIS
TO ME?
[ GASPS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
ONION!
AW, MAN! WHAT OTHER
GALS AND GUYS YOU GOT?!
HA, COOL --
INVISIBLE GUY.
AND STAY OUT. [ LAUGHS ]
UM, THANKS FOR DINNER --
AND FOR LISTENING.
WELL, THANKS
FOR BREAKING INTO MY HOUSE.
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT OTHER STUFF.
IT'S GONNA BLOW OVER.
YOU'RE A ROCK.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE, RIGHT?
UH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WELL, WHATEVER YOU ARE,
DON'T BE A STRANGER.
YEAH, I CAN STOP BY ANYTIME
IF YOU NEED INSPIRATION.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OR IF YOU WANT,
YOU COULD COME OVER
TO THE TEMPLE SOMETIME, TOO.
YOU COULD EVEN BRING ONION
FOR STEVEN TO HANG WITH.
OH, WELL,
THAT SOUNDS GREAT TO US.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, STEVEN?
YOU READY FOR ANOTHER ROUND
WITH THIS GUY?
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ Chuckling ]
YEAH, WE'LL SEE.
♪ YOU ♪
♪ ARE LIKE YOU ♪
♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN.
Jamie: STEVEN.
JAMIE.
SAFE.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
WE HAVE FUN.
SO, YOU GOT THE GOODS?
OH, I'VE GOT GOODER
THAN THE GOODS.
BUM-DA-DA-DUM-DUM
DUM-DA!
WHA--? A PLAY!
I'M HOLDING AUDITIONS
TONIGHT.
IT'S A LOCAL PRODUCTION
DRIFTING THROUGH SPACE,
LOOKING FOR STARS.
[ Bad Italian accent ]
IF YOU NEED A GREAT ACTOR,
YOU COME TO THE RIGHT GUY.
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ Normal voice ]
AN ACCENT.
FROM WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
ACTING.
JAMIE, JAMIE, JAMIE.
WHERE'S EVERYONE ELSE?
UH, YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT SHOWED UP.
BUT, HEY, SOME PLAYS ONLY HAVE
ONE PERSON IN THEM,
SO WE'RE ALREADY IN
200% BETTER SHAPE THAN THAT.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
SOME STRANGE MATH...
BUT I'M READY.
GREAT.
HERE'S A COPY
OF THE SCRIPT.
"BEACH CITY OR BUST:
THE TALE OF WILLIAM DEWEY."
THIS IS MY FIRST PRODUCTION,
SO IT NEEDS TO BE EXCITING.
IT NEEDS TO BE CLASSIC.
IT NEEDS TO BE FULLY FUNDED
BY MAYOR DEWEY.
AND IT IS...
BECAUSE HE WROTE IT.
WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
I'M GLAD YOU ASKED.
THIS IS THE STORY
OF HOW BEACH CITY
WAS FOUNDED
NEARLY 200 YEARS AGO
BY MY GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-GREAT
GRANDFATHER,
WILLIAM DEWEY.
IT'S A TRULY IMPORTANT
HISTORICAL TALE
WITH A LOT OF SENTIMENTAL AND
POLITICAL IMPORTANCE TO ME.
WELL, WE'RE JUST ABOUT
TO GET STARTED.
UH, WOULD YOU LIKE TO SIT IN
ON THE REHEARSAL, MAYOR?
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
OH, PARDON ME.
OKAY, STEVEN.
SINCE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO SHOWED UP,
YOU'LL BE PLAYING THE LEAD ROLE
OF WILLIAM DEWEY.
NAILED THE AUDITION.
AND FOR THE OTHER ROLES,
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO PLAY...
ALL OF THEM.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THE SHIP IS OUT AT SEA.
THE SUN BEATS DOWN ON THE CREW
WHILE THEY STAND ON DECK.
SUDDENLY, THE TALL,
RUGGEDLY HANDSOME MAN
STANDING IN FRONT OF THEM
SPEAKS...
"CREW, I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD BE
PART OF THIS JOURNEY WITH ME
AS WE SEARCH FOR A NEW LAND
TO BUILD A DISTINGUISHED
NEW CITY IN.
"OH, CAPTAIN WILLIAM DEWEY,
YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD CAPTAIN.
NEVER HAS A VOYAGE BEEN
SO SUPER GOOD."
"GOOD POINT,
FIRST MATE BUDDY."
[ IMITATES ALL LAUGHING ]
FOR FUN.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
OH, NO.
IS THAT A WILD SQUALL
APPROACHING US?
SURELY THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
"BE CALM, MY CREW."
I'LL JUST SAVE US WITH MY
HEROIC, SUPERNATURAL ABILITY."
AND THEN WILLIAM DEWEY
GROWS INTO A 50-FOOT GIANT
AND CARRIES THE BOAT
SAFELY TO SHORE.
THE CREW THINKS HE'S SO GOOD
AT BEING CAPTAIN
THAT THEY ELECTED HIM TO BE
THE FIRST MAYOR OF BEACH CITY.
THE END.
WOW, MAYOR DEWEY.
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
[ CHUCKLES ] YEAH.
WILLIAM DEWEY
IS A REALLY, UH,
GOOD CHARACTER...
BUT MAYBE WE COULD BRING OUT
ANOTHER SIDE OF WILLIAM DEWEY?
SEE HIS STRUGGLES?
THE GREAT WILLIAM DEWEY
DIDN'T STRUGGLE.
HE WAS GOOD AT EVERYTHING
ON THE FIRST TRY --
JUST LIKE ME
WHEN I WROTE THIS PLAY.
NOT A SINGLE WORD
NEEDS TO BE CHANGED.
BUT MAYBE --
[ SCOFFS ]
DON'T FORGET
WHO'S FUNDING THIS.
WELL, NICE HUSTLE,
GENTLEMEN.
KEEP IT UP.
AYE, AYE.
THIS IS GONNA BE
A DISASTER.
WHAT?
IT'S A TERRIBLE STORY.
WILLIAM DEWEY
IS TOTALLY UNBELIEVABLE.
'CAUSE HE GROWS
50 FEET?
NO,
HE'S GOT NO CHARACTER.
BUT THE SCRIPT KEPT SAYING
HE WAS REALLY GOOD.
EXACTLY.
HOW CAN A GUY
HAVE NO FAULTS?
TO BE HUMAN
IS TO BE FLAWED.
A REAL HERO
MUST STRUGGLE.
THAT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
AND, ALSO,
TOTALLY NOT REPRESENTED
IN MAYOR DEWEY'S SCRIPT.
[ SIGHS ]
MY FIRST PLAY --
AND PROBABLY MY LAST.
HEY, PEARL.
PEARL?
STEVEN, YOU'RE BACK.
YEAH.
SHOW BUSINESS IS ROUGH.
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
NOT UNLESS YOU CAN MAKE
WILLIAM DEWEY INTERESTING.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
WILLIAM DEWEY?
I'M GONNA BE HIM
IN THIS PLAY.
BUT HE'S TOTALLY BORING.
HE'S PERFECT,
AND HE NEVER MAKES MISTAKES.
[ SIGHS ] WISH I COULD SAY
THE SAME FOR MYSELF.
YEAH,
BUT NOBODY'S LIKE THAT.
EVERYBODY
GETS STUFF WRONG.
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO KEEP GOING,
AND IT'S HARD,
WHICH IS WHY IT'S GREAT
WHEN YOU NEVER STOP TRYING.
WHEN DID YOU
GET SO SMART?
HMM.
THIS ISN'T JUST BORING.
IT'S HISTORICALLY
INACCURATE.
WHO WROTE THIS?
MAYOR DEWEY.
[ LAUGHS ]
HE WASN'T EVEN THERE.
BUT I WAS.
YOU WERE THERE?
WAIT,
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED?
WELL, FOR STARTERS,
"RUGGEDLY HANDSOME"
SEEMS RATHER GENEROUS.
STEVEN...
THIS IS SO REAL.
IT'S LIKE IT WAS WRITTEN
BY SOMEONE WHO LIVED IT.
IT WAS.
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU CAN TELL,
BUT I WROTE THE JOKES.
I CAN TELL.
IT'S SO GRITTY,
SO PASSIONATE, SO...
HISTORICALLY ACCURATE?
AND THE DRAMA?
THIS IS THE PLAY
WE SHOULD BE DOING.
LET'S DO IT THEN.
LET'S PUT ON THIS VERSION
OF THE PLAY.
BUT HOW?
WE'D NEED NEW COSTUMES,
NEW PROPS --
WE HAVE NO TIME.
AND MAYOR DEWEY
WILL HAVE OUR HEADS.
BUT JAMIE,
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF --
"A REAL HERO STRUGGLES."
BY JIMINY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS SHOW WILL GO ON
TOMORROW NIGHT
WITH YOU
AS CAPTAIN WILLIAM DEWEY
AND I AS
THE REMAINING ROLES.
ALL OF THEM?
[ INHALES ]
ALL OF THEM.
Both: [ HISSES ]
BOOM, AHH,
ACTING.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
MIND IF I HAVE A SEAT?
OKAY...
OH, YOU KNOW,
I WROTE THIS PLAY.
I HOPE MAYOR DEWEY
ISN'T MAD ABOUT THE CHANGES
GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO SEE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
OF COURSE.
THIS COULD EITHER
MAKE OR BREAK MY CAREER.
YOU COULD LOSE YOUR JOB
AT THE POST OFFICE?
THIS COULD EITHER
MAKE OR BREAK MY HOBBY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
ACTING.
Jamie:
BOARDIES AND GENTLEBOARDIES,
TONIGHT, I AM THRILLED
TO PRESENT TO YOU...
"THE TALE OF WILLIAM DEWEY."
Man: YEAH --
BEACH CITY RULES.
Woman: SHH.
OH, CAPTAIN, MY CAPTAIN,
HOW LONG UNTIL THE SOFT LIPS
OF OUR SAILING SHIP
KISS THE RUGGED BEARD
OF NEW LANDS?
I KNOW WE'VE BEEN JOURNEYING
FOR MANY MONTHS,
BUT SURELY WE'LL RUN
INTO SOMETHING SOON.
THE OCEAN
CAN'T BE THAT BIG.
Pearl: [ LAUGHS ]
THERE HE IS.
HI, STEVEN.
YOU'RE SO TALENTED.
[ GIGGLES ]
BACK HOME THEY CALLED ME
"DEWEY THE DUNCE,"
SAID I COULDN'T FIND LAND
EVEN IF I WAS STANDING ON IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT THE...
AND I'M STARTING TO FEAR
THAT THEY WERE RIGHT.
WHAT LIGHT THROUGH
YON STAGE LEFT BREAKS?
OH, WHAT NOW?
Jamie: IT IS THE EAST,
AND WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
WHAT?
THIS WASN'T IN THE SCRIPT.
THIS WASN'T IN THE BUDGET,
EITHER.
GREETINGS. I AM PEARL.
AND I COME TO YOU
AS A MESSENGER
OF THE BRILLIANT,
ROSE QUARTZ.
WE ASK THAT YOU
TURN YOUR SHIP AROUND.
THE LAND
YOU ARE HEADED FOR
IS NO WALK IN THE PARK
FOR YOUR SPECIES.
NONSENSE.
I WON'T TAKE ORDERS
FROM THE LIKES OF YOU.
[ SCOFFS ]
WELL, THEN...
YOU SHOULD TURN AROUND
LEST YOU FALL INTO THE SEA.
AND YOU KNOW,
HUMANS AREN'T
VERY GOOD SWIMMERS.
THEY AIN'T.
I'LL JUST RETURN HOME
LIKE THE FAILURE DUNCE
I AM.
UGH. I CAN'T EVEN
TURN A SAIL RIGHT.
WHY MUST I ALWAYS STRUGGLE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
WOW, DAD,
WHAT A LOSER.
OH, CAPTAIN, MY CAPTAIN,
WE'VE DRIFTED MILES
FROM OUR COURSE.
THESE WAVES ARE NOTHING LIKE
I'VE EVER SEEN BEFORE.
NONSENSE.
THIS IS ONLY A DRIZZLE.
OKAY, MAYBE
A LIGHT SUMMER STORM.
[ MONSTER ROARS ]
WHAT'S THAT PORTSIDE?
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
LEVER.
OH.
[ AUDIENCE MURMURS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
CAPTAIN, IT'S GOT ME.
FIRST MATE BUDDY.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T GIVE UP YOUR SEARCH.
YOU'RE THE BRAVEST MAN I KNOW,
BECAUSE YOU TRY,
EVEN THOUGH
YOU FAIL SO, SO MUCH.
BUDDY, NOOOO!
[ SOBBING ]
OH, BUDDY,
A STALE BISCUIT TO THE END.
[ GASPS ]
[ ROARING ]
AND NOW MY BOAT
WILL SINK INTO THE DEPTHS.
DEWEY THE DISASTROUS DUNCE.
WHAT'S THIS?
HOLY ANCHOVIES.
THE QUADRUPLE NOOGIE.
A MOVE THAT'S ONLY BEEN
SPOKEN OF IN LEGENDS.
AH.
IT HEADS THIS WAY.
OH, PLEASE, GODDESS OF NOOGIES,
DON'T HURT ME.
WHOA. I'VE MADE IT!
LAND!
SWEET, SOLID LAND!
[ KISSING ] UGH.
THANK YOU, GIANT WOMAN.
Jamie: YOU MAY NOT WANT TO STAY,
THIS LAND IS DANGEROUS.
NO, I WILL STAY.
FOR I AM WILLIAM DEWEY,
AND I DON'T GIVE UP
IN THE FACE OF FAILURE.
[ Bad Italian accent ]
THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME GREAT.
Jamie: VERY WELL THEN.
BUT I CAN'T PROMISE YOU
I WON'T INTERFERE AGAIN.
[ Normal voice ]
I SHALL NAME THIS NEW LAND
IN HONOR OF MY DEAD
FIRST MATE, BUDDY.
I'M ALIVE.
OKAY,
BEACH CITY IT IS.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHAT?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
CONTINUE ]
NICE TO KNOW GREAT GRANDPA
WAS A REAL PERSON WITH FLAWS.
GUTSY MOVE DAD.
All: MAYOR DEWEY!
MAYOR DEWEY! MAYOR --
ONE FOR YOU,
AND ONE FOR YOU...
EXCUSE ME.
IF I COULD HAVE A MOMENT
WITH THE TALENT.
OH.
JAMIE.
[ LAUGHS ] OH, YEAH.
FANTASTIC WORK.
I LOVED THE MESSAGE.
"VOTE MAYOR DEWEY."
HOW ABOUT I OFFER
YOU ANOTHER ROLE --
LEAD DIRECTOR OF BEACH CITY
COMMUNITY THEATER.
YOU COULD PUT ON
MORE PLAYS --
AS LONG AS THE BUDGET
ALLOWS IT.
[ STAMMERING ]
UH, THANK YOU, SIR.
A LOT OF THE CREDIT
SHOULD GO TO PEARL.
YOU COULD SAY SHE WAS
AN "INSIDE SOURCE."
I AM A GEM
OF MANY TALENTS --
A DEDICATION TO FACT
IS JUST ONE OF THEM.
THANK YOU FOR PRESERVING
MY LEGACY.
OH, WHAT'S 200 YEARS
BETWEEN FRIENDS.
WELL...
I MUST BE OFF THEN
TO BASK IN THE ADULATION
OF MY CONSTITUENTS.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T REMEMBER
THERE BEING A CAMPAIGN SLOGAN
AT THE END OF THAT STORY.
ART DOESN'T ALWAYS
NEED A REASON, PEARL.
SOMETIMES IT'S JUST GOTTA
MAKE THE AUDIENCE HAPPY.
THAT'S WHY YOU ALWAYS
END ON A JOKE.
♪ YOU ♪
♪ ARE LIKE YOU ♪