>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHERE ARE YOU?
[ CLICKS TONGUE ]
YOU'RE A MESS, STEVEN.
>> Pearl: I KNOW I HAD EIGHT.
HEY, STEVEN, HAVE YOU SEEN A GEM
SHARD ANYWHERE?
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
>> Steven: NO.
HAVE YOU SEEN MY PANTS?
THEY'RE ALSO VERY IMPORTANT.
>> Pearl: I'M SERIOUS, STEVEN.
THESE SHARDS HAVE A POWERFUL
PARTIAL CONSCIOUSNESS THAT HAS
BEEN HARNESSED BY GEMS
THROUGHOUT HISTORY IN ORDER TOP
CREATE...
>> Steven: [ Thinking ] THEY
WEREN'T IN THE KITCHEN, EITHER.
UNDER THE BED!
NO, WAIT.
I LOOKED THERE, TOO.
AND THEN PEARL WALKED IN...
[ GASPS ]
PEARL!
>> Pearl: ...WANED AS THE
SHARDS...
>> Steven: OH, GEEZ.
SHE'S REALLY EXPLAINING
SOMETHING.
[ SIGHS ] I CAN'T JUST START
LISTENING NOW.
I'D BE LOST.
JUST LIKE MY PANTS.
>> Pearl: ...COULD BECOME A
MONSTER.
THAT'S WHY IT'S VERY, VERY
IMPORTANT THAT IT'S KEPT AWAY
FROM ANY KIND OF GARMENT.
IF YOU SEE IT, BRING IT TO ME
RIGHT AWAY.
I'M GOING TO CHECK IN TOWN.
>> Steven: FOR MY PANTS?!
I GUESS I'LL KEEP LOOKING HERE.
THAT'S UNUSUAL!
[ PANTING ]
COME ON! WE USED TO BE FRIENDS!
WE USED TO GO EVERYWHERE
TOGETHER!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOO!
GOT YOU NOW, PANTS!
[ GRUNTING ]
HYAH!
I WEAR THE PANTS IN THIS
RELATIONSHIP.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
HMM?
OH!
IT'S A...THINGY.
IS THIS PEARL'S SHARD THINGY?
WHOA!
HA!
NOW WHO'S SMART?
OW! OW! OW! OW! OW!
STOP!
OH.
THANKS.
I GOT TO GET YOU TO PEARL.
HEY, PEARL!
PEARL!
SHE MUST STILL BE LOOKING FOR MY
PANTS.
>> AAH! PLEASE HELP ME!
AAH! NO! GET THEM AWAY!
>> Steven: AAAAAAH!
[ SEAGULLS SQUAWKING ]
AAAAAAH!
>> I'M NOT FRIES!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> AH, WHERE'S YOUR FACE, FRYBO?
BEING PART OF THE FRYMAN FAMILY
MEANS YOU GOT TO SELL FRIES.
AND BE MY SON, WHICH YOU ARE.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> SO, YOU'RE ALREADY HALFWAY
THERE.
KEEP AT IT, FRYBO.
>> I'M PETE...Y.
>> Steven: HI, PETEY!
>> WHEN I TOLD MY DAD I WANTED
TO BE PART OF THE FRYMAN FAMILY
BUSINESS, I DIDN'T THINK IT
MEANT BEING STUCK IN A SWEATY
OLD COSTUME.
THINGS USED TO BE DIFFERENT,
STEVEN.
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT BACK THEN
EXCEPT MAKING MYSELF DIZZY ON
THE OLD SEAHORSE RIDE AT
FUNLAND.
>> Steven: OH, FRYBO, YOU'RE
HILARIOUS.
>> [ SIGHS ]
I WISH THERE WAS A WAY FOR THIS
COSTUME TO DO ITS JOB WITHOUT ME
IN IT.
>> Steven: MAYBE IT CAN, PETEY.
MAYBE IT CAN.
[ VOCALIZING ]
AAH! AAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAH!
[ SEAGULLS SQUAWKING ]
WAIT! I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA.
MNH! MNH!
SHOO, SHOO!
WAH!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ BOING! ]
>> WHOA.
>> Steven: STOP!
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
GET UP!
>> Steven: DO A LITTLE DANCE.
>> Both: UGH!
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> WHOA! ALL RIGHT!
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TI--
I MEAN, GOOD JOB, BUDDY!
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
FRYBO.
[ CHUCKLES ]
KEEP IT UP!
>> EEE!
I'M FREE!
YOU GOT THE JOB, FRYBO!
LET'S SHAKE ON IT.
BR-BR-BR-BR-BR-BR-BR-BR-BR-BR!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
HE'S GOT JOKES!
>> OKAY. NO MORE SHAKING.
PUT ME DOWN!
UNH!
JUST GO MAKE PEOPLE EAT FRIES.
HA HA HA!
LET'S GO BE KIDS!
[ COIN CLATTERS ]
[ MOTOR WHIRRING ]
[ RATTLING ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ]
THIS SEAHORSE USED TO MAKE ME SO
HAPPY.
NOW IT'S JUST GIVING ME
WHIPLASH.
[ WHIRRING STOPS ]
[ BUZZER ]
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S JUST NO
POINT TO IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> Steven: I-I-I JUST FEEL
TINGL-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y!
>> [ SIGHS ]
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND WHEN YOU HAVE
A JOB.
>> Steven: I DO HAVE A JOB.
I PROTECT HUMANITY FROM MAGIC
AND MONSTERS AND STUFF.
>> I MEAN A REAL JOB THAT YOU
GET PAID FOR.
>> Steven: I'M PAID IN THE
SMILES ACROSS THE TOWN'S FACES.
>> I DON'T SEE ANYONE SMILING.
YOU PICK UP A JOB TO BUY A HOUSE
OR RAISE KIDS OR TO...
IMPRESS YOUR DAD.
YOU WORK AWAY YOUR LIFE, AND
WHAT DOES IT GET YOU?
>> Steven: SMILES AND FACES?
>> NO.
YOU GET CASH -- CASH THAT CAN'T
BUY BACK WHAT THE JOB TAKES...
NOT IF YOU RODE EVERY SEAHORSE
IN THE WORLD.
[ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: WHOA.
WANT TO TRY THE JELLYFISH?
>> AAAAAH!
>> THAT CAME FROM THE FRY SHOP!
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
>> WHOA!
>> WE DIDN'T TELL HIM TO DO
THAT!
DID WE TELL HIM TO DO THAT?!
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ TENTACLES WHIPPING ]
>> PLEASE!
NO MORE FRIES!
[ GAGS ]
>> Steven: FRYBO, STOP!
>> AAH!
>> [ COUGHS ]
I DON'T EVEN LIKE FRIES!
>> WHY ISN'T HE LISTENING?!
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW!
>> PETEY!
WHERE'S ALL THIS COMING FROM?
AW, I GET IT.
I PUSHED YOU TOO HARD.
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO BE AS
GOOD A FRYMAN AS YOU COULD BE.
YOU'RE A TOUGH KID FOR PUTTING
UP WITH IT AS LONG AS YOU DID.
THE TRUTH IS, YOU'RE A VALUED
MEMBER OF FRYMAN BROTHERS,
INCORPORATED, AND ALL ITS
AFFILIATES!
OOH! ARGH!
[ CHOKES ]
>> D-A-A-AD!
>> Steven: NO!
HE'LL MASH YOUR POTATOES!
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?!
>> Steven: MY JOB!
>> WHOA!
OHH!
[ TENTACLES WHIPPING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
DID YOU PUT MY MISSING SHARD IN
THAT FRY COSTUME?
>> Steven: YES!
>> Pearl: DIDN'T YOU HEAR WHAT I
SAID ABOUT THE LIVING ARMOR AND
INFANTRIES AND MANY, MANY
DEATHS?!
>> Steven: NO!
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN...
>> [ SQUEALS ]
>> Pearl: [ GROANS ]
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: UGH! THE KETCHUP!
IT'S EVERYWHERE.
I CAN'T SEE.
>> Steven: SHARDS.
NEED!
>> Pearl: WHA...?
STEVEN?
>> [ Crying ] DAD!
AAH!
GO AWAY!
>> PETEY?
>> YOU ARE AWFUL!
I HATE YOU!
I'VE ALWAYS HATED YOU!
>> WAIT.
YOU'VE ALWAYS HATED FRYBO?
>> Both: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: WHERE?
>> Steven: YOUR MOVE...FRYBO.
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> Steven: ATTACK!
>> [ SCREAMING ]
>> Steven: I DIDN'T WANT TO DO
THIS, BUT YOU LEAVE ME NO
CHOICE.
UNDERWEAR -- GO!
>> [ SCREECHING ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
>> FINE.
>> Steven: I'M OKAY.
AS SOON AS I BARED MY BUTT, I
KNEW HE'D CRACK.
[ DRUMMING ]
[ CREAK ]
>> YOU WERE GREAT, FRYBO.
KIDS TODAY JUST DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
AND NOW...
THEY NEVER WILL.
>> Pearl: WEREN'T PEOPLE SCARED
OF IT BEFORE HE ATTACKED THEM?
>> Steven: Shh!
>> IT'S TIME...
TO SEND HIM OFF.
[ SIGHS ]
AS GREASY IN DEATH AS HE WAS IN
LIFE.
>> DAD, UM...
I'LL...
ARE YOU GOING TO GET ANOTHER
COSTUME?
>> NO, I DON'T NEED ANOTHER
FRYBO.
I'VE GOT THE FRYMAN.
[ TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: PEARL, I THINK OUR
WORK HERE IS DONE.
>> Pearl: PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON,
STEVEN.
>> ALMOST DONE.
STEVEN, GET THE HUBCAPS.
>> Steven: HUBBIN' IT UP!
>> HUB IT GOOD.
THIS IS A HIGH-PROFILE JOB.
>> Steven: YOU MEAN 'CAUSE IT'S
THE MAYOR'S ELECTION-MOBILE?
>> IF WE DO THIS RIGHT, WE MIGHT
GET POLITICAL FAVORS.
>> Steven: I'M NOT SURE WHAT
THAT IS, BUT I LIKE IT.
>> AH!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> HEY, HEY, HEY!
I'M NOT PAYING FOR FATHER-SON
BONDING HERE.
[ GRUNTS ]
UNIVERSE, CONTROL THAT KID.
>> STEVEN!
I'M SORRY, MAYOR DEWEY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH, THIS ONE'S ON THE HOUSE.
>> ON THE HOUSE, EH?
I LIKE THE WAY YOU DO BUSINESS,
UNIVERSE.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> MAYOR DEWEY!
MAYOR DEWEY!
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: POLITICAL FAVORS.
>> AH, YOU RASCAL.
ENOUGH WITH THE HOSE FIGHTS.
>> Steven: OH, OKAY.
>> WHAT THE...
>> Both: WHOA!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
>> WHAT IS WITH THIS CAT?
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
GOT YOU GUYS.
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> UH, PRETTY COOL, AMETHYST.
>> Steven: REALLY COOL!
I WISH I COULD SHAPESHIFT LIKE
YOU.
>> Amethyst: YOU COULD PROBABLY
LEARN.
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> Amethyst: SURE.
YOU GOT A GEM.
>> WHOA! MAGIC STUFF.
SHOULD I GET OUT OF HERE?
IS THERE GONNA BE AN EXPLOSION?
>> Steven: AH, IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
DAD.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, IT'S FUN.
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: HEY, PEARL.
[ BARKS ]
>> Steven: DO MORE.
>> Amethyst: CHECK IT OUT.
[ HOWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SQUAWKS ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, YOU'RE
OVERDOING IT.
>> Amethyst: UH, CHILL IT, DUDE.
>> Pearl: JUST BECAUSE YOU CAN
SHAPESHIFT DOESN'T MEAN YOU
SHOULD.
>> Steven: CAN YOU SHAPESHIFT?
>> Pearl: [ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, OF COURSE --
>> Amethyst: WELL, OF COURSE I
CAN.
I'M PERFECT.
WHOMP! WHOMP! [ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: ALL GEMS HAVE
SHAPESHIFT POWERS, STEVEN.
WE CAN TURN INTO OBJECTS, WE CAN
CHANGE PARTS OF OUR BODIES, OR
WE COULD DO THAT.
>> Amethyst: WHOMP! WHOMP!
>> Steven: I WANT TO TRY IT ALL.
>> Pearl: DON'T BITE OFF MORE
THAN YOU CAN CHEW, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: WHOMP! WHOMP!
>> Pearl: UGH!
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT, SHOW ME
HOW TO CHANGE INTO A HUGE LION.
>> Amethyst: ACTUALLY, FOR ONCE,
PEARL IS RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS, YOU GOT
TO START WITH SOMETHING EASY.
>> Steven: LIKE THAT CAT YOU
TURNED INTO?
>> Amethyst: THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
NOW, FOLLOW MY LEAD.
FIRST -- THINK OF WHAT YOU WANT
TO BE, AND THEN JUST SHAKE IT
OUT.
SEE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
NOW YOUR TURN.
>> Steven: OKAY.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
CA-A-T.
>> Amethyst: NAH, YOU'RE TOO
TENSE.
JUST RELAX AND FEEL IT.
MMM. BIORHYTHMS, YO.
>> Steven: FE-E-E-EL I-I-T.
>> Amethyst: UH, IF YOU'RE NOT
READY, WE CAN TRY LATER.
>> Steven: NO WAY. I CAN DO IT.
[ SIGHS ]
YEAH. YEAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: WELL, IT WAS A GOOD
TRY.
[ CAT MEOWING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: THIS IS SO COOL!
>> Amethyst: YOU SHOULD GO SHOW
YOUR DAD.
HE'S GONNA FREAK OUT!
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> Steven: DAD, I'M BACK.
>> HEY, STU-BALL.
>> Steven: CHECK IT OUT.
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> Steven: I SHAPESHIFTED MY
FINGER INTO A CAT.
>> WHOA!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
IS -- IS THAT A THING YOU CAN DO
NOW?
THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
>> Steven: I KNOW. RIGHT?
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS SHOW ON THE
ROAD.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> [ MEOWING ]
>> THAT'LL BE $1.05, STEVEN.
>> Steven: MM, OKAY.
HERE'S A NICKEL AND A BUCK.
>> Both: WHAT?!
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> OH, STEVEN. THAT'S ADORABLE.
>> [ PURRS ]
>> ARE YOU MAKING IT PURR?
>> Steven: IT KIND OF DOES WHAT
IT WANTS.
>> REALLY?
YOW!
>> Steven: SEE WHAT I MEAN?
BAD CAT FINGER!
>> AH, I'M SURE IT JUST WANTS TO
PLAY.
>> Steven: YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
IT'S JUST LIKE YOU, STEVEN.
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CAT FINGERS MEOW ]
HA HA!
>> Steven: HEY, PEE DEE!
WHOA.
YOU WORK THE DEEP FRYER NOW?
MAKE ME SOME FRY BITS.
>> STEVEN, I TAKE MY JOB
SERIOUSLY.
PLEASE USE THE ACTUAL MENU.
>> Steven: GIVE ME THE BITS.
THE BITS!
>> ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
IT'LL BE OVER SOONER IF YOU JUST
GIVE HIM WHAT HE WANTS.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: WHOA. HEY, HEY.
IT'S NOT FOR ME.
IT'S FOR THESE GUYS.
[ CAT FINGERS MEOW ]
>> WHAT THE...
>> UH, HERE'S YOUR...BITS.
[ CAT FINGERS CHOMPING ]
>> I CAN'T LOOK AWAY.
>> STEVEN, THAT IS FREAKISH.
>> Steven: NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S NATURAL.
SHAKE...IT...OUT.
[ CAT FINGERS MEOWING ]
SEE?
>> Both: WHOA!
>> YOU KNOW WHO WOULD LOVE THIS?
YOUR OLDER BROTHER.
YO, RONALDO!
>> WHAT'S UP, DAD?
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
I GOT TO TAKE A PIC FOR
"KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD."
[ CAT FINGERS MEOW ]
>> Steven: WHAT'S THAT?
>> IT'S MY BLOG.
KEEP...BEACH...CITY...WEIRD!
>> [ GROANS ]
>> Steven: CAN I SEE THE
PICTURE?
[ CAT FINGERS YOWL ]
YIKES!
OH, OOH. SORRY, GUYS.
I GUESS CAT FINGERS DON'T
FUNCTION WELL AS...FINGERS.
[ CAT FINGERS MEOWING ]
>> Steven: Shh!
I'M JUST GETTING A SNACK.
WHOA!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, NEED SOME
HELP?
>> Steven: NAH, IT'S COOL.
>> Amethyst: OH, GOOD.
SEE YOU LATER, THEN.
>> Steven: HUH?
>> Amethyst: WE'RE TAKING THE
GEM SLOOP OUT TO SEA TO FIGHT A
LIVING ISLAND.
>> Steven: WHAT?
[ CAT FINGERS MEOW ]
UH...AMETHYST, WAIT!
I WANT TO GO ON THE GEM SLOOP!
I WANT TO SEE A LIVING ISLAND!
WAIT! WAIT! WAIT!
[ SPLASH ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
COME ON! YOU CAN MAKE IT!
[ CAT FINGERS MEOWING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> Steven: UH...I-IT'S NOTHING.
UH, I JUST TURNED ALL MY FINGERS
INTO CATS.
>> Amethyst: [ SNORTS ]
>> Pearl: WE HAVE TO STAY AND
HELP STEVEN.
>> Garnet: WE CAN'T.
THIS IS A TECTONIC EMERGENCY.
WE'LL DEAL WITH STEVEN WHEN WE
GET BACK.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, I BLAME YOU
FOR THIS.
>> Amethyst: EH, THAT'S FAIR.
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
STEVEN! JUST TRY TO STAY CALM!
[ CAT FINGERS MEOWING ]
>> Steven: ENOUGH!
NO MORE CAT FINGERS.
I WANT STEVEN FINGERS.
AND I DON'T MEAN LITTLE ME-HEADS
ON FINGERS.
I MEAN MY REGULAR FINGERS.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
>> [ MEOWS ]
[ CATS MEOWING ]
>> Steven: UH...
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> Steven: WHOA! AAH! OH! OH!
STOP!
>> [ MEOWS ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
AMETHYST!
PEARL!
GARNET!
[ GASPS ]
DAD!
>> [ HUMMING ]
[ CLANK ]
HELLO? WHO'S THERE?
[ CATS MEOWING ]
WE'RE CLOSED.
COME BACK TOMORROW -- WHOA,
WHOA!
>> Steven: AAH!
[ GROANS ]
DAD!
>> HUH?
[ CATS MEOWING ]
[ GASPS ]
STEVEN?!
>> Steven: DAD!
[ GROANS ]
HELP!
THE CAT FINGERS ARE TAKING OVER
MY BODY!
[ GROANS ]
>> HOLD ON! WHOA!
I'LL GET YOU OUT OF THERE!
>> Steven: DAD!
>> WHOA!
>> Steven: NO!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: BAD! BAD CAT FINGERS!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> CAN'T YOU MAKE THEM GO AWAY?
>> Steven: I TRIED, BUT IT MADE
IT WORSE.
OOH, MY LIFE IS OVER.
I CAN'T GO ON MAGIC ADVENTURES.
I CAN'T EVEN OPEN THE FRIDGE.
AND I'LL NEVER GET TO HAVE
ANOTHER WATER FIGHT WITH YOU,
DAD, 'CAUSE THESE THINGS HATE...
WATER!
THEY HATE WATER.
DAD, SPRAY ME AGAIN!
[ CATS YOWLING ]
>> WHOA!
AAAH!
>> Steven: IT'S NOT ENOUGH
WATER!
[ GASPS ]
TURN ON THE SUPERWASH!
>> NO. I WON'T DO IT.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
>> Steven: YOU'VE GOT TO.
I'M A MONSTER!
I'M AN ADORABLE CAT MONSTER!
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT!
YOU'RE MY SON!
>> Steven: DAD! PLEASE!
AAH!
[ WHIRRING ]
[ BUZZER ]
[ CATS YOWLING ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: DAD.
[ GRUNTS ]
WE DID IT.
>> [ MEOWS ]
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
[ BOTH PANTING ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
OKAY, LET ME SEE IT.
WELL, YOU -- YOU -- YOU GOT THEM
TO GO AWAY?
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW --
ALWAYS LISTEN TO ME AND NEVER
LISTEN TO AMETHYST.
>> Amethyst: THAT'S FAIR.
>> Garnet: IT GOES TO SHOW YOU
SHOULD HAVE A LITTLE MORE FAITH
IN STEVEN.
>> Steven: YEAH, THAT WOULD'VE
BEEN A TOTAL CAT-TASTROPHE.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS FLATLY ]
>> Pearl: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: BUT I'M FEELING MUCH
BETTER MEOW.
>> Together: OHH.
>> Steven: EH?
>> Pearl: NO.
>> Steven: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAT GOT YOUR TONGUE?
>> Garnet: OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> Steven: WAIT.
I'VE BEEN COMING UP WITH CAT
JOKES ALL MORNING.
YOU GUYS, I'M FELINE FINE.
EVERYTHING'S PURR-FECT.
OH, COME ON.
I'M JUST KITTEN AROUND.