>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ SEAGULL CRIES ]
>> Amethyst: HEY, STEVEN!
DO YOU WANT TO TRY SOME SPECIAL,
NEW FRENCH FRIES?
>> Steven: DO I?!
[ CHOMPS ]
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLING ]
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLING ]
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHING ]
>> Steven: H-O-O-O-O-O-T!
>> Amethyst: THEY'RE "SPECIAL"
BECAUSE THEY'RE SEASONED WITH
FIRE SALT!
>> Steven: [ SCREAMING ]
[ GULPS ]
>> STEVEN, WHAT ARE YOU --
AAH!
OW!
>> Steven: [ Slurring ] SOWWY,
LARS.
>> UGH.
STEVEN, WHO DO YOU THINK HAS TO
CLEAN UP THIS MESS?
SADIE, CLEAN UP THIS MESS.
>> NO WAY! IT'S YOUR TURN!
I CLEANED THE LAST FIVE STEVENS!
>> AW, COME ON!
THAT FALL MESSED UP MY BACK!
IT HURTS REALLY BAD.
>> FINE. MOVE ASIDE.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
CAN YOU GRAB THE SOAP?
>> OHH!
IT HURTS SO MUCH!
>> MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE THE DAY
OFF.
>> OKAY!
YOU GONNA BE FINE ON YOUR OWN?
>> WELL, I GUESS SO, BUT...
>> YOU'RE THE BEST, PLAYER 2!
>> AWW.
[ DOOR DINGS ]
UH, I CAN'T RUN THIS PLACE BY
MYSELF!
>> Steven: I COULD HELP!
THIS PLACE HAS GIVEN ME SO MANY
DELICIOUS DONUTS.
IT'S TIME I GAVE BACK.
>> I HEREBY DEPUTIZE YOU AS
"LARS FOR THE DAY."
NOW, IT'S TIME I SHOWED YOU THE
EMPLOYEE ROOM.
>> Steven: WHOA.
THIS IS THE MOST MAGICAL PLACE
I'VE EVER SEEN!
>> LET ME GIVE YOU THE TOUR.
THESE ARE THE EXTRA SUPPLIES,
CUPS, PLASTIC SILVERWARE.
SOMETIMES I SLEEP ON THE NAPKINS
WHEN I GET TIRED.
>> Steven: IS THAT WHY THEY'RE
CALLED NAP-KINS?
>> NOT REALLY, NO.
GOOD JOKE, THOUGH.
ON BREAKS, WE CHILL OUT HERE.
WE CAN EVEN WATCH TV!
SOMETIMES, LARS WILL COVER FOR
ME SO I CAN WATCH
"CANINE COURT."
AND NOW, MOST IMPORTANT OF ALL,
THIS IS WHERE WE STORE THE
DONUTS.
THEY'RE MAILED IN FROM SOME
CORPORATE BAKE-STATION.
>> Steven: YOU MEAN YOU DON'T
MAKE THEM HERE?
>> NO, NOT SINCE...
THE ACCIDENT.
NOW, STEVEN, THIS JOB IS A BIG
RESPONSIBILITY, SO YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO WATCH THIS VIDEOTAPE.
>> Steven: WHAT IS IT?
>> IT'S LIKE A DVD SHAPED LIKE A
BOX, AND IT'LL TELL YOU
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW.
[ RETRO POP MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> Steven: MR. SMILEY USED TO
WORK HERE?
>> NO, BUT HE USED TO BE AN
ACTOR/R&B SINGER.
>> ♪ DONUTS AT THE BIG DONUT ♪
♪ THEY MAKE THE WORLD GO ROUND,
A TREAT WHEN YOU ARE DOWN ♪
♪ DONUTS -- WOW! -- AT THE BIG
DONUT -- BAM! ♪
♪ DUNK THEM IN COFFEE OR TEA,
NAPKINS ARE ALWAYS FREE ♪
♪ NOW, IF A CUSTOMER CHOKES ON A
DONUT ♪
THAT AIN'T RIGHT.
♪ STATE LAW REQUIRES THAT YOU
ASSIST THEM ♪
HELP 'EM OUT, NOW.
♪ TAKE BOTH HANDS, PUSH BELOW
THE DIAPHRAGM ♪
♪ GET THEM HAPPY AND BREATHING
AS FAST AS YOU CAN ♪
THAT'S THE LAW.
♪ IN THE EVENT OF A FIRE ♪
DON'T PANIC. STAY CALM.
♪ THERE IS A FIRE EXTINGUISHER
AGAINST THE BACK WALL ♪
♪ THERE IS A 6% SALES TAX ON
EDIBLE GOODS ♪
♪ 'CAUSE TAX EXEMPTION IS FOR
NON-PREPARED FOODS ♪
♪ ...IN COFFEE OR TEA, NAPKINS
ARE ALWAYS FREE ♪
[ Echoing ] ♪ FREE, FREE ♪
>> Steven: THAT WAS GREAT!
ARE ALL VIDEOTAPES THAT
INFORMATIVE?
>> IN MY EXPERIENCE, YEAH.
IT STARTED OUT AS JUST A SUMMER
JOB, BUT THAT WAS TWO SUMMERS
AGO.
>> HMM. I'LL HAVE A--
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
♪ DONUTS, AT THE BIG DONUT ♪
>> HEY!
>> Both: ♪ THEY MAKE THE
WORLD GO ROUND ♪
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU USED TO BE
A REAL ACTOR/R&B SINGER.
>> "USED TO BE"?
[ Mumbling ] KIDS, THEY DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING.
>> WOW, I'M IMPRESSED!
[ DOOR DINGS ]
LAST TIME SOMEONE MENTIONED THAT
SONG, WE COULDN'T GET MR. SMILEY
TO GO HOME.
>> Steven: ♪ TO PERK UP, YOU
GOTTA PERCOLATE ♪
♪ A HOT CUP OF COFFEE MAKES THE
PERFECT DATE ♪
>> [ Chuckling ] AWW, THANKS!
MAYBE I SHOULD PHONE UP LARS,
TELL HIM HE CAN STAY HOME 'CAUSE
I FOUND HIS REPLACEMENT!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: REALLY?!
>> OH. NO, TH-THAT WAS A JOKE.
>> Steven: I KNOW WE BOTH LOVE
LARS...BUT THIS JOB IS THE BEST
THING THAT'S EVER HAPPENED TO
ME, AND WE SHOULD FIRE LARS.
>> WE CAN'T "FIRE LARS."
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
WHY NOT?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I MEAN, HE
MAY DO THINGS LIKE COME IN LATE
AND LEAVE ALL THE REALLY HARD
WORK FOR ME, BUT --
LOOK, I LIKE LARS!
HE -- HE'S A NICE GUY...
ONCE YOU GET TO KNOW HIM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THERE WAS THIS ONE TIME -- THE
NEW "ARMY OF WAR" GAME WAS
COMING OUT.
BUT LARS WAS BANNED FROM THE
ONLY PLACE SELLING IT.
[ LAUGHS ]
HE WANTED IT SO BAD!
SO WHO DOES HE BEG TO STAND IN
LINE FOR SEVEN HOURS?
ME! [ CHUCKLES ]
I DIDN'T THINK MUCH OF IT.
WHEN I GOT TO HIS HOUSE, I SAW
HE CLEANED UP HIS ROOM A LITTLE,
AND HE GOT A BIG BOX OF OYSTER
CRACKERS.
THEY'RE MY FAVORITE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
HE LET ME BE HIS "PLAYER 2," AND
WE SPENT THE WHOLE NIGHT
TOGETHER.
>> Steven: THAT REALLY IS NICE.
MUST'VE BEEN ONE GREAT VIDEO
GAME!
>> YEAH, IT WAS.
>> Steven: MAYBE WE COULD DO
SOMETHING NICE FOR LARS.
♪ DONUTS, D-D-DONUTS ♪
♪ DONUTS, DONUTS, DONUTS,
DONUTS, DONUTS, DONUTS ♪
>> I-I THOUGHT YOU WANTED THIS
TO BE A SURPRISE!
HE WOULD HEAR US A MILE AWAY!
>> Steven: BUT THE DONUT FEVER'S
FRIED MY SOUL!
AAH! [ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
AW, HE ALREADY ORDERED PIZZA!
>> [ LAUGHING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Both: HUH?
>> DO A FLIP!
>> OH, YEAH!
>> [ PANTING ]
HEY, LARS, THANKS FOR INVITING
US OVER.
>> IT'S NO PROBLEM...
[ LAUGHS ]
...'CAUSE I GOT THE WHOLE DAY
OFF BY FAKING A SEVERE BACK
INJURY!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Steven: UGH!
HE WAS FAKING THIS WHOLE --
UH, DON'T WORRY!
WE CAN HANDLE THE BIG DONUT!
WHO NEEDS CRUMMY, OLD LARS?
>> [ Crying ] STEVEN, HE'S MADE
A FOOL OF ME!
IDIOT!
[ CRYING ]
HE'S BURNED ME BEFORE.
JUST ONCE, I'D LIKE TO BURN HIM
BACK!
>> Steven: I KNOW HOW TO BURN
PEOPLE!
WAIT RIGHT HERE.
ACTUALLY, THIS MIGHT TAKE A
WHILE.
YOU'D BETTER GO HOME.
SEE YOU TOMORROW AT WO-O-O-RK!
[ DOG PANTING ]
[ DOGS BARKING ]
>> Steven: FIRE SALT!
>> HUH?
>> Steven: BURN! BURN PEOPLE!
>> YOU KNOW WE CAN'T ADD
ANYTHING TO THE DONUTS!
>> Steven: IT'S JUST A LITTLE
FIRE SALT.
I WAS GOING TO PRANK LARS.
>> HE DID REALLY HURT MY
FEELINGS...
A LITTLE.
BUT WHAT KIND OF PERSON DOES
THAT MAKE YOU IF YOU TRY TO HURT
HIM BACK?
>> Steven: A...HERO?
[ DOOR DINGS ]
>> [ GROANING ]
MY BACK!
SADIE, I FINALLY GOT OUT OF BED,
BUT I DON'T THINK I CAN WORK
SADIE, DON'T MAKE ME WALK ALL
THE WAY TO THE BREAK ROOM!
[ HISSING ]
>> Steven: SADIE...
THIS IS GONNA BE SO FUNNY!
>> YO, SADIE, WHERE YOU AT?
ARE YOU SLACKING OFF?
>> [ Monotone ] LARS.
>> Steven: HI, LARS!
>> WHY IS STEVEN IN A DONUT
SUIT?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
HOW'S YOUR BACK?
>> UH, ACTUALLY, IT STILL HURTS
LIKE --
>> REALLY.
>> NO, NO, IT'S COOL.
I KNOW I CAN COUNT ON YOU TO
HELP, "P" 2.
>> SURE. JUST RELAX.
IN FACT...WHY DON'T YOU HAVE A
DONUT?
[ SIZZLING ]
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>> CAREFUL. IT'S A LITTLE HOT.
>> Steven: [ SNICKERING ]
>> HEY, THIS IS PRETTY GOOD.
THIS A NEW FLAVOR OR SOMETHING?
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
SHE SAID -- SHE SAID IT'S HOT!
[ RUMBLE! ]
>> [ SCREAMING ]
>> STEVEN, HELP LARS!
>> Steven: UH, LARS, DRINK THIS!
[ WHISTLE! ]
AAH!
[ GROANS ]
>> NO! LARS, COME BACK!
[ SMOKE ALARM BEEPING ]
STEVEN, I DIDN'T WANT THIS!
>> Steven: I KNOW HOW TO FIX
THIS!
WE JUST NEED TO GET LARS TO CALM
DOWN.
>> HOW ARE WE GONNA FIND HIM?!
>> AAH!
>> Steven: I THINK HE WENT THIS
WAY!
>> AND OF THE MANY TREASURES IN
OUR WONDERFUL CITY, THIS IS
AS MAYOR, I'M PROUD TO UNVEIL
THIS -- THE LARGEST BOWL OF ICE
CREAM IN BEACH COUNTY!
[ CROWD GASPING ]
YES, LET'S ALL SCREAM...
FOR ICE CREAM.
>> AAH!
[ SPLAT ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
[ CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
>> YEAH. IT MELTED, GARY!
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID THAT
AT THE MEETING!
>> [ SCREAMING ]
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: HEY, WHY'S DONUT
GUY BREATHING FIRE?
>> Steven: I TRIED TO PRANK
LARS, BUT I USED TOO MUCH FIRE
SALT!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN...
THAT'S HILARIOUS.
>> YOU...
DID...THIS...TO ME?
>> Steven: [ YELLING ]
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHING ]
[ FLAMES ROARING ]
>> IT WASN'T STEVEN!
IT WAS ME.
>> Amethyst: OH, NOW IT'S
GETTIN' GOOD!
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
>> AFTER ALL I DO FOR YOU, YOU
LIE TO ME SO YOU CAN SNEAK OFF
WITH SOME OTHER GIRL?!
>> Steven: AND OTHER BOYS!
[ GASPS, WHIMPERS ]
>> [ Crying ] THAT NIGHT WE
PLAYED VIDEO GAMES, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT MEANT TO YOU, BUT EVER
SINCE THEN, I CAN'T GET THE
THOUGHT OUT OF MY HEAD THAT
YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
THAT NIGHT I REALLY THOUGHT --
"PLAYER 2" -- IS THAT JUST YOUR
WAY OF SAYING I COULD HAVE BEEN
ANYONE?
>> SADI--
[ COUGHING ]
>> Steven: ♪ IF A CUSTOMER
CHOKES ON A DONUT ♪
♪ STATE LAW REQUIRES THAT YOU
ASSIST THEM ♪
♪ TAKE BOTH HANDS, PUSH BELOW
THE DIAPHRAGM ♪
>> [ RETCHES ]
>> Steven: ANOTHER DAY SAVED BY
STEVEN UNIVERSE, WITH THE BONUS
MUSICAL STYLINGS OF
HAROLD SMILEY.
YOU'RE WELCOME!
>> I'M NOT APOLOGIZING.
>> UH, NO! [ WHEEZES ]
I WANT TO HELP!
BUT I GET IT IF YOU WANT TO BE
ALONE.
>> OH, NO, NO, NO! STAY.
I-I MEAN, YOU CAN HELP.
BUT FIRST, LET'S GET YOU SOME
WATER, AND MAYBE GET YOU OUT
OF THOSE BURNT SHIRTS.
>> Amethyst: HEY, WE MAKE A
PRETTY GREAT TEAM.
[ CHOMPING ]
>> Steven: YOU WERE ABSOLUTELY
NO HELP WHATSOEVER.
>> Amethyst: EH.
HEY! HOW 'BOUT THIS ONE HERE?!
>> Pearl: WHAT ONE?
>> Steven: THIS LITTLE ONE!
IT'S ADORB-ABLE.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THE LEGENDARY
GLASS OF TIME WON'T BE NEARLY SO
SMALL AND INSIGNIFICANT.
IT'LL BE BEAUTIFUL AND GRAND,
LIKE THIS ONE!
>> Garnet: I THINK IT'S THIS
ONE.
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Pearl: YOU MEAN THE BIGGEST
ONE?!
HOW ARE WE EVEN SUPPOSED TO GET
THAT BACK TO THE WARP PAD?
>> Garnet: I CAN CARRY IT.
>> Pearl: WAIT!
WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL WHICH ONE
WE TOUCH!
YOU REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED LAST
TIME WE WERE HERE.
>> Steven: WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Amethyst: HEY, GUYS!
I'M MAKIN' THE CALL, AND IT'S
THIS JANKY ONE HERE!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
[ ALL GASP, WHIMPER ]
>> Amethyst: UH...
NOPE, IT WASN'T.
>> Garnet: LOOK OUT!
>> Pearl: WHOA! UGH!
>> Garnet: WE DON'T HAVE MUCH
TIME!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, COME ON!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: W-WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?!
>> Steven: AMETHYST GETS TO KEEP
HERS!
>> Amethyst: DARN TOOTIN'!
>> Steven: I'M GONNA GET THE ONE
I PICKED OUT!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Steven: MY NAME'S STEVEN.
YOU'RE GONNA LIVE WITH ME.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, COME ON!
AAH!
>> Steven: I'M A-COMIN'!
I'M A-COMIN'!
>> Pearl: [ PANICKED LAUGH ]
>> Garnet: HANG ON.
>> Amethyst: HURRY UP. HURRY UP.
HURRY UP. HURRY UP.
>> Garnet: GOTCHA.
>> Pearl: WELL DONE, GARNET!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
>> Amethyst: [ SLURPS ]
>> Steven: HOT POTATO!
WE'RE DOING THAT AGAIN, RIGHT?!
>> Pearl: UNFORTUNATELY, WE'LL
HAVE TO WAIT ANOTHER HUNDRED
YEARS FOR THE SEA SHRINE TO
REFORM 'CAUSE SOMEBODY COULDN'T
KEEP THEIR HANDS TO THEMSELVES.
>> Garnet: YOU HAVE A LOBSTER ON
YOUR BUTT.
>> Pearl: HUH? EEE!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
[ ALARM CLOCK BEEPING ]
>> Steven: BEACH-A-PALOOZA!
>> Amethyst: BEACH-A-WHA-WHOZAA?
>> Garnet: PALOOZA.
>> Steven: THAT WAS A LOT OF
FUN, YOU GUYS.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
AFTER YOU, SIR.
BUH-BYE!
[ HUMMING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> YEP.
>> MM-HMM.
>> Steven: DAD! DAD!
ARE YOU READY TO REHEARSE?
WHOA!
>> UHH...
WE'RE HAVING A BIT OF A DAY.
>> Steven: IS IT STUCK?
>> YEAH.
>> Steven: WHY DOES A BOAT NEED
A CAR WASH?
>> HUH!
[ MUMBLING ]
>> SORRY, BUDDY.
I DON'T THINK I CAN PLAY IN THE
CONCERT TONIGHT.
I GOT TO DEAL WITH THIS.
>> Steven: YOU'RE BAILING ON
BEACH-A-PALOOZA?!
BUT THE WHOLE TOWN'S GONNA BE
THERE!
>> STEVEN, THAT'S LIKE 15
PEOPLE.
NEXT TIME, BUD, I PROMISE.
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE IF YOU BRING IT
FORWARD A LITTLE BIT.
>> Steven: STUPID BOAT GETTIN'
ALL STUCK.
NOBODY LIKES YOU, BOAT!
WISH I COULD'VE BEEN THERE TO
TELL MY DAD YOU WERE TOO FAT!
[ ZAP! ]
>> THAT'S IT. JUST BACK HER IN.
SHE'LL DEFINITELY FIT.
>> Steven: WHAT THE...
[ GASPS ] DAD! DAD!
>> HEY, STU-BALL.
YOU EXCITED FOR BEACH-A-PALOOZA!
>> Steven: DAD! DAD!
FAT, IT'S FAT!
FAT, FAT, FAT!
>> RUDE!
>> Steven: NOT YOU! THE BOAT!
THE BOAT!
>> HUH? WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
STOP!
>> HUH?
>> NICE CATCH, STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
THE THING!
YOU TOOK ME BACK IN TIME, DIDN'T
YOU?!
OH, MAN.
PEARL'S GONNA FLIP WHEN SHE
FINDS OUT YOU WERE THE REAL ONE!
>> LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT THE
BOAT'S FAT!
>> [ GRUMBLING ]
>> OH, NO! YOUR TRUCK!
[ CRASH! FWOOSH! ]
>> OH! WHOA! AAH!
[ EXPLOSION ]
>> [ Muffled ] AAH!
>> GOT TO SAVE THE VAN!
>> I WISH I COULD GO BACK AND
STOP MYSELF FROM STOPPING MY
DAD!
[ ZAP! ]
>> THAT'S IT. JUST BACK HER IN.
SHE'LL DEFINITELY FIT.
>> Steven: WHAT THE...
[ GASPS ] DAD! DAD!
[ ZAP! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ Muffled ] WHAT?
>> Steven: Shh!
>> Steven: FUTURE STEVEN?
>> Steven: LISTEN,
TWO-MINUTES-AGO STEVEN.
WE CAN'T GO AROUND TRYING TO
CHANGE TIME STUFF.
IT JUST MAKES THINGS WORSE!
[ CRASH ]
>> OH, NO! HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?!
>> Steven: AWW, MAN.
I REALLY WANTED TO PLAY AT
BEACH-A-PALOOZA!
TOO BAD YOU AND I CAN'T BE IN A
BAND.
>> Both: WAIT A MINUTE!
>> Steven: [ HUMMING ]
[ ZAP! ]
>> Both: STEVEN! UGH!
>> Steven: [ MOANS ]
STEVEN?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> Steven: NO TIME TO EXPLAIN!
>> Steven: WANNA JOIN OUR BAND?!
>> Steven: YES!
BUT DIDN'T DAD SAY HE WOULD PLAY
WITH US?
>> Steven: HE HAD AN EMERGENCY
AT THE CAR WASH.
>> Steven: WE SHOULD GO HELP
HIM!
>> Steven: NO!
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
THE BOAT'S FAT, TRUST US.
>> Steven: OKAY, SO, WHO'S OUR
FOURTH?
WE NEED A DRUMMER.
>> Steven: NOT A PROBLEM,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: HEY, IT'S THE TIME
THING --
[ "STEVEN AND THE STEVENS"
PLAYS ]
>> Steven: ♪ CAN'T YOU SEE IT IN
MY EYES? ♪
♪ I'M THE ONE, I'M THE ONE ♪
>> Steven: 2!
>> Steven: 3!
>> Steven: 4!
>> Steven: ♪ I'M NOT LIKE THE
OTHER GUYS ♪
>> Steven: ♪ HE'S NOT LIKE
ANYBODY ♪
>> Stevens: ♪ AHH, AHH ♪
>> Steven: ♪ WELL, THAT'S NOT
COMPLETELY RIGHT ♪
♪ THERE'S A FEW THAT I'M JUST
LIKE ♪
♪ STEVEN AND THE STEVENS ♪
>> Stevens: ♪ AHH, AHH, AHH ♪
>> Steven: ♪ WE'RE GONNA MAKE
YOU SMILE ♪
♪ ME, MYSELF, AND I, AND HIM ♪
>> Stevens: ♪ ARE ALL THE SAME
GUY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ STEVEN AND THE
STEVENS ♪
>> Steven: ♪ COME ON, NOW, DON'T
BE SHY ♪
♪ ME ♪
>> Steven: ♪ MYSELF ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND I AND HIM ♪
>> Steven: THAT'S ME!
>> Stevens: ♪ ARE ALL THE SAME
GUY ♪
[ CRASH! ]
>> Steven: HEY!
GREAT SINGING, STEVEN!
>> Steven: THANKS, STEVEN!
>> Steven: CAN I SING LEAD THIS
TIME?
>> Steven: WELL, I USUALLY SING
LEAD VOCALS WHEN I PLAY WITH
DAD.
>> Steven: SO DO I!
>> Steven: ME, TOO!
>> Steven: ME, TOO, TOO!
WE ALL DO! WE'RE ALL STEVEN!
>> Steven: WELL, ONE OF US HAS
GOT TO BE THE BAND LEADER!
>> All: HMM.
>> Steven: HMM.
>> Steven: HMM. OH!
THE LEADER SHOULD BE THE
ORIGINAL STEVEN!
>> All: THE ONE THAT'S BEEN
AROUND THE LONGEST!
>> Steven: YEAH! ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA!
>> Steven: OH, HO, HO!
>> Steven: MM-HMM.
DONE AND DONE!
STEVEN 2, YOU'RE THE SMART ONE.
STEVEN 3, YOU'RE THE FUNNY ONE.
STEVEN 4, YOU'RE THE SENSITIVE
ONE.
AND I'M...
[ GLEAM! ]
...THE HANDSOME ONE!
OKAY?
>> Both: OKAY!
>> Steven 4: OKEY-DOKEY,
ARTICHOKEY!
>> Steven: STEVEN 4, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?!
YOU'RE NOT THE FUNNY ONE!
STEVEN 3 IS!
>> Steven 3: WELL, WE'RE ALL THE
SAME PERSON, SO WE'RE ALL
EQUALLY PRONE TO BEING
HILARIOUS.
>> Steven: NO, NO!
THAT WAS TOO SMART AN
OBSERVATION FOR YOU, 3!
YOU'RE THE FUNNY ONE!
>> Steven 2: WAIT, WHICH ONE AM
I AGAIN?
>> Steven: DANG IT, NUMBER 2,
YOU'RE THE SMART ONE!
>> Steven 4: HEY, IF STEVEN 1 IS
THE HANDSOME ONE, DOES THAT MEAN
THE REST OF US AREN'T
GOOD-LOOKING?
>> Steven 3: NO WAY!
WE'RE ALL EXTREMELY ATTRACTIVE!
>> Steven 2: LET'S GO GET JOBS
AS MODELS!
>> Steven: HEY!
NONE OF YOU ARE THE HANDSOME
ONE!
I'M THE HANDSOME ONE!
AH! NO!
I DIDN'T MEAN --
WE DECIDED...
[ SIGHS ]
LET'S TAKE FIVE.
>> All: THERE'S A 5th STEVEN?
>> Steven: NO!
I MEAN A FIVE-MINUTE BREAK!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> All: WE KNOW.
[ WAVES CRASHING ]
>> Steven: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M SO...ANNOYING!
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR ME TO QUIT
THE MUSIC BUSINESS.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven 3: ♪ STEVEN! ♪
♪ STE-STE-STE STEVEN! ♪
>> Steven: WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT'S ALL THIS NOISE?!
>> Steven 3: ♪ STE-STE-STE -- ♪
>> Steven: I THOUGHT WE AGREED
THAT STEVEN AND THE STEVENS WAS
GONNA BE A LIGHT-HEARTED
THROWBACK TO EARLY ROCK 'N'
ROLL, NOT THIS MESS OF SCREAMING
AND DISTORTION!
>> Steven 3: LOOK, STEVEN.
STEVEN AND I WERE TALKING, AND
STEVEN AGREES.
YOUR ATTITUDE JUST ISN'T WORKING
FOR US.
>> Steven 2: WE'VE BEEN A LOT
MORE PRODUCTIVE WITHOUT YOU.
>> Steven 4: WE ALREADY WROTE AN
ANGSTY SONG ABOUT THAT TIME YOU
MADE US FEEL BAD FOR NOT BEING
HANDSOME.
>> Steven: YOU'RE KICKING ME OUT
OF THE BAND?!
WAIT.
WHO'S PLAYING DRUMS?
>> Steven 4: AMETHYST SAID SHE'D
DO IT.
>> Amethyst: I'M DOWN FOR
WHATEVER.
>> Steven: OH, COME ON!
>> Steven 3: ♪ STEVEN'S A BIG,
FAT MEANIE ♪
♪ A BIG FAT MEANIE ZUCCHINI ♪
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
>> Amethyst: WHOA, DUDE.
>> Steven: LISTEN UP!
YOU CAN'T KICK ME OUT OF THE
BAND!
I'M THE ORIGINAL STEVEN.
I CREATED YOU!
STEVEN AND THE STEVENS WAS MY
IDEA!
WITHOUT ME, YOU'D ALL BE
NOTHING!
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S IT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
>> All: STEVEN, NO!
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: WISH I COULD HAVE
BEEN THERE TO TELL MY DAD YOU
WERE TOO --
[ ZAP! ]
AH!
[ MUFFLED TALKING ]
>> Steven: DON'T START THE BAND,
STEVEN.
IT'LL ONLY TEAR US APART.
[ ZAP! ]
>> All: HO, HO!
WE ALL HAVE TIME THINGS!
>> Steven: YOU'LL NEVER CATCH
ME, YOU TURKEYS!
HA!
[ ZAP! ]
>> All: WE GOT TO STOP ME.
>> Steven: I'M OKAY, GUYS.
I JUST -- WHA--
>> Steven: TOO FAR BACK!
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: [ RETCHES ]
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ ZAP! ]
>> All: HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ZAP! ]
[ ALL GROWL ]
>> Steven: JUST TAKE ME BACK TO
THE BEGINNING.
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: AMETHYST GETS TO KEEP
HERS!
>> Amethyst: DARN TOOTIN'!
>> Steven: I'M GONNA GET THE ONE
I PICKED OUT!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Steven: MY NAME'S STEVEN.
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: STOP RIGHT THERE!
GIVE ME THE TIME THING, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WAIT.
ARE YOU FUTURE ME?
>> Steven: JUST HURRY UP AND
GIVE IT!
[ ZAP! ]
HUH?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: WHA--
>> Steven: DON'T MAKE ME HURT
ME, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WHY DO YOU NEED IT SO
BAD?
>> Steven: JUST GIVE IT TO ME!
[ ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ]
[ ZAP! ZAP! ]
[ ZAP! ]
>> Steven: GIVE IT UP, STEVEN!
I KNOW EVERYTHING YOU'RE GONNA
DO BEFORE YOU DO IT!
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
HUH?
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
>> Amethyst: 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18...
>> Pearl: UH...
>> Steven: [ CRYING ]
>> Steven: STOP IT!
>> All: HUH? WHAT?
HUH?
>> Steven: LOOK AROUND YOU.
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
WHEN STEVEN FIGHTS STEVEN, WHO
IS THE WINNER?
WHAT HAVE WE BECOME?
>> Steven: WHAT IS IT?
>> Steven: WHAT'S WRONG WITH US?
>> Steven: WHAT HAVE WE BECOME?
>> Steven: WE'RE NOT THE STEVENS
WE ONCE WERE.
AND TO FIX THAT, I HAVE TO END
IT!
AAH!
[ POP! POP! POP! POP! POP! ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> Steven 3: STEVEN, PLEASE!
YOU GOT TO -- AAH!
>> Steven: STEVEN, DAD CAN'T
PLAY BEACH-A-PALOOZA WITH YOU.
THE BOAT'S FAT.
YOU GOT TO FIND ANOTHER WAY.
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> Steven: STAY COOL FOREVER,
STEVEN.
MWAH. ARRIVEDERCI.
AAH!
>> Steven: ♪ CAN'T YOU SEE IT IN
AOUR EYES? ♪
♪ WE'RE THE ONE, WE'RE THE ONE ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ TWO ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ THREE ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ FOUR ♪
>> Steven: ♪ WE'RE NOT LIKE THE
OTHER GUYS ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ WE'RE NOT LIKE
ANYBODY ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ AHH ♪
>> Steven: ♪ BY THE WAY, DON'T
GO BACK IN TIME ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AHH ♪
>> Steven: ♪ OR YOU'LL DESTROY
YOURSELF ♪
♪ STEVEN AND THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'RE GONNA MAKE YOU SMILE ♪
♪ I ACCIDENTALLY CREATED AN
ALTERNATE TIMELINE ♪
♪ STEVEN AND THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ COME ON NOW, DON'T BE SHY ♪
♪ I LEARNED TO STAY TRUE TO
MYSELF ♪
♪ BY WATCHING MYSELF DIE ♪