♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
Steven:
SNIFFLING CROISSANT!
YOU REALLY KNOW ME,
INTERNET.
HEY, GUYS!
YEAH, STEVEN?
YOU GUYS SHOULD
TAKE THIS ONLINE QUIZ I FOUND.
IT TELLS YOU WHAT...
IT TELLS YOU
WHAT CHARACTER YOU ARE
FROM
"CRYING BREAKFAST FRIENDS"!
EH...WHY?
IT'S JUST FUN
TO SEE YOURSELF
AS A CARTOON CHARACTER.
LIKE WEEPING EGGCUP,
WHO'S NEUROTIC AND UPTIGHT,
OR PINING GRAPEFRUIT,
THE SENSITIVE OLDER ONE
WHO WISHES
HE WAS A BETTER ROLE MODEL.
UH, MAYBE
WE CAN DO THAT THING
AFTER
WE'VE FIXED THE VAN.
[ SIGHS ] OKAY.
I'LL GO
FIND SOMEONE ELSE!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT CARTOON SHOW?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANYTHING ANYMORE.
[ PANTING, GASPS ]
HEY, STEVEN.
IS THERE ANY MORE ENGINE OIL?
I NEED IT
FOR THIS SANDWICH.
I...THINK THAT'S FOR CARS.
WELL, IS THERE
ANY MORE OF IT?
DAD'S PROBABLY
GOT SOME OUTSIDE.
OH! BUT, UH, YOU GOT TO
TAKE THIS ONLINE QUIZ.
WHICH CRYING BREAKFAST FRIEND
ARE YOU?
THAT SHOW'S REALLY WEIRD.
WHO WANTS TO WATCH A CARTOON
ABOUT PEOPLE CRYING?
I DO!
OKAY, OKAY!
UH...
WHAT'S THE FIRST QUESTION?
DO YOU EVER
ACT WITHOUT THINKING?
NOPE. NEVER.
ARE YOU AFRAID OF TAKING RISKS
AND TRYING NEW THINGS?
[ CHOMPS ]
[ Muffled ] TERRIFIED.
AMETHYST, ARE YOU
TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY?
OF COURSE I AM.
OKAY.
ARE YOU INSECURE
ABOUT YOUR RELATIONSHIPS
AND HOW YOU'RE PERCEIVED
BY OTHER PEOPLE?
NNNNO.
YES? EH...
WHAT'S THE RIGHT ANSWER?
THERE IS
NO RIGHT ANSWER.
YOU'RE JUST SUPPOSED TO
ANSWER HONESTLY.
NAH, I'M BORED.
WAIT --
I HAVE LOADS MORE
PROBING, PERSONAL QUESTIONS
TO ASK!
GARNET! W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY ROOM?
I SAW A CORRUPTED GEM.
I FOLLOWED IT THROUGH THE TUNNEL
IT DUG IN THE ROCK.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WHERE DID IT
COME FROM?
IT'S SIMILAR
TO PEARL'S DESCRIPTION
OF THE CREATURE SHE SAW
SLINKING THROUGH THE TEMPLE.
YOU SAW THE SLINKER?!
I THOUGHT WE AGREED
THERE WAS NO SLINKER
AND THAT WE WEREN'T GOING TO
CALL IT "THE SLINKER".
YES, WE DID.
BUT NOW IT'S UNDENIABLE
THE CREATURE EXISTS
AND THAT STEVEN'S NAME STUCK.
YES!
NO!
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST LET ME LOOK FOR IT?
BECAUSE YOU WON'T.
HOW LONG'S THIS THING
BEEN IN HERE?
AH! [ LAUGHS ]
LOOK, STEVEN!
I'M A PACHYDERM!
[ LAUGHS ]
OH! AND THERE'S
A PRIZE INSIDE!
Shhh! Keep quiet.
[ GROANS ]
OH, GARNET.
STERN BUT PRACTICAL.
JUST LIKE SPILT MILK.
YOU'RE NOT STILL ON ABOUT
THAT DUMB CARTOON, ARE YOU?
OH, RIGHT -- THE QUIZ!
DO YOU GET DEFENSIVE
WHEN PEOPLE ASK YOU QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE FEELINGS
YOU PREFER TO KEEP HIDDEN?
DON'T GET ALL PSYCHO-LOGICAL
ON ME, STEVEN.
UH...SORRY?
[ CREATURE CHATTERING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
THERE!
[ PANTING ]
WHOA, MAMA!
DID YOU GET IT?!
NO.
[ GRUNTS ]
AW, MAN!
I THINK MY FAVORITE ROUND THING
WAS IN THERE.
[ SIGHS ] I'LL GET YOU
A NEW ROUND THING.
UGH! THIS IS MY STUFF
YOU'RE MESSING WITH!
IF IT'S GONNA GET --
UGH! -- WRECKED,
I'M GONNA BE
THE ONE TO WRECK IT!
SEE?!
THAT'S HOW IT'S DO--
[ GASPS ]
AMETHYST GOT POOFED!
SLINKER!
[ CREATURE CHATTERING ]
[ Voice breaking ]
G-G-G-GARNET?
STEVEN, REMEMBER --
OUR BODIES ARE ONLY AN ILLUSION.
AMETHYST WILL BE FINE.
B-B-BUT PEARL TOOK
TWO WHOLE WEEKS TO COME BACK.
AND I ALREADY MISS AMETHYST
SO MUCH!
DON'T WORRY. SHE'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
[ GASPS ]
LITERALLY.
AMETHYST'S BACK!
UGH. HUH?
LOOKS LIKE YOU...
GREW A FEW FEET
SINCE THE LAST TIME
I SAW YOU!
NYUK, NYUK, NYUK!
THAT WAS FAST.
EVEN FOR YOU.
EH!
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I DIDN'T WANT TO
KEEP MY BIGGEST FAN WAITING.
[ LAUGHS ]
UGH!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
HMM.
[ LAUGHS ]
OKAY, OKAY!
WE GOT
A SLINKER TO SLINK!
[ GRUNTS ]
WA-UGH!
HMM.
WHERE WOULD I GO
IF I WAS A MONSTER?
HEY! OVER HERE.
YOUR NEW FORM
IS REALLY INTERESTING.
THANKS, STEVEN.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU COULD
COME BACK THIS DIFFERENT.
THANKS, STEVEN.
SO, WHY'D YOU COME BACK
WITH FOUR LEGS?
'CAUSE I LIKE WALKING!
WOW.
I WANT FOUR LEGS, TOO!
NO, YOU DON'T.
AMETHYST RUSHED
HER REGENERATION.
SHE SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN HER TIME.
LIKE PEARL?
YES. PEARL PUT A BIT MORE...
THOUGHT INTO HOW SHE CAME BACK.
Amethyst:
PEARL, PEARL, PEARL!
YOU KNOW
I CAN HEAR YOU!
I'M SORRY I'M NOT LIKE PEARL
WITH HER FANCY FORM
AND HER CLEAN ROOM
WITH NO MONSTERS IN IT.
[ Echoing ]
AMETHYST?
AMETHYST'S GEM!
SHE GOT POOFED AGAIN!
THIS IS A GOOD OPPORTUNITY
FOR HER.
NOW SHE CAN MAKE
A BETTER FORM.
[ GASPS ]
SHE'S COMING BACK!
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS MUCH BETTER!
[ CHUCKLES ]
SHE'S DOING PEARL!
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, GARNET. WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF MY NEW LOOK, GARNET?
I'M MORE LIKE PEARL NOW.
ISN'T IT WONDERFUL? HA!
I FEEL [Singsong voice]
PRACTICALLY PERFECT!
WE NEED TO FOCUS ON
LISTENING FOR THE CREATURE.
[ As Pearl ]
OH, BUT I CAN'T FOCUS.
ALL THESE ROCKS
ARE DIFFERENT SIZES.
WE'LL HAVE TO ORGANIZE THEM
BY SHAPE AND COLOR.
DIDN'T ANYONE TELL NATURE
HOW I WANT IT TO LOOK?
[ LAUGHS ]
DON'T ENCOURAGE HER.
BUT I NEED ENCOURAGEMENT,
GARNET.
I NEED
EVERYONE'S CONSTANT APPROVAL.
I NEED TO LOQUACIOUSLY CONVERSE
SO I CAN SHOW OFF...
[ Normal voice ]
HOW SMART I AM.
YOU CAN CONVERSE
WITH ME.
LET'S FINISH THAT QUIZ.
DO YOU NEED TO PLAN AHEAD
BEFORE YOU ACT?
[ As Pearl ]
OH, THOROUGHLY.
DO YOU OBSESS
OVER LITTLE DETAILS?
COMPLETELY ENTIRELY!
WOW,
YOU'RE SO METHOD.
NEXT TIME,
CAN YOU COME BACK AS ME?
THIS IS NOT A GOOD CHOICE
FOR YOUR FORM.
LIGHTEN UP, GARNET.
CAN'T YOU TAKE A JOKE?
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
YOU'VE MADE YOURSELF
RIDICULOUS.
RIDICULOUS?!
Keep your voice down!
The creature.
GRRR! YOU WANTED ME TO BE
MORE LIKE PEARL, AND NOW I AM!
Pearl would have taken
her regeneration seriously!
WHAT DO YOU CARE?!
MY FORM IS MY BUSINESS!
It's my business when it affects
the strength of the team!
SO WHAT?!
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH?
[ SCREAMS ]
AMETHYST!
ARE YOU SAYING I'M WEAK?!
[ SCREAMS ]
IS IT WEIRD
I'M GETTING NUMB TO THIS?
UNH?
MNH!
[ GRUNTING ]
OKAY!
YOU KNOW, I WASN'T
FEELING THIS AT FIRST,
BUT I THINK
I MIGHT BE COMING AROUND!
HA!
YO, STE-MAN.
MY SEAMS STRAIGHT?
DOES THAT NEW FORM...
HURT YOU?
NO.
HEY, GARNET.
HOW'D YOU LIKE
TO MIX IT UP WITH THIS?
[ LAUGHS ]
JUST A LITTLE SOMETHIN'
I THREW TOGETHER. YOU KNOW.
THIS FORM
ISN'T SUSTAINABLE, AMETHYST.
BUT...
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAID
I NEEDED
TO BE STRONGER!
[ CREATURE CHATTERING ]
OKAY, IF IT'S MY MONSTER,
THEN I'LL DEAL WITH IT.
[ GRUNTING ]
RAAAHHH!
Steven: AMETHYST!
STAY BEHIND ME!
AMETHYST!
HAH!
[ AMETHYST GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
AMETHYST!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ STRAINING ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLS ]
Garnet: LET IT GO!
NO!
UGH. YOU WANTED ME
TO BE STRONGER!
I'M DOING IT!
I'M BEING WHAT YOU WANT!
I DON'T WANT THIS!
HUH?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT?!
JUST TELL ME,
AND I'LL DO THAT!
I CAN'T TELL YOU,
AMETHYST!
YOU HAVE TO FIGURE THIS OUT
FOR YOURSELF!
[ STRAINING ]
SHE CAN'T.
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO THINK ABOUT HERSELF!
WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
GOOD CATCH.
Pearl:
I KNEW THAT THING WAS REAL!
WHEN AMETHYST GETS BACK,
WE HAVE TO GO FIND IT.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN?
FOUR HOURS.
FOUR HOURS?!
SHE'S NEVER TAKEN SO LONG.
WHAT IS SHE DOING
IN THERE?
I'M NOT SURE.
I WAS TOO HARD ON HER.
[ SIGHS ]
OH, OH!
SHE'S COMING BACK!
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYONE BE SUPPORTIVE.
[ GROANS ]
WHAT?
AW,
YOU BARELY CHANGED.
STEVEN!
IT'S PERFECT.
EHH, WHATEV.
IT'S JUST WHAT FEELS RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY IT'S PERFECT.
IT IS
A MARKED IMPROVEMENT.
YOU FINALLY FIXED
THAT SHOULDER STRAP
THAT'S ALWAYS
BUGGED ME!
WELCOME BACK!
WELL DONE,
AMETHYST!
KNOCK IT OFF!
HUNNHH!
WE GOT TO
GO FIND THE SLINKER!
NO, IT'S HUG TIME!
UGH!
THIS IS SO DUMB!
[ SIGHS ]
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪