♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
♪♪
[ Waves crashing,
gulls squawking in distance ]
[ Sighs ]
She'll call when she's ready.
For now, you just
have to let go.
[ Squawking continues ]
[ Sighs ]
♪ I wish I could
tell you that I -- ♪
Aah, aah!
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Ah! Ah! Ugh!
Okay, Universe. This is it!
Connie's finally ready to talk.
No expectations.
Just let her say
what she needs to say!
Aw.
Peridot: Steven!
[ Chuckles ]
It's us.
Oh, hi, Peridot.
Hi, Lapis.
Don't forget Pumpkin!
[ Barks ]
[ Chuckles ]
Hi, Pumpkin!
I'd told you he'd answer.
It's so good to see you.
I'm glad you're okay.
Lapis was worried you lost
your phone on Homeworld,
but I said, "No way!
He's probably
just ignoring us."
Sorry, guys.
There's been...a lot going on.
Like what?
Tell us!
Well, Connie is
really mad at me.
No, no, no, no.
Tell us about space!
And start from
the beginning.
Uh, okay.
I was trying to protect
Beach City,
so I surrendered myself
to Homeworld,
and I was put in
a big, empty room,
and I ended up on trial
in front of the Diamonds!
On trial?
What?
In front
of the Diamonds?
Yeah, and...
You were in front
of Blue Diamond?
And Yellow! But it's okay.
I escaped in a palanquin
and went underground and...
You ran from Blue
and Yellow Diamond?!
Yes.
Peridot,
we have to
leave Earth now.
[ Sighing ] Uh-oh.
[ Pumpkin barking ]
Wait. We can't leave.
What about all our crops?
Guys?
Ugh. The vegetables
will have to deal.
Okay. Okay, but, uh,
we're only halfway through our
rewatch of "CPH" season four.
[ Chuckles ]
We'll bring the box set
with us.
But how are we going to
watch it without the TV?
We'll bring the TV.
Uh, Lapis?
Huh?
Peridot?
Oh, Steven.
Good. Let's go.
Wait. What?
We'll find
some remote spot
in the universe
to hide out in.
The Diamonds
will never find us.
Lapis, don't worry.
They're looking for me
on Homeworld.
They don't know I'm here.
We're safe.
Yeah. Come on.
We've gotten away with
worse.
They've never been able
to hunt me down
for my many crimes
against them.
This is different.
Steven is important,
and our transgressions
are piling up!
They're going to take their
anger out on this planet,
just like they did
before.
I can't.
I won't let myself
get caught up
in another war.
[ Whimpers ]
I don't want you to leave,
but I won't ask
you guys to stay
if you don't feel safe.
If you have to go,
I understand.
Right.
Peridot,
if you want the TV,
levitate it over here.
Hey, um,
what about our meep morps
we've made?
We can't leave them
behind.
We can bring them, too.
But they're installations!
They need the context
of the barn!
If -- if we move them,
they'll become...
performance pieces.
There's no need
to get so emotional!
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Performance art isn't bad,
just misunderstood.
Hmm, maybe I can
do something.
Ah!
Our smaller-than-average lake!
Guh!
[ Pumpkin barking ]
-Whoa.
♪♪
There. Now we can bring
our whole life with us --
you, me, and all
of our things.
Right. Right!
Well, let's get going.
You're leaving
right now?
I thought that...
I -- I don't know
what to say.
Goodbye, Steven.
Good luck.
[ Sniffles ]
Peridot, don't you
want to say bye?
Uhh...
[ Whimpers ]
Umm...
[ Gasps ] Wait.
Where's Pumpkin?
She's not inside?
She was just standing
next to me!
We have to find her.
I'll check from above.
Peridot,
you search the ground.
-I'll help, too! Pumpkin?
-Pumpkin?!
Pumpkin? Pumpkin!
Pumpkin?
[ Softly ] Pumpkin.
Pumpkin!
Where are you, buddy?
[ Panting ]
Pumpkin!
♪♪
You know, I'm really
going to miss you guys
when you're in space.
Well, that's a given.
I'm a very precious Gem.
Without me,
you would have crumbled
under The Cluster's
obstructive force
or have been smushed
by Jasper.
I'm --
Peridot, there!
Pumpkin! Ngh!
Is she okay?
Um...
Pumpkin!
You know, I can
probably still help you
when I'm out in space.
I'll just video chat
from my tablet.
Uh, t-there's
no Wi-Fi in space.
Well, maybe it's best
if we can't reach you.
If the Diamonds do show up
and destroy the planet,
we'll never know!
Lapis was very agitated when
she heard you were on Homeworld.
I was bending over backwards
to make her feel better.
Watch this.
[ Grunting ]
[ Laughs ] That is good.
Oh, yeah.
She loves this.
[ Groans ]
Maybe it's good
that we'll be away
from everything
where nothing can change,
no surprises
or developments.
She's been through
so much.
She needs consistency.
But what about you?
[ Gasps ]
Another kindergartner!
Fresh produce?
Pumpkin is fresh produce!
[ Both panting ]
It's just onions?
Pumpkin would never
associate
with this
inferior sphere.
-Aah!
Uh, Onion?
What are you --
Hey, is that my hat?
Well, that was a bust.
We'll never find Pumpkin.
Peridot...
[ Rustling ]
Pumpkin?
[ Whimpers ]
Have you been here
the whole time?!
She was hiding?
Come on, Pumpkin.
We need to leave.
[ Whimpers ]
Pumpkin!
Don't you walk away
while I'm talking
to you.
[ Whimpers, barking ]
[ Grunting ]
Sometimes, you have to do things
you don't want to do,
like get jettisoned into
space to live forever
on a floating rock
with a barn,
and just us for as long
as time exists!
Lapis needs us!
Peridot, give her a second.
She's doing it to herself!
Pumpkin, do as you're told!
Aah!
[ Whimpers ]
Whoa, Peridot.
It sounds like you
don't really want to go.
I'm sorry, Pumpkin.
I didn't mean
to yank you around.
It's just we don't have
a choice in this.
What do you mean,
you don't have a choice?
Peridot, you should really
talk to Lapis about this.
I can't.
What? Why not?
Oh, great.
You found her!
Now, let's go.
♪♪
[ Shivering ]
[ Shivers ]
Wait...Lapis?
Pumpkin doesn't want to go.
Pumpkin doesn't
know better.
We do.
Actually, I...
I don't want to go either.
What?!
-Aah!
-Ooh-whoa!
-[ Yelps ]
Peridot, what are you
trying to say?
It's just, if something
happens on Earth,
I want to be here for it!
But -- no!
Why are you
telling me this now?!
Because we're about to leave!
Isn't that the worst time?
Yes.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Then why didn't
you tell me sooner?
Well, there are many
things I should say,
but they would upset you,
so in general,
I don't say those things.
Peridot, that's lying!
[ Groaning ]
Okay, then! The truth is...
I think that we should stay,
and if -- and if the time comes,
if the Diamonds do come to wipe
this planet off the star maps,
I think we should fight
for this life we've built
instead of tearing it up
out of the ground!
I think we can win.
I think you can win.
Earth is our home now.
Isn't it worth fighting for?
What do you say, Lapis?
♪♪
I am not getting caught
in the middle
of another war.
♪♪
Wait! No!
You're supposed to
reward me
for my emotional honesty!
[ Sighs ]
[ Insects chirping ]
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
You're all set up,
and you can stay here
as long as you need.
Wow. [ Groans ]
Thanks.
[ Sighs ]
What do we do now?
[ Alarm beeping ]
♪♪
[ Barking ]
Ooh. Hey there, girl.
Yo, Steven!
This a bad time?
Of the three things I have to do
in the sink now,
this is the one
I least mind you seeing.
Ugh, Peridot is still depressed
all up in your B-room?
Yeah. She still hasn't
gotten over Lapis leaving
and taking the barn
with her into space.
I think she just needs
a little more time to herself.
Nope, that's it,
we're getting her out.
Wait, Amethyst!
Uh, Peridot?
[ Country music playing ]
You...feeling
any better?
Uugghhh.
[ Music stops ]
So,
what have you been up to?
[ Mumbling ]
I, uh, couldn't really
hear you there.
[ Groans ]
Nothing.
You've been in this bathroom
kind of a long time.
Maybe you should
get some fresh air.
What's the point?
To feel better?
Come on, Peridot!
I can't stand seeing you
like this.
Like what?
Dude, let's just get
out of the house.
We could go check out
my old kindergarten!
We met all those other Amethysts
up in space,
and they all came out of
the same rock as me.
I've been meaning to get a look
at the old neighborhood
now that I've met
the neighbors.
That sounds fun.
What do you say, Peridot?
you can make us feel dumb
by telling us all the stuff
we don't know!
I miss that.
Great, it's settled!
Let's get out of
the bathroom.
-Can I bring my music?
-[ Whimpers ]
No.
♪♪
Ugh.
Why exactly are we taking
this outdated,
clackity ship there?
The prime kindergarten has
a very convenient warp pad.
Eh, we're taking
the scenic route!
Come on, Peridot! Take a look
at the beautiful countryside.
No.
Your efforts to entrance me
with Earth's beauty
are pointless.
My sector of countryside
was perfect.
Now it's somewhere in space.
Just let me know
when we get there.
Good ol' kindergarten!
Just the way I left it!
Aw,
some things never change!
Gah, actually,
everything's different now!
Man, I-I used to think this
place was full of empty holes,
but now it's like
it's empty with holes
which were once full!
All those Amethysts
I met in space --
they were all here!
While I was right there
in the ground.
But now I can finally start
putting some faces to holes!
Hohohoh, let's see...
Hup!
This must've been 8XJ!
Ooh!
8XK!
8XL!
Peridot: Actually, the order
goes from top to bottom.
That's 8XJ.
Really?
Yes.
Curly hair, right?
Yeah! How'd you know?
You can tell from the iron
deposits in the formation there.
And that's 8XL
down below.
Whoa, that's pretty amazing,
Dot.
This used to
make sense to me.
I thought life was generated
in a kindergarten.
Formless, aimless energy
channeled into
new, useful gems.
But life doesn't start
in a kindergarten.
It ends here.
I've gotten used to
plants everywhere.
Bugs and breeze
and sunshine...
all of that has been
sucked out of this place.
It's with the Amethysts
that were produced here,
and now this place is
nothing but a miserable husk.
All of the Amethysts
are gone.
Hey!
Oh, all the well-made Amethysts
are gone.
Yo, not better.
And nothing will ever
grow here again,
not even this flower.
Wait!
Oh!
I've never seen anything
growing here,
and I've been hanging around
this joint for 5,000 years.
Man,
it looks healthy, too.
Wow!
That's Earth for you --
always bouncing back.
I don't know.
I'd have to run some tests
to see if this is
not an anomaly.
You want to try
planting stuff here?
You know how to farm!
Yeah,
that could be fun!
It could be
an interesting experiment.
Yeah! Let's re-garden
the kindergarten!
[ Zing! ]
♪♪
[ Gulls crying ]
[ Alarm beeping ]
♪♪
Peridot: They don't need
any more water after yesterday,
but according to...
-Ahh.
...several tutorials I read,
the roots should be
starting to take hold.
Oh, yeah?
So that's something
we can check for today,
as soon as --
Steven!
What are you doing
in that bathing gown?!
Get dressed already!
Oh, uh, right.
[ Train whistle blows ]
Do you think
they grew much overnight?
Yeah, I bet the place
looks even better!
We should plant
even more stuff.
What do you think
we should do next?
What about hydrangeas?
Uh, which one's that?
I don't know,
but it sounds good, right?
What do you think,
Peridot?
Hey, thanks for
doing this with me.
What? Haha, come on.
It was fun.
I'm just glad
I was able to fix something.
Yeah, the kindergarten looks
better than ever!
[ Wind whistling ]
Well, I don't know
why I'm surprised.
I should've known
not to have hope.
But maybe
if we try again...
It's not going to work!
It's never going to work,
okay?!
Hey, don't be a jerk!
We were just trying to
cheer you up.
And good job with that!
I feel just great
now that I know
that nothing's ever
going to get better!
Everything is just
ruined forever!
We can't get
any of it back!
Not my home! Not Lapis!
And not this crummy planet,
either!
We might as well just
throw it all in the garbage
and toss ourselves in after,
because it's
all just hopeless trash!
Peridot, maybe the sunflowers
didn't work,
but we know
something can grow here.
This clod's just like us!
Too dumb
to get with the program!
[ Squish! ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Rumbling ]
Uhhh.
-Uh?
-Waaaa!
[ Crack! ]
[ Roars ]
Oh, of course!
Peridot!
[ Roars ]
Whoa!
[ Panting ]
Want to
get this together?
Let's do it!
♪♪
[ Roaring ]
I need to
go to the bathroom.
Man, you were right.
The kindergarten really is
dead forever.
I was a fool to think we could
reinstitute life there.
[ Sighs ]
Tell me about it.
All right. I will.
I was pretty much using this
as a distraction
from losing Lapis,
losing the barn,
and just a general sense of
complete hopelessness
I tend to deal with
on a day-to-day basis.
But it really only
confirmed for me
that once you mess something up,
it's ruined for good
and nothing will ever
be able to grow again.
Yeah, we got the subtext.
Oh, wow.
What about all this?
Now that's some plants.
Huh.
Guess the countryside out here
is pretty beautiful.
But who cares?
I wanted to have this
for the kindergarten!
Even if there was nothing we can
do for that one patch of land,
there's still a whole Earth
blooming all around us.
Yeah!
Why don't we try gardening
in literally any other place?
It'll be easier than trying to
plant in the kindergarten.
That dirt doesn't care
how green your thumb is.
Green thumb!
'Cause you're green.
[ Laughs ]
I know that!
So, are ya in?
Um...
Do it, do it, do it,
say yes!
Ugh. Fine. I've got literally
nothing else to do.
Oh, yeah!
Yay!
♪♪