>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Pearl: WOW.
THOSE WATER CONSTRUCTS REALLY
DID A NUMBER ON GREG'S VAN.
HMM.
>> Amethyst: EH, GIVE IT A REST,
PEARL.
THAT THING WILL BE BUSTED
FOREVER.
>> Pearl: I COMPLETELY DISAGREE.
IT'S JUST A SIMPLE HUMAN
MACHINE.
I'M SURE I CAN FIGURE THIS WHOLE
THING OUT BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
>> Steven: HEY, GUYS!
>> ZOOP!
I'VE GOT SOMETHING THAT'LL PATCH
THIS VAN UP REAL GOOD.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
IS IT SOME KIND OF COMPLEX HUMAN
TOOL?
>> YEP -- HIGH-QUALITY DUCT
TAPE.
SOME WELL-PLACED DUCT TAPE CAN
PATCH ANYTHING UP IN A PINCH.
SEE?
>> Pearl: I'M SURE I CAN FIX
THIS WITHOUT YOUR TAPE.
>> WELL, GEE.
LET ME AT LEAST GIVE YOU A HAND.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: UH, DAD, BE CAREFUL!
>> WHEW!
>> Steven: I'M SORRY YOU HURT
YOUR LEG AND YOUR VAN GOT ALL
SMASHED UP BECAUSE OF ME.
>> [ Chuckling ] YOU APOLOGIZE
TOO MUCH.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T HAVE TAGGED
ALONG ON THAT CRAZY ADVENTURE,
BUT AT LEAST I GOT TO SPEND SOME
TIME WITH MY FAVE GUY.
>> Steven: WHAT IF YOU STAYED
WITH US UNTIL YOU GOT BETTER?
>> HEY, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
BUT WON'T I GET IN THE WAY OF
YOUR TRAINING?
>> Pearl: YES.
>> Amethyst: WAIT.
STEVEN, DON'T YOU HAVE HEALING
POWERS NOW?
>> Pearl: OH, RIGHT! YES!
YOU FIX GREG. I'LL FIX THE VAN.
NOBODY HAS TO LIVE WITH US.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YEAH!
HMM-HMM!
HERE GOES SOMETHING NEW AND
EXCITING.
HMM! MM! [ SLURPS ]
AND...GO!
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
OKAY. YOU SHOULD BE BETTER NOW.
>> OKAY. IF YOU SAY SO.
[ GROANS ]
UGH-AHH!
>> Steven: DAD!
WHY DIDN'T IT WORK?
>> HEY, SORRY, BUDDY.
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED A LITTLE
MORE PRACTICE.
>> Steven: BUT I WAS DOING SO
WELL BEFORE.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
YOUR POWERS ARE A BIT FICKLE,
AFTER ALL.
>> Garnet: JUST GIVE IT A BIT
MORE TIME.
>> CHEER UP, STEVEN.
AT LEAST NOW WE GET TO SPEND
MORE TIME TOGETHER, RIGHT?
>> Steven: Y-YEAH. RIGHT.
>> Garnet: HMM.
>> Pearl: GARNET, CAN YOU GIVE
ME A HAND?
[ WHAM! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: ♪ DEAR OLD DAD,
REMEMBER WHEN ♪
♪ YOU'D SING TO ME? ♪
♪ WILL YOU DO IT AGAIN? ♪
♪ DEAR OLD DAD, REMEMBER HOW ♪
♪ I WOULD SIT ON YOUR
SHOULDERS? ♪
♪ WELL, HOW 'BOUT IT NOW? ♪
♪ DEAR OLD DAD, I WAS WONDERING
WHY ♪
♪ AS I GET OLDER NOW, THE DAYS
KEEP GOING ON BY ♪
♪ DEAR OLD DAD, REMEMBER THIS,
TOO ♪
♪ IN THIS WHOLE WIDE WORLD,
THERE'S NO ONE LIKE
YO-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-U ♪
♪ THERE'S NO ONE LIKE
>> ♪ MY DARLING SON, I REMEMBER
WHEN ♪
♪ I WOULD SING TO YOU, AND I
WOULD DO IT AGAIN ♪
♪ BELOVED CHILD, REMEMBER THIS,
TOO ♪
♪ IN THIS WORLD OF GEMS,
THERE'S NO ONE LIKE
YO-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-U ♪
>> Both: ♪ YO-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-U ♪
♪ YO-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-U ♪
[ SONG ENDS ]
>> Amethyst: BOMBS AWAY!
>> UGH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> Pearl: AHH.
OHH.
AHH.
>> Garnet: YOU'RE BACK.
THE GEODE IS CRACKED.
WE MUST LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
>> Amethyst: OH, NO.
>> Garnet: YOU, TOO, STEVEN.
>> Steven: YEAH!
>> OH, REALLY?
>> Steven: OH! OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S OKAY, STEVEN.
I'LL BE FINE.
YOU GO ON YOUR MISSION.
>> Steven: A-ARE YOU SURE?
>> OF COURSE.
>> Steven: THANKS, DAD!
WE'LL BE BACK BEFORE YOU KNOW
IT!
>> OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT YOUR OLD MAN.
MY LEG'S NOT GETTING ANY MORE
BROKEN.
IF I NEED SOMETHING, I'LL
JUST...CRAWL.
MY ARMS ARE STILL NOT BROKEN.
>> Amethyst: OH, BROTHER.
>> Pearl: NOW, GREG, THERE'S NO
NEED TO BE SO PATHETIC.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS TO YOU, YOU
CAN CALL US WITH THIS.
[ TWINKLE! ]
>> [ GASPS ] WHAT IS IT?
>> Garnet: IT'S A WARP WHISTLE.
>> WARP WHISTLE.
>> Garnet: IF YOU BLOW IN IT,
THE WARP PAD WILL ACTIVATE AND
ALERT US THAT WE NEED TO RETURN.
>> Steven: SEE, DAD?
YOU'LL BE FINE!
>> [ SIGHS ]
RIGHT. I'LL BE FINE.
GOOD LUCK ON YOUR MISSION, SON.
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
>> Amethyst: MAN.
THIS PLACE IS JANKED UP.
>> Steven: WOW!
WAS THERE AN EXPLOSION OR
SOMETHING?
>> Garnet: ALMOST.
>> Pearl: WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING AT
IS A SYNTHETIC STORM THAT WAS
CONTAINED IN --
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
>> Amethyst: IS THAT THE WARP
WHISTLE?
>> Steven: AAH! DAD NEEDS ME!
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
[ TWINKLE! ]
DAD, I'M HERE!
IS EVERYTHING --
>> HEY, STEVEN!
JUST MAKING SURE THIS THING
ACTUALLY WORKS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: WHEW! OKAY.
WE'LL BE BACK LATER.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
SORRY FOR THE HOLDUP!
>> Pearl: IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> Amethyst: HEY, DID GREG FALL
DOWN AND BREAK HIS BUTT?
HA HA!
>> Garnet: THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
>> Amethyst: I KNOW.
>> Pearl: LIKE I WAS SAYING,
THIS IS A SYNTHETIC --
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
>> Steven: I'M SURE IT'S VERY
IMPORTANT.
[ TWINKLE! ]
DAD?!
>> I'M REALLY SORRY, BUT...
WHERE'S THE REMOTE?
>> Steven: THAT'S ACTUALLY A
VERY IMPORTANT QUESTION.
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
IT WAS VERY IMPORTANT.
>> Pearl: OKAY.
SO, IF THE GEODE BREAKS, THE
STORM WILL BE UNLEASHED AND OUR
BODIES WILL BE VAPORIZED.
>> Steven: THEN WE'D BE DEAD.
>> Garnet: THAT'S WHERE YOU
COME IN.
>> Steven: SAY WHAT?!
>> Garnet: YOU SHOULD TRY AND
SEAL THAT CRACK WITH YOUR
HEALING POWERS.
>> Steven: BUT...WHAT IF...
I CAN'T DO IT?
>> Garnet: IT WON'T HURT TO TRY.
>> Steven: OKAY.
[ SLURPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S NOT WORKING!
UGH!
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN -- JUST
WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS GETTING
BETTER.
>> Garnet: DON'T BEAT YOURSELF
UP, STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: YEAH!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
>> Pearl: WE'LL FIND ANOTHER
WAY.
>> Steven: EH.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO CALL MYSELF
A CRYSTAL GEM IF I CAN'T EVEN --
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
[ GASPS ]
DAD? DAD?!
DA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-D!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
DAD, ARE YOU OKAY?!
ANSWER ME!
>> AHH! STEVEN!
YOU JUST MISSED THE FUNNIEST
COMMERCIAL.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
IT WAS THAT ONE FOR THE DOG
TREATS WHERE THE DOG'S DRESSED
UP LIKE A DOCTOR.
[ LAUGHS ]
IF I EVER GET HEARTWORMS, I'M
EATING THOSE DOG TREATS.
>> Steven: DAD!
YOU'RE ONLY SUPPOSED TO USE THE
WARP WHISTLE FOR REAL
EMERGENCIES, LIKE IF YOU FELL
DOWN AND BROKE YOUR BUTT!
>> [ Chuckling ] YEAH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ]
IT'S OKAY.
>> UH...SINCE YOU'RE HERE,
YOU -- YOU MIND GRABBING ME A
SNACK FROM THE BIG DONUT?
>> Steven: YEAH. SURE THING.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, YOU GUYS.
>> Garnet: WE'LL BE IN THE
TEMPLE.
>> Pearl: WE HAVE TO COME UP
WITH ANOTHER PLAN -- QUICK.
>> Amethyst: YO, DUDE, NO
WORRIES ABOUT EARLIER.
YOU'LL GET AHOLD OF YOUR POWERS
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
>> Steven: THANKS, AMETHYST.
>> Amethyst: GET ME A CROISSANT.
>> Steven: AWW!
I FORGOT TO ASK DAD WHAT KIND OF
DONUTS HE WANTS.
AHH.
HEY, DAD, I --
>> [ HUMMING ]
OLé!
STEVEN!
HA! YOU HAD ME SCARED THERE,
SON.
DIDN'T SEE YOU STANDING IN THE
DOORWAY.
YOUR OLD MAN'S STILL GOT IT!
WHAT, THIS?
I GUESS I COULDN'T WAIT FOR
THOSE DONUTS.
OH. OH, YEAH.
OH-HO-HO-HO!
OUCH!
OH-HO-HO-HO-HO!
>> Steven: JUST STOP, DAD.
I GET WHAT'S GOING ON.
YOUR LEG'S NOT BROKEN AT ALL,
IS IT?
>> IT WAS BROKEN, BUT YOU HEALED
IT BACK AT THE CAR WASH.
>> Steven: YOU LIED TO ME!
NOW I CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE!
>> WHAT?!
>> Steven: THE GEMS NEEDED ME TO
FIX THE BROKEN ROCK, BUT MY
POWERS AREN'T WORKING!
IT -- IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU!
YOU MESSED WITH MY HEAD!
>> NO! I-I DIDN'T MEAN FOR --
I JUST WANTED TO LIVE WITH MY
SON AGAIN!
>> Steven: I REALLY THOUGHT I
WAS GETTING BETTER.
I FINALLY FELT LIKE A
CRYSTAL GEM!
NOW WHAT IF I CAN'T DO...
ANYTHING?
>> STEVEN, DON'T BEAT
YOURSELF UP!
THIS IS MY FAULT!
>> Steven: YEAH! YEAH, IT IS!
UGH!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?!
MY POWERS -- THEY'RE --
I'M SORRY.
I -- [ GASPS ]
DAD!
>> IT'S TIME FOR ME TO FIX THE
TROUBLE I'VE CAUSED.
>> Steven: NO!
>> [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ WHISTLE PLAYS ]
>> Steven: DAD!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPS ]
DAD! BE CAREFUL!
>> DON'T WORRY, STEVEN!
YOUR OLD MAN'S GONNA -- AAAH!
>> Steven: DAD!
>> OOH! AHH! UHH!
OHH!
>> Steven: ARE YOU OKAY?
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
>> STEVEN, GET OUT OF HERE!
I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS!
>> Steven: NO, YOU'RE NOT!
>> BUT I MESSED UP YOUR POWERS!
I DID EVERYTHING I'M NOT
SUPPOSED TO DO, AND NOW YOU
CAN'T HEAL!
>> Steven: I HEALED YOU, RIGHT?
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
>> HEY, GET IN THERE AND PATCH
THINGS UP, JUST LIKE YOU PATCHED
UP YOUR OLD MAN!
[ ZAPPING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: DOUBLE HEALING
[SLURPS] POWERS!
UGH!
[ ZAPPING CONTINUES ]
IT'S STILL NOT WORKING!
>> AH, FORGET IT!
I'VE GOT ANOTHER IDEA!
[ CREAKING ]
[ ZAPPING STOPS ]
THERE. SEE?
ALMOST AS GOOD AS NEW.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
NO WAY.
>> Pearl: SO, I'VE REALIGNED THE
AXLES...
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
>> Pearl: ...REPLACED THE SPARK
PLUGS...
>> IT'S NEVER LOOKED THIS GOOD!
>> Pearl: ...SEALED THE LEAKS IN
THE INTAKE MANIFOLD GASKETS,
AND RECALIBRATED THE TIMING
BELT.
AS LONG AS YOU EASE UP ON SECOND
GEAR, YOUR TRANSMISSION SHOULD
BE FINE.
>> PEARL!
I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
>> Pearl: [ WHIMPERING ]
>> SO, UH, NOW THAT I'M FEELING
BETTER, IT'S ABOUT TIME I MOVE
BACK HOME.
CAN'T HAVE ME MESSING UP MORE
MAGIC STUFF.
JUST IN CASE YOU HAVE TROUBLE
AGAIN.
>> Steven: GOOD NIGHT, DAD.
>> GOOD NIGHT, STEVEN!
[ POP! ]
>> Steven: WHOA.
>> Garnet: INACTIVE.
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
INACTIVE.
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Pearl: INACTIVE.
>> Amethyst: DO WE HAVE TO CHECK
ALL OF THEM?
THEY'RE ALL STILL INACTIVE,
LIKE ALWAYS.
>> Garnet: WE NEED TO MAKE SURE.
>> Steven: I'VE NEVER SEEN SO
MANY WARP PADS BEFORE!
I HOPE I HAVE ENOUGH OF THESE
CRYING BREAKFAST FRIEND
STICKERS.
WHERE DO ALL THESE WARP PADS GO,
ANYWAY?
>> Pearl: WELL, STEVEN, THESE
WARP PADS WERE USED TO TRAVEL
OFF-PLANET.
THEY WERE OUR CONNECTION TO THE
GEM HOME WORLD AND TO
GEM-CONTROLLED PLANETS ALL OVER
THE UNIVERSE.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
YOU MEAN WE COULD GO ANYWHERE WE
WANT IN OUTER SPACE?
>> Amethyst: YEAH, WE COULD DO
THAT IF THEY WEREN'T ALL BUSTED.
>> Pearl: IT'S TRUE.
THE GALAXY WARPS HAVE ALL BEEN
INACTIVE FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
>> Steven: CAN'T WE FIX THEM?
>> Garnet: NO.
>> Pearl: IT'S FINE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'LL ALWAYS HAVE MY MEMORIES OF
OTHER WORLDS.
BUT NOW I'M HERE...ON EARTH...
FOREVER.
>> Steven: WITH ME!
>> Pearl: RIGHT. WITH YOU.
IT REALLY IS INCREDIBLE OUT
THERE, THOUGH.
I WISH YOU COULD SEE IT, STEVEN.
>> [ CRYING ]
[ BOTH CRYING ]
[ ALL CRYING ]
>> STAY TUNED FOR ANOTHER
EPISODE OF
"CRYING BREAKFAST FRIENDS."
>> YEESH. I MUST BE GETTING OLD.
I USED TO LIKE CARTOONS.
>> Steven: HEY, DAD, DID YOU
KNOW THE GEMS USED TO TRAVEL ALL
OVER OUTER SPACE?
>> [ CHUCKLES ] YEAH.
THEY'RE PRETTY FAR OUT, SON.
>> Steven: I THINK PEARL REALLY
MISSES GOING OUT THERE.
[ GASPS ]
DAD, CAN YOU HELP ME BUILD A
SPACESHIP?
>> YOU KNOW, THAT MIGHT BE A
LITTLE OUTSIDE MY SKILL SET.
HOW 'BOUT A BUNK BED WITH WINGS?
I COULD PROBABLY DO THAT.
>> Steven: NO WAY!
WE COULD TOTALLY BUILD A
SPACESHIP!
PEOPLE HAVE DONE IT BEFORE, AND
WE'RE PEOPLE.
>> WE ARE PEOPLE.
>> Steven: AND PEARL WOULD LOVE
IT SO MUCH TO SEE SPACE AGAIN.
>> SURE. WHY NOT?
HOW HURT COULD WE GET?
MY AUNT AND UNCLE HAD A GREAT
LOVE FOR AVIATION AND EACH
OTHER.
THEY CHERISHED THE YEARS THEY
SPENT TOGETHER, AND THEY HELD ON
TO EVERY BELONGING THEY EVER
OWNED -- KIND OF LIKE ME AND MY
STORAGE SHED.
I'M STARTING TO THINK OUR FAMILY
HAS A PROBLEM.
>> Steven: THIS IS GREAT!
I HEREBY DECLARE THIS BARN TO
BE UNIVERSE & UNIVERSE'S
UNIVERSE OF SPACE TRAVEL HQ!
OKAY. NOW.
>> Pearl: "UUU SPACE TRAVEL"?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> Steven: WE BUILT A SPACESHIP!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: A SPACESHIP?
>> Steven: A SPACESHIP!
[ BIRDS CAWING AND CHIRPING ]
>> NOW, REMEMBER, STEVEN, IF YOU
RUN IN TO ANY TROUBLE OUT THERE,
YOU CAN ALWAYS BAIL.
THERE'S NEVER ANY SHAME IN
BAILING.
>> Steven: FATHERLY ADVICE
UNDERSTOOD!
THANK YOU, DAD.
LIGHT THE ENGINES.
>> ROGER THAT!
>> Steven: NEXT STOP -- OUTER
SPACE!
>> BLAST-OFF!
>> Steven: UH!
OOH! UHH!
>> Pearl: AAH!
>> Steven: NO SHAME!
AAH!
>> Pearl: I THINK YOUR
CALCULATIONS MAY HAVE BEEN OFF.
>> WELL, THEY CAN'T BE OFF IF
YOU DON'T DO ANY.
>> Pearl: DID YOU REALLY THINK
THIS WAS GONNA WORK?
>> Both: MNH-MNH-MNH.
>> Pearl: HERE. LOOK.
YOU NEED SMOOTH, CURVING
SURFACES.
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
GET ENOUGH SPEED TO BREAK
EARTH'S GRAVITATIONAL PULL.
PROBABLY SWEPT-BACK WINGS FOR
SUPERSONIC FLIGHT, AIRTIGHT
COCKPIT WITH EJECTOR SEAT, AND
WE'LL NEED SOME SERIOUS ENGINES,
OR MAYBE ROCKETS WOULD BE
BETTER.
>> Steven: I VOTE ROCKETS!
>> WHOA, WHOA. HOLD ON A SEC.
WE'RE NOT ACTUALLY TALKING ABOUT
BUILDING SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
RIGHT?
>> Pearl: WHAT?! THIS?
[ LAUGHS ] OF COURSE NOT.
THAT WOULD BE RIDICULOUS.
I MEAN, YES, THEORETICALLY, IT'S
NOT A STRETCH.
YOU'VE GOT PLENTY OF SPARE PARTS
HERE, ALBEIT FOR INCREDIBLY
PRIMITIVE PROPULSION-BASED SPACE
TRAVEL.
THE IDEA IS LUDICROUS.
IT WOULD NEVER WORK, ALTHOUGH
SEVERAL HUMANS, A MONKEY, AND A
DOG DID MAKE IT INTO SPACE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I'VE NEVER EVEN
THOUGHT OF IT BEFORE.
THIS COULD ACTUALLY WORK!
>> Both: UH...
>> Pearl: I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, AND I AGREE -- IT WOULD
BE INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS, A
FOOL'S ERRAND.
THIS CHAIR IS DISGUSTING.
BUT AREN'T THE TRUE FOOLS THE
ONES WHO DON'T SEIZE AN
OPPORTUNITY, DESPITE ALL THE
INHERENT RISKS?
AND I'D BE ABLE TO SHOW STEVEN
THE WONDERS OF THE COSMOS!
AND MAYBE JUST FOR A SECOND,
FROM A DISTANCE, I COULD SEE
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON WITHOUT ME.
ALL RIGHT! LET'S DO IT!
>> Steven: OOH, SPACE TRAVEL!
G-O-O-O-O-O!
[ LAUGHS ]
WAH-O-O-O-O-O-O-OO!
>> GROUND CONTROL TO MACH 2.
COME IN, MACH 2.
HOW YOU DOING, BUDDY?
>> Steven: AAH! AAH-AAH-AAH-AAH!
WOW! [ MUTTERING ]
>> YOU THINK WE'RE TAKING THIS A
LITTLE FAR?
>> Pearl: WE'RE NOT EVEN CLOSE
TO BEING DONE.
>> WE'RE NOT?
>> Pearl: OKAY, STEVEN.
GO AHEAD AND BRING HER DOWN.
[ ENGINE BACKFIRES ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ SPROING! ]
>> Steven: UGH! WHOO!
>> WAS IT SUPPOSED TO FALL APART
LIKE THAT?
>> Pearl: DON'T WORRY.
THIS WAS JUST TO TEST MY ENGINE
CONCEPT.
I'LL WORK OUT THE KINKS IN THE
NEXT ONE.
>> HANG ON. HANG ON. NEXT ONE?!
>> Pearl: IS THERE A SHOP IN
TOWN THAT CARRIES F-1
SINGLE-NOZZLE LIQUID-FUELED
ROCKETS?
>> YOU REALLY ARE SERIOUS!
>> Pearl: OF COURSE!
WE'RE ALSO GOING TO NEED A
SPACE SUIT FOR STEVEN SO HE
DOESN'T FREEZE OR EXPLODE.
>> Steven: [ IMITATES
EXPLOSION ]
>> WHOA.
YOU ARE NOT TAKING HIM TO SPACE.
>> Pearl: YES, I AM.
>> NO! I'M NOT ALLOWING IT!
>> Steven: BUT WHY?
THIS IS WHY WE FOUNDED
UNIVERSE & UNIVERSE!
>> STEVEN, YOU'RE GROUNDED.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> NO, NO.
I MEAN YOU'RE GROUNDED.
YOU DON'T GET TO LEAVE EARTH.
>> Steven: OH. WHAT?!
>> AS C.E.O. AND SUPREME SPACE
COMMANDER, I HEREBY GROUND THIS
ASTRONAUT AND CANCEL THIS
MISSION.
>> Steven: AW, MAN!
STUPID COMPANY BY-LAWS.
>> Pearl: HEY!
WHO MADE YOU C.E.O.?!
>> HE DID.
>> Pearl: FINE.
IF NEITHER OF YOU WILL HELP,
I'LL JUST DO IT BY MYSELF -- NOT
LIKE IT'LL BE MUCH DIFFERENT.
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> I'M SORRY, BUD.
SOMETIMES YOU JUST GOT TO KNOW
WHEN TO BAIL.
[ MUTTERING ]
>> Steven: [ SNORING ]
WHA?
>> Pearl: SHH! WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING REALLY COOL?
>> [ SNORING ]
NO. DON'T GIVE HIM A BANANA.
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS.
>> Pearl: PRESENTING THE
BRAND-NEW
BALLISTIC-FLIGHT-CAPABLE
UNIVERSE MACH 3!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
SPACESHIP!
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
>> Pearl: WAIT, STEVEN.
KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS, LAUGHS ]
WHOA! IT'S EVEN GOT THE LOGO
FROM THE VAN!
>> Pearl: AND IF YOUR DAD ASKS,
WE'LL SAY WE BORROWED IT.
>> Steven: WHOA.
LOOK AT ALL THE BUTTONS!
I MUST PRESS THEM ALL.
>> Pearl: IF YOU WANT, STEVEN,
WE COULD TAKE HER OUT FOR AN
ENGINE CHECK.
[ TWINKLE! ]
IT'LL BE QUICK.
[ RUMBLING ]
>> WHA?!
WHAT THE...?
PEA-A-A-A-RL!
STEVEN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ BOOM! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
WOW! LOOK!
YOU CAN SEE THE TEMPLE!
>> Pearl: MM-HMM.
>> HEY, CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
WHERE DO YOU TWO THINK YOU'RE
GOING?!
>> Steven: HEY, DAD, GUESS WHERE
I AM.
>> I KNOW WHERE YOU ARE!
IT'S WHERE YOU'RE GOING THAT
CONCERNS ME!
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY, DAD.
THIS IS JUST A QUICK TEST
FLIGHT.
>> Pearl: THIS WILL BE PERFECTLY
FINE -- JUST A POP OVER TO THE
NEAREST STAR SYSTEM.
I'LL GIVE HIM BACK IN 50 YEARS.
>> Steven: 50 YEARS?
>> WHAT?!
I'LL BE DEAD IN 50 YEARS!
PEARL, YOU BRING HIM BACK RIGHT
NOW, OR I'LL --
HELLO? HELLO?!
>> Steven: PEARL, I'M NOT
SUPPOSED TO GO.
PEARL!
>> Pearl: OH, THIS IS SO
EXCITING!
STEVEN, YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT.
[ NOTES PLAY ]
[ DISCORDANT CHORD PLAYS ]
HANG ON TIGHT!
>> Steven: MM!
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ ALARM BLARING ]
PEARL!
>> Pearl: WE CAN MAKE IT.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> Steven: PEARL!
>> Pearl: I'M GONNA SHOW IT TO
YOU.
>> Steven: UH...UH...
[ BLARING CONTINUES ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> Steven: WE NEED TO GO, PEARL!
WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT!
>> Pearl: BUT WE'RE ALMOST
THERE!
>> Steven: PEARL!
I KNOW YOU MISS SPACE, AND I
KNOW YOU WORKED HARD, BUT
SOMETIMES YOU JUST GOT TO KNOW
WHEN TO BAIL.
>> N-O-O-O-O-O-O-O!
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE.
AHHHH.
OHHHHH.
OHH, THIS KID'S KILLING ME.
UGHHHH!
>> Pearl: I'M SO SORRY.
I ALMOST GOT US KILLED.
>> Steven: I'M USED TO IT.
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T HELP YOU GO
TO SPACE.
WE'LL GET THERE SOMEDAY -- I
PROMISE.
>> Pearl: YOU KNOW, I THINK I'D
RATHER BE HERE ON EARTH.
>> Steven: WITH ME!
>> Pearl: YEAH. WITH YOU.