>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
SHIELD.
[ WARBLE! WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
NO, NOT BUBBLE -- SHIELD!
[ GROANS ]
UGH.
[ GROANING ]
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
THE GEMS CAN ALL SUMMON THEIR
WEAPONS.
WHY CAN'T I?!
ISN'T THERE SOMEBODY WHO CAN
HELP ME?!
[ RUMBLING ]
WHA--
[ DOLPHINS CHATTERING ]
HUH?
[ GULPS ] HUH?
WHA--
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: GOOD MORNING!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: BRAVO!
THIS GUY SURE KNOWS HOW TO MAKE
AN ENTRANCE!
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MR. DOLPHIN?
>> [ CHATTERS ]
>> Steven: OH, MY GOSH!
UNCLE GRANDPA!
YOU'RE REALLY HERE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I MEAN, I LITERALLY CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
HOW IS THIS EVEN POSSIBLE?!
>> Uncle Grandpa: DON'T WORRY,
BRO -- NONE OF THIS IS CANON.
BUT THIS IS!
[ CLANK! ]
[ CREAK! POP! WHIP! ]
[ BLAM! ]
[ BOOM! ]
[ WHISTLE! ]
[ FOG HORN BLOWS ]
>> OH, NO!
OUR SHIP!
>> Uncle Grandpa: SO, I HEAR
YOUR BELLY'S BEING A BIT OF A
BUMMER.
>> Steven: YEAH.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO PULL MY
SHIELD OUT OF MY GEM ALL
MORNING.
>> Uncle Grandpa: HMM.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK-SEE.
YOU SHOULD MAKE SURE YOU GET
THIS THING POLISHED AT LEAST
TWICE A YEAR.
[ CLUNK! CLUNK! ]
>> Steven: SO, DO YOU THINK YOU
CAN HELP ME?
I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE TO
PROTECT MY FRIENDS.
>> Uncle Grandpa: HMM. YEP.
IT'S THE BELLY BLUES.
I'VE DEFINITELY SEEN THIS
BEFORE.
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> Uncle Grandpa: I WAS THERE!
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
>> Steven: UH...
>> Uncle Grandpa: WHOA! HEY!
IT'S A RAD NEW CARTOON
PICTURE SHOW!
HEY! HEY! HI, THERE!
>> Steven: AWW! IT WAS FUNNIER
LAST TIME.
>> Uncle Grandpa: GOOD MORNING?
>> Steven: I DON'T REMEMBER THAT
AT ALL.
>> Uncle Grandpa: SO, YOUR
SHIELD ONLY COMES OUT WHEN YOU
NEED TO PROTECT YOURSELF.
>> Steven: YEAH.
>> Uncle Grandpa: WELL, THEN,
YOU JUST NEED SOMETHING TO
PROTECT YOURSELF FROM -- LIKE
THIS COOL MEGA SUPER AWESOME
ROCKET LAUNCHER.
>> Steven: UH, UNCLE GRANDPA,
THIS DOESN'T SEEM SAFE.
>> Uncle Grandpa: DON'T WORRY
KID -- I'M WEARING A HELMET.
[ BOOM! WHISTLE! ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
[ TAP! WHIRL! ]
[ POOF! ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: ANYTHING?
>> Steven: NO.
>> Uncle Grandpa: THEN HOW ABOUT
A BEE-ZOOKA?
>> Steven: AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Uncle Grandpa: OR A SNAKE
SHOOTER?
>> Steven: OHH! OHH! OHH!
>> Uncle Grandpa: OR THE
BEE-ZOOKA AGAIN?
>> Steven: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Uncle Grandpa: HMM.
STILL NOTHIN'.
OH, I KNOW!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, HAVE YOU
SEEN STEVEN THIS MORNING?
>> Amethyst: YEP.
HE'S HANGING OUT WITH SOME
WEIRDO.
I THINK HE'S TRYING TO VAPORIZE
STEVEN.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
[ WARBLE! WARBLE! WARBLE! ]
[ CRANK! ]
STEVEN!
[ BOOM! ]
>> Steven: NO, NOT BUBBLE --
SHIELD!
[ POP! ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: HMM.
I WOULD HAVE SWORN A DOOMTASTIC
DEATH RAY OF DASTARDLY
DESTRUCTION WOULD HAVE WORKED.
YOU WANT TO TRY THE BEES AGAIN?
>> Amethyst: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHO IS THIS STRANGER?
>> Steven: HE'S NOT A STRANGER!
HE'S UNCLE GRANDPA!
[ HONK! HONK! ]
>> Amethyst: UNCLE...GRANDPA?
>> Pearl: SO, THAT WOULD MAKE
HIM GREG'S BROTHER...
AND FATHER?
>> Garnet: THAT WOULD EXPLAIN A
LOT.
>> Belly Bag: THAT'S RIGHT!
HE'S NOT JUST YOUR
UNCLE GRANDPA, STEVEN --
HE'S EVERYONE IN THE WORLD'S
UNCLE GRANDPA!
AND WHEN HE COMES TO TOWN,
YOU'RE SURE TO HAVE A FUN TIME!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
WE'RE IN SPACE!
[ THUD! THUD! THUD! ]
>> Pearl: UGH! EE-EE-EE!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
OHH! UGH!
>> Amethyst: AGH!
MY HEAD IS ON BACKWARDS!
>> Garnet: [ SHUDDERS ]
[ POP! TING! ]
GEM HUDDLE!
>> Pearl: OBVIOUSLY, WE'RE
DEALING WITH SOME SUPERPOWERFUL,
REALITY-WARPING ENTITY.
>> Garnet: HE COULD BE A DANGER
TO THE FABRIC OF SPACE ITSELF.
>> Amethyst: I DON'T KNOW, GUYS.
HEH. I KIND OF LIKE HIM.
>> Steven: HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT?
>> Uncle Grandpa: ARE YOU
FORMING A SECRET CLUB?
>> Both: CAN WE JOIN TOO?
>> All: AAAH!
>> Pearl: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
UM, UNCLE GRANDPA...
>> Uncle Grandpa: GOOD MORNING.
>> Pearl: YES.
WE HAVE DECIDED TO --
>> Uncle Grandpa: PLAY VIDEO
GAMES?
>> Pearl: NO. UH --
>> Uncle Grandpa: RUN AROUND
IN CIRCLES?
>> Pearl: NO.
>> Uncle Grandpa: EAT A
THREE-WAY SUB?
>> Amethyst: YO.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
[ CLEARS THROAT ] NO.
WE HAVE DECIDED --
>> Garnet: THAT YOU ARE A DANGER
TO STEVEN AND THE PLANET EARTH
AND WE MUST DESTROY YOU.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> Uncle Grandpa: BAD MORNING.
>> Steven: WAIT! NO!
YOU GUYS, DON'T HURT HIM!
>> Narrator: CRYSTAL GEMS!
RUN AWAY!
>> Uncle Grandpa: COME ON, KID.
LET'S GO!
>> Amethyst: OOF!
WH-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y?!
>> Steven: I'M SORRY!
THEY'RE NOT USUALLY LIKE THIS!
>> Uncle Grandpa: QUICK!
BELLY BAG, WE NEED A PLOT HOLE!
>> Belly Bag: SURE THING,
UNCLE GRANDPA!
[ WHOOPING ]
[ BOTH PANTING ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: [ PANTING ]
>> Steven: WHERE ARE WE?
>> [ SINGING OPERATICALLY ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: GOOD MORNING!
[ LAUGHING ]
NOW, WHERE'D I PUT THAT LITTLE
KID?
OH, YEAH!
GOOD MORNING!
OH, LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND
THERE.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> Steven: WHOA. WHERE AM I?
>> Uncle Grandpa: WELCOME TO
THE UGRV!
>> Steven: THE WHA?
>> Uncle Grandpa: THE
UNCLE GRANDPA RECREATIONAL
VEHICLE.
>> Steven: OH, COOL!
MY DAD LIVES IN A VAN, TOO!
DID YOU USED TO BE A ROCK STAR?
>> Uncle Grandpa: I'M STILL A
ROCK STAR, KID.
>> Uncle Grandpa #2: HEY,
STEVEN, I'LL GIVE YOU THE TOUR!
>> Steven: WOW! IT'S HUGE!
YOU COULD FIT A MILLION VANS IN
HERE!
>> Uncle Grandpa: ACTUALLY, IT'S
MORE LIKE 40 OR 50 VANS.
SEE?
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ CAT YOWLS ]
[ CAT SHRIEKS ]
>> Pizza Steve: OH, HEY.
IT'S JUST ME, PIZZA STEVE --
JUST THE COOLEST AND TASTIEST
STEVE WHO EVER LIVED.
>> Steven: HI, PIZZA STEVE!
I'M A STEVE, TOO --
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
>> Steven: STEVE-N UNIVERSE?
COME ON, UNCLE G.
I'VE GOT TWO RULES -- NO MORE
THAN 40 OR 50 OR VANS AND ONLY
ONE STEVE ALLOWED!
>> Uncle Grandpa: YEAH, BUT THIS
STEVEN IS SPECIAL.
>> Mr. Gus: YEAH!
HE'S A CRYSTAL GEM!
>> Uncle Grandpa: GOOD MORNING,
MR. GUS.
>> Mr. Gus: WHAT'S UP,
UNCLE GRANDPA?
>> Steven: WHOA! MR. GUS!
HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ME?
>> Mr. Gus: I HAVE A
COMPREHENSIVE KNOWLEDGE OF ALL
MAGICAL DENIZENS OF THE
MULTIVERSE.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT THE
CRYSTAL GEMS.
COME HERE, MAN. CHECK THIS OUT.
I EVEN MADE MY OWN GEMSONA.
MY GEM IS ON MY TAIL, AND MY
WEAPON IS A FRYING PAN.
>> Uncle Grandpa: NICE LINE
WORK, MR. GUS!
>> Steven: THAT'S REALLY COOL,
MR. GUS.
I WISH I WAS AS COOL AS YOUR
DRAWING.
>> Mr. Gus: SOMETHING WRONG?
>> Uncle Grandpa: STEVEN DOESN'T
KNOW HOW TO SUMMON HIS SHIELD.
>> Mr. Gus: YOU DON'T SAY?
OH, THAT'S SIMPLE.
STEVEN'S POWERS ARE MATERNAL.
CONTROL OF HIS GEM IS BASED ON
EMOTIONAL CLARITY.
HIS SHIELD ONLY COMES OUT WHEN
HE'S FEELING EXTREME EMOTIONS
OF --
>> Pizza Steve: HEY, MR. GUS!
I FIXED YOUR DRAWING!
>> Mr. Gus: HEY!
WHY DIDN'T YOU DO THAT ON A NEW
LAYER?!
>> GRFT: [ ROARS ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: OH, HI,
GIANT REALISTIC FLYING TIGER!
YOU GOT ANY ADVICE FOR STEVEN?
>> GRFT: [ ROARS ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: I'M NOT GONNA
TELL HIM THAT.
THAT ONLY WORKS ON CATS.
>> Steven: WELL, NOW WHAT?
>> Uncle Grandpa: WE JUST SIT
HERE UNTIL SOMETHING HAPPENS.
[ VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING ]
SOMETHING HAPPENED!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Belly Bag: [ SLURPS ]
BURP!
[ ALL PANTING ]
>> Garnet: HOO!
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY OUT
OF HERE.
>> Pearl: WE'LL NEVER ESCAPE!
THIS IS OUR NEW HOME!
>> Garnet: PEARL, YOU'RE
OVERREACTING.
>> Pearl: I'M NOT OVERREACTING!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Amethyst: [ YAWNS ]
UGH!
HEY, WHERE'S STEVEN?
>> Pizza Steve: LOOKING FOR ME,
PIZZA STEVEN UNIVERSE?
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
THAT'S NOT MY BABY!
>> Amethyst: AW, NICE!
>> Pizza Steve: WHOA! HOLD ON!
>> Amethyst: PIZZA!
>> Pizza Steve: DON'T EAT
PIZZA STEVE!
>> Garnet: EW.
>> Amethyst: [ MUNCHING ]
[ SLURPS ]
>> Garnet: OKAY.
I'M READY FOR THIS EPISODE TO
END.
UGH!
[ SHATTER! ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: [ SLURPING ]
[ SIGHS ]
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T HELP YOU
LEARN TO USE YOUR SHIELD,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY,
UNCLE GRANDPA.
I HAD A LOT OF FUN TODAY.
>> All: STEVEN!
>> Garnet: GET AWAY FROM THAT
MAN!
>> Pearl: HE'S A MONSTER!
>> Amethyst: [ HISSES ]
>> Steven: HEY, CUT IT OUT,
GUYS!
HE'S DOWN ENOUGH ALREADY!
>> Uncle Grandpa: OH, GOOD
MORNING!
[ CRACK! ]
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
THAT SMARTS.
[ TINK! ]
>> All: FINISH HIM!
>> Steven: NO! DON'T HURT HIM!
[ Slow-motion ] STO-O-O-O-P!
[ TWINKLE! ]
WHOA!
[ CLUNK! ]
I DID IT, UNCLE GRANDPA!
I REALLY DID IT!
>> Uncle Grandpa: YAY!
>> Pearl: PROTECTING HIM
ACTIVATED STEVEN'S POWERS?!
>> Garnet: HE MUST REALLY CARE
ABOUT THIS STRANGER.
>> Amethyst: I HOPE HE DIDN'T
CARE ABOUT THAT PIZZA.
>> Steven: LISTEN!
IT WAS A BIG, WEIRD SURPRISE
WHEN UNCLE GRANDPA SHOWED UP
HERE TODAY.
WE'VE NEVER MET ANYONE LIKE
UNCLE GRANDPA.
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST ATTACK PEOPLE
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE TO STICK UP FOR THEM
AND LISTEN TO WHAT THEY HAVE TO
SAY.
YOU GUYS ALWAYS DO THAT FOR ME.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOW COULD I BE SO BLIND?!
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY!
>> Amethyst: I ALSO APOLOGIZE
FOR PEARL.
>> Garnet: THANK YOU.
YOU'VE TAUGHT US A VALUABLE
LESSON, UNCLE GRANDPA.
>> Uncle Grandpa: WELP, I THINK
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
BYE-BYE!
>> [ ROARS SADLY ]
>> Uncle Grandpa: REMEMBER,
KIDS -- DON'T BE AFRAID TO BE
SUPERWEIRD.
STEVEN AND I HAVE GOT YOUR BACK.
SEE WITH EYES UNCLOUDED BY HATE
AND ALWAYS REMEMBER TO SAY...
"GOOD MORNING!"
BOY, THAT SURE MAKES MY EYES
HURT.
NOW LET'S SEE HERE.
DEXTER, DEE DEE, BLOSSOM,
BUBBLES, BUTTERCUP, ED, EDD,
EDDY, BILLY, MANDY, MAC,
JUNIPER, SWAT KATS, FLAPJACK,
FINN.
AH, STEVEN!
NOW WHO'S NEXT?
[ MID-TEMPO GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: WHOO! GO, DAD!
>> SEE? WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
I MAY BE LOSING MY HAIR, BUT
THE MAGIC'S STILL THERE.
HMM?
>> Steven: WHO'S WITH YOU IN
THIS OLD PICTURE?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S MY PAL MARTY.
>> Steven: YOU'VE NEVER TOLD ME
ABOUT HIM.
>> YEAH, HE'S JUST AN OLD AMIGO
FROM WAY BACK WHEN.
HE'S DEAD TO ME.
>> Steven: WHO WAS HE?
>> HE WAS MY MANAGER BACK WHEN
I FIRST MET YOUR MOM.
I'VE TOLD YOU THAT WHOLE STORY,
HAVEN'T I?
>> Steven: NOT THE VERSION WITH
MARTY.
>> GEESH.
THEN IT'S STORY TIME.
SIT BACK.
GET COMFY.
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT COMFY.
>> Steven: STORY FOR STEVEN!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
THIS IS THE TALE OF HOW YOUR
FATHER MET YOUR MOTHER.
NOW INCLUDING MARTY.
[ UP-TEMPO GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ELECTRIC GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ SOME ♪
♪ SAY I HAVE NO DIRECTION ♪
♪ THAT I'M A LIGHT-SPEED
DISTRACTION ♪
♪ BUT THAT'S A KNEE-JERK
REACTION ♪
♪ STILL ♪
♪ THIS IS THE FINAL FRONTIER ♪
♪ EVERYTHING IS SO CLEAR ♪
♪ TO MY DESTINY I STEER ♪
♪ THIS LIFE IN THE STARS
IS ALL I'VE EVER KNOWN ♪
♪ STARS AND STARDUST AND
INFINITE SPACE IS MY ONLY HOME ♪
♪ BUT THE MOMENT THAT I HIT
THE STAGE ♪
♪ THOUSANDS OF VOICES
ARE CALLING MY NAME ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IN MY HEART IT'S
BEEN WORTH IT ALL OF THE WHILE ♪
♪ AND AS MY ALBUMS FLY OFF
OF THE SHELVES ♪
♪ HANDING OUT AUTOGRAPHED PICS
OF MYSELF ♪
♪ THIS LIFE I CHOSE ISN'T EASY
BUT SURE IS ONE HECK OF A RIDE ♪
♪ AT THE MOMENT THAT I HIT
THE STAGE ♪
♪ I HEAR THE UNIVERSE CALLING
MY NAME ♪
♪ AND I KNOW DEEP DOWN
IN MY HEART ♪
♪ I HAVE NOTHING TO FEAR ♪
♪ AND AS THE SOLAR WIND BLOWS
THROUGH MY HAIR ♪
♪ KNOWING I HAVE SO MUCH MORE
LEFT TO SHARE ♪
♪ A WANDERING SPIRIT
WHO'S TEARING ITS WAY♪
♪ THROUGH THE COLD ATMOSPHERE ♪
♪ I FLY LIKE A COMET ♪
♪ SOAR LIKE A COMET ♪
♪ CRASH LIKE A COMET ♪
♪ I'M JUST A COMET ♪
[ HANDS CLAPPING ]
THANKS FOR COMING, EVERYBODY.
I'M MR. UNIVERSE.
IF YOU LIKED WHAT YOU JUST
HEARD, GO CHECK OUT OUR
MERCH TABLE.
MY MANAGER, MARTY, CAN HOOK
YOU UP WITH CDs AND T-SHIRTS.
OH, WAIT.
HE'S NOT THERE.
I GUESS I'M GOING OVER THERE
NOW.
>> "SPACE TRAIN TO THE COSMOS."
>> YEAH!
♪ ONE-WAY TICKET ♪
♪ AND I'M READY TO RI-I-DE ♪
>> [ Chuckling ] OH.
BUT HOW WILL YOU GET BACK?
>> BACK?
>> BACK TO EARTH?
>> I'M NEVER COMING BACK.
>> UGH, THAT'S AWFUL!
THIS IS YOUR HOME.
>> UH...
YOU WANT THAT?
YOU CAN HAVE IT!
>> HMM?
>> OH, AND IT COMES WITH
A FREE T-SHIRT!
YOU'LL PROBABLY NEED A BIGGER
ONE.
I'VE GOT AN EXTRA EXTRA-LARGE
IN MY VAN.
STAY RIGHT THERE!
>> STARCHILD!
MEET VIDALIA.
>> NICE VAN.
REALLY LIVING THE HIGH LIFE.
>> SO, HOW WAS THE SHOW?
>> IT WAS GREAT!
ONE PERSON SHOWED UP!
OH!
I HAVE TO GIVE HER THIS FREE
T...SHIRT.
>> GREG!
YOU CAN'T GIVE STUFF AWAY FOR
FREE!
WHAT ABOUT MY 75%?
75% OF NOTHING IS NOTHING!
ARE YOU WORTH NOTHING?
>> NO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
I'M GONNA MAKE US BOTH RICH!
AND AS FAR AS THESE SALTWATER
SAPS KNOW, WE ALREADY ARE!
SO LET'S LIVE IT UP BEFORE
WE HIT THE ROAD, ALL RIGHT?
NEXT STOP -- EMPIRE CITY!
>> YOU KNOW...
I'll CATCH UP WITH YOU.
MAYBE SHE'S OVER THERE?
>> Amethyst: WHOOO?
>> OH, JUST SOME GIANT
MYSTERIOUS LADY WITH ENORMOUS
PINK HAIR.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN ANYONE
LIKE THAT AROUND, HAVE YOU?
>> Amethyst: SURE HAVE, PAL.
>> [ GULPS ] WH-WHERE?
>> Amethyst: WELL, UH...
IF I TOLD YOU ANY MORE,
I'D HAVE TO KILL YOU!!
HOO HOO HOO!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> HEY! WAIT!
HOLD ON A SEC!
WHOA! OOH.
[ PANTING ]
>> Amethyst: THIS LONG-HAIRED
HUMAN WAS TALKING TO ME OVER
BY THE FENCE.
>> Pearl: IT SPOKE TO YOU?
>> Amethyst: HE WAS ASKING
ABOUT ROSE.
LOOK! THERE HE IS!
>> YO.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST! WAIT!
>> Amethyst: IT'S YOU!
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS ONE AROUND HERE BEFORE.
OH, I REALLY LIKE YOUR HAIR.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, LEAVE HIM
BE!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE HE'S BEEN!
I'M VERY SORRY ABOUT THIS, UH,
YOU?
>> WHOA!
>> Garnet: OH, AMETHYST.
YOU'RE WITH A HUMAN.
>> Amethyst: HE FOLLOWED ME OVER
THE FENCE.
>> Pearl: WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
>> Garnet: STATE YOUR PURPOSE.
>> UH, I WAS KIND OF LOOKING
FOR THE MYSTERIOUS PINK LADY,
KIND OF REALLY TALL, LOTS OF
BIG, CURLY HAIR.
>> Amethyst: SEE?
HE'S TALKING ABOUT RO--
>> Pearl: I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
MAKE HIM GO AWAY.
>> Garnet: I'LL JUST THROW HIM
BACK OVER THE FENCE.
>> HUH? OH! WHO-O-A!
>> Pearl: EXCELLENT IDEA.
HUMANS SHOULD STAY ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE FENCE LIKE THE SIGN
SAYS.
>> PLEASE! NO THROWING!
>> WAIT!
MR. UNIVERSE?
>> IT'S YOU.
WHOA. OW!
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> Pearl: YOU KNOW THIS HUMAN?!
>> HE WAS PLAYING A CONCERT ON
THE BEACH, AND...I COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
>> NO ONE COULD IGNORE
THE UNIVERSE.
>> OH! I BROUGHT YOU THIS!
IT'S THE FREE T-SHIRT THAT CAME
WITH YOUR FREE CD!
>> WHY, THANK YOU!
His gimmick is space!
>> Pearl: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Amethyst: HEY, PLAY
SOMETHING, MUSIC MAN!
>> Garnet: BETTER MAKE IT GOOD.
>> AW, MAN.
I'M WORKING ON THIS AWESOME
NEW SET.
IT'S GONNA KILL AT MY NEXT SHOW.
"NEXT SHOW"?
AW, GEEZ.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
>> Pearl: NIGHT...TIME?
>> YEAH, MARTY'S PROBABLY
LOOKING FOR ME.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO HIT THE ROAD.
IT'S A BIG SHOW IN A BIG CITY,
AND I DIDN'T DROP OUT OF
COMMUNITY COLLEGE FOR NOTHING!
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> WELL, YOU BETTER HURRY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS YOUR
SPACE TRAIN TO THE COSMOS.
>> OKAY!
I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
UH, I HOPE THE STARS WILL ALIGN
FOR US TO MEET AGAIN!
>> I'M SURE THEY WILL!
>> Amethyst: BYE, MUSIC MAN!
>> Pearl: I CAN SING.
>> Garnet: [ SNICKERS ]
>> Pearl: WHAT?
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
>> MAN, GREG, YOU REALLY
MISSED OUT.
VIDALIA'S FRIENDS WERE WILD
AND CRAZY.
GLAD THAT TOWN WASN'T A TOTAL
WASTE.
>> I MET SOME WILD LADIES, TOO.
THEY CHANGE SHAPE AND APPEAR
OUT OF BEAMS OF LIGHT.
>> AH, AH, AH, AH, AH.
SAVE THE POETRY FOR EMPIRE CITY,
STARCHILD.
WE'VE GOT A BIG DAY AHEAD OF US
TOMORROW.
>> I'M SERIOUS, MARTY.
SOMETHING'S GOING ON BACK THERE.
>> ARE YOU NUTS?
JUST WAIT TILL YOU SEE WHAT'S
AHEAD OF US.
IT'S FAME!
HEY, WHAT'S JAMMED IN YOUR
TAPE DECK?
YOU BEEN PUTTING PENNIES
IN HERE, YOU WEIRDO?
PLAY SOMETHING FOR ME,
STARCHILD.
>> ♪ DO YOU BELIEVE IN
DESTINY? ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES AND LEAVE
THE REST TO ME ♪
>> SNORE!
YOU'RE GONNA PUT PEOPLE TO SLEEP
WITH THAT!
WHERE'S THIS SCHLOCK COMING
FROM?
>> I-I JUST CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT THAT WOMAN AT THE SHOW.
>> OH, HERE WE GO.
HOW BIG WAS SHE?
>> 8 FEET TALL...
MASSIVE HAIR.
>> SEE, GREG, THIS IS YOUR
PROBLEM.
YOU WANT ONE HUGE WOMAN
WHEN YOU CAN HAVE MULTIPLE
SMALLER ONES.
>> UGH.
MARTY, WOMEN ARE PEOPLE.
>> JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
I'M GONNA GET YOU EVERYTHING
YOU WANT.
>> WHAT IF I WANT TO GO BACK?
>> WHAT?!
>> WHAT IF I WANT TO GO BACK
AND BE WITH HER?!
>> NO ONE CARES ABOUT YOUR
FEELINGS, GREG.
THEY'RE MAKING YOU LOSE SIGHT
OF WHAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT!
>> WATCH THE ROAD!
[ HORN BLARES ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
>> [ PANTING ]
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS DECIDE
WHAT'S IMPORTANT?
>> BECAUSE I'M YOUR MANAGER, AND
YOU'RE JUST SOME SPACED-OUT KID!
I'M TAKING YOU TO THE CITY, AND
YOU'RE GONNA PLAY, AND YOU'RE
GONNA LIKE IT.
MAYBE YOU'LL EVEN MAKE ME SOME
MONEY FOR ONCE.
>> GET OUT OF MY VAN.
>> SIT DOWN, GREG.
>> I SAID, GET OUT OF MY VAN!
>> OOH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
YOU'RE MAKING A HUGE MISTAKE!
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
>> HEY!
ARE YOU IN THERE?
I CAN PLAY FOR YOU NOW!
I EVEN REVAMPED MY AWESOME SET!
THIS ONE'S FOR YOU,
MYSTERY WOMAN!
♪ DO YOU BELIEVE IN DESTINY? ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES AND LEAVE
THE REST TO ME ♪
♪ DO YOU BELIEVE IN FANTASY? ♪
♪ I HAVE TO WHEN IT'S
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME, OH ♪
♪ WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? ♪
♪ IN THE REAL WORLD ♪
♪ SO CLOSE I COULD TOUCH YOU ♪
♪ WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? ♪
♪ AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO ME-E-E? ♪
[ WHIR! ]
OH! YOU'RE WEARING THE...
SHIRT.
>> PLEASE GO AWAY.
>> I-I'M SORRY.
DID I...?
>> [ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE AWFULLY CUTE.
AND I REALLY WANT TO PLAY
WITH YOU.
BUT YOUR LIFE IS SHORT, AND YOU
HAVE DREAMS.
I WON'T LET YOU GIVE UP
ON EVERYTHING YOU WANT.
>> WELL, THAT'S GONNA BE
A PROBLEM.
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE EVERYTHING I WANT!
>> [ CHUCKLING ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
>> Steven: YOU LOVED HER!
>> COME HERE, YOU!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHING ]
>> RAH!
>> Steven: OH, MAN.
MARTY WAS THE WORST!
>> OH, YEAH.
HE WAS AWFUL!
BUT I GUESS I OWE HIM A LOT.
HE MADE IT EASY FOR ME TO STAY.
>> Steven: I'M GLAD YOU DID.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
[ POP! ]