[ Computer beeps ]
-Hello?
-Hi, Peridot.
Steven, can you hear me?
-I-I can hear y--
-Can you hear me?!
-I can hear y--
-[ Grumbles ]
How do I
work this stupid thing?
Ahh!
Steven?
Hi, Peridot.
Steven!
[ Laughs ]
Behold
my resourceful genius!
I figured out how to
get Wi-Fi in the barn.
The connection
is fast enough to stream
"Camp Pining Hearts"
in all 1,080 p's.
It took me a while, but let me
tell you how I did it.
-So, I had to go through...
[ Computer beeps ]
Peridot?
So, there I was, face to face
with one of those big --
[ Static squeals ]
-Peridot, you're breaking up.
...running for my life
with nothing but a --
[ Static squeals ]
-And then it bit me!
[ Computer beeps ]
And now the Wi-Fi works
perfectly.
What did you do today?
I learned
how to do this.
What?
Lapis, get over here.
Is that Steven?
-Yes.
-Oh, no! Steven, what happened?
Oh, you guys, it's fine.
It's just a --
How did he
get trapped in there?
Why aren't you
doing something?
Lapis, relax.
It's my communication pad.
Who did this to you?
Steven,
I'll get you out of there.
Where's your gem on this thing?
I-I can't find it!
Lapis?
-What?
-He must be inside.
-Wait. Lapis --
-It's just a screen!
Sto--
-Oh, geez.
[ Pants ]
Oh, thank the stars.
I thought you were a goner.
Step aside, Peridot.
I have to free him.
Lapis, no!
I'll save you,
Steven!
I'll save you
like you saved me!
-Calm down!
-Wait! Stop!
I'm fine!
Steven!
You're okay!
Oh, sorry, Peridot.
It's okay.
Just take it easy with that bat.
Aw, look. It's Lion.
W-Wait, Lion.
Lion, be careful!
Lion, no!
[ Buzz ]
No!
That was Connie's laptop!
Lion!
He should really be more careful
with other people's stuff.
-Mnh.
[ Static squeals ]