♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ BIRDS AND INSECTS CHIRPING ]
IT WAS SO INTENSE
DOWN THERE!
WE WERE ALREADY A FEW LAYERS
INTO THE EARTH'S CRUST
WHEN SUDDENLY --
WA-PAMO! KA-POWIE!
ALL THESE
GROSS CLUSTER LIMBS
STARTED CLAWING
AT THE DRILL!
SO, I WHIP OUT THE OLD
PHOTON BLASTER AND "PEW! PEW!
P-CHOW! CHOW!"
TAKE THAT, CLUSTER!
AND STEVEN WAS ALL,
"MY FEELINGS!"
AND THEN UP
AND PASSES OUT ON ME!
THEN EVERYTHING STARTED GLOWING,
AND...WELL, YEAH, WAIT.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
I'M SURE STEVEN CAN FILL YOU IN
ON THE REST
SINCE HE'S THE ONE
WHO SAVED US.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN IT,
RIGHT, STEVEN?
TELL 'EM
WHAT HAPPENED IN THERE!
STEVEN?
HOLD ON A SEC.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ MURMURS ]
I SEE YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR FRIEND.
YEAH.
WHEN I SAW HER
IN MY DREAMS,
IT LOOKED LIKE
SHE WAS FIGHTING SO HARD
TO KEEP MALACHITE
FROM ESCAPING.
LAPIS SPENT AN UNBEARABLE AMOUNT
OF TIME FUSED WITH JASPER.
THE EMOTIONAL AND PHYSICAL
STRAIN OF THAT TYPE OF FUSION,
I CAN'T IMAGINE.
SHE'S GONNA NEED
A LOT OF TIME TO RECOVER.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
COME ON.
I'M DYING TO HEAR MORE
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
UNDERGROUND.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY.
[ CLATTERING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
LAPIS, YOU'RE OKAY!
STEVEN!
YOU'RE...LEAVING.
I HAVE TO, STEVEN.
I DON'T BELONG ON EARTH,
NOT WITH THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
I NEVER HAVE.
IT'S OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
I JUST WISH
WE COULD'VE HUNG OUT MORE.
I FEEL LIKE
I ONLY GET TO SEE YOU
WHEN SOMETHING HORRIBLE'S
GOING ON.
THAT'S JUST
HOW IT IS WITH ME.
STEVEN...THANK YOU.
GOODBYE AGAIN.
BYE.
[ GRUNTS ]
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO STAY?
YOU COULD ALWAYS
COME BACK TO THE TEMPLE WITH US
AND LIVE
IN THE BATHROOM AGAIN.
NO THANKS.
I HAVE SEEN WHAT GOES ON
IN THERE.
BESIDES, I'VE GROWN ACCUSTOMED
TO THIS PLACE.
AND I SHOULD PROBABLY
FIX THE HOLE THAT I MADE
WITH MY GIANT ROBOT.
MM. OKAY, WELL,
HAVE FUN REDECORATING!
WELL, THAT'S EVERYTHING...
AND THEN SOME.
STEVEN,
YOU READY TO GO HOME?
ALL SEAT BELTS
ARE FASTENED!
PERIDOT SAYS
SHE'S STAYING.
EH, IT'S PROBABLY
FOR THE BEST.
I DON'T THINK
SHE WOULD'VE FIT IN THE VAN.
YOU GUYS GO ON AHEAD.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU ON LION.
SURE, UH, OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU IN A BIT.
SEE YAAA!
NOW, WHERE IS THAT FELINE?
LION?!
HEY, LION?!
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
LE-E-E-E-E-E-ON!
I HAVE A BIG STEAK RIGHT HERE
IN MY HAND FOR YOU!
WHOOPS, I DROPPED IT,
AND IT FELL OUT OF EXISTENCE.
YOU CAN'T HIDE FROM ME FOR TOO
LONG 'CAUSE YOU LOVE ME SO MUCH!
WHOA!
LAPIS!
[ GRUNTING ]
WHEW!
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
I...THOUGHT YOU LEFT.
I WAS LEAVING.
BUT THEN I REALIZED
I'VE GOT NOWHERE TO GO.
WHO KNOWS WHAT THEY'D
DO TO ME BACK HOME
AFTER WHAT I DID
TO JASPER.
I CAN'T GO BACK TO HOMEWORLD,
AND I CAN'T STAY HERE.
SURE, YOU CAN.
WHAT?
YOU CAN TOTALLY
STAY HERE.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
HERE HERE.
YOU CAN LIVE ANYWHERE.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO
STAY IN BEACH CITY
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
OOH, Y-YOU COULD LIVE
IN SURF CITY OR SEA CITY,
AQUA TOWN, BAYBURG,
AND THAT'S JUST THE PLACES I
KNOW OF OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD!
I CAN SHOW YOU AROUND.
REALLY?
YEAH. WE CAN FIND YOU
A NEW PLACE TO LIVE.
I REALLY ONLY KNOW
THE TRI-STATE AREA,
BUT MY PHONE'S GOT
A GLOBAL POSITIONING SYSTEM.
OH, UH...OKAY.
LET'S GO LOOK.
READY, FREDDY?
MY NAME'S LAPIS.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU OKAY LIKE THIS?
MM-HMM.
UHHHH! UHHHH!
UHH!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ TRAIN HORN BLOWS ]
WHOO!
SO, HOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU COULD LIVE OUT HERE
IN THE COUNTRY!
NO NOISE, NO RULES.
IT'D JUST BE YOU
BECOMING ONE WITH NATURE.
WHOA!
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO DO THAT?
IT'S FUN!
IF YOU LIVED
IN THESE TREES,
YOU COULD BUILD
A GIANT BIRD'S NEST
AND HAVE SQUIRRELS
FOR PETS.
YOU COULD EAT ACORN PIE
EVERY NIGHT,
AND WHEN IT GETS HOT
OR IT RAINS,
YOU'D BE PROTECTED
BY THESE NICE LEAVES.
LEAVES?
[ GASPS ]
LAPIS, LOOK AT THIS!
THIS LEAF TURNED ORANGE.
THAT MEANS THE SEASONS ARE
CHANGING FROM SUMMER TO FALL.
SOON, IT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO
ALL THE LEAVES ON ALL THE TREES.
WOW.
SO, WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
OH. I'M NOT SURE.
THAT'S OKAY.
THERE'S PLENTY OF PLACES
WE HAVEN'T BEEN YET.
COME ON.
WHAT'S THIS?
THIS MUST BE
EMPIRE CITY!
ISN'T IT COOL?
IT'S VERY...BRIGHT.
YEAH,
THAT'S WHY THEY SAY,
"WHAT HAPPENS IN EMPIRE CITY
NEVER SLEEPS"!
SO, WHAT DOES HAPPEN
IN EMPIRE CITY?
WELL, LET'S SEE...
IF YOU LIVED HERE,
YOU COULD GET A COOL APARTMENT
AND BE A SINGLE GEM
TAKING ON THE BIG CITY.
YOU'D HAVE A FUN JOB
AT A LOCAL COFFEE SHOP
AND COME HOME
TO A WACKY ROOMMATE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AW.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT SHADOWY PLACE
OVER THERE?
OH, THAT'S JERSEY.
[ CAR HORNS HONKING ]
IS IT POPULATED
BY MACHINES?
NO, THOSE ARE CARS.
THEY MAKE A LOT OF SMOG,
THOUGH.
[ COUGHS ]
Y-YOU'D LIKE IT IN JERSEY.
THE PEOPLE HERE
SEEM TO HATE THE EARTH, TOO.
Man: QUIT FLYIN' IN OUR SKY,
YA MOOKS!
Both: PBHT!!
[ LAUGHING ]
WOW.
LAPIS, IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL
UP HERE!
EH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS I CAN SEE
WHY YOU LIKE IT.
HOLD ON!
[ POW ]
WHOA!
CHECK IT OUT!
WHOO-HOO!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
HEY, WE MADE IT OUT
ALL THE WAY OVER THE OCEAN!
[ LAUGHS ]
I WONDER
HOW FAR OUT WE ARE.
OH, COOL.
THE GALAXY WARP!
UM, LAPIS? I'M SLIPPING
A LITTLE THERE, BUD.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
LAPIS.
LAPIS, I'M SLIPPING!
I'M GONNA --
UH, SORRY!
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS WHERE
I WAS ABANDONED.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHOA.
IT'S LIKE A MIRROR.
IT WAS THOUSANDS
OF YEARS AGO.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
I WAS ONLY MEANT TO VISIT
FOR A SHORT TIME,
BUT I GOT CAUGHT...
[ EXPLOSION ]
IN THE MIDDLE OF A WAR.
IT WAS AWFUL.
I TRIED TO RUN, BUT...
...I WAS PICKED UP
BY A HOMEWORLD SOLDIER
AND CONFUSED
FOR A CRYSTAL GEM...
AND USED AS A TOOL.
THEY'D ASK ME,
"SHOW US YOUR BASE.
WHERE IS YOUR LEADER?"
I DIDN'T KNOW, AND I COULDN'T
SAY, "I'M NOT ONE OF THEM."
IT SOON BECAME CLEAR
THAT THERE WAS NO HOPE
IN STOPPING THE REBELLION.
ALL OF THE HOMEWORLD GEMS FLED.
IN ALL THE PANIC OF ESCAPING
EARTH, I WAS LEFT BEHIND.
[ SHATTER ]
[ WHIRRING ]
AND THERE I STAYED.
FREEDOM IN MY SIGHT,
BUT OUT OF REACH FOR AGES.
UNTIL I WAS FOUND.
[ SIGHS ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'LL...BE FINE.
LET ME TAKE YOU BACK.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO TAKE A MINUTE?
IT'S FINE.
I JUST WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
OKAY.
FOR A MOMENT, I REALLY FELT LIKE
THINGS WERE DIFFERENT.
BUT THEY'RE NOT.
NO MATTER WHERE I GO,
I'M TRAPPED.
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE NOT UNDERWATER,
YOU'RE NOT IN A MIRROR.
THIS TIME, YOU'RE FREE!
BUT I'M STILL ON EARTH.
YEAH, BUT NOTHING IS STILL
ON EARTH.
EVERYTHING'S
ALWAYS CHANGING.
THE LEAVES...
THE CITIES...
[ CAR HORNS HONKING ]
EVEN JERSEY CHANGES.
MY DAD SAYS THE REST STOPS
USED TO BE PRETTY GROSS,
BUT NOW THEY HAVE SUSHI!
THIS ISN'T THE SAME WORLD
THAT HELD YOU PRISONER --
NOT ANYMORE, AND I KNOW
IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE HOME,
BUT MAYBE
THAT CAN CHANGE, TOO.
I KNOW YOU CAN'T
GO BACK TO HOMEWORLD,
BUT IF YOU STAY HERE...
IT'LL BE YOUR CHOICE
TO STAY HERE.
IT'S FUNNY.
FOR ALL THE TIME
I SPENT ON EARTH,
I BARELY SAW ANY OF IT.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
THAT'S SUPER SAD.
I...
I WANT TO SEE IT.
YEAH?
I WANT TO STAY HERE.
HERE?
LIKE, HERE HERE?
YEAH, HERE HERE!
YES, HEAR, HEAR,
EVERYBODY!
WHAT ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU?!
LAZULI, NICE TO SEE YOU
UP AND ABOUT.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?!
THIS IS MY NEW HOME
AWAY FROM HOMEWORLD!
NO, IT'S NOT!
IT'S MINE!
RIGHT, STEVEN?
UH...
OH, BOY.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
Peridot: AND THEN I'LL SAY,
"HEY, AS ONE REFUGEE TO ANOTHER,
IT ISN'T SO BAD THAT WE CAN
NEVER GO BACK TO HOMEWORLD,
AM I RIGHT?
WHY DON'T WE WATCH
THE SUN COME UP
AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO
WITH ALL THIS TIME,
EH, LAZULI?"
AND THEN SHE'LL SAY,
"YES, PERIDOT.
AS IMPRESSED AS I WAS BY YOU
ON THE SHIP,
I AM EVEN MORE IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR NEW COMPACT LOOK
AND CAPACITY FOR FRIENDSHIP.
I'M SO GLAD WE'RE GOING
TO BE LIVING TOGETHER."
PERIDOT.
FACET FIVE.
[ CLICK ]
LET'S BEGIN.
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
WAIT, WHAT?
I REALLY THOUGHT I WOULD BE
LIVING ALONE HERE.
YEAH,
BUT THIS IS EVEN BETTER.
OH, HERE,
HOW ABOUT THIS?
I SAW THIS ON AN EPISODE
OF A TV SHOW.
I DIDN'T SEE HOW IT ENDED,
BUT I'M SURE
IT WORKED OUT GREAT.
WE'LL DIVIDE
THIS PLACE IN HALF.
YOU'LL BOTH HAVE
YOUR OWN SPACE.
HIGH CEILINGS,
REAL WOOD FLOORS,
CONVENIENT LOCATION IN THE HEART
OF THE COUNTRY.
SO WHAT DO YA THINK,
ROOMIES?
I LIKE THE CUT OF YOUR GEM,
STEVEN QUARTZ.
NO. NO WAY!
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
YOU'RE THE ONE GETTING
ALL THE GOOD STUFF!
YOU'VE GOT THE PROPELLER
AND PAINT CANS ON YOUR SIDE!
YOU CAN DO TONS
WITH THOSE!
OOH, ACTUALLY, I KIND OF
WANT THE PAINT CANS.
YOU WANT
TO TRADE SOMETHING?
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT PAINT CANS.
THAT'S NOT THE PROBLEM.
BAH.
WHAT'S WRONG, LAPIS?
IT'S HER.
UGH!
SHE'S THE PROBLEM!
I CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT OF
HAVING TO LOOK AT HER EVERY DAY.
SHE'S THE ONE WHO DRAGGED ME
BACK TO EARTH.
HEY, IT WASN'T MY IDEA.
I WAS HEADED TO EARTH,
AND I NEEDED AN INFORMANT.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
A SIMPLE MISSION.
THINGS DIDN'T EXACTLY WORK OUT
FOR EITHER OF US.
YOU USED ME
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE DID!
BUT IT'S NOT
LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
IT'S DIFFERENT NOW.
I'M DIFFERENT.
IT'S TRUE, LAPIS.
PERIDOT HAS REALLY
COME INTO HER OWN
SINCE SHE'S BEEN LIVING
ON EARTH.
I SABOTAGED
MY OWN MISSION!
I HELPED SAVE THE EARTH!
I EVEN YELLED
AT YELLOW DIAMOND!
SHE'S PROBABLY SENDING
A WHOLE FLEET
TO FIND ME
AND SHATTER ME RIGHT NOW!
I'M KIND OF A BIG DEAL.
A BIG, ANTI-HOMEWORLD DEAL!
STEVEN, I DON'T THINK
THIS IS GONNA WORK.
UH, UM, MAYBE
WE COULD PUT UP A CURTAIN?
ER, SORRY.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
GONNA BE OKAY.
I FORGOT THAT THE LAST TIME YOU
SAW EACH OTHER WASN'T SO OKAY.
THAT WAS IN THE PAST.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT NOW!
AGGH!
I KNOW.
BUT OBVIOUSLY
SHE DOESN'T.
SHE'S THE ONE
THAT NEEDS TO KNOW!
I WANT HER TO UNDERSTAND.
AW, PERIDOT, THAT'S SWEET.
THAT'S THE "YOU"
YOU NEED TO SHOW HER.
SHOW HER MY SWEET?
I GOT YOU.
CARDS ARE A GREAT WAY
TO TELL SOMEONE SOMETHING
IF YOU CAN'T BE FACE-TO-FACE
WITH THEM.
OR IF THEY DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOUR FACE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE HER A TASTE
OF THE SWEET VERSION OF PERIDOT.
HERE, LOOK.
IT'S YOU AND LAPIS
HOLDING HANDS!
WHERE ARE OUR NOSES?
OH, THAT'S KIND OF PART
OF MY STYLE LATELY.
IS NOT HAVING FINGERS
ALSO YOUR STYLE?
NO, I'M -- I'M JUST BAD
AT DRAWING HANDS.
UH, SO HERE'S YOUR PART.
COME HERE.
WRITE AN APOLOGY INSIDE
TO LAPIS
SO SHE KNOWS HOW SORRY YOU WERE
ABOUT BEFORE,
AND THAT EVERYTHING
IS OKAY NOW.
IF YOU WRITE IT
FROM YOUR HEART,
YOUR FEELINGS
WILL REACH HER.
JUST TRY TO BE SINCERE.
HMM.
[ SIGHS ]
Peridot: HEY, LAZULI!
HEY, LAZULI!
HEY!
UGH.
LAZULI!
HEY!
WHY ISN'T SHE RESPONDING?
I'M NOT SURE.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS UP THERE.
LAPIS?
HUH?
ARE YOU UP THERE?
YES, STEVEN?
GO ON.
STEVEN DID THE OUTSIDE,
AND I DID THE INSIDE.
"SORRY I INTERROGATED YOU.
YOU WERE JUST FULL OF
SUCH USEFUL INFORMATION.
THAT'S A SINCERE
COMPLIMENT.
PERIDOT."
THE NOSES!
ONE CAN ONLY CONCLUDE
THAT IT WAS THE LACK OF NOSES!
IT SEEMS ILLOGICAL TO ME
THAT IT WOULD BE ANY OF
THE WRITING ELEMENTS.
IT TOOK ME OVER AN HOUR
TO COMPOSE IT,
AND I WAS THE MOST SINCERE,
AS PER STEVEN'S INSTRUCTIONS.
IT COULD BE SHE'S JUST
NOT MUCH OF A READER?
HOW ABOUT A GIFT?
ANOTHER APPROACH.
YES. BUT WHAT?
HMM.
THINK OF THINGS SHE LIKES.
THINGS SHE LIKES.
LAPIS LAZULIS ARE TYPICALLY
PARTIAL TO WATER AND FLYING.
HMM.
AH!
[ GASPS ]
NO.
NO?
NUH-UH.
BUT IF!
YEAH?
NAH.
YEAH, THAT'D PROBABLY BE
OVERDOING IT.
[ BOTH SIGH ]
HMM.
WATER.
I THINK YOU HAVE SOMETHING
WITH THAT.
YOU CAN'T SEE THROUGH THOSE,
RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, YES.
BUT IT'S VERY BLURRY.
GOOD TO KNOW.
WELL, HERE WE ARE!
H-2 OH, MY GOSH!
IT'S A SMALLER
THAN AVERAGE LAKE!
IT'S FROM THE HOLE
WHEN WE DRILLED.
PERIDOT AND I SEALED IT
AND FILLED IT WITH WATER.
IT'S A GIFT FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE WATER'S YOUR THING.
[ CHUCKLES ]
PRETTY GOOD, RIGHT?
THE BARN'S OUT HERE
IN THE COUNTRY,
BUT NOW YOU CAN GET
YOUR MOISTURE FIX WHENEVER.
DO ALL THAT
WATER STUFF YOU DO.
WATER?
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH!
YOU DO REALIZE
THAT I SPENT
THE LAST FEW MONTHS TRAPPED
UNDER THE OCEAN, RIGHT?
SURE!
BUT I THOUGHT --
IT WAS AN ENDLESS,
CRUSHING DARKNESS.
WET AND BLEAK
AND SUFFOCATING.
WATER WAS THE TOMB I LIVED IN
FOR THOSE MONTHS.
TOMB, YOU SAY?
YEAH.
I'M KIND OF TAKING A BREAK
FROM WATER RIGHT NOW.
BUT THANKS...
FOR THE LAKE.
UHH.
[ GROANS ]
DON'T WORRY, STEVEN.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
Peridot: A POOL!
WHAT A CLODDY IDEA.
OF COURSE
SHE WOULDN'T LIKE THAT.
THERE'S NOTHING!
NOTHING!
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING.
SOMETHING, SOMETHING.
MAYBE, UH, INSTEAD OF
SOMETHING SHE LIKES,
GIVE HER SOMETHING
YOU LIKE.
A PIECE OF YOU!
UM...OKAY.
HOW ABOUT MY
"CAMP PINING HEARTS" DVD?
WHICH SEASON?
FIVE?
TRASH.
I KNOW. UGH!
LOG DATE -- WHATEVER.
FACET -- WHATEVER!
[ GROANS ]
WHATEVER!
CLEARLY THERE IS NOTHING
IMPORTANT ENOUGH
FOR ME TO GIVE TO LAZULI.
AT LEAST I HAVE YOU,
TAPE RECORDER.
TA-DA!
SEE, THE RIBBON
IS EVEN BLUE.
I GOT YOUR NUMBER.
UH, HERE.
I'LL UNWRAP IT FOR YOU.
WHEN I WAS STUCK HERE,
STEVEN GAVE ME THIS
TAPE RECORDER AS A GIFT,
AND I DIDN'T REALLY GET IT
AT FIRST,
BUT IT MADE ME
FEEL BETTER.
JUST TO TALK ABOUT ALL THE WEIRD
STUFF THAT WAS HAPPENING.
IT'LL HELP YOU, TOO.
YOU, UH, PRESS THE BUTTON
TO RECORD,
AN-AND TH-THEN
YOU TALK INTO IT.
[ CLICK ]
I DON'T WANT
YOUR GARBAGE.
[ SHATTERS ]
GUH! WHAT? WERE YOU TRAPPED
IN A TAPE RECORDER, TOO?!
LOOK. I GET IT, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE CONFUSED.
YOU CAN NEVER GO BACK
TO HOMEWORLD.
THIS PLACE DOESN'T EXACTLY
FEEL LIKE HOME YET!
YOU'RE ALONE!
NO ONE COULD POSSIBLY KNOW
WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE!
OH, WAIT. I DO!
WE'RE THE SAME!
EXCEPT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE ALONE.
SO, TELL ME, THEN,
WHAT YOU WANT FROM ME.
AND WHATEVER THAT IS...
[ SIGHS ] I'LL DO IT.
I WANT YOU...
TO LEAVE!
OKAY.
LAPIS, WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO MEAN TO HER?
SHE'S REALLY TRYING.
WHY DO YOU TRUST HER,
STEVEN?
BECAUSE I KNOW HER!
LAPIS, YOU'RE NOT EVEN
GIVING HER A CHANCE.
YOU SHOULD'VE AT LEAST
GOTTEN TO KNOW HER
BEFORE YOU DECIDED
YOU DON'T LIKE HER.
NOW IT'S TOO LATE.
AND SHE'S NEVER
COMING BACK AGAIN.
AAAAAAH!
OH, SHE'S
COMING BACK AGAIN.
AAAAAH!
THEY'RE HERE!
AAH!
[ GASPS ] RUN!
WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT'S A ROAMING EYE,
A HOMEWORLD TRACKING VESSEL.
I TOLD YOU --
I'M PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE!
[ WHIRRING ]
AH! OH.
[ BOTH SIGH ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
THIS IS IT, STEVEN!
THEY'RE GOING TO WIPE
MY PRECIOUS GRIN
OFF THE FACE
OF THIS PLANET!
STAY BEHIND ME!
I'LL PROTECT YOU!
[ GASPS ]
HOLY SMOKES.
STEVEN!
HOLY SMOKES!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WE SAW THE SHIP AND CAME AS FAST
AS WE COULD.
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
LAPIS SAVED US.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE HOMEWORLD
REALLY HAS IT OUT FOR PERIDOT.
Lapis: PERIDOT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ GIGGLES ]
UMM...
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ METALLIC THUMP ]
[ ALL GASP ]