♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
Steven:
FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION...
THE KOALA, A MARSUPIAL
FROM THE FORESTS OF AUSTRALIA,
AND THE SLOTH, HAILING FROM
THE FORESTS OF SOUTH AMERICA.
WHO SHOULD BE CROWNED
THE KING
OF THE "HANGING AROUND,
DOING NOTHING" MAMMALS?
I THINK SLOTHS EAT POOP.
GROSS.
WELL, THAT'S DEFINITELY
GOING TO AFFECT THE RANKINGS.
Eating poop would be
better than this.
[ Snickers ]
Just let him do his thing.
SO GLAD I DON'T HAVE TO
DEAL WITH THIS TOMORROW.
OH, YEAH,
THEY'RE CLOSING SHOP
TO GET THOSE GULLS
OUT OF THE VENTS.
ANY PLANS?
NAH.
WOULD YOU...WANT TO
COME BY MY PLACE?
I KNOW IT'S KIND OF
BEEN AWHILE,
BUT WE COULD GET SOME FOOD,
WATCH SOME MOVIES.
NAH. SOUNDS BORING.
I'LL SEE IF BUCK
WANTS TO DO STUFF.
WELL, I HOPE YOU GUYS
HAVE FUN TOGETHER.
YEAH. WE WILL.
HEY, STEVEN?
YOU'RE STARING A LITTLE BIT.
No, I'm not.
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]
HEY, LARS?
WHY DIDN'T YOU WANT TO
HANG OUT WITH SADIE?
[ GRUNTS ]
I SEE HER AT WORK.
WHY DO I NEED TO SEE HER
ON MY DAY OFF?
BUT AREN'T YOU GOING TO
GET MARRIED, AND HAVE KIDS,
AND NAME ONE OF THEM
AFTER HIS UNCLE STEVEN?
OH, LET ME THINK...NO.
ME AND SADIE
AREN'T GETTING MARRIED.
WE AREN'T EVEN DATING.
AND IF SHE THINKS WE ARE,
THAT'S HER PROBLEM.
YOU'RE LYING.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT SADIE.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT, SO BUTT OUT!
GO ANNOY SOMEONE ELSE.
You little weirdo.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST ADMIT
YOU LOVE HER?!
[ GRUNTS ] LARS.
LARS?
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE
SUCH A JERK ALL THE TIME.
I WISH I COULD JUST SHOW YOU.
AAH!
AAH! HUH?
WHA? WHOA.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS ISN'T THE TEMPLE.
THIS ISN'T MY VOICE.
WHOA -- I'M LARS?
OOH! [ WHIMPERING ]
I'M NAKED!
I MUST'VE JUMPED INTO
LARS' MIND.
I GUESS WHILE I'M IN HERE,
I'D BETTER DO MY BEST TO RESPECT
LARS' BODY, AND HIS PRIVACY.
NO. WE CAN DO THIS, DANTE.
WE HAVE TO TALK TO HIM.
HI, THERE.
OH, THERE'S OUR BOY.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
UH...TALLER?
HERE YOU GO. OH, IT'S GOOD TO
SEE YOU THIS MORNING, LARAMIE.
WHO'S LARAMIE?
I MEAN...LARS.
NOW, LARS, WE KNOW SCHOOL
IS A TOUCHY SUBJECT,
BUT WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT THIS.
"F-F-F-F-F-F-B-D-F."
THAT DOESN'T SPELL
ANYTHING.
PLEASE, LARS.
WE LET YOU MOVE INTO THE ATTIC,
AND YOUR GRADES
ARE STILL BELOW AVERAGE.
ALL WE'RE ASKING FROM YOU
IS...
Both: A LITTLE EFFORT.
WOW. YOU GUYS SEEM SO NICE.
I'M SURE I DON'T WANT TO
LET EITHER OF YOU DOWN.
I, LARS,
PROMISE TO GO OUT
AND DO MY VERY BEST
AT BEING YOUR SON.
WOW.
HE DIDN'T EVEN SWEAR.
AND HE'S WEARING
THE PLUGS I GOT HIM.
I'M LARS. [ CHUCKLES ]
I'M LARS, I'M LARS, I'M LARS!
HEY, ONION?
LOOK. I'M LARS.
♪ I'M LARS FOR THE DAY ♪
HEY, IT'S BUCK
AND SOUR CREAM.
HI, GUYS.
WHATCHA DOING?
HANGING OUT?
YEAH.
THAT'S COOL.
WOULD YOU SAY YOU HANG OUT
MORE LIKE KOALAS OR SLOTHS?
I'M ASKING FOR STEVEN.
I LIKE THAT KID.
YEAH, HE'S THE BEST.
[ CHUCKLES ]
TELL STEVEN WE'RE MORE LIKE
SLEEPING TIGERS.
OKAY.
THEN I'LL BE A PANTHER.
[ GROWLS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
OH. HEY, LARS.
HI, JENNY.
UGH. DAD MADE ME WORK
THIS MORNING.
NOW I STINK LIKE PIZZA
AND FISH.
YOU DON'T STINK.
LARS? WHAT A NICE THING
TO SAY.
I CAN SAY WAY NICER STUFF.
LIKE YOU'RE REALLY COOL
AND PRETTY AND FUN TO BE AROUND.
[ LAUGHS ]
LARS,
THIS IS SO UNLIKE YOU.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
HUH?
THIS ISN'T THE LARS
WE KNOW.
MAYBE LARS IS ACTUALLY...
A GOOD GUY WHO LIKES
MAKING PEOPLE FEEL GOOD.
YEP. YOU GOT ME.
THAT'S THE KIND OF VIBE
I WANT ON OUR DANCE CREW.
[ GASPS ] LARS IS
GOING TO BE PSYCHED!
BUCK IS PLEASED.
CAN HE DANCE, THOUGH?
CAN I?
[ HUMMING ]
WHOA! LARS GOT MOVES!
WHOO.
WE GOING TO A DANCE COMPETITION,
AND WE NEED YOU.
COME WITH US.
[ GASPS ]
OH. SORRY. I CAN'T.
THERE'S SOMEONE
WHO NEEDS ME MORE.
[ BUZZER ]
OKAY, OKAY, GEEZ.
HOLD YOUR HORSES.
STILL WANT TO HANG OUT?
WELL, IF IT AIN'T
THE HUMAN BOOMERANG --
ALWAYS COMING BACK TO ME?
LOOK, SORRY.
I WAS GOING TO WATCH A MOVIE,
IF -- IF YOU WANNA?
I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
N-NOTHING FANCY.
I DON'T NEED
ANYTHING FANCY.
[ LAUGHS ]
JUST GET IN HERE.
ARE THOSE HEARTS
IN YOUR EARS?
THERE'S A BUNCH OF STUFF
DOWN THERE YOU PROBABLY
HAVEN'T SEEN YET.
TAKE YOUR PICK.
"NIGHT TERRORS,"
"ENJOY THE VIOLENCE,"
"CRITTER CREMATORIUM,"
"THE ORGAN PICKLER, PART 7"?
I KEEP TELLING YOU,
THAT'S THE GOOD ONE.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
"FANGS OF LOVE."
I THINK I'D RATHER
HAVE MY ORGANS PICKLED.
AND YOU LOVE ME?
EVEN LIKE THIS?
I DOOOOOOOOO!
[ HOWLS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
DIDN'T I TRY TO WARN YOU?
[ CRYING ]
THEY JUST WANTED...
TO BE TOGETHER.
[ SOBBING ]
HEY? WHAT IS WITH YOU
TONIGHT, HUH?
[ SNIFFLING ]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[ BLOWS NOSE ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
LOOK, IT'S LIKE YESTERDAY
I ASKED IF YOU WANTED
TO COME OVER,
BUT YOU MADE A BIG DEAL,
SAYING NO IN FRONT OF STEVEN,
AND NOW YOU'RE HERE?
IT'S JUST, IT'S GETTING TO
BE KIND OF A ROLLER COASTER,
ISN'T IT?
ROLLER COASTERS ARE FUN.
[ SIGHS ] IT'S LIKE
YOU'RE ONE WAY IN PRIVATE
AND A DIFFERENT WAY
IN PUBLIC.
YOU ACT LIKE I DON'T KNOW YOU
DON'T WANT TO BE SEEN WITH ME,
BUT I DO KNOW.
I'M NOT STUPID.
DON'T BE SAD.
IT'S JUST, I NEED TO KNOW.
HOW DO YOU REALLY
FEEL ABOUT ME?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I LOVE YOU.
UGH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
FINALLY TELLING YOU.
NUH!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
ALL RIGHT, I GET IT.
I SEE HOW IT IS.
SOME CUTE LITTLE HEART GAUGES,
SOME DUMB, FLUFFY MOVIE,
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR SADIE.
RIGHT, LARS?
UH, D-- I-I-I JUST WANTED
TO FIX EVERYTHING.
GET OUT!
[ GRUNTING ]
STOP. YOU'RE HURTING ME!
Sadie: GOOD!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND!
I UNDERSTAND ENOUGH!
YOU'RE ONLY MY FRIEND
WHEN IT'S CONVENIENT FOR YOU.
JUST GET OUT OF MY LIFE!
[ GASPS ]
I'M NOT LARS!
WHAT?!
I'M...STEVEN.
I JUST WOKE UP THIS MORNING
WITH MY MIND IN LARS' BODY.
UGH! I DIDN'T MEAN TO HURT
YOUR FEELINGS LIKE THIS.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
MAYBE YOU ARE STEVEN.
LARS WOULD NEVER
APOLOGIZE TO ME.
WAIT. SO DOES THIS MEAN
LARS' MIND IS INSIDE YOUR BODY?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T KNOW?
MAYBE WE SHOULD CHECK?
YA THINK?
AT LEAST WE GOT
SECOND PLACE.
[ BOTH PANTING ]
HEY, LOOK, IT'S LARS
AND DOUGHNUT GIRL.
IT SEEMS LIKE LARS IS
REALLY TURNING A CORNER.
OH, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
WHERE'S HE GOING?
WHO'S THAT GIRL?
LET'S FOLLOW HIM
AND FIND OUT.
[ Chuckling ]
OH, MARTHA!
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S LOCKED.
[ GRUNTS ]
HYAH!
WHY ARE THEY BREAKING
INTO STEVEN'S HOUSE?
OUR LARS --
A BURGLAR.
NOW, NOW, YOU KNOW WE'VE
BEEN READY FOR THIS DAY.
[ BOTH PANTING ]
THERE YOU ARE.
HOW DO YOU SWITCH BACK?
THIS LOOKS WEIRD,
BUT DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
♪♪
COME ON, WAKE UP!
Steven:
[ GROANING ] AAH!
GUHHH...
OH!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MNH. HUH? SADIE?
[ GASPS ]
HOW DID I GET HERE?
WHAT ARE ALL YOU DOING HERE?
LARS, DON'T GET MAD.
HUH?!
BUT STEVEN REALLY
DIDN'T MEAN TO...
YOU. WHAT DID YOU DO?!
I SPENT THE DAY WITH
MY MIND IN YOUR BODY.
[ GASPS ]
UNH! AAH!
WHOA. WHERE'S YOUR CHILL?
BUCK IS NO LONGER PLEASED.
I'M SO SORRY.
HE WASN'T LIKE THIS
THIS MORNING.
I WAS ACTING WEIRD ALL DAY
AND YOU ALL JUST LIKED IT?
PLEASE DON'T MAKE A SCENE,
LARAMIE.
MNH! [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
DAAH!
♪♪
[ DOORBELL CHIMES ]
HEY, LARS?
UM...I'M REALLY, REALLY
SORRY ABOUT YESTERDAY.
I GOT YOU A CARD.
IT'S GOT A KOALA AND A SLOTH.
I HOPE I DIDN'T RUIN
YOUR FRIENDSHIP WITH SADIE.
WITH SADIE?
OH, WHAT DID YOU SAY TO HER?
I SAID YOU LOVED HER.
[ THUD! ]
A-AND WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SHE THOUGHT YOU'D ONLY SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO HURT HER.
YEAH.
I GUESS SHE'S RIGHT.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY EVERYONE
LIKED THE YOU ME
BETTER THAN THE REAL ME.
NOT EVERYONE.
UH, HEY.
HEY! [ PANTING ]
WEIRD DAY YESTERDAY,
HUH? [ CHUCKLES ]
UGH. EVERY DAY
IN BEACH CITY IS WEIRD.
THAT'S WHY I HATE IT HERE.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
THE REAL YOU.
YEAH? UH, UH,
YOU SHOULD COME OVER LATER,
YOU KNOW, BRING A MOVIE
TO WATCH OR SOMETHING.
[ LAUGHS ] OKAY.
AWESOME.
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO,
I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪
THEY TOLD ME
THERE WASN'T ENOUGH ROOM
ON THE ROAD FOR THE UNIVERSE.
AND I TOLD THEM,
THE UNIVERSE IS MY ROAD.
VROOM, VROOM!
STEVEN?
OH, HEY, CONNIE!
THANKS FOR LETTING ME
PRACTICE, DAD.
THIS CAR'S GREAT!
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT BE
TOO SMALL TO LIVE IN.
AH, THE VAN'S
STILL HOME SWEET HOME.
I JUST THOUGHT NOW THAT
I'M SWIMMING IN DOUGH,
WHY NOT GET A NEW CAR?
A NEW CAR?
BUT IT'S GOT THIS BIG
"USED" STICKER ON IT.
I LIKE TO THINK OF IT AS MORE
"EXPERIENCE" THAN "USED."
THIS BABY'S
A DONDAI SUPREMO
FROM THE ERA
OF FROSTED TIPS,
MOOD RINGS,
SLAP BRACELETS.
YOU KNOW,
BEFORE YOU KIDS WERE BORN.
WHAT A TIME TO BE ALIVE.
I'VE HAD MY EYE ON THE DONDAI
SINCE WAY BACK WHEN.
I LOVED THAT CAR.
I WANTED THAT CAR.
ALSO, THESE THINGS ARE CRAZY
ON THE ROAD.
FRONT WHEEL SUSPENSION,
TONS OF PONIES.
BUT BEST OF ALL...
IT HAS A TAPE DECK!
[ CHILL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
♪♪
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ COUGHING ]
GIVE ME A WASH, OLD MAN.
UH, RIGHT AWAY,
YOUNG MAN.
IS THAT...?
KEVIN!
I DIDN'T SAY
IRON THE SOCKS.
I SAID I WANT
MY SOCKS PRESSED.
WHOA -- WAIT, WAIT.
CAREFUL WITH THE TIRES,
GRANDPA.
I GOT A BIG RACE TODAY,
AND MY CAR HAS TO LOOK
AS BEAUTIFUL AS ME.
BACK OFF, KEVIN!
HE'S NOT A GRANDPA!
HE'S JUST A REGULAR PA!
[ CLICK ]
HAVE WE MET BEFORE?
I THINK I'D REMEMBER
A TWERP LIKE YOU.
YOU DO REMEMBER
A TWERP LIKE ME!
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU -- YOU JUST LOOK LIKE
ANOTHER GUY WE KNOW.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE...
KEVIN.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
HEY!
HE FORGOT TO...
EH, WHAT DO I CARE?
I'M RICH.
[ GROWLS ]
I HATE KEVIN!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WATCH THE FOUR LETTERS,
SCHTUBALL.
HATE'S A STRONG WORD.
IT'S A STRONG
FEELING, TOO.
DO YOU KNOW THAT GUY?
WELL, KINDA.
WHEN WE FUSED
INTO STEVONNIE,
WE MET HIM
AT THE DANCE AND --
HE WAS A CREEP!
STEVEN!
THAT'S FIVE LETTERS!
HE KEPT ASKING US
TO DANCE WITH HIM,
EVEN THOUGH WE SAID NO.
IT WAS REALLY...
UNCOMFORTABLE.
HE DIDN'T EVEN CARE ABOUT
HOW WE FELT -- AT ALL!
[ SIGHS ]
I HAD NO IDEA THAT HAPPENED.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
THAT GUY, HE'S NOT EVEN WORTH
THE TIME OF DAY.
DON'T EVEN GIVE HIM
THE SATISFACTION
OF THINKING ABOUT HIM.
THANKS, MR. UNIVERSE.
[ SIGHS ]
STILL MAD ABOUT KEVIN?
YES.
ME TOO.
YOU DON'T SEEM MAD.
I'M THINKING MAD.
I STILL FEEL LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING BIG
I WANT TO SAY TO HIM,
YOU KNOW?
SOMETHING TO MAKE HIM THINK,
LIKE WE'RE THINKING.
YEAH. TOO BAD WE CAN'T JUST RACE
AGAINST HIM --
TO USE
THE FIRST PLACE RIBBON
TO WIPE THAT SMUG LOOK
OFF HIS FACE!
BUT WE'RE KIDS.
KIDS CAN'T DRIVE.
THAT'S AGAINST THE LAW.
WE WEREN'T KIDS
WHEN WE MET KEVIN.
I SMELL
WHAT YOU'RE STEPPIN' IN.
EW.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
UGH! MY PRACTICE
DIDN'T PAY OFF AT ALL!
THAT WAS SO BAD!
[ TECHNO MUSIC PULSING ]
I KNOW, BABY,
I'M THE WORST.
[ SCOFFS ]
ANYONE ELSE
THINK THEY CAN BEAT ME
AND MY HIMITSU X-12
ON THE DOWNHILL COURSE,
STEP RIGHT UP.
COME ON, HOW AM I GOING
TO GET A COOL-DOWN LAP
IF NO ONE WANTS TO GO?
[ ENGINE REVS ]
I'LL RACE YOU!
HUH?
AH! AAH!
HA!
IS THAT A '96 SUPREMO?
[ EXCITED WHISPERING ]
UH...
I THINK IT'S A DONDAI?
A SUPREMO IS A DONDAI!
WOW. REALLY?
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU DON'T KNOW
THE TRUE POWER
OF THE SUPREMO?
UH...
Kevin: HA!
THAT'S WHY I KNEW
THOSE BRATS
AT THE CAR WASH --
THEY'RE YOU!
YOUR WHOLE "TWO KIDS IN A
BEAUTIFUL TRENCH COAT" ROUTINE
WON'T FOOL ME THIS TIME,
SO DON'T EVEN TRY IT!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I'M MADE OF
WHEN I BEAT YOU AT THIS RACE!
HEH.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
DO YOU?
YOU'VE HAD A TASTE
OF KEVIN,
AND NOW YOU'RE OBSESSED.
WHAT?
I GET IT.
I HAVE THAT EFFECT ON PEOPLE.
IT'S CUTE.
BUT AREN'T I A LITTLE OLD
FOR YOU?
GAH!
DO YOU WANT TO RACE OR NOT?
THE START IS AT THE TOP
OF THE MOUNTAIN.
WE GO WHEN THE CLOCK
STRIKES THE HOUR.
FIRST ONE
TO THE BOTTOM WINS.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THAT LAST PART.
AH. [ GROWLS ]
[ TIRES SQUEAL ]
[ COUGHING ]
THAT GUY IS GOING DOWN.
[ CRICKETS CHIRP ]
[ ENGINES IDLING ]
[ GROWLS ]
YOU KNOW, THIS MOUNTAIN PASS
HAS SOME REALLY
BEAUTIFUL VIEWS.
SHAME YOU'LL ONLY BE SEEING
MY TAIL LIGHTS THE WHOLE TIME.
YOU WISH.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
IT'S KEVIN TIME.
[ ENGINE REVS ]
SHOOT!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
♪♪
HM.
I WON'T LET YOU WIN!
HA HA! [ LAUGHS ]
OH.
OH, MY GOSH.
THIS IS IT!
ARE THEY GONNA CRASH?
NO!
WE'RE ABOUT TO WITNESS
THE TRUE POWER OF THE SUPREMO!
OH.         OH.
OH.                          OH.
[ TIRES SQUEAL ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
HUH?
SO YOU DO KNOW HOW
TO USE THAT THING.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GROWLS ]
[ ENGINE REVS ]
I KNOW YOU WANT TO BE CLOSE,
BUT THIS IS A LITTLE CLINGY.
UGH.
FEEL LIKE
GIVING UP YET?
OH!
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE
SUCH A JERK ALL THE TIME?
THE TRUTH IS
I DON'T MEAN TO BE THIS WAY.
I-I JUST LASH OUT
BECAUSE OF MY LITTLE BROTHER.
[ INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS ]
HE'S SICK.
BEEN SICK ALL OUR LIVES.
SOMETIMES I THINK
IF I ACT REAL COOL
AND NEVER LET ANYONE
SEE MY PAIN,
THEN MAYBE THE PAIN
WILL GO AWAY.
AND MAYBE I CAN TAKE
HIS PAIN AWAY, TOO.
KEVIN, I HAD NO IDEA.
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ LAUGHS ]
DUDE!
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A BROTHER!
I'M LIKE THIS BECAUSE I THINK
IT'S FUNNY!
[ GROWLS ]
CHOWZERS.
KEVIN!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
KEVIN...
[ GASPS ]
OH! NO!
WE HAVE TO BEAT HIM.
HE DESERVES TO LOSE!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRP ]
[ PANTING ]
A-ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK SO.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
[ BOTH SIGH ]
SEEMS LIKE THE CAR
IS SAFE, TOO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WE'RE GETTING KEVIN BACK.
WE'RE ABOUT TO BEAT HIM
AT HIS OWN GAME!
YEAH, BUT WHY DO WE EVEN
HAVE TO PLAY HIS GAME?
BECAUSE --
HE'S -- HE'S...
DAGH!
I KNOW!
SO WHY SHOULD HE GET TO HAVE
ANY SAY OVER HOW WE FEEL?
HE DOESN'T.
BUT HE'S THE REASON
WE'RE RACING.
STEVEN,
HE'S THE REASON WE FUSED.
[ GASPS ]
WE ARE OBSESSED WITH HIM.
I WANT TO FINISH
THIS RACE...
BUT NOT FOR HIM.
RIGHT.
FOR US!
THE SUPREMO ISN'T MOVING!
UGH, THAT'S IT.
I'M GONNA GO UP THERE AND CHECK
IF THEY'RE OKAY.
WAIT!
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ TIRES SQUEAL ]
♪♪
FINALLY.
YOU CAUGHT UP.
I WAS WORRIED YOU'D MISS
SEEING ME WIN.
WHAT, SO YOU'RE SHY NOW?
WHAT?
Connie: WHOA.
[ GIGGLES ]
[ GROWLS ]
AW! I WAS ROOTING FOR YOU,
DONDAI!
KEVIN IS THE WORST!
BOO!
WHAT, WHAT?
THAT'S RIGHT!
FIRST PLACE, BABY!
IT'S LIKE
I INVENTED WINNING.
GOOD RACE.
YOU TRYING TO KISS MY HAND
WITH YOUR HAND OR SOMETHING?
YOU KNOW, KEVIN,
YOU WERE RIGHT.
[ SCOFFS ] I KNOW.
ABOUT WHAT?
THE VIEW FROM THE MOUNTAIN
WAS PRETTY GREAT.
HEY! DON'T TRY
TO TEACH ME A LESSON!
YOU LOST!
SECOND PLACE ISN'T SO BAD...
FOR MY FIRST TIME
DRIVING A CAR.
[ SCOFFS ]
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE SO OBSESSED WITH ME,
YOU'RE GONNA DRIVE AWAY.
FINE! GO PLAY WITH
SOME KIDDY TOY CARS!
I COULD BEAT YOU AT THAT, TOO!
DON'T FORGET,
YOU'RE OBSESSED WITH ME!
OBSESSED!
OBSEEEEEESSED!
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO ♪
♪ I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪