♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
LOG DATE 7-1-1-2.
IT'S THE THIRD ROTATION
OF THE EARTH
SINCE COMMENCEMENTS OF A
[INHALES SHARPLY]
COLLABORATIVE APPROACH
TO STOPPING THE CLUSTER.
[ CHALK SCRATCHING ]
Pearl:
I'VE FINISHED DRAWING UP
THE BLUEPRINTS
FOR THE DRILL HEAD.
PERIDOT, IF YOU COULD COME
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS...
REMIND ME AGAIN WHY
I SHOULD LISTEN TO YOU.
OH, RIGHT.
[ TAPE REWINDING ]
THE PEARL HERE HAS EXHIBITED
AN APTITUDE FOR ENGINEERING
THAT I BEGRUDGINGLY RESPECT,
THOUGH THAT DOESN'T EXPLAIN
THE SPONTANEOUS SINGING,
CRYING,
SINGING WHILE CRYING.
[ LAUGHS ]
WHY DID YOU GIVE HER THAT?
WELL, WE DID
DESTROY ALL HER STUFF.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT MAKE HER FEEL
A LITTLE BETTER.
[ TAPE REWINDING ]
CLODS! MUDDY CLODS!
RUNNING OUT OF WAYS
TO SAY CLODS.
ALL RIGHT.
I CHASED AWAY THOSE COWS.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
BEFORE WE BEGIN,
WOULD YOU MIND UNFUSING?
IT'S MAKING ME
INCREDIBLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
WHAT?!
WHAT'D I SAY?!
DO WE REALLY
HAVE TO DO THAT?
HER HAVING FREE REIGN
OF THE PLACE
MADE ME
INCREDIBLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
[ GRUNTING ]
HERE YOU GO, PEARL.
OH, GOOD.
HMM.
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I SAID I NEEDED TUNGSTEN --
TUNGSTEN.
UH, WHAT DOES TUNGSTEN
LOOK LIKE?
TUNGSTEN. AH!
UGH. NEVER MIND.
I'LL JUST DO IT.
MEH.
[ GROANING ]
I JUST NEED SOME SORT
OF LEVERAGE OPTIMIZER.
[ Chuckling ]
LEVERAGE OPTIMIZER?
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
OH! HA.
YOU MEAN YOU WANT
A SCREWDRIVER?
[ LAUGHS ]
DO YOU HAVE ONE OR NOT?
UH, W-WHY DON'T YOU JUST USE
THIS ONE?
BECAUSE IT WAS OUTSIDE
MY RADIUS.
[ Chuckling ] HEY.
HEY, PERIDOT,
WHAT DO YOU CALL THIS?
A SCENT SPONGE.
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
OKAY, WHAT'S THIS?
VISION SPHERE.
PERIDOT, THAT'S --
WAIT, WAIT, STEVEN.
PERIDOT, THESE?
[ Angrily ] TOUCH STUMPS.
THIS?
GRAVITY CONNECTORS.
THIS?!
THAT'S YOUR BUTT!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
OH, MAN, PERIDOT,
YOU'RE KILLING ME!
I AM NOT! THAT WOULD VIOLATE
OUR TRUCE AGREEMENT.
[ Laughing ] NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE FUNNY.
FUNNY?
PERIDOT,
IF YOU CAN GET
THE MAGNETRON
OUT OF THAT MICROWAVE,
WE'LL HAVE
EVERYTHING WE NEED --
EXCEPT FOR
THE DRILL HEAD.
WHY DON'T I JUST GET
AN INJECTOR DRILL HEAD
FROM THE KINDERGARTEN?
OH.
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU COULD TRY.
Garnet: SHE'S NOT GOING
TO THE KINDERGARTEN
WITHOUT A CHAPERONE.
WHAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE JOKING.
YOU'LL KNOW WHEN I'M JOKING.
[ MUTTERS ]
ME AND STEVEN
CAN GO WITH HER.
EH?
YEAH,
WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON HER.
APPROVED.
KEEP HER IN LINE, AMETHYST.
YOU GOT IT!
[ GROANS ]
LOG DATE 7-1-1-2.
THE AMETHYST AND THE STEVEN
HAVE VOLUNTEERED
TO HELP ME DISMANTLE
THIS ERA-ONE DRILL.
HOW STYLISTICALLY
DISPLEASING.
THE NEWER ONES
HAVE A NICER FINISH.
YOU MAKING MORE NERD NOTES?
WHAT IS...NERD?
[ SNICKERS ]
CAN YOU USE IT
IN A SENTENCE?
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
NERD --
YOU ARE A NERD.
[ LAUGHS ]
AMETHYST,
CUT THAT OUT.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THIS PLANET IS ANNOYING,
AND EVERYTHING
IS ANNOYING.
AMONGST ITS TRANSGRESSIONS
IS THE NEED FOR THE AMETHYST
TO ASK PERMISSION
FROM THE PERMAFUSION.
PERMAFUSION?
IS THAT WHAT YOU CALL GARNET?
I COULD CALL HER
LOTS OF THINGS.
I COULD CALL HER TWO THINGS --
TWO CLODS!
[ LAUGHS ]
WALKING AROUND LIKE
SHE'S ONE CLOD.
[ LAUGHS WICKEDLY ]
[ SNICKERS ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
SHE'S NOT EVEN FIGHTING!
SHE'S -- YOU KNOW, SHE'S JUST,
YOU KNOW, LIKE A...
YOU KNOW!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU'RE A REAL GEM,
"PERRY."
YES. I AM. A GEM.
OKAY, OKAY.
DO STEVEN NEXT.
WHAT'S WEIRD
ABOUT STEVEN?
WHERE DO I EVEN BEGIN?
HE'S SOME SORT
OF HYBRID ABOMINATION.
I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND
HOW HE FUNCTIONS.
HIS ORGANIC HALF
CONSUMES SO MUCH ENERGY
THAT HE HAS
TO CONSTANTLY FEED,
AND HE SPENDS SO MUCH TIME
EXPELLING
THAT HE HAS A WHOLE ROOM
DEDICATED TO IT.
[ LAUGHING ]
UH, NO,
SOMETHING ELSE --
TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE!
[ CONTINUES LAUGHING ]
[ SNORTING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
THE STRANGEST THING IS,
AMETHYST,
YOU THINK YOU HAVE TO LISTEN
TO THEM.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE IN CHARGE!
HA!
THAT'S YOUR BEST JOKE YET.
NO, REALLY.
PEARL IS A PEARL.
GARNET IS A FUSION.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
HEY!
YOU'RE THE ONLY CRYSTAL GEM
THAT'S ACTUALLY A GEM.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
WHAT?
YOU OUTRANK EVERYONE
ON YOUR TEAM.
THEY SHOULD BE LISTENING
TO YOU.
YOU'RE A STRONG, SINGULAR,
FULLY FUNCTIONAL SOLDIER,
DESPITE THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE DEFECTIVE.
DEFECTIVE?
WELL, SURE.
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU'RE SMALL.
SO?
WELL,
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE.
HOLD ON.
WAIT, WAIT.
LET ME GUESS.
THIS --
THIS IS THE HOLE
YOU CAME OUT OF.
TOO SMALL, TOO LOW,
THE EXIT MARKS LOOK
ABOUT 500 YEARS NEWER
THAN EVERY OTHER HOLE.
HMM.
THIS PLACE MUST'VE BEEN EMPTY
WHEN YOU CAME OUT.
NO WONDER YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO LOOK LIKE!
PERIDOT.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED
TO LOOK LIKE?
WELL,
YOU'RE A QUARTZ.
THEY'RE HUGE,
LOYAL SOLDIERS.
YOU SHOULD BE TWICE YOUR SIZE,
BROAD-SHOULDERED, INTIMIDATING,
BUT YOU SIMPLY STAYED
IN THE GROUND TOO LONG.
ARE YOU SAYING I'M WRONG?
[ LAUGHS ]
"GEMETICALLY" SPEAKING, YES.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S ALL SO [CHORTLES] FUNNY.
[ LAUGHS WICKEDLY ]
AMETHYST.
HEY, SOLDIER,
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP ME
GET THIS HUNK OF DRILL OFF.
SEE?
LOOK AT THAT!
YOU CAN DO EVERYTHING
A NORMAL QUARTZ CAN DO.
LET'S HEAD BACK AND SHOVE
THIS THING IN PEARL'S FACE.
AMETHYST,
ARE YOU OKAY?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
OH!
IT'S LOVELY.
TO THINK WE'D BE USING
THE SAME TECHNOLOGY THAT STARTED
ALL THIS TO FIX IT --
THIS DRILL
IS PURE IRONY!
ACTUALLY,
IT'S MOSTLY CARBONITE.
WOULD THAT MAKE IT
"CARBONY"?
[ GROANS ]
OH, OH, OH! AMETHYST!
CHECK OUT THIS -- HMM --
"RHYTHMATIC" PULVERIZER.
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S FUNNY. I'M SO FUNNY.
WHATEVER, DUDE.
THAT WAS
THE INCORRECT RESPONSE.
HEY, AMETHYST ISN'T LAUGHING
WHEN I DO THESE THINGS.
WHY ISN'T SHE LAUGHING?
PERIDOT,
YOU REALLY HURT HER FEELINGS.
WHAT?
YOU WERE PRETTY MEAN TO HER
AT THE KINDERGARTEN.
MEAN? NO WAY.
I WAS BEING...COOL.
AMETHYST LOVED IT.
SHE'S PROBABLY TELLING THE PEARL
HOW MUCH FUN SHE HAD NOW.
AMETHYST, HI, HI!
HI, AMETHYST!
SHE -- SHE WON'T EVEN LOOK
AT ME.
IT'S MAKING ME FEEL...
SMALLER.
YOU FEEL BAD.
THAT'S HOW YOU MADE HER FEEL.
[ SCOFFS ]
WHO CARES ABOUT HOW SHE FEELS?
WHO CARES
ABOUT ANY OF YOU?!
YOU'RE ALL JUST ROCKS,
RUDDY MUDDY CLUMPS BENEATH
MY GRAVITY CONNECTORS!
[ ROARS ]
OHH!
[ SIGHS ] ANOTHER ONE
OF HER TEMPER TANTRUMS.
I'M SURPRISED YOU TWO MADE IT
BACK FROM THE KINDERGARTEN
WITHOUT DRIVING
EACH OTHER CRAZY.
YEAH.
[ BIRD CAWING ]
[ SIGHS ]
THIS LITTLE THING --
[ MUTTERING ANGRILY ]
AAH!
UGH.
HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING
UP THERE?
I'M FINE.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
[ MACHINERY BEEPS ]
AAH!
NO, NO, NO, NO! STOP!
PERIDOT?
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
OOF!
THE PANEL.
WHOA!
WAIT!
OOF!
[ GASPS ]
IT'S OKAY!
I GOT I-I-I-T!
[ SCREAMING ]
WHAT THE...AAH!
AMETHYST!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ MUSIC ENDS ]
IT'S OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
IT WAS JUST A DRILL.
[ LAUGHS WEAKLY ]
[ COUGHS ]
UH...PERIDOT?
AAH!
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT. I SWEAR!
HEY,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE KNOW YOU DIDN'T MEAN
TO START THE DRILL.
UH, YEAH.
AND THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT, TOO.
WE LEAVE FOR ONE SECOND,
AND EVERYTHING GOES
OFF THE RAILS!
I BLAME THE COWS.
NO, IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE.
WE'LL REBUILD IT STRONGER,
BETTER.
WE'LL ADD SEATBELTS!
[ GRUNTS ]
AH!
HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
IT'S A GOOD THING
PERIDOT WAS THERE TO SAVE YOU.
[ METAL CLATTERS ]
YES,
IT IS A GOOD THING.
LISTEN. I, UM...
JUST SPIT IT OUT.
UGH!
WHY ARE YOU EARTHLINGS
SO DIFFICULT?!
LOG DATE 7-1-1-2.
THIS ENTIRE PLANET
IS BACKWARDS.
THERE HASN'T BEEN ONE INSTANCE
OF CORRECT BEHAVIOR
EXHIBITED BY ANY ONE
OF THESE CRYSTAL GEMS.
I HAVE CONCLUDED
THAT THEY ARE ALL DEFECTIVE.
BUT I AM NO BETTER.
I FAILED MY MISSION,
AND NOW I'M WORKING
WITH THE ENEMY,
AND I CAN'T EVEN
GET THAT RIGHT.
I HAVE APPARENTLY
"HURT" AMETHYST'S "FEELINGS,"
WHICH WAS NOT MY INTENT.
IF I'VE DAMAGED MY STANDING
WITH THE BEST GEM HERE,
THEN I'VE MADE
A SERIOUS MISTAKE.
I'M STILL LEARNING.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND.
I'M SORRY.
PERIDOT, FACET FIVE.
END LOG.
AS YOU CAN SEE --
OH, PERIDOT!
[ SCOFFS ]
Amethyst:
HEY, UH, PERIDOT.
THANKS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL A NERD.
I'LL BE SURE TO ADD THAT
TO MY NOTES.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
BIG.
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ SNORING ]
MM.
STEVEN!
[ GASPS ] GARNET!
IS IT MORNING ALREADY?
IT'S MIDNIGHT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, STEVEN.
OH, MAN,
ARE YOU FINALLY GONNA TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE A FUSION
OF THE GEMS RUBY AND SAPPHIRE
LIKE YOU PROMISED?
YOU ALREADY KNOW
ABOUT ALL THAT, STEVEN.
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S TRUE.
BUT WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW IS
HOW RUBY AND SAPPHIRE FIRST MET.
O-M-G! I DON'T!
[ CHUCKLES ]
Garnet:
THE EARTH, 5,750 YEARS AGO.
IT WAS A PROMISING SITE
OF A NEW GEM COLONY,
BUT PROGRESS
WAS BEING THWARTED
BY A SMALL
PERSISTENT GROUP OF REBELS.
A TEAM OF DIPLOMATIC GEMS
WERE SENT FROM HOMEWORLD
TO INVESTIGATE.
AMONG THOSE GEMS
WAS SAPPHIRE,
A RARE ARISTOCRATIC
HOMEWORLD GEM
WITH THE POWER TO SEE
INTO THE FUTURE.
ASSIGNED TO HER
WERE THREE RUBIES...
HUP!
...COMMON SOLDIERS
WITH A MISSION TO PROTECT HER.
HEY, CAN'T WAIT
FOR THOSE REBELS TO GET HERE.
[ CHUCKLES ] YEAH.
WHEN I SEE THOSE REBELS,
I'M GONNA PUNCH THEM
RIGHT IN THEIR FACES.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M GONNA PUNCH THEM
ALL OVER THEIR BODIES,
AND THEN IT'LL BE OVER.
-WHAT IF I JUST PUNCH YOU?
-OW!
OH, COME ON.
WE'LL PUNCH THEM TOGETHER
WHEN WE FUSE.
THAT'S WHY THEY SENT,
UH, THREE OF US.
THREE THIS!
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, I, UM,
I'M SO SORRY, I --
LET ME, UH --
I'M FINE.
WHAT?
IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS BOUND TO HAPPEN.
I -- OH.
OKAY.
NOW, PLEASE WAIT HERE.
I MUST ATTEND TO MY DUTIES.
-RIGHT.
-YES.
SAPPHIRE HAD BEEN CALLED
TO EARTH BY BLUE DIAMOND
SPECIFICALLY TO SHARE
HER VISION OF THE FUTURE.
MY DIAMOND, I'VE ARRIVED.
BLUE DIAMOND SPOKE.
"SAPPHIRE, TELL ME
WHAT WILL HAPPEN HERE."
I FORESEE THE REBELS
ATTACKING THE CLOUD ARENA.
BEFORE THEY ARE CORNERED,
THEY WILL DESTROY
THE PHYSICAL FORMS
OF SEVEN GEMS,
INCLUDING TWO OF MY RUBY GUARDS
AND MYSELF.
IMMEDIATELY AFTER MY FORM
IS DESTROYED,
THE REBELS
WILL BE CAPTURED.
THE REBELLION
ENDS HERE.
"THANK YOU, SAPPHIRE,"
BLUE DIAMOND SAID, RELIEVED.
"THAT'S ALL I NEEDED TO KNOW."
I LOOK FORWARD TO SPEAKING
WITH YOU AGAIN
ONCE I REFORM
BACK ON HOMEWORLD.
SAPPHIRE KNEW
SHE WOULD BE A CASUALTY,
BUT IT DID NOT FAZE HER.
SHE SAW HER WHOLE LIFE
LAID OUT BEFORE HER,
AND SHE HAD ALREADY
ACCEPTED ALL OF IT.
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL PLACE
TO BUILD A COLONY.
I WISH I COULD HAVE SEEN
MORE OF THIS PLANET.
UH, THERE'S STILL TIME.
THAT IS A NICE THOUGHT.
BUT, NO.
Rose: BLUE DIAMOND,
LEAVE THIS PLANET.
THIS COLONY
WILL NOT BE COMPLETED.
IT'S THE REBELS!
Ruby: WHO ARE YOU?
SHOW YOURSELVES!
-WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS.
THE ATTACK
WAS RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
[ SWORDS CLASH ]
-HM?
-AAH!
HEE-YAH!
[ SHOUTING ]
HUP!
YEAH!
[ ALL SHOUT ]
HA!
AAH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
[ GROANS ]
THANK YOU, RUBY.
YOU DID YOUR BEST.
RUBY SUDDENLY REALIZED
WHAT SAPPHIRE MEANT.
SHE HAD KNOWN
THAT RUBY WOULD FAIL.
SAPPHIRE HAD ACCEPTED IT,
BUT RUBY -- RUBY COULD NOT.
NO!
WHAT?
[ GASPS ] WHAT?
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
WHAT -- WHAT IS THIS?
WAIT. THIS IS --
HM?
LET'S GO.
UH, BYE.
IS THIS --
-AH!
THE FURIOUS CROWD CLOSED IN
AROUND RUBY AND SAPPHIRE.
THEY HAD NEVER SEEN FUSION
OF TWO DIFFERENT TYPES OF GEMS.
"UNBELIEVABLE."
"DISGUSTING."
"THIS IS UNHEARD OF."
BLUE DIAMOND'S VOICE
CUT THROUGH THE CROWD.
"THE REBELS HAVE FLED.
SAPPHIRE, THIS IS NOT
THE SCENARIO YOU DESCRIBED."
THIS IS NOT WHAT I SAW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
-I --
-NO, IT WAS ME.
"CLEARLY," SAID BLUE DIAMOND.
"HOW DARE YOU FUSE
WITH A MEMBER OF MY COURT."
FORGIVE ME. I --
"YOU WILL BE BROKEN FOR THIS."
WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
NOOOO!
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
I HAVE TO GET YOU
BACK UP THERE.
THEY WERE GONNA BREAK YOU.
WHO CARES?
THERE'S TONS OF ME.
[ GRUNTS ]
UH!
AAH!
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
SAPPHIRE HAD KNOWN
EVERY MOMENT OF HER LIFE --
HOW IT WOULD HAPPEN AND WHEN.
BUT BECAUSE OF RUBY'S
IMPULSIVE GESTURE,
SHE SUDDENLY
JUMPED THE TRACK OF FATE.
AND EVERYTHING
FROM THAT INSTANT ON
WAS WRONG AND NEW.
SHE COULDN'T SEE.
SHE COULDN'T MOVE.
SHE WAS FROZEN.
AH!
WE HAVE TO GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT,
THIS SHOULD BE GOOD FOR NOW.
THANK YOU.
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
WHA?
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
WHAT KIND OF RUBY
AM I SUPPOSED TO BE?
LOOK AT THIS.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT
YOU'RE STRANDED HERE.
HOW AM I GONNA SAVE YOU?
YOU ALREADY DID.
WHAT?
YOU ALREADY SAVED ME.
[ HUFFS ]
I'VE SEEN GEMS FUSE BEFORE,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
THAT'S WHAT IT FELT LIKE.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT --
I NEVER REALIZED
THAT FUSION --
THAT YOU DISAPPEAR
LIKE THAT.
IT'S NEVER LIKE THAT.
WHENEVER I FUSE,
IT'S ALWAYS JUST BEEN ME,
BUT BIGGER.
I-I'VE NEVER HAD
A THIRD EYE BEFORE.
I'VE NEVER HAD
MORE THAN ONE.
IT WAS NICE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH.
♪♪
Ruby and Sapphire:
♪ WHERE DID WE GO? ♪
♪ WHAT DID WE DO? ♪
♪ I THINK WE MADE
SOMETHING ENTIRELY NEW ♪
♪ AND IT WASN'T QUITE ME ♪
♪ AND IT WASN'T QUITE YOU ♪
♪ I THINK IT WAS SOMEONE
ENTIRELY NEW ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ UM ♪
♪ WELL, I JUST CAN'T
STOP THINKIN' ♪
♪ SO ♪
♪ UM ♪
♪ DID YOU SAY
I WAS DIFFERENT? ♪
♪ AND YOU HADN'T BEFORE? ♪
♪ OF COURSE NOT ♪
♪ WHEN WOULD I HAVE EVER? ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY ♪
♪ NO, NO, DON'T BE ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU'RE HERE
FOREVER ♪
♪ WHAT ABOUT YOU? ♪
♪ WHAT ABOUT ME? ♪
♪ WELL, YOU'RE HERE, TOO ♪
♪ WE'RE HERE TOGETHER ♪
[ HUMMING ]
[ BOTH HUMMING ]
I WAS BACK.
I WAS SOMEONE,
AND I DIDN'T KNOW WHO.
BUT FELT LIKE
I WAS GETTING THE HANG
OF MY STRANGE, NEW FORM.
AND THEN I FELL.
AH!
[ GRUNTING ]
OW.
AH!
DON'T HURT HER!
DON'T HURT...ME?
IT'S YOU -- THE FUSION.
WE DIDN'T MEAN TO FUSE.
WELL, WE DID THIS TIME.
WE'LL UNFUSE.
WE'LL -- WE'LL --
NO, NO, PLEASE.
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
AND THERE THEY WERE --
ROSE QUARTZ,
THE LEADER OF THE REBELLION
AND HER TERRIFYING RENEGADE,
PEARL.
I DON'T UPSET YOU?
WHO CARES
ABOUT HOW I FEEL?
HOW YOU FEEL IS BOUND TO BE
MUCH MORE INTERESTING.
HOW I FEEL?
I-I FEEL LOST...
AND SCARED...
AND -- AND HAPPY.
WHY AM I SO SURE
THAT I'D RATHER BE THIS
THAN EVERYTHING
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE?
AND THAT I'D RATHER
DO THIS
THAN EVERYTHING
I WAS SUPPOSED TO DO?
[ LAUGHS ]
WELCOME TO EARTH.
CAN YOU TELL ME,
HOW WAS RUBY ABLE TO ALTER FATE?
WHY WAS SAPPHIRE
WILLING TO GIVE UP EVERYTHING?
WHAT AM I?
NO MORE QUESTIONS.
DON'T EVER QUESTION THIS.
YOU ALREADY ARE THE ANSWER.
SO, WHAT WAS IT?
THE ANSWER?
LOVE.
WOW.
I KNEW IT.
SO DID IT.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]