>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
>> ♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: ♪ HEY, MR. POSTMAN,
BRING ME A POST ♪
♪ BRING ME THE POST THAT I LOVE
THE MOST ♪
HUH? [ GASPS ]
MY SONG CAME TRUE!
DO YOU HAVE A PACKAGE FOR ME
TODAY?
>> HOLD ON.
LET ME SEE WHAT I'VE GOT HERE.
DID YOU ORDER A LOAF OF BREAD
WITH A STAMP ON IT?
>> Steven: NO.
>> DID YOU ORDER A JURY SUMMONS
FOR R.J. FINKLE?
>> Steven: THAT'S NOT ME -- I'M
STEVEN.
>> OH, RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT --
HERE IT IS -- STEVEN UNIVERSE.
>> Steven: HA! THIS THING IS
GONNA HELP ME SAVE THE WORLD!
>> REALLY?
IT SAYS IT'S FROM
WACKY SACKS SUPPLY COMPANY.
>> Steven: GARNET, AMETHYST, AND
PEARL THINK I SHOULDN'T GO ON
MAGIC ADVENTURES BECAUSE I DON'T
KNOW HOW TO USE MY GEM POWERS.
>> THAT SEEMS REASONABLE.
>> Steven: BUT THERE ARE OTHER
WAYS I CAN HELP.
>> WITH A WACKY SACK?
>> Steven: EXACTLY!
>> YOU KNOW HOW YOU CAN SAVE MY
WORLD?
SIGN HERE, PLEASE.
>> Steven: AH!
>> BARB YELLS AT ME IF I DON'T
GET SIGNATURES.
>> Steven: THAT'S AWFUL.
[ ENERGY PULSING ]
[ GASPS ]
GARNET, AMETHYST, AND PEARL ARE
BACK!
>> W-WAIT! STEVEN!
WHAT IS A WACKY SACK?
>> Steven: HUH?
>> Garnet: HELLO, STEVEN.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, WE DO NOT
NEED THAT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO FIT IN THE
FRIDGE.
>> Amethyst: WHAT?
I GOT THIS.
HUP!
LOOK -- IT FITS!
[ CRACKING ]
HA! OH, MAN, WE COULD MAKE A BIG
OMELET OR A QUICHE OR BIG
SUNNY-SIDE-UPS!
>> Pearl: WE FOUGHT A GIANT
BIRD.
>> Amethyst: WE CAN BAKE IT --
THAT'S A THING, RIGHT?
>> Pearl: WE'RE ONLY HERE FOR A
SECOND.
WE'VE GOT TO GO BACK OUT.
>> Steven: WHAT? WHY?
>> Pearl: WE HAVE TO PLACE THIS
MOON GODDESS STATUE ON THE TOP
OF THE LUNAR SEA SPIRE BEFORE
MIDNIGHT.
WITHOUT IT, THE WHOLE PLACE WILL
FALL APART!
OH, STEVEN, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE SPIRE IN ITS HEYDAY.
IT WAS AN OASIS FOR GEMS ON
EARTH.
[ POP! ]
IT'S ABANDONED NOW, BUT WE CAN
STILL SAVE IT WITH THIS STATUE.
>> Steven: WHA--
THAT'S PERFECT!
>> Pearl: WHAT? WHY?
>> Steven: BECAUSE I CAN HELP
CARRY IT FOR YOU...IN THIS!
WHOOOSH!
WHHHHHMMM!
WHHHHHSSSW!
PWING-PWING-PWING-PWING-PWING!
>> Pearl: A...HAMBURGER?
>> Steven: IT'S A NOVELTY
BACKPACK SHAPED LIKE A
CHEESEBURGER!
AW, I BLEW IT.
I WAS JUST GONNA WEAR IT ONE
DAY, AND YOU GUYS WOULD BE LIKE,
"DANG, STEVEN, THAT'S SO COOL!"
BUT THIS IS OBVIOUSLY IMPORTANT
GEM BUSINESS.
>> Pearl: YES, SO YOU SHOULD LET
US TAKE CARE OF IT.
>> Steven: WHAT?
I'M A GEM!
>> Pearl: BUT YOU'VE STILL GOT A
LOT TO LEARN.
>> Amethyst: SO LET HIM COME.
IT'LL BE EDUCATIONAL.
>> Pearl: HMM. ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN CARRY IT IN YOUR
HAMBURGER.
>> Steven: MM! CHECK THIS OUT --
EVERYTHING'S A POCKET!
EVEN THE CHEESE IS A POCKET!
I CAN FIT A LOT MORE STUFF IN
HERE.
GIVE ME A MINUTE.
I'LL PACK EXTRA SUPPLIES.
>> UGH!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
>> KID, DON'T SHAKE ME!
>> Steven: MR. QUEASY!
>> OHH, I GOT A MEDICAL
CONDITION.
>> Steven: YOU'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA COME IN HANDY.
>> UGH!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, LET'S GO!
>> Steven: UH, COMING!
>> Pearl: WHOA, STEVEN, DID YOU
BRING YOUR WHOLE ROOM?
>> Amethyst: BACK THAT THANG
UP.
>> Garnet: LET'S WARP.
>> Amethyst: SUCK IT IN, STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
>> Pearl: DO YOU REMEMBER HOW TO
DO THIS?
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
OH! WHOO-HOO-HOO!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: KEEP YOUR HEAD IN.
COME ON!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
UGH!
WHOA!
THE SEA SPIRE!
>> Together: OHH.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
>> Pearl: IT WASN'T LIKE THIS A
HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
>> Garnet: I'M SENSING
STRUCTURAL INSTABILITY.
>> Steven: OH, YEAH, THAT'S
NEVER GOOD.
>> Pearl: GAH! STEVEN!
>> Steven: WHAT?
>> Pearl: ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
WE'RE TAKING STEVEN BACK!
>> UGH! MY ACHIN' STOMACH!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
OH, MR. QUEASY!
>> KID, YOU'RE KILLIN' ME.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
THIS PLACE IS YOUR HERITAGE!
I WANT YOU TO STAY AND HELP, BUT
YOU'VE REALLY GOT TO TAKE THIS
SERIOUSLY.
CAN YOU DO THAT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: YOU GOT IT, DUDE!
>> Pearl: YES.
>> Garnet: ENOUGH.
WE HAVE TO MOVE.
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THE HOLDUP?
WE CAN CLEAR THIS EASILY.
>> Garnet: NO. THE MAGIC THAT
SUSTAINS THE WHIRLPOOL CREATES A
VORTEX THAT WILL PULL US BELOW.
[ ENERGY PULSATES ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
>> Pearl: SO WE CAN'T JUMP?
>> Steven: OH, WAIT!
>> Amethyst: WHAT ARE THOSE FOR?
>> Steven: THEY WERE FOR KEEPING
WARM, BUT CHECK IT OUT.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
>> Garnet: WHOA!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: WAIT!
>> Steven: WHOA! OH!
>> Amethyst: HE'S GETTING SUCKED
DOWN!
>> Together: STEVEN!
>> Steven: CHEESEBUR-R-R-R-GER!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Pearl: UGH!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, WAY TO GO!
COME ON, GUYS!
[ ENERGY PULSING ]
[ WHIP! ]
HYUP!
♪ STEVEN-STYLE ♪
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: DON'T EVER DO THAT
AGAIN!
>> Steven: SORRY.
>> Pearl: BUT...IT WAS PRETTY
GREAT.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS EVEN WORSE THAN THE
OUTSIDE.
UGH! THAT'S -- OH!
OH, THIS DIDN'T USED TO BE SO --
OH, AND THE WATER DAMAGE...
THIS PILLAR...
OH, AND THIS HAD A HEAD.
OH, STEVEN, ONCE THE STATUE'S IN
PLACE, IT'LL RESTORE ALL OF THIS
TO ITS FORMER GLORY --
UGGGH! AAAAH!
AAAAH! AAAAAHH!
>> Steven: WHAT WAS THAT GOOBER?
>> Pearl: CRYSTAL SHRIMP.
>> Amethyst: YOU GUYS, WE GOT A
PROBLEM.
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
IT'S AN INFESTATION!
AND WE HAVE TO PASS THROUGH
THERE TO GET TO THE TOP.
>> Steven: CAN'T YOU JUST SQUISH
'EM?
>> Pearl: DON'T TOUCH THAT!
THEIR SHARDS ARE DEADLY!
WE NEED TO CLEAR A PATH.
AMETHYST, IF YOU GO AROUND TO
THE SIDE AND DISTURB THEM WITH A
SPIN ATTACK...
AND, GARNET, IF YOU MOVE TO THE
CEILING AND STRIKE THIS EXACT
SPOT...
THEN I CAN ADVANCE WITH MY --
>> Steven: BAGEL SANDWICH!
[ SHRIMP SQUEAK ]
[ SHRIMP SQUEAKING ]
>> Garnet: BRILLIANT.
>> Amethyst: OH, HEY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
>> Pearl: UH, UH.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT WOULD
WORK?
>> Steven: WELL, IF I WERE A
SHRIMP, THAT'S WHAT I WOULD DO.
>> Amethyst: YOU ARE A SHRIMP.
>> Pearl: I JUST WANT EVERYONE
TO KNOW -- MY PLAN WOULD HAVE
ALSO WORKED.
>> Garnet: WATCH OUT!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Amethyst: WHAT ARE WE GONNA
DO?
>> Steven: WHAT -- ME?
>> Garnet: WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>> Amethyst: CHEESEBURGER
BACKPACK!
CHEESEBURGER BACKPACK!
PEARL, COME ON.
>> Pearl: OHH, ALL RIGHT.
>> Both: CHEESEBURGER BACKPACK!
CHEESEBURGER BACKPACK!
>> Steven: A RAFT!
[ ZIP! WHOOSH! ]
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
>> Garnet: AH!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THAT'S SO
SENSIBLE.
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> All: AAH!
[ WHIP! WHOOSH! ]
[ CREAK! ]
>> Garnet: GOOD IDEA, ANYWAY,
STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, THEY CAN'T
ALL BE WINNERS.
>> Pearl: THIS IS IT --
THE MOON GODDESS PEDESTAL.
AND THE MOON IS ALMOST OVERHEAD!
IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO SAVE THIS
PIECE OF HISTORY!
>> Garnet: STEVEN, THE STATUE.
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Steven: UH, I-I, UH...
UH, UH, I...
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THE HOLDUP?
>> Steven: I DON'T HAVE IT.
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
>> Steven: I MUST HAVE LEFT IT
ON THE BED!
>> Pearl: THERE'S -- THERE'S NO
TIME!
>> Steven: WAIT!
I HAVE AN IDEA!
>> UGH!
>> Pearl: AH.
>> Amethyst: COULD THAT WORK?
>> Garnet: MM-MNH-MNH.
>> UGH!
KID, DON'T SHAKE ME!
[ ENERGY PULSING ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> WH-O-O-O-O-O-OA!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
>> Pearl: OHH!
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Garnet: EVERYONE, KEEP
STEADY!
>> Amethyst: WHOA!
OHH!
>> Steven: NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO!
[ CRACKING ]
AAH!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
AAAAAH!
>> Steven: [ GASPING ]
[ ALL GASPING ]
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I BROKE IT!
>> Pearl: NO, STEVEN, THE SPIRE
WAS FALLING APART WHEN WE GOT
HERE.
YOU HANDLED EVERYTHING WELL
UNDER PRESSURE.
YOU DID GREAT.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, 2 OUT OF 4 OF
YOUR IDEAS WORKED -- THAT'S 50%.
>> Steven: YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE
RIGHT -- THEY CAN'T ALL BE
WINNERS.
[ BURBLING ]
WHOO!
>> Both: CHEESEBURGER BACKPACK!
CHEESEBURGER BACKPACK!
>> Garnet: IT'S A THREE-HOUR
PADDLE HOME.
>> Steven: ANYONE WANT A WET
BAGEL?
EVERYONE'S OUT.
GUESS I'M MAKING US BREAKFAST.
PEARL!
GARNET!
AMETHYST!
IS ANYONE HOME?
HMM.
[ BEEPS, WHIRS ]
[ BEEPS ]
ONE, TWO, THREE...WARP IN!
[ THUD! ]
[ SIGHS ]
GUESS THEY'RE STILL OUT SAVING
THE WORLD.
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU ARE OUT OF CONTROL.
PEARL!
GARNET!
IT'S DONE!
[ SIGHS ]
THAT THING'S TOO GOOD FOR ME TO
EAT ALONE.
IT'S A...TOGETHER BREAKFAST.
[ WARBLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AH, GARNET! PERFECT.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY HEALTHY, BUT
IT'S IN A STACK, SO I GUESS YOU
COULD SAY IT'S A...BALANCED
BREAKFAST.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, I MADE US ALL
I THOUGHT WE COULD EAT TOGETHER
LIKE -- LIKE BEST BUDS.
>> Garnet: I CAN'T STAY.
THERE'S BUSINESS TO ATTEND TO
INSIDE THE TEMPLE.
>> Steven: AW, BUSINESS?
LIKE WHAT?
>> Garnet: I HAVE TO BURN THIS.
[ DISEMBODIED WHISPERING ]
>> Steven: COOL!
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
UH!
>> Garnet: I HAVE TO BURN THIS,
TOO.
>> Steven: NO! MY APPS!
DOOR!
OPEN DOOR.
AW, YOU NEVER WORK WHEN I NEED
IT.
>> Amethyst: DUMB POLICE!
UH, YOU'RE DUMB!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
OH, MAN.
I TOTALLY GOT YOU.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN THE LOOK ON
YOUR FACE.
>> Steven: OH, I KNEW IT WAS
YOU.
>> Amethyst: [ SCOFFS ] HOW?
>> Steven: 'CAUSE THAT'S A WATER
GUN, AND I'M NOT DUMB.
>> Amethyst: YOU GOT SOMETHING
ON YOUR SHIRT.
DUUUUH-UMB.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ WARBLING ]
HEY!
THAT'S MY DOOR.
>> Pearl: OH, AMETHYST, THERE
YOU ARE.
CARE TO EXPLAIN WHAT ONE OF MY
SWORDS WAS DOING IN YOUR ROOM?
>> Amethyst: HAVING A SWORD
PARTY.
>> Pearl: OH, PLEASE!
YOU TOOK IT.
>> Amethyst: I DID NOT.
>> Pearl: IT'S FINE.
IT'S IN THE PAST.
I FORGIVE YOU.
>> Amethyst: [ SCOFFS ]
>> Pearl: ALSO, I CLEANED UP
YOUR AWFUL, AWFUL MESS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Amethyst: YOU DID WHAT?!
I HAVE A SYSTEM!
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
WAIT!
>> Pearl: WHAT'S THE MATTER,
STEVEN?
>> Steven: I WANTED US ALL TO
HAVE BREAKFAST TOGETHER, SO I
MADE TOGETHER BREAKFAST, BUT
EVERYONE KEEPS LEAVING.
>> Pearl: OH, THAT'S NICE.
>> Steven: OH, NO!
NOT YOU, TOO.
I CAN'T LET THIS BECOME TOGETHER
BRUNCH.
[ PANTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYS ]
WHA--?
>> Pearl: HMM.
THERE WE GO.
AHH!
>> Steven: HEY, PEARL!
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
YOU KNOW IT'S DANGEROUS FOR YOU
INSIDE THE TEMPLE.
>> Steven: WE'RE GONNA HAVE A
NICE TOGETHER BREAKFAST EVEN IF
I HAVE TO GET MY SHOES WET.
[ EXCLAIMS ]
>> Pearl: WHAT?!
GET OUT OF THERE!
>> Steven: I'LL SWIM IT OVER TO
YOU.
SEE?
DOGGY PADDLE, FORWARD.
OH, GOSH.
WAIT.
UH, DOGGY PADDLE, REVERSE.
REVERSE!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHAT THE...?
[ SCREAMING ]
WHOA!
[ EXCLAIMING ]
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA!
KEEP IT TOGETHER, BREAKFAST!
[ GROANS ]
>> Amethyst: BETTER.
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: OH, HEY, STEVEN.
DID YOU COME DOWN THE WATERFALL?
PEARL GETS SO MAD THAT I HAVE
HER JUNK, BUT IT'S ALWAYS
FALLING DOWN HERE.
>> Steven: JUNK LIKE WHAT?
>> Amethyst: JUNK LIKE...YOU!
I'M GONNA THROW YOU IN THE JUNK
PILE.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
>> Amethyst: ISN'T IT AWFUL?
PEARL ORGANIZED EVERYTHING.
>> Steven: IT STILL LOOKS MESSY
TO ME.
>> Amethyst: AW, THANKS.
I TRY.
BOOM!
OH, WHAT'S THAT, STEVEN?
>> Steven: IT'S A TOGETHER
BREAKFAST.
>> Amethyst: ALL RIGHT! SNACKS!
>> Steven: NO!
IT'S FOR EVERYONE TO EAT
TOGETHER.
THAT'S THE ESSENCE OF TOGETHER
BREAKFAST.
>> Amethyst: AHH.
GIVE ME! GIVE ME!
>> Steven: AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WE HAVE TO EAT IT TOGETHER!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: HUH?
WHOA!
[ EXCLAIMS ]
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
YOU CAN'T OUTRUN ME!
WE BOTH HAVE SHORT LEGS.
[ EXCLAIMS ]
>> Steven: HUH?
WHAT?!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN!
I'M HUNGRY!
>> Steven: JUST HOLD ON!
AN EXIT!
WHOO!
[ GRUNTS ]
SKILLS!
>> Amethyst: GET BACK HERE.
>> Steven: YOU'RE COMPLETELY
MISSING THE POINT OF THIS.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> Amethyst: HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
THERE YOU ARE.
>> Steven: PEARL! SWEET!
TWO OUT OF THREE.
>> Pearl: OH, OH!
STEVEN, BE CAREFUL.
>> Steven: WHY?
WHA--?
[ GASPS ]
WHOA.
[ PULSATING ]
>> Pearl: YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
BE IN HERE.
THIS IS THE CRYSTAL HEART.
OH!
IT'S CONNECTED TO THE MOST
DANGEROUS AREAS OF THE TEMPLE.
HOLD ON TIGHT AND DON'T LOOK
DOWN.
>> Steven: HUH?
>> Pearl: OH!
>> Steven: [ SCREAMS ]
OH, HEY.
THIS ISN'T SO BAD.
[ SCREAMS ]
UH, NEVER MIND.
WHOA!
[ BUBBLING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
AW.
[ DISEMBODIED WHISPERING ]
[ SIZZLES ]
[ DISEMBODIED SCREAMING ]
>> PEARL: Steven, we're getting
you out of here.
>> AMETHYST: Come on.
>> Steven: HUH?
THIS IS GREAT!
WE'RE ALL TOGETHER.
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
HUH?
>> Steven: WE CAN FINALLY EAT.
I MEAN, WE DON'T HAVE ANY FORKS,
BUT WE CAN USE OUR HANDS.
I'M NOT GONNA JUDGE.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, GO!
>> Steven: OKAY.
WANT TO MEET IN THE KITCHEN?
[ WARBLES ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ DISEMBODIED YELLING ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Garnet: IT'S TRYING TO
ESCAPE.
FORCE IT BACK.
>> Amethyst: GET BACK!
>> All: STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ MOANS ]
TOGETHER BREAKFAST?
[ SCREAMS ]
>> Pearl: IT'S TAKEN REFUGE IN
ORGANIC MATTER.
>> Garnet: NOW IT HAS ALL THE
POWER OF A BREAKFAST.
WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT.
>> Pearl: AAH! IT'S HORRIBLE!
>> Steven: I DIDN'T WANT THIS.
I JUST WANTED TO EAT TOGETHER
LIKE -- LIKE BEST BUDS.
[ GROANING ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN, YOU'VE GOT TO
GET AWAY.
>> Steven: BUT MY BREAKFAST.
THAT'S ENOUGH!
[ Straining ] I DON'T CARE IF
YOU...ARE THE MOST IMPORTANT
MEAL OF THE DAY.
[ GRUNTING ]
I MADE YOU TO BRING US TOGETHER,
NOT TO TEAR US APART!
[ PANTING ]
I'M SORRY, GUYS.
I GUESS I DREAMED TOO BIG.
>> Steven: IT LOOKS GREAT.
IT'S EVEN MORE TOGETHER AND EVEN
MORE BREAKFAST.
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS ]
I DON'T THINK I CAN EAT THIS.
>> Amethyst: LET'S ORDER A
PIZZA.
>> Steven: PIZZA'S A BETTER
IDEA.
>> Pearl: YEAH. IT'S GOOD.
>> Steven: DEFINITELY.
>> Garnet: IT DID TRY TO KILL
US.