>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Garnet: STEVEN?
>> Steven: [ GIGGLES ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN.
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
>> Steven: [ GIGGLES ]
>> Garnet: COME ON OUT.
YOU KNOW I CAN SENSE YOU.
>> Steven: STEVEN BOMB!
[ Laughing ] WHOA!
I GOT YOU.
>> Garnet: YOU GOT ME.
>> Steven: AND NOW YOU'RE BLIND.
>> Garnet: TINY HANDS -- MY ONLY
WEAKNESS.
>> Steven: WHOA!
WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY?
>> Garnet: TELL ME WHAT YOU
THINK I DID.
[ WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL! ]
[ VIDEO-GAME MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ HISS! ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BOOM! ]
HUH!
[ HISS! ]
[ BOOM! ]
YOU -- REVEAL YOURSELF!
[ WHIRL! ]
[ HISS! ]
[ BOOM! ]
>> TOP O' THE MORNING TO YOU,
GARNET.
NOTHING LIKE SOME MORNING
TRAINING TO GET THE BLOOD
PUMPING.
AM I RIGHT?
>> Garnet: HOPPER, NICE TO SEE
YOU, TOO.
>> BY THE WAY, HAVE YOU SEEN
HOPPY?
SHE WAS HOPPIN' EXCITED TO TRAIN
WITH US.
[ WHOOSH! WHIP! ]
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
>> YA-A-A-A-A-A-H!
WA-A-A-A-A-A-A-H!
HYAH!
GARNET.
>> Garnet: HOPPY.
>> WOW, GARNET.
I CAN TELL YOU'VE BEEN TRAINING.
YOUR POWER LEVELS ARE HOPPIN'
HIGH!
>> YES, HOPPER, BUT THEY COULD
ALWAYS BE HIGHER.
WE SHOULD TRAIN MORE.
I NEARLY HAD TO JUMP ON YOU THAT
TIME.
>> OOOOOOOH!
>> Garnet: WE CAN TRAIN SOME
OTHER TIME, HOPPY.
RIGHT NOW THERE'S A GEM ARTIFACT
TO RECOVER.
>> I WONDER WHAT IT IS THIS
TIME.
MAYBE A MAGIC POWER AMULET OR A
FLYING POWER CARPET OR MAYBE AN
ENCHANTED POWER ONION!
>> Garnet: WHATEVER IT IS, WE
SHOULD HURRY.
THERE'S SOMEBODY AT HOME THAT I
NEED TO GET BACK TO.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> Garnet: MY MOST FAVORITE
PERSON IN THE WORLD.
>> HAVE YOU EVER TOLD HIM THAT?
>> Garnet: NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> Garnet: I'M NOT STRONG
ENOUGH.
>> WILL WE GET TO MEET HIM SOON?
>> Garnet: NOT YET.
HE'S NOT READY TO LEARN THAT I
HAVE SECRET ANIMAL FRIENDS.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> [ CROAKING ]
WHOA.
[ ZAP! ZAP! ZAP! ]
HIS POWER LEVELS ARE HOPPIN'
PRETTY LOW.
>> Garnet: I CAN REVIVE HIM.
[ POP! ]
[ SLURPS ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
>> [ SHUDDERS ]
RINGO!
HA HA!
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME!
>> Garnet: TELL US YOUR NAME,
STRANGER.
>> MY NAME IS RINGO.
I AM BUT A HUMBLE CARETAKER OF
THE SHRINE ATOP YONDER MOUNTAIN.
>> HOW DID YOU GET THOSE WOUNDS?
WAS IT FROM SOME KIND OF
TRAINING?
>> WELL, YOU SEE, AN INNOCENT
FOX MAN WANTED TO SEE THE
SHRINE.
SUCH A SWEET, SWEET FOX MAN.
NATURALLY, I OBLIGED.
INSIDE RESTED THE SACRED MAGIC
GEM OF ULTIMATE POWER!
IT WAS THEN THAT THE FOX MAN
DOUBLE-CROSSED ME.
HE USED THE POWER OF THE GEM TO
BANISH ME FROM MY OWN SHRINE.
OHH!
EVER SINCE THEN, I'VE BEEN
SEARCHING FOR SOMEONE STRONG
ENOUGH TO HELP ME.
>> Garnet: THAT GEM MUST BE
CONTAINED.
NO ONE SHOULD HAVE THAT MUCH
POWER.
>> OH, YOU CAN HAVE THE GEM.
I JUST WANT MY SHRINE BACK.
>> Garnet: WE'LL GET IT BACK
FOR YOU.
>> Both: HOP FIVE!
>> Garnet: DON'T WORRY, STEVEN.
I'LL BE HOME SOON.
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> WE'RE HERE!
>> HOLY HOP!
HIS POWER IS OFF THE CHARTS!
>> BE CAREFUL, GARNET.
DON'T HOP OFF MORE THAN YOU CAN
CHEW.
>> Garnet: FOX MAN, GIVE US THE
GEM.
>> WHAT?
YOU AGAIN?
>> [ HISSES ]
>> OH, I SEE WHAT THIS IS.
[ BOOM! ]
>> AAH!
>> IF YOU WANT THE GEM, YOU'LL
HAVE TO DEFEAT ME!
>> Garnet: SO BE IT.
RAH-UNH!
>> R-R-R-R-R-R-AH!
>> Garnet: AHHHHHHHHH!
AHHHHHH!
AHHHHHHHHH!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ ALL GRUNT ]
>> SEE?
I TOLD YOU HE WAS STRONG.
UGH.
>> Garnet: THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO GET STRONGER.
>> [ GASPS ] TRAINING TIME!
>> [ HUMMING ]
RINGO!
[ HUMMING ]
>> Garnet: [ GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Both: WEIGHTED GAUNTLETS.
>> Garnet: [ GROANING ]
UGH!
>> SHE JUST GAINED 10 POWER FROM
THAT ONE PUNCH!
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
>> COME ON, GARNET.
YOU CAN DO THIS!
YOU'VE JUST GOT TO REMEMBER WHAT
YOU'RE FIGHTING FOR.
>> Garnet: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
RAH!
HUH!
HUH! HUH!
HUH! HUH! HUH! HUH! HUH!
[ ALL GASP ]
HUH! HUH! HUH! HUH! HUH! HUH!
7,000. 8,000. 10,000!
NUMBERS HAVE NO MEANING!
>> Garnet: I'M READY.
>> All: SO COOL!
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> WE'RE HERE!
>> Both: UGH!
>> BACK AGAIN, HUH?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE HUNGRY FOR
ANOTHER DELICIOUS BEATING.
>> Garnet: ACTUALLY, THAT LAST
ONE SPOILED MY APPETITE.
>> HOW DARE YOU INSULT MY
COOKING SKILLS?
WHAT?! IMPOSSIBLE!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
AHH! OHH! AHH!
[ GROANING ]
OHH. OH, THAT HURTS.
NOW GIVE BACK THE GEM.
BUT I'M THE SWORN PROTECTOR OF
THE GEM.
WHAT DID THAT LIAR TELL YOU?
>> [ GASPS ] NO!
>> YOU DUMMIES FELL FOR IT.
NOW THE SACRED MAGIC GEM OF
ULTIMATE POWER IS MINE!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GROWLS ]
ULTIMATE RINGO!
>> CURSE YOU, RINGO!
I'LL MAKE YOU PAY FOR THIS!
>> TOO BAD YOU DIDN'T OUTFOX ME
WHEN YOU HAD THE CHANCE!
>> [ GASPS ]
[ ALL GASPS ]
>> Garnet: AN ON...
>> ...ION...
>> RING.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Garnet: WE WILL AVENGE YOU,
FOX MAN.
RINGO, YOU MUST BE DEFEATED!
>> AHEM.
THE NAME'S "ULTIMATE RINGO."
>> WH-WH-WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> WELCOME TO MY RINGO ZONE!
IT IS HERE WHERE MY POWERS ARE
STRONGEST.
YOU WANT TO STOP ME?
GO ON.
IT'LL AMUSE ME.
AND AFTER I BEAT YOU, MAYBE I'LL
DESTROY THE PLANET JUST 'CAUSE I
CAN.
>> Both: YOU MONSTER!
READY TO HOG, DROP, AND ROLL!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> OWW!
>> Garnet: HOPPY, NO!
[ NOISEMAKER SOUNDS ]
HOPPY -- I MEAN, HOPPER, NO!
[ BOTH GROAN ]
>> Garnet: NOW, THIS IS BAD.
>> Both: W-W-WEIGHTED HAIR?
>> WITHOUT HER WEIGHTED HAIR,
GARNET'S POWER IS HOPTASTROPHIC!
>> Garnet: RINGO!
>> ULTIMATE!
>> Garnet: OOH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> Garnet: AAH!
UGH!
>> Both: GARNET!
>> Garnet: [ GROANS ]
I'M SORRY, STEVEN.
I WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
[ GASPS ]
>> AH, WHAT A NICE PHOTO.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THERE'S SOMETHING
NOT QUITE RIGHT.
OH! I KNOW!
[ POP! CHOMP! ]
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
>> NOM NOM NOM NOM NOM.
>> Garnet: [ GROWLS ]
AAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> HUH?
>> AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> OHH!
>> [ GROANS ]
THIS IS GETTING RIDICULOUS!
OHH! WHOA!
CHAH!
UGH!
AAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Both: HIP-HOP HOORAY!
>> UGH!
>> AND SO GARNET USED THE GEM TO
RETURN THE FOX MAN TO HIS
ORIGINAL FORM.
AND AS FOR RINGO [CHUCKLES] HE
STAYED TRAPPED IN THE RINGO ZONE
FOREVER.
THAT DAY, GARNET LEARNED A
VALUABLE LESSON -- THAT BEING
STRONG WAS ABOUT MORE THAN JUST
HOW MANY MOUNTAINS YOU CAN PUNCH
IN HALF.
IT WAS ABOUT LOVE.
AND THERE WAS NO GREATER LOVE
THAN GARNET'S LOVE FOR STEVEN.
>> Steven: AND THEN YOU CAME
BACK HERE AND I GOT YOU AND YOU
WERE BLIND, AND THAT'S WHAT YOU
DID TODAY!
>> Garnet: YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY
MUCH WHAT HAPPENED.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ] REALLY?!
>> Garnet: NO.
[ BOTH CHEWING ]
>> Steven: MM.
[ SPITS ]
LOOK, DAD! I'M AMADEUS!
[ German accent ] MY FATHER --
HE DISAPPROVES OF ME!
>> HA! WELL, CHECK THIS OUT.
[ CHEWING ]
[ SPITS ]
TA-DA!
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
>> BETCHA CAN'T TOP THAT!
>> Steven: BET I CAN!
[ SPITS ]
[ CHEWS ]
MMM! MM-MMM-MMM!
[ INHALES DEEPLY, SPITS ]
[ CAN CLATTERS ]
HA-HA! BEAT THAT!
>> HUH.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE, MY SON.
BUT THE NAME OF THE GAME AIN'T
DISTANCE NOR ACCURACY.
>> Steven: IT AIN'T?
>> NO, STEVEN.
THIS CHALLENGE IS ALL ABOUT WHO
CAN SPIT THE COOLEST.
ALLOW ME TO DEMONSTRATE.
[ CHEWING ]
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SPITS THREE TIMES ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
WOW, DAD!
UH, DAD? YOU OKAY?
>> [ Strained ] HELP ME, SON.
[ GROANS LOUDLY ]
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
OHH!
[ SIGHS ]
BEAT THAT.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
YOU'RE ASKING FOR IT.
[ MUNCHING GREEDILY ]
[ Muffled ] YOU'RE REALLY ASKING
FOR IT.
[ MUNCHING GREEDILY ]
HURRICANE...SPIN...SPIT!
[ MACHINE-GUN FIRE ]
MY HURRICANE SPIN SPIT IS
UNBEATABLE.
>> BY JOVE! IT'S FULL OF SEEDS!
>> Steven: DAD?
>> CONGRATULATIONS, SON.
YOU WIN BY A MILE.
[ CHEWING ]
I CROWN THEE YOUR
WATERMELAJESTY.
MY LIEGE.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Steven: [ SNORING ]
[ FLY BUZZING ]
[ YAWNS ]
MM.
[ SMACKING LIPS ]
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
HUH?
HOLY WATERMELON!
[ GRUNTS ]
IS THIS...
[ GASPS ]
CAN'T BE. THEY'RE ME!
THEY'RE ALL ME!
>> Garnet: HMM.
THIS IS REALLY IMPRESSIVE.
>> Pearl: I SUPPOSE.
YOUR MOTHER HAD THE POWER TO
GROW SENTIENT PLANT LIFE TO ACT
AS HER DEFENDERS.
>> Amethyst: BUT ROSE'S PLANTS
MOVED AND STUFF.
THESE GUYS DON'T DO...ANYTHING.
>> Steven: AMETHYST, BE CAREFUL.
THIS ONE'S JUST A BABY.
AWW! LOOK AT HIM.
SO PRECIOUS.
>> UGH!
[ GROANS ]
OHH. THIS IS REALLY WEIRD.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO WITH ALL OF
THEM?
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
THERE.
THAT'S A MIGHTY-FINE-LOOKING
TABLE, RIGHT, BABY MELON?
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
MM-HMM.
>> STEVEN! WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
YOU GOT A PERMIT FOR THIS SETUP?
>> Steven: OH!
UH, HEY, MR. SMILEY.
UM...HERE.
TRY ONE OF MY
WATERMELON STEVENS!
>> HMM.
YEAH, I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF WEIRD-LOOKING.
UH, BUT...I'LL GO AHEAD AND
ACCEPT YOUR BRIBE.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: HEY, THERE.
>> HEY, STEVEN.
WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT?
>> Steven: JUST A LITTLE SIDE
PROJECT I GOT GOING ON.
>> OH, REALLY?
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S GREAT.
HOW'D YOU GET SUCH HANDSOME
WATERMELONS?
>> Steven: LET'S JUST SAY
THERE'S A LITTLE STEVEN IN EVERY
ONE OF THEM.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
GREAT SALES PITCH, DUDE.
SO, HOW MUCH FOR ONE?
>> Steven: HOW MUCH?
UH, I WAS JUST GONNA GIVE YOU
ONE, SADIE.
>> COME ON. I INSIST.
I LOVE SUPPORTING LOCAL
BUSINESSES.
>> Steven: MM.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
>> WHOA!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> Steven: HEY, RONALDO.
>> DON'T MIND ME.
JUST DOING SOME LIVE BLOGGING
ABOUT YOUR WEIRD WATERMELONS.
[ LAUGHS ]
"CHECK...OUT...THESE WEIRD
WATERMELON GUYS DOWN...BY...THE
FUNLAND...ENTRANCE.
IT'S...REALLY..."
>> STEVEN, YOU SHOULDN'T KEEP
YOUR CUSTOMERS WAITING LIKE
THIS.
I'LL JUST GIVE YOU FIVE BUCKS
AND TAKE ONE, OKAY?
>> Steven: SADIE, WAI--
>> WHAT?
YOU'RE ONLY SELLING THEM FOR
$5?!
HEY, EVERYBODY!
COME GET A WATERMELON STEVEN!
HE'S PRACTICALLY GIVING THEM
AWAY!
HURRY BEFORE THEY'RE GONE
FOREVER!
[ ALL CLAMORING ]
>> Steven: AND ANOTHER AND
ANOTHER AND ANOTHER AND ANOTHER.
COOL. 100 PIECES OF MONEY.
OH. HEY, ONION.
UM...YOU WANT...MY MONEY?
OH!
SORRY FOR THE MISUNDERSTANDING.
I'M ALL OUT OF
WATERMELON STEVENS.
SORRY, ONION.
BABY MELON IS NOT FOR SALE.
[ HURRIED FOOTSTEPS DEPART ]
ONIO-O-O-O-N!
[ GROWLS ]
GIVE ME BACK MY BABY MELON!
MY BABY MELON!
[ SIGHS ]
MY PRECIOUS.
I...THOUGHT I'D NEVER SEE YOU
AGAIN.
YOU'RE...ALIVE?!
I REALLY SHOULDN'T BE SO
SURPRISED ABOUT THIS.
OH, MAN.
THE OTHER ONES MUST BE ALIVE,
TOO, RIGHT?!
[ UP-TEMPO THEME PLAYS ]
[ THEME ENDS, BUTTON CLICKS ]
>> "KEEP BEACH CITY WEIRD"
PRESENTS...
OH, HANG ON A SECOND.
[ GRUNTS ]
...FIRST EVER OFFICIAL
MUTANT-WATERMELON AUTOPSY.
>> Steven: RONALDO, STOP!
>> STEVEN! GET OUT OF HERE!
YOU'RE GONNA RUIN MY
WEBSCLUSIVE!
>> Steven: RONALDO! IT'S ALIVE!
>> NOT FOR LONG.
>> Steven: NO! DON'T DO IT!
OW!
>> WHAT?
G-GET AWAY FROM ME! STAY BACK!
[ ALL HISSING ]
AAH! NO!
OHH! OOH! OHH!
>> Steven: NO!
UH, RONALDO, I'LL GO GET HELP!
>> STEVEN!
IS THE CAMERA GETTING ALL OF
THIS?
SWEET!
AAH! OHH! OHH!
>> Steven: PEARL! GARNET!
AMETHYST!
>> All: WHAT?
>> Steven: MY WATERMELONS CAME
TO LIFE, AND THEY'RE ATTACKING
PEOPLE!
>> All: WHAT?!
[ ALL GASP ]
[ BIRD CRIES ]
>> Amethyst: WOW.
>> Pearl: YOU SAID THEY'RE
HURTING PEOPLE?
>> Garnet: ROSE'S PLANTS LIVED
TO FIGHT.
>> Pearl: HE CAN'T CONTROL THEM.
STEVEN.
[ ALL STOMP ]
GET IN THE HOUSE.
>> Steven: BUT --
>> Pearl: NOW.
[ ALL HISS ]
>> Amethyst: OH, WHAT?!
BRING IT, MELONS!
>> Garnet: GEMS, DO YOUR THING.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: WAIT! DON'T!
COME ON, BABY MELON.
WE HAVE TO STOP THIS.
>> Amethyst: [ PANTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: HYAH!
[ WAR CRIES ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
COME ON.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
>> Steven: EVERYONE, PLEASE
STOP!
I'M OKAY! LOOK!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT ANYMORE!
>> Amethyst: [ CRYING ]
THEY'RE GONNA PUT ME IN THE
GROUND!
[ SOBBING ]
NO!
[ CONTINUES SOBBING ]
THOSE FLOWERS ARE LOVELY!
AAH!
>> Pearl: LET GO OF MY SPEAR,
YOU LITTLE TWERPS!
I'LL DESTROY YOU!
>> Steven: THIS IS BAD,
BABY MELLY.
HOW DO WE END THIS CARNAGE?
[ SMACK! ]
[ GRUNTS ]
BABY...MELON?
[ GASPS ]
[ EXCLAIMS ]
[ COUGHING ]
AH, LET ME THROUGH, YOU MELON
HEADS.
BA-BABY MELON.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU STOPPED THE WATERMELONS FROM
FIGHTING EVERYONE ELSE...
BY MAKING THEM FIGHT YOU.
LOOK AT WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
YOU THINK I WANTED THIS?!
YOU SHOULD ALL BE ASHAMED!
HE KNEW THIS IS WHAT IT WOULD
TAKE TO CALM YOUR RAGE.
HE UNDERSTOOD TRUE LOYALTY.
GO!
THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
AND DON'T COME BACK UNTIL YOU
UNDERSTAND WHAT HE DID FOR ME...
FOR ALL OF US.
>> Garnet: SPOKEN LIKE A TRUE
KING.
>> Steven: THEY DON'T NEED A
THEY'RE THEIR OWN MELONS NOW.
[ MUNCH! MUNCH! MUNCH! ]