♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
[ Yawns ]
Night, Peridot.
Nothing left to do but dream.
Hmm.
Ronaldo: Steven!
[ Pounding on door ]
Steven!
Ste--ven!
Ronaldo,
it's the middle of the night.
You have to come
to the lighthouse.
I've found
something weird.
You've found something
weird every day
since my dad got you
that telescope.
I know. I'm amazing.
You won't believe
my latest discovery.
There's something
on the moon.
Can't you call Nanefua?
Not a fourth time.
Hmm.
This is the moon base.
It's always been there.
You have a moon base?!
I have so many questions.
One -- Why didn't you tell me
about your moon base?
Two --
Take me to your moon base.
Three -- Why does it
look like a barn?
It doesn't look like a --
Wait, what?
♪♪
Lapis?
Whoa!
Thanks, Lion.
That super warp takes
a lot out of you, huh?
[ Yawns ]
You and me both,
buddy.
You stay here and rest up,
okay?
♪♪
Why would Lapis bring
the Barn to the moon?
Thought she wanted to get as far
away from Earth as possible.
♪♪
Lapis?
Lapis Lazuli?
This is weird.
All the meep morps
are still here, but no Lapis.
Now, what is going on?
[ Humming in distance ]
♪♪
Lapis?
Lapis!
-[ Gasps ]
Steven.
Hup!
I can't believe it.
It's so good
to see you again.
Oh, really?
What's going on?
I-I thought you'd be halfway
across the galaxy by now.
Aren't you worried about
the Diamonds coming to attack?
I got...distracted.
By this orb thing?
What is it?
Promise
you won't judge me.
I sleep with a teddy bear.
No judgments.
Wha--
Wha-huh?
Beach City?
Please explain this to me.
This orb is
an observation device.
The Diamonds use them
to watch activity
on their colonies
from afar.
Wow.
Can I try?
Sure.
Whoa.
But, Lapis, what are
you using it for?
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
You're spying on us?
Well, I wouldn't
call it spying
because that would
make me feel bad.
Oh, Lapis.
I couldn't stand not knowing
what was going on.
I'm still terrified of
the Diamonds coming to Earth,
but I got just outside the
Milky Way and I felt so lonely.
So why didn't you
just come back?
I want to, but I just can't,
not after the way I left.
What would Peridot say?
What if the Diamonds show up?
What if something bad happens?
Well, what if
something good happens?
[ Laughs ]
Uh, Lapis?
You okay?
♪♪
♪ It all became so lovely ♪
♪ Those bluest skies
above me ♪
♪ Those funny feelings ♪
♪ I had never felt
before I met you ♪
♪ I thought
I'd stay a while ♪
♪ I tried to
learn to smile ♪
♪ So many colors
I had never even known ♪
♪ Maybe I'll find myself
sitting on that distant shore ♪
♪ Maybe I'm not alone ♪
♪♪
♪ Then I see the colors
fading ♪
♪ Gentleness of light
escaping ♪
♪ Shadows of my fear invading ♪
♪ Have I seen this all before ♪
♪ I know that
there's something residing ♪
♪ A terror deep inside me ♪
♪ I couldn't understand
how you could be so bold ♪
♪ Maybe I'll find myself
smiling on that distant shore ♪
♪ Maybe I'm not alone ♪
I might have overreacted
about the Diamonds.
You really think
they're coming?
I don't even know anymore.
I've done so much
because I was afraid.
I left Peridot behind.
I took the Barn
and her morps.
Hey,
at least she has Pumpkin.
[ Sighs ]
I was so sure the Diamonds
would destroy my new home
that I did it myself.
It's like I'm back
inside the mirror,
except I put myself here.
Oh, the moon's not so bad.
Are you kidding?
The moon sucks.
There's nothing here.
Maybe I'm tired
of running away.
Maybe I'd rather
be with everyone
and be in danger
than be safe and alone.
They'd be glad
to have you back.
I don't know.
If I went back now,
there's no way things
could go back to how they were.
Yeah,
but that's all right.
Things would just
be different.
What do you mean?
Well, what if you weren't
way out in the country?
You could drop the Barn
on the beach.
Then we'd all
be neighbors.
I'd come over to borrow
a cup of a sugar
and you'd be like,
"What's that?"
[ Both laugh ]
[ Yawns ]
When you go back,
we should all hang out more.
Huh, when I go back.
-This is what you wanted.
-[ Gasps ]
Lapis?
Blue Diamond: You begged us for
a colony of your own,
and now all you want
to do is be rid of it.
First there were
too many Organics.
Then their cities were
too difficult to dismantle,
and --
and now these Crystal Gems.
We're tired of
your excuses, Pink.
The Diamonds!
This Rose Quartz
can't hurt you.
You can't be swayed
by a few unruly Gems.
Enough.
You must understand,
you are a Diamond.
Everyone on this planet
is looking to you.
You don't even
have to do anything.
Just smile and wave.
Show everyone you're unfazed
by this little uprising.
Your gems will fall into line,
and these Crystal Gems
will be no more.
As long as you
are there to rule,
this colony will be completed.
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Mom's sword?
Is that...
Pearl?
[ Screams ]
Steven, are you okay?
Were you dreaming?
I...I saw the Diamonds.
What? What are you
talking about?
I dreamt about them.
They were right in this room.
What does that mean?
Are they coming?
I...I don't know.
What if they are?
What if they're close?
Why else would you see them?
Steven.
♪♪
Ugh!
Lapis, hold on!
♪♪
Ah!
Ahhh!
Where are you going?
As far from Earth
as I can!
I'm leaving.
You should be used
to that by now.
You don't have to run,
Lapis.
Just --
Just stay with us.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
I-I'm not like you
and your friends, Steven.
I can't just let go
of what happened to me.
I can't go through that
again.
Would you rather
be alone?
I'm sorry.
Wait!
♪♪
Lion, I need you to
take me to Pearl.
♪♪
I watched the leader
of the Crystal Gems,
Rose Quartz, shatter
Pink Diamond!
So how did a rose quartz,
with no business
being anywhere near
Pink Diamond, get so close
in the first place?
Aagh!
I can't believe you've had
your phone for a month
and you haven't
used it at all!
That's not true!
I use it to tell the time!
Sigh. Come here, P.
Ugh. Let's change
your wallpaper.
[ Shutter clicks ]
Looks great!
Okay, now texting
is in the messages.
Just click on this green icon.
Pearl, can I ask you someth--
Hold on, Steve-o,
I'm in
the middle of a demonstration!
Okay, anyway, and you can type,
I mean, pretty much
anything you want.
[ Message chime ]
You really should
have a case for this.
I do!
Okay. I have a bunch of actual
phone cases in my room. Hup!
Don't throw that thing against a
rock or anything until I'm back.
Pearl...
What is it, Steven?
You remember how Mom
shattered Pink Diamond?
Well, I was just wondering
if maybe you shattered
Pink Diamond?
I...
I-it's okay!
You can tell me!
[ Grunting ]
Why can't you just
talk to me about this?!
I got the...
phone case.
Oh, yes! The phone case!
Thank you, Amethyst!
Ha ha -- whoops! So clumsy.
It's probably safer
if I just keep it in here.
Wait, come on!
Just put it in this,
then put it in your head!
What was that?
[ Sighs ]
[ Waves crashing,
gulls crying ]
[ Message chime ]
"I want to tell you,
but I can't"?!
[ Vacuum running ]
Pearl, I'm ready to talk!
Uh, what?!
I-I got your text.
"I want to tell you but I
can't," with a monkey emoji?
Steven, I didn't send that.
I haven't used my phone since
I put it away this morning.
Maybe you butt dialed me...
with your gem?
No, that's impossible.
Hang on, I'll pull it out, and
we'll get to the bottom of this.
See, here.
See, I --
Maybe this? No.
Maybe this?
No. Maybe -- may-may this?
No.
Pearl, are you okay?
Ugh. Where could I have put it?
I know it's in there somewhere.
[ Gasps ]
You just sent another one!
♪♪
Steven... I need you to go
inside my gem and find my phone.
What? I-is it stuck
in there or something!?
There are certain things
I can't tell you,
but I can tell you
that I need my phone.
Please!
I can bring you back out
once you find what
you're looking for.
Your phone...
Exactly!
I'll keep your phone, text me
with mine when you find it.
Huh!
[ Humming ]
There's a Pearl
inside Pearl's pearl?
Oh, Steven!
Where should I put you?
Certainly not with the spears.
Human paraphernalia?
Personal items?
Let's just go alphabetical.
S... S-T...
Wait, no! Don't file me!
You sent me in here
for your cell phone!
My phone?
Well, all right, let's see.
P-H-O-...
Ah, hmm. Nothing.
Oh, it's a cellular phone!
I must have put it under "C"!
It should be right... here.
It should be right here!
Unless... some other me took it.
There's more of you in here?
Oh, no, not here.
I made sure of that.
I'm very good at
compartmentalizing everything.
That's why I get to be surface,
and they have to be put away.
Well, if one of those
Pearls has the phone,
can you tell me
where to find her?
Oh, you don't want
to go where they are.
It's a mess.
Let's just stay here,
where everything
is alphabetized!
Come on, I can handle it!
All right. Don't say
I didn't warn you.
[ Waves lapping shore ]
This doesn't look like a mess.
It looks like... the past.
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, that kind of mess.
Hey, Pearl inside Pearl
inside Pearl's pearl.
You upset about the whole
missing phone situation, too?
No, it's Rose!
What was she thinking?!
She can't have a baby!
Well, this is awkward.
What am I going to do
when she disappears?
I'm going to lose her,
just like I lost my --
what was it you said?
Your cell phone?
[ Wailing ]
My cell phone!
Look, it's going to be okay!
That's why you sent me in here,
I'm going to help you find it.
I think I know where it is.
It's probably where I
lost everything else.
♪♪
Huh?
It better not turn out that
her phone was in her pocket...
or she left it on the dresser
or dropped it in the toilet.
Seems about as likely
as putting it away
in your repressed war memories.
Pearl?
I mean, Pearl inside Pearl
inside Pearl
inside Pearl's pearl!
Is this really about
your phone or what!
We're the only ones left.
Homeworld...
they were all leaving.
We thought we'd won.
There was a bright light
and everyone was...
Why did I do it?
What do you mean?
Just tell me!
♪♪
[ Grunting ]
Mom?
I thought this was Pearl's...
What are you doing here?
W-what?!
[ Shouting ]
I... I knew it!
It was you who shattered her.
Pink Diamond?
But... I don't understand.
♪♪
The palanquin?
[ Indistinct whispering ]
And then you'll be done!
It's going to be easy!
There's got to be another way!
I mean, maybe...
Blue and yellow don't care!
They never have!
This is "Pink Diamond's" colony.
We can end it all
right here, right now.
You know this is crazy, right?
Your status, my purpose --
none of it will matter anymore.
This will change everything.
I know. Isn't it exciting?
[ Sighs ]
It is!
We can leave
our old lives behind.
If this is really my world,
I want to give it
to the Crystal Gems.
I want to live here
with human beings.
I want to live here with you!
We'll both finally be free!
Okay, I'm ready!
Pearl!
I can't believe
I'm going to do this.
I can't exactly
shatter myself.
♪♪
[ Blows, grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Convincing?
Very much so, my diamond.
Soon it will be just "Rose."
Wait. There's one last
thing I need to do.
Yes?
No one can ever
find out we did this.
I never want to look back.
So, for my last order
to you as a diamond, please,
let's never speak of this again.
No one can know.
♪♪
[ Gasps ]
Sorry to make you
come all this way.
♪♪
I know.
I wanted to tell you
for so long.
Mom was Pink Diamond.
What?!
♪♪