Ooh!
Guys, it's time for
a new episode
of "Crying Breakfast Friends"!
You guys, I'm so excited
it's finally back.
I even stayed off the Internet
all day
'cause I didn't want to
get...spoiled.
[ Chuckles ]
Because they're food?
I know I used that joke
last week,
but, for real, this is
supposed to be a big one.
All right, play!
♪ Tears of sorrow,
tears of joy ♪
♪ There'll be tears
till the very end ♪
♪ Food with feelings ♪
♪ Crying breakfast friends ♪
[ Noisemaker squeals ]
[ Balloon squeaks ]
Oh, that looks fun.
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, Pear.
What's wrong, Pear?
It's Spoon!
Why are you crying?
Oh, Spoon, I invited my friends
over for a breakfast party
[voice breaking]
but nobody came!
[ Sobs ]
Aw.
Oh, but --
but that's why we're here.
-Huh?
[ Sproing! ]
We came for your party.
I'm sorry we were late.
Please forgive us.
I forgive you.
Yay!
Yes! Conflict resolved!
Sweet catharsis!
I didn't think I'd be crying
this early into the episode.
[ All gasping ]
Whoa.
What's that?
It's a fridge?
Is it more food?
French toast?
Aah! [ Pants ]
Oh, my gosh. Is this...
Breakfast time...
is over.
I think
I know what this is.
Clear the table.
Yeah. Get a box to go.
There's only room for one meal
at a time, and that's us --
Together:
The angry lunch enemies!
It's lunch!
I knew it!
Theory confirmed!
Stop cryin'!
-Hey.
-Wait.
Maybe there can be two meals
at the same time.
Want to try it?
[ Grumbles ]
Okay.
But I'm angry about it.
What?
Fried egg.
No.
Avocado. Bacon strips.
Yes!
Please!
[ Gasps ]
Brunch!
They're brunch!
Ahh!
Huh? It's over?
Wow.
I can't wait
for the next episode --
whenever that is.
Am I right?
Okay, friends,
see you next time.