♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven:
♪ And if you think we can't ♪
♪ We'll always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Steven: We'll be fine!
I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna
walk Connie out.
Don't worry! I'm not going
back into space or anything.
[ Laughs ]
They're never gonna
let me out of their sight again.
Connie?
Connie! I know you got to
get home and get some sleep,
but once
you're all rested up,
I can't wait to tell you
about everything!
Being on Homeworld
was crazy!
After I turned myself in,
they put me on trial!
And Lars was there.
We got chased by killer robots.
[ Chuckles ]
What a wild ride that was.
And uh...I'm really happy
to see you again.
Umm...a-are you happy
to see me, too?
Of course I'm happy
to see you, Steven.
Uh, but?
But how could you just
give yourself up like that?
Well, first,
I said I was my dad,
and then I said
I was my mom.
[ Scoffs ] No.
I mean, you just gave up.
I had to.
They were gonna take
all those people.
They were gonna
take you!
But what about
our training?
Stevonnie.
Jam buds.
I believed in us.
We could have done it
together.
This is different.
This whole thing was my fault,
but I knew that I could fix
it all if I turned myself in.
And look --
No one got hurt.
Well, except for Lars,
but I saved him, too.
But... I'm hurt.
No, you're not.
You're safe.
You're here. I'm here.
We're safe. Everything's fine.
It's not, though.
You know, it was
a tough decision for me to make,
but it had to be done.
You don't get it.
Get what?
Let's go, Lion.
[ Roars ]
"Wow, Steven,
that was so brave of you.
I'm so glad you're back."
What?!
And Lars is still in space?!
Yeah, he is,
but don't worry,
he's with
some very nice gems
who are on the run
from their Homeworld overlords.
Oh, Laaaars.
Sadie, he's fine.
We can go see him anytime
through Lion.
Glad he's not -- At least he's
some kind of alive.
You told his parents,
right?
You're kind of
my practice run for that.
[ Bell dings ]
[ Sighs ]
Let's do this quick.
I can't be away from work
too long.
I'm basically
their only employee now.
[ Shouting, booing ]
Whoa, what's going on?
Man: We're sick of it!
Am I right about it?!
Aliens nearly abducted
the whole town.
And what did Mayor "Billiam"
Dewey do about it?
That is right.
Jack and squat!
[ All shouting ]
Steven, I'm going to
Lars's parents' house.
Okay, I'll
catch up with you.
And that is why
you should vote for me,
your favorite Nanefua,
for mayor of Beach City!
[ All cheering ]
When I say "Do we want Dewey?"
you say "No."
Do we want Dewey?
All: No!
Nanefua: Okay, good job.
Hmm.
"Can't hang today.
Mayor D's getting blamed
for Gem stuff,
and it's totally my fault."
I don't know, Universe.
This doesn't look good.
How's this?
Oh.
That looks great.
But I may need more.
My gosh. I've never had
an opponent before.
Even when I ran for mayor
of high school, I ran unopposed.
Probably because
I made up the position.
If only
I could've warned you
about this abduction stuff
sooner,
then everything
would be fine now.
I really
dropped the ball.
You're right, Universe.
This is all your fault.
Huh.
How about we call
an impromptu town meeting
on the boardwalk?
I'll tell everyone what happened
and how you weren't
involved at all,
and everyone'll
feel better
and vote for you
in the next election.
All right, Universe.
The ball's
back in your court.
Just, uh...
don't drop it again, huh?
So, in conclusion, Mayor Dewey
had nothing whatsoever to do
with the abductions.
Everything was my fault
because I unknowingly provided
some space Gems
with a list of names
and put everyone in danger.
Mayor Dewey
would never do anything
to purposefully endanger
the town.
He basically
just keeps a low profile
and doesn't get involved
in much of anything.
Yeah, maybe
he should be involved!
He's the mayor!
[ Crowd booing ]
Thanks for listening,
and please vote for him
in the next Beach City
mayoral election.
Oh, ho, ho, yeah!
Hello, everyone.
Thanks for coming. Wow!
This whole abduction business
was a real close call,
huh? Whoo.
But look around you.
Everyone is safe
and accounted for.
That's not true!
What about my friend Lars?
Who?
What? Lars!
Lars Barriga?!
Mr. And Mrs. Barriga's son!
Did you even know
he was still missing?
Did you know he was
still somewhere in space?!
What kind of mayor
doesn't know when his own people
are lost in space?!
The donut boy?
Is that why the donut shop was
closed this morning?
Yeah, but --
Do not worry.
I will do everything in my power
to hire a new donut boy.
[ Crowd booing ]
No!
You've got to be
kidding me!
How did this get
on the Internet so fast?
I didn't invite any press
to this event.
Someone posted it
on Tube-Tube.
Only 12 people
have seen it.
12 people?!
That's half the town!
I'm finished, Universe.
I don't know
of many political figures
that have made
a comeback
after getting a tomato
to the face.
Oh, again, and again,
and again, and again.
You need to stop
looping that.
Look, we're gonna
get through this together, okay?
Tomorrow is
the big debate.
You still have one more chance
to win back the town's love.
But Steven, some of the things
people have been saying about me
are really painful
and mean.
We've just got to change
the conversation.
We can start with this.
"How to talk to people"?
I'm going to get you ready
for that debate,
even if it takes
all night.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
All right.
[ Yawns ]
Today's the day.
You got your note cards,
you look great,
and if anyone brings up
the alien invasion thing,
I wrote a bunch of Ocean Town
jokes for you to use.
Aww, shucks, Universe.
You're like the son
I never had.
You...have a son.
I know that.
You're just very different
from him, is all.
[ Crowd chanting "speech" ]
[ Whines ]
I'm rooting for you,
Dew Drops.
[ Weakly ] Thanks.
[ Chanting continues ]
[ Chanting stops ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Microphone feedback ]
People of Beach City.
You might think
that being a mayor is a fine
and glamorous
sort of thing.
I can understand why my opponent
would want the position.
But I've been mayor of this city
for a decade,
and I know some things
that Ms. Nanefua does not.
You see, when you're the mayor,
you get blamed for everything.
When the boardwalk has termites,
it's the mayor's fault.
When aliens steal people,
When the mayor crashes
the mayor mobile
into the only cell tower
in town, it's the mayor's fault.
Most people can't handle that
kind of pressure, but I can.
So, I say to you,
Beach City citizens,
just enjoy
our wonderful ocean breeze
and don't worry
about a thing.
Just let Dewey "do" it
for you!
[ Crowd murmuring,
applause ]
Nice.
You know, Mayor Dewey,
you are right.
I am?
A-About what?
I have blamed you
for too many things,
and that is not helping.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
What?
Blaming our problems
completely on the mayor
is not getting us
anywhere.
When one of us suffers,
the town suffers.
When you suffer, Mayor Billiam,
So, no longer will I
point my fingers at you.
I will extend all my fingers
on both my hands
to everyone here today
and ask that we share
responsibility
for the welfare and safety
of Beach City, together!
Thank you.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Chanting "Nanefua" ]
You got this, Mayor Dewey.
[ Stammering ]
Uh, did you ever notice
how people from Ocean Town --
Oh, who am I kidding?
Beach City deserves
a real mayor.
Someone wise and collected
like Ms. Nanefua.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
Wait.
No, no, no.
I withdraw
from the race.
You can find the key to the city
under the city welcome mat.
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Sighs ]
Mayor Dewey,
what're you doing?!
Y-You can't just
throw the election like that.
W-We could still win!
Well, I know
it's not very traditional
to do that in the middle
of a debate,
but why drag it out?
We could have won!
I really believed in you!
I really believed in us!
Well, you were wrong.
What do you want me
to say?
How about, "I'm sorry.
We were in this together,
and I let you down."
Come on, Universe.
You know she's gonna be
a better mayor than me.
It was
the right thing to do.
I guess, but...
I still feel betrayed.
That's probably
how Connie feels.
Yeah, I don't know
what you're talking about,
but I've got to find
a new job.
[ Humming ]
[ Tapping, phone dialing ]
[ Dialing continues ]
♪♪
Steven: "Hey, Connie.
How are you today?
Hope everything's going okay.
It'd be cool if
you told me it was...
I guess I miss you.
I know yesterday I said,
'I guess,' but I mean,
I do miss you...
Hope you didn't get your phone
mixed up with a tennis ball.
Ha ha."
A tennis ball?
Really, Universe?
[ Sighs ]
Help! Ah! Yah!
Back!
Ugh!
Hey, uh, Stevearoni,
ugh,
want to help
your old Pa over here?
Uh, yeah, Dad,
one sec.
♪♪
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm on it.
[ Grunts ]
Are you good? Are you safe?
Do you still love me?
Yeah, of --
of course, buddy.
It's just some hoses.
I can buy new ones.
I still have like
$9 million left,
and what better way
to spend that
than on some hoses,
right, kiddo?
Yeah, Dad.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
[ Gasps ]
Ronaldo: Steven!
So. Did you ever get around
to watching
the "Koala Princess" box set
I lent you
three months ago?
[ Sighs ]
Hey, is everything okay?
You're looking
a little glum.
I am a little glum.
Do you want to
talk about it?
Um, it's just space lag
from when
I went to space.
Hmm.
[ Sighs ]
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
Ah!
Wait. No.
I need to play it cool.
Ronaldo: I'm just gonna assume
by your silence
that you're entangled within
the immersive koala lore
of the show.
Did you get to the part
where Koala Princess
and Kanga-Roofus kiss?
Greg: Steven, you want to help
us with these groceries?
Coming.
Eh? Eh?
[ Voice muffled ]
Check this out, Steven.
[ Normal voice ]
It's farm fresh.
Uh, thanks guys,
but the fridge is full.
Not the fridge
at our vacation house.
-Whoo!
-Vacation.
I thought,
"Why spend money on hoses
when I can spend it
on houses?"
So I found a place
we could rent
for the weekend
by searching online.
Back in the old days
we just went door-to-door
hoping one was unlocked,
but this is the new days.
Okay. Well, have fun.
Uh, Steven, you're going
on vacation, too.
[ Coughs ]
Oh, yes.
This is the perfect time
for a vacation.
I mean, how often are we
on the same planet together?
Yeah. And you'll be
with your favorite Gems
and your favorite dad.
Agree with Amethyst.
Turn to Steven.
Steven, you should go.
No,
with more enthusiasm.
Steven,
it's a vacation!
I mean, I would,
but I'm really tied up
with something important.
Ronaldo: In the end,
the wombats were for naught,
but it really
makes you think.
I'll go.
Aced it.
Greg: Here it is,
temporary home
sweet temporary home.
-Is that my bed?
-Yeah.
I want you to be
a comfortable as possible,
finally have
some family time.
I feel like you haven't
had that in a while.
Yeah, maybe.
This place is great.
They have one
of those refrigerators
that dispense water,
not to mention four windows
and an analog clock!
Hmm, says here
we can't use
the water dispenser
or the clock.
Windows must be kept
closed at all times,
and remove all shoes
before entering.
Hmm.
Hey, Greg, did you invite
anyone else, party guy,
about three feet long,
hissing, reptilian?
No.
Well, you might want
to factor in a plus one.
-Oh! Party guy, no!
-I promise.
It's gonna be
a really good time.
It's a great place, Dad.
It only bit Pearl once,
but, like, we're Gems.
She'll be okay.
[ Groans ]
It isn't the pain.
It's the surprise.
Hey, Amethyst, do you think
you could...
Yeah.
Hey, Steven.
Hi, Amethyst.
Man, you can see the stars
so clearly out here.
It's pretty, huh?
Huh?
Uh, I don't know.
It's okay.
-Hey, hey.
It's okay
if it isn't okay.
The sky?
Yeah.
-What?
-I don't know.
So, uh, you really
into phones now?
No.
♪♪
[ Owl hoots ]
Hey, Schtuball,
won't you take my place?
I've been in here way too long.
I'm gonna become a raisin.
Steven,
you should join me.
Become a raisin.
Okay, but one sec.
Steven, I know
what's troubling you.
You do?
Gosh.
I really messed up, didn't I?
You didn't do
anything wrong.
Pink Diamond
was a villain.
It was 5,750 years ago.
Pink Diamond was
ravishing the planet.
-Yeah, I know.
-Oh.
Pink Diamond was bad.
Everything bad
had to happen
so good things
could kind of happen.
Uh, good.
You understand.
Buzz.
At least wiggle a little.
Greg: Come on. Can't you
give it another shot?
Amethyst:
What are we supposed to do?
He just doesn't want
to talk about it.
But I know
it's not space lag.
This is some Gem thing
he knows I won't understand.
I don't know anything
about Homeworld.
about your society.
Whatever horrible things
he saw out there,
you guys have to
put it into context.
If Steven won't
talk to us,
then the help we can
give him is limited.
We've all tried
to coax it out of him
except for...
Me?
But I have no idea
what Homeworld is like now.
Pearl, please.
He knows you know
about space stuff.
It can't hurt to try.
Mm.
♪♪
Huh. It sure is quiet
out here, huh?
Yeah.
So, Homeworld...
I always hoped
you'd see it some day,
but I thought
I'd be there with you.
Being taken there
as a prisoner,
I suppose it was something
of a dramatic experience.
It's just, Steven,
I'm sure you have
a lot of questions
you'd like answers to,
like about the Diamonds,
for instance.
There are things that are
impossible for me to explain.
But I want to.
I --
Steven, I --
Connie hates me!
What?
We weren't listening.
Also continue, Steven.
I'm not upset about
what happened on Homeworld
although, yeah, a lot of that
was really messed up.
But my relationship with Connie
is even more messed up.
I left her behind
to go to Homeworld
after promising we'd face
everything together.
I'm sure I really hurt her.
I've been calling
and texting her for a week,
but she hasn't
responded once.
Connie might never
talk to me again.
[ Crying ]
Steven!
I'll go get him.
I don't know anything
about Homeworld,
but I know about this.
Steven?
Steven's not here.
Oh, that's too bad.
So I guess I'll just
talk to this
Steven-shaped barrel
instead.
If you must.
Schtuball, if this was
about Connie,
why didn't you say
anything sooner?
I was embarra...
You were embroidered,
embroiled,
emboldened to talk
to your old man
about your problems?
I was embarrassed,
okay?
You and the Gems
all liked Connie,
and I was worried that if you
heard what happened
that you'd be
mad at me too.
Oh, Steven, of course
we're not mad.
And I'm sure
Connie's not mad, either.
Well, at least I'm sure
she doesn't hate you.
That whole handing-yourself
over-to-Homeworld thing
was definitely
a high-stress situation.
It really scared
all of us.
I'm not exactly
over it either,
but I guess
carting you off
to the middle of nowhere
to spend time with you
is my way
of dealing with it.
Maybe having some distance
from you is Connie's way.
But the last thing I did was
send her a bunch of dumb texts.
I made some weird joke
about tennis,
and I don't even know
if it makes sense.
Tennis?
See?
No wonder
she hasn't responded.
Uh, Steven, you don't
get any service out here.
What are you
even telling me?
Maybe she's been
trying to get in touch
with me this whole time,
and I haven't seen it!
What if she thinks
I'm ignoring her?
Dad! We have to
find cell service.
Right.
Go, go, go!
Okay.
Floor it!
How we doing?
Take a right.
Nah, back up.
No, wait!
Keep going.
We're heading
for a cliff, buddy.
Just a little further.
Gonna have to stop soon.
Almost got it.
Ahh!
[ Sighs ]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yes!
We've got service.
[ Gasps ]
Ronaldo: Steven! When I didn't
hear back from you,
I was sure a nefarious plot
was afoot.
Well?
No. No messages
from Connie.
♪♪
Aw. You'll get
through this, buddy.
I know it hurts now,
but give it time.
I know.
I need to let it go.
Got room for three more?
Always.
Nice night, isn't it?
Steven: Yeah.
♪♪