♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
WE'RE FINALLY HOME!
AWW,
HELLO HOUSE!
HELLO, BED!
MM! [ LAUGHS ]
HELLO, TV!
WE'VE GOT SOME CATCHING UP
TO DO.
HELLO, KITCHEN.
HELLO, FOOD!
[ GROANS ]
UH-OH,
DID THAT CAKE GO BAD?
THAT WAS A CAKE?
HELLO, TEMPLE!
HELLO, BEACH!
HELLO, TOWN!
AND HELLO, MY FAVORITE PLACE
TO GET A SNACK, THE BIG DONUT!
IS CLOSED?!
OH, HEY STEVEN.
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU FOR A WHILE!
YOU MISSED
ALL THE EARTHQUAKES.
[ PANTING ]
I WAS OUT IN THE FIELD,
SAVING THE WORLD!
WOW, NICE.
ARE YOU
CLOSING UP?
I REALLY WANTED
A DONUT.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
AT LEAST ONE IN THERE.
SORRY, I ALREADY SET THE ALARM
FOR THE NIGHT.
BUT, SADIE!
I'VE BEEN GONE
SO LONG,
AND ALL THE FOOD
IN OUR HOUSE WENT BAD.
AND I'M JUST STARVING.
UM, I THINK FISH PIZZA
IS STILL OPEN.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M HUNGRY ENOUGH FOR A MEAL.
BUT YOU'RE STARVING?
NO,
I'M DYING!
BLEGH!
WELL,
IF YOU'RE DEAD NOW,
I GUESS YOU CAN'T
COME BY TOMORROW.
I WON'T
BE DEAD THEN!
WHAT HAPPENS TOMORROW?
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
WE STARTED BAKING OUR OWN DONUTS
AFTER THAT WORKPLACE-SAFETY
LAWSUIT GOT THROWN OUT.
SO IF YOU GET HERE TOMORROW
RIGHT WHEN THE SHOP OPENS,
YOU CAN HAVE
THE VERY FIRST,
FRESH
DONUT OF THE DAY.
WHAT AN HONOR!
FIRST THING TOMORROW,
I'LL BE HERE
RIGHT WHEN
THE STORE OPENS
TO TASTE YOUR FIRST
DELICIOUS DONUT OF THE DAY!
YEAH, SURE.
LATER, STEVEN!
[ ALARM CLOCK BEEPING ]
MM, 6:55 A.M.
THAT SHOULD GIVE ME
ENOUGH TIME
TO GET TO THE BIG DONUT
RIGHT WHEN IT OPENS AT 7:00.
AND I CAN START ANOTHER
BEAUTIFUL, BEACH CITY DAY.
[ SIGHS ]
IT FEELS SO GOOD TO BE HOME.
HELLO, BEACH CITY!
IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK!
WHOA!
I JUMPED SUPER HIGH!
I DIDN'T KNOW I COULD DO THAT!
♪♪
OH, MY GOSH!
THIS IS A NEW POWER!
IT'S LIKE I'M SUPER LIGHT!
WHOOP!
I CAN JUMP REALLY HIGH
AND FLOAT DOWN REALLY SLOW!
JUMP!
FLOAT.
♪♪
AND JUMP!
Woman: THE CAPTAIN HAS TURNED ON
THE SEATBELT SIGN.
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT SOME BOYS
IN THE SKY AHEAD OF US.
WHOA.
♪♪
BEACH CITY LOOKS SO SMALL
FROM UP HERE.
OH MAN,
I WANT TO JUMP AROUND FUNLAND!
HUH?
HMM.
I GUESS IT MIGHT TAKE A WHILE
TO LAND.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T HAVE JUMPED
SO HIGH.
OH, STEVEN, HOW DO YOU KEEP
GETTING IN THESE PREDICAMENTS?
HMM?
HEY, IT'S AMETHYST!
SHE COULD HELP ME!
AMETHYST!
HEY, OVER HERE!
YO, STEVEN!
ARE YOU STILL UP?
LAST CHANCE
FOR SOME CAKE!
AH, SHE CAN'T HEAR ME!
I'M TOO FAR AWAY!
[ GRUNTS ]
NO, NO! LOOK UP HERE!
HEY!
WHO'S THE WISEGUY?
SHE SAW ME!
OH,
THERE'S STEVEN,
JUST FLYIN' AROUND.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO, AMETHYST,
COME BACK!
WAIT,
CAN STEVEN FLY?
YEAH,
I THINK I REMEMBER THAT.
NO, NO,
I'M THINKING OF LAPIS!
HEY, STEVEN!
HOW DID YOU LEARN
HOW TO FLY?
AMETHYST!
GO GET HELP!
WHAT?!
UGH,
SHE CAN'T HEAR ME.
HEY, AIR-STEVE!
AMETHYST!
I NEED YOU TO --
DANG, TOO SLOW.
BETTER ASK QUICKER.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I COULD REALLY USE
YOUR ASSISTANCE
DEALING WITH THE SUDDEN
APPEARANCE -- AW, RATS.
...OF A POWER WHICH PREVIOUSLY
WAS UNBEKNOWNST TO ME
WHICH I CAN'T CONTROL --
UMM.
DUDE, SUMMARIZE!
GO GET GARNET!
HMM.
WELL, GARNET?
WHAT ARE
YOU ALL DOING?
STEVEN IS FALLING!
HE NEEDS OUR HELP!
I'LL CATCH YOU,
STEVEN!
I THINK
IT'S GONNA BE A WHILE.
OH, OH, OH!
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
[ CAR ALARM BLARES ]
I FOUND A PHONE.
WHOSE IS IT?
THAT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
[ Ringing ]
HELLO?
Ground control
to Steven Universe.
Steven!
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
SEE?
HE'S GOT THIS.
Not exactly!
I THINK THIS IS SOME KIND
OF NEW POWER!
ROSE COULD REGULATE
THE SPEED OF HER DESCENT.
YEAH, AND SHE COULD CONTROL
HOW FAST SHE FELL.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
STEVEN,
TRY FALLING A LITTLE FASTER.
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT HOW,
AND IT'S TAKING FOREVER
TO REACH THE GROUND.
Can you guys just
keep me company until I land?
♪♪
[ GRUNTS ]
OOH.
♪♪
OH.
[ SIGHS ]
♪♪
IS IT A BROOM?
NO, IT'S A SPEAR!
[ ALARM CLOCK
BLARING IN DISTANCE ]
AMETHYST: Hey, Steven,
why's your alarm going off?
[ GASPS ]
6:55 A.M.
THAT SHOULD GIVE ME
ENOUGH TIME
TO GET TO THE BIG DONUT
RIGHT WHEN IT OPENS AT 7:00.
FRESH!
OH, NUTS!
MY DONUTS!
GUYS,
I NEED TO GET DOWN RIGHT NOW!
WHAT'S THE HURRY,
DUDE?
YOU GOT
NOWHERE TO BE.
HE'S CLEARLY VERY TIRED
FROM BEING UP ALL NIGHT,
AND HE'S EAGER
TO GET SOME SLEEP.
There's no time to explain!
Just help me down!
HOW WE SUPPOSED TO
DO THAT?
MAYBE WE COULD
WEIGH HIM DOWN?
IT'S NOT ENOUGH!
KEEP IT COMING!
OOF!
MORE, MORE!
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS WORKING.
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
NOTHING'S WORKING!
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU CAN PUT ON ME?
JUST THIS
ALARM CLOCK.
♪♪
IT'S PAST 7:00.
THANKS FOR TRYING, GUYS,
BUT THERE'S NO POINT ANYMORE.
SORRY, STEVEN.
IT WASN'T MEANT
TO BE.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ CRASH! ]
IT WAS TOO MEANT TO BE.
[ SIGHS ]
MY FIRST DAY BACK,
AND IT'S ALREADY RUINED.
I WONDER WHO'LL GET MY DONUT
INSTEAD OF ME?
PROBABLY PEEDEE.
HE'LL BE UP FOR HIS MORNING JOG.
MR. SMILEY WILL HAVE
THE SECOND DONUT.
LARS WILL EMBEZZLE ONE.
RONALDO WILL BUY ONE
THAT HE THINKS IS A MUTANT.
ONION'LL BUY ONE
AND TAKE IT FOR GRANTED.
AND THEN MAYOR DEWEY
WILL ORDER A DOZEN,
AND THEN A DOZEN-DOZEN
FOR THE WHOLE TOWN!
AND THEN A DOZEN-DOZEN-DOZEN
FOR ALL THE STARVING CHILDREN
IN THE WORLD!
[ CHEERING ]
BUT NOT FOR STEVEN.
THEY'LL SAY, "WHERE'S STEVEN?
WE SAVED A DONUT FOR HIM."
BUT THEY WON'T SEE ME
BECAUSE I'M IN THE SKY.
AND THEN,
THEY'LL FEED MY DONUT TO A DOG.
AND THEN I'LL DIE.
♪♪
ALAS,
POOR STEVEN!
I KNEW HIM WELL.
NOOOO!
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
I'M FALLING!
OH GEEZ, I'M FALLING.
GUYS!
YEAH, BUT IF HE DID HAVE
A JET PACK,
HE COULD JUST PUT IT ON
UPSIDE DOWN!
UH, THEY STILL CANT HEAR ME!
MY PHONE!
I DROPPED MY PHONE!
WHY DO MY POWERS
JUST KEEP COMING AND GOING?
I WAS JUST SO HAPPY TO BE HOME.
WAIT!
THAT'S IT!
HAPPINESS!
MY FLOATING POWER'S TIED
TO MY EMOTIONS!
[ GROANS ] RIGHT,
JUST LIKE ALL MY STUPID POWERS!
OOH!
OKAY, RIGHT, I CAN CONTROL THIS!
I JUST
HAVE TO THINK HAPPY THOUGHTS
AND NO NEGATIVE THOUGHTS!
SO, WHAT MAKES ME HAPPY?
DONUTS?
NO, I'M NOT GONNA GET ANY.
THE BEACH!
NO,
THAT'S WHERE I'M GOING TO DIE.
[ THUD ]
MOM?
OH GEEZ,
THOSE FEELINGS ARE COMPLICATED.
COME ON, COME ON, BRAIN,
TIME'S RUNNING OUT!
I JUST NEED SOMETHING
THAT MAKES ME HAPPY!
SOMETHING I CAN ALWAYS DEPEND ON
TO CHEER ME UP!
♪♪
MY GUYS!
THEY SPENT ALL NIGHT WITH ME
JUST TO KEEP ME COMPANY.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH I MESS UP,
THEY'LL BE THERE TO HELP ME.
BUT IF HE CAN'T CONTROL
HIS POWER --
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HOW IS IT
ALL RIGHT?
BY NOW, STEVEN HAS REALIZED HIS
POWERS ARE TIED TO HIS EMOTIONS.
JUST LIKE I KNEW WOULD HAPPEN.
HE'S USED THE MEMORIES
OF HAPPY AND SAD THINGS
TO LAND SAFELY BEHIND US,
READY TO GIVE US A HUG.
[ GRUNTS ]
CLOSE ENOUGH.
GUYS!
WAIT!
YOU HAVE
SOMEWHERE ELSE TO BE!
WHAT?
THERE'S NO TIME!
RUN TO THE BIG DONUT!
RUN!
UH, OKAY!
I WOULD'VE LIKED
A HUG.
[ PANTING ]
[ GASPS ]
NO WAY!
NO WAY, NO WAY, NO WAY, NO WAY!
OOH!
OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
UH...
YOU'RE JUST OPENING?
I THOUGHT I WAS LATE!
LATE?
WE ALWAYS OPEN AT 7:30
ON SUNDAYS.
AHH, DUH!
WELL,
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
HERE YOU GO!
MY TREAT!
A FRESH-BAKED FROSTED DONUT
WITH SPRINKLES!
MY FAVORITE!
UGH!
OH.
OH, BOTHER.
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO ♪
♪ I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪
♪♪
LATER, MOM!
AW, YEAH.
THIS IS GONNA BE SICK.
THANKS AGAIN FOR HELPING ME
TAKE ALL THIS STUFF OUT, STEVEN.
NO PROBLEM! I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO BE A ROADIE.
WHETHER THEY'RE LIFTING
THE HEAVIEST EQUIPMENT,
FIGHTING OFF CRAZY FANS,
OR JUST OFFERING MORAL SUPPORT,
ROADIES WORK
BEHIND THE SCENES
TO MAKE ALL MAGIC
ONSTAGE POSSIBLE.
I ONLY REALLY NEED
THE LIFTING,
BUT I GUESS WE'LL SEE
WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT.
WHOA!
MAA!
MA-MA-MA-MA-MA-MA-MA.
NO, I CAN'T BE BACK
BEFORE 10:00.
I'M DOING A SHOW TONIGHT,
YELLOWTAIL.
MA-MA-MA!
MA-MA-MA-MA,
MA-MA-MA-MA-MA-MA!
IT IS TOO
A VIABLE CAREER!
80% OF GERMANS
MAKE THEIR LIVING DEEJAY'ing!
WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST ACCEPT
THAT I DON'T WANT TO BE
A FISHERMAN LIKE YOU?!
UH...
BYE, YELLOWTAIL.
MR-MR-MR.
YOU OKAY,
SOUR CREAM?
YEAH.
I JUST CAN'T DEAL WITH MY
STEPDAD ON MY CASE ALL THE TIME.
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO BRING HOME FISH
WHEN I COULD BRING HOME
SICK BEATS?
IF HE WANTS TO "MUH-MUH-MUH"
SO MUCH ABOUT IT,
HE DOESN'T
HAVE TO COME.
UGH. ALL THAT ARGUING
MESSED UP MY STOMACH.
I'M GONNA GO
USE THE BATHROOM.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
WAIT! DON'T LEAVE!
WAXING IS FREE!
OH.
WHAT'S UP, STU-BALL?
JUST HELPING SOUR CREAM
TAKE HIS GEAR TO THE WAREHOUSE.
OH, LIKE A ROADIE,
HUH?
YEAH!
W-WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WELL,
SAME-OLD, SAME-OLD.
NOT TOO BUSY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE
IT'LL PICK UP SOON.
THANKS, KIDDO.
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ AIR BRAKES HISS ]
WHOA!
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT THING.
STEVEN, DON'T TELL THEM
ABOUT THE FREE WAX.
♪♪
MARTY?
YOU MEAN
YOUR ROTTEN OLD MANAGER?
I'LL PROTECT YOU,
DAD!
EH, DON'T WORRY.
I GOT A HOSE.
SO, [CHUCKLES] THIS IS WHERE
YOU WORK NOW, STARCHILD.
A RUNDOWN OLD CAR WASH?
GUESS THE MUSIC BIZ WASN'T AS
GOOD TO YOU AS IT'S BEEN TO ME.
UH,
HEY, MARTY.
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
THIS IS MY SON,
STEVEN.
WHOA!
GUESS I'LL CALL YOU
STARCHILD JUNIOR.
[ LAUGHING ]
UGH.
ANYWAY, UH, THINGS ARE TOTALLY
FINE HERE IN OLD BEACH CITY,
BUT, UH, IF YOU NEED ME
TO WASH THAT HUGE BUS OF YOURS,
IT'D PROBABLY HELP ME OUT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
LISTEN, STARCHILD, I CAN DO YOU
ONE BETTER THAN A CAR WASH.
YOU AND I HAVE
SOME UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
EH, SORRY,
MR. U.
I TOTALLY
CLOGGED UP YOUR TOI--
WHOA! DAD?
SOUR CREAM?
W-WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
UH...[ CHUCKLES ]
S.C.
OOF!
JUST LOOK AT YOU.
WHEN DID
YOU GET SO TALL?
UH,
LIKE NINE YEARS AGO.
WHOA! [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY,
CLEARS THROAT ]
SORRY I'VE BEEN GONE
SO LONG,
BUT YOU KNOW HOW THE MUSIC BIZ
CAN BE, R-I-I-IGHT?
NO.
CAN YOU
TELL ME ABOUT IT?
WELL, YOU SEE,
THE MUSIC INDUSTRY
IS LIKE A BIG BEEHIVE
OR FACTORY WHERE...
MAN...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE RELATED.
YOU DON'T SEE
THE RESEMBLANCE?
MM...
ALSO,
IN THE BIZ,
THEY MAKE IT REALLY HARD
TO HAVE ANY FREE TIME AT ALL.
YOU GOT
TO WORK LONG HOURS...
KIND OF.
...EVERY DAY
AND ON WEEKENDS.
HEY,
SOUR CREAM.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
BUT SHOULD I HAUL YOUR EQUIPMENT
OVER TO THE WAREHOUSE WHILE
YOU CATCH UP WITH YOUR DAD?
WHAT'S THIS
ABOUT EQUIPMENT?
HELLO!
WHAT DO YOU GOT GOING ON
OVER HERE, MY FRIEND?
JUST GETTING READY TO SET UP FOR
THIS SEMI-ANNUAL DEEJAY NIGHT
RAVE THING
I DO IN BEACH CITY.
A RAVE, YOU SAY?
HMM...
S.C.,
I HAVE A GREAT IDEA.
I'VE DECIDED TO HANG OUT
IN BEACH CITY AND, UM...
MAKE UP
FOR LOST TIME WITH YOU.
AND WHILE WE'RE...
CHILLIN',
I'LL PROMOTE
YOUR LITTLE ENGAGEMENT.
WHAT'S THIS SHINY CARD
WITH YOUR CONTACT INFO ON IT?
JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
WE PRO MUSIC TYPES CALL
A LAMINATED
BUSINESS CARD.
THAT IS SO LEGIT!
MAN, YOU'RE SO LUCKY
YOUR DAD IS IN THE BIZ.
THROWING A COOL
SEMI-ANNUAL DEEJAY RAVE THING
IS A CLASSIC
FATHER-SON BONDING EXPERIENCE.
MORE CLASSIC
THAN FISHING?
JUST WAIT!
WE'RE GONNA CRAM
NINE YEARS OF BONDING
INTO ONE
SPECTACULAR EVENT!
THIS IS IT?
IT'S SO...PUNY.
I MEAN,
WHAT IS THIS?
A CONCERT FOR ANTS?
WE COULD INVITE
SOME ANTS.
AUNTS, UNCLES --
MUSIC IS FOR EVERYBODY.
LISTEN, BUDDY,
YOU WANT TO REACH PEOPLE, RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO HOLD THEM
IN YOUR LITTLE HAND, RIGHT?
UH,
I GUESS SO.
YOU WANT TO SQUEEZE THEM
UNTIL THEIR EYES POP OUT!
UH,
YOU LOST ME A LITTLE.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
IF YOU WANT TO BRING PEOPLE IN,
YOU CAN'T PLAY
OUT IN THE STICKS!
YOU GOT TO BE
WHERE THE PEOPLE ARE!
NOW THIS
IS MORE LIKE IT!
WE'LL SET UP RIGHT HERE
IN THE SAND.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
AS SOUR CREAM'S ROADIE,
I HAVE TO VOICE MY CONCERN.
YOU THREW A SHOW HERE
ON THE BEACH FOR MY DAD,
AND JUDGING FROM WHAT HE SAID,
YOU DIDN'T DO A GOOD JOB AT ALL.
OKAY. CAN I REAL TALK WITH YOU
FOR A SECOND? REAL TALK.
I MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES BEFORE,
WHEN I WAS YOUR DAD'S MANAGER,
AND -- REAL TALK? --
I WAS A JERK.
BUT -- REAL TALK --
I'VE LEARNED A LOT ABOUT MYSELF
AND THE MUSIC BUSINESS
SINCE THEN.
SO I CAN TELL YOU,
WITH CERTAINTY,
THINGS AREN'T GONNA BE
LIKE THEY WERE LAST TIME.
REAL TALK.
WOW.
YELLOWTAIL NEVER REAL TALKS
WITH ME.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S LIKE TO WORK
WITH A PROFESSIONAL, KID.
NOW, HOLD ON.
I'M GONNA WORK SOME MAGIC.
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
MARTY HERE.
TALK TO ME.
YEAH,
I KNOW I CALLED YOU...
OKAY. YOU READY?
BOOM!
Sour Cream: WOW!
AM I...GLOWING?
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOTHING LESS FOR MY TALENTED,
SOON-TO-BE-FAMOUS DEEJAY.
CHECK THIS OUT,
BROSKI.
WOW.
I'VE ONLY SEEN GEAR THIS GOOD
ON THE INTERNET.
IS THIS FOR ME?
IT'S FOR US,
MY MAIN COOL CAT!
WOW.
I CAN TOTALLY RAVE
TO THIS.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ALL SET
ON ROADIES, HUH?
GUESS I'LL JUST
CARRY MYSELF HOME.
HEY, STARCHILD JR.,
CATCH!
YOU'RE IN THE BIG LEAGUES NOW,
LITTLE ROADIE.
[ GASPS, LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
GEEZ!
WHAT DOES GREG FEED
THAT KID?
UH...
HEY,
LET ME RAP WITH YOU
ABOUT THE SETUP
I HAVE ENVISIONED, OKAY?
OKAY!
SO, THE STAGE IS GONNA BE HUGE,
AND THE SPEAKERS EVEN HUGER.
[ HUMMING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
♪♪
[ SEAGULL SQUAWKING ]
HMM?
♪♪
[ DANCE MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
Man:
STEVEN UNIVERSE!
DON'T MIND ME,
FOLKS!
JUST A HUMBLE ROADIE
DOING A MIKE CHECK.
THIS MIKE LOOKS GREAT!
HEY, SOUR CREAM, WE'RE READY
TO GO WHENEVER YOU ARE.
OKAY, I GUESS I'LL GO OUT
AND GET STARTED.
THAT'S NOT HOW WE DO THINGS
IN THE MUSIC BIZ.
LET A PROPER HYPE MAN
SET THE STAGE FOR YOU.
WHOA. I'VE NEVER BEEN
PROPERLY HYPED BEFORE.
THANKS, DAD!
[ CLICKS TONGUE ]
[ ALL CHEERING ]
IT'S SOME GUY!
HOW'S IT GO--
IS THIS MIKE EVEN ON?
[ FEEDBACK ]
HOW YOU FEELING, BEACH CI-TAY!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
YOU KNOW, I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
SOMEONE WITH GOOD TASTE,
SO YOU GOT TO BELIEVE ME.
THIS SHOW IS SPECIAL TO ME.
IT'S PERSONAL.
BECAUSE I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO A FRESH, RAW EXPERIENCE,
TO A WHOLE NEW FLAVOR,
TO A BRAND-NEW...
SODA!
WHAT?
GUACOL-A-A-A!
[ AUDIENCE MURMURING ]
THAT'S RIGHT.
GUACOLA!
THE WORLD'S FIRST
GUACAMOLE SODA.
EACH CAN COMES WITH THE POWER
OF THREE WHOLE AVOCADOS!
NOW, COME ON, BEACH CITY.
ARE YOU READY TO GUAC?
[ GRUNTS ]
OOF! UGH!
UGH!
THIS IS TERRIBLE! WHAT THE --
FROM CONCENTRATE?
[ AUDIENCE GROANING ]
AWW,
THAT'S NASTY.
[ GROANING ]
UGH!
IT'S NOT EVEN GOOD ON CHIPS!
♪♪
DAD!
STEVEN, IS THIS GROSS-OUT DRINK
PART OF SOUR CREAM'S SHOW?
NO WAY,
DAD!
IT'S ALL MARTY!
MRR-MRR?!
MA-MA-MA-MA-MA!
MA-MA-MA-MA!
YELLOWTAIL, WAIT!
SOUR CREAM NEEDS YOU!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
START PLAYING.
DAD,
YOU'RE RUINING MY SHOW!
THIS ISN'T
YOUR SHOW.
HOW DO YOU THINK
WE HAVE THIS SETUP --
THIS PARTY BUS,
THESE ROADIES?
I'VE GOT A GOOD DEAL
WITH GUACOLA.
YOU'RE LUCKY I'M LETTING YOU IN
ON THE GROUND FLOOR.
BUT I THOUGHT THIS WAS ABOUT
MAKING UP FOR LOST TIME,
NOT SOME LAME SODA.
LOOK, KID, I NEED
THIS GUACOLA DEAL, OKAY?
DON'T BE SELFISH!
MUH!
MUH-MUH-MUH!
MUH-MUH-MUH-MUH-MUH!
MUH MUH!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
MUH...UGH.
I SAID I DON'T NEED YOU OR
GUACOLA TO DO WHAT I WANT TO DO!
I NEVER HAVE!
I CAN DO THIS SHOW
ON MY OWN!
FINE.
[ FEEDBACK ]
HEY, UNIVERSE,
I ONLY CAME HERE
BECAUSE I'M LEGALLY OBLIGATED
TO GIVE YOU THIS.
HUH?
DON'T SAY
I NEVER GAVE YOU NOTHIN'.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
WELL,
I GUESS THAT'S IT.
SO MUCH FOR ME
AND THE MUSIC BIZ.
I'M SORRY,
SOUR CREAM.
[ HORN HONKING ]
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
MA MA-MA-MA-MA!
AW, MAN!
IT'S MY STEPDAD.
HE WAS JUST WAITING FOR ME
TO FAIL
SO HE COULD GET ME
AND PUT ME TO WORK ON HIS BOAT.
FINE.
TAKE ME TO YOUR BIG SMELLY BOAT
SO I CAN FISH MY LIFE AWAY!
MA-MA-MA MA-MA-MA MA-MA-MA.
IT'S...MY OLD GEAR?
MA-MA
MA-MA-MA-MA-MA MA!
WHAT?
YOU WANT ME TO PLAY?
MA-MA-MA,
MA-MA-MA.
GEE...UH...
THANKS, YELLOW DAD.
MA-MA-MA!
[ LAUGHS ]
GOOD ONE,
DAD!
HEY, STEVEN, SINCE YOU'RE STILL
MY OFFICIAL ROADIE,
HELP ME SET UP.
YEAH!
LET'S KICK IT!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
YOU KNOW, THE MUSIC BIZ
CAN BE REALLY TRICKY.
I'M SURE SOUR CREAM
WILL MAKE IT BIG ON HIS OWN.
EVEN IF HE DOESN'T MAKE IT BIG,
SOUR CREAM'LL BE OKAY,
AS LONG AS HE'S DOING SOMETHING
THAT MAKES HIM HAPPY.
EH, YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE MONE--
EEEEEEEE!
DAD? [ GASPS ]
$10 MILLION?!
YOU'RE RICH!
♪ LOOK AT YOU GO ♪
♪ I JUST ADORE YOU ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I KNEW ♪
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SO SPECIAL ♪