♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
Garnet: WE NEED
TO TRACK DOWN PERIDOT.
WE FOUND HER POD.
WE KNOW
SHE'S OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
SHE CAME TO EARTH
WITH A JOB TO DO,
AND ODDS ARE
SHE'S STILL GONNA TRY TO DO IT.
THAT'S WHY
I'VE GATHERED YOU HERE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS SO YOU COULD
HELP ME FOLD ALL THIS LAUNDRY.
MM, THAT TOO.
THE CHORE WHEEL IDEA YOU HAD
FELL APART FAST.
WASN'T ME.
I JUST REALLY ENJOY
DOING ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
IT'S BETTER
IF WE DO THEM TOGETHER.
HUMANS SHOULD JUST
STOP WEARING CLOTHES.
IT'D BE
A LOT FUNNIER.
HEY!
I'M A CIVILIFIED PART-HUMAN,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
CLOTHING IS A MUST.
HMM.
THIS IS A LOT.
I BET THIS FOLDING
WOULD GO FASTER
IF RUBY AND SAPPHIRE
WERE HERE.
I'M SURE THEY'D BE GLAD
TO SEE YOU, STEVEN,
BUT I AM NOT UNFUSING
FOR LAUNDRY.
AW.
GARNET,
YOU DON'T THINK
PERIDOT WOULD COME LOOKING
FOR US, DO YOU?
WE WEREN'T HER PRIORITY.
SHE WAS SENT HERE TO DO
SOMETHING IN THE KINDERGARTEN.
DO YOU THINK SHE'S STILL
GOING TO TRY TO REACTIVATE IT?
MM.
IF SHE GETS IT UP AND RUNNING,
THE INJECTORS WILL TURN BACK ON.
IN...JECTORS?
W-WHAT ARE THOSE?
YOU'VE ALREADY
SEEN THEM.
WELL, YOU'VE SEEN THEM
DISABLED.
IF PERIDOT
REACTIVATES THEM,
THEY'LL PICK RIGHT UP
WHERE THEY LEFT OFF --
PLANTING GEMS
IN THE CRUST OF THE EARTH,
WHERE THEY'LL INCUBATE
AND SUCK THE LIFE
RIGHT OUT OF THE GROUND.
WE CAN'T LET PERIDOT
RESTART GEM PRODUCTION HERE.
IF WE DO, THE ENTIRE PLANET
WILL BECOME...
JANKED.
GARNET! [ LAUGHS ]
THAT MOUTH!
[ LAUGHS ]
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL STOP HER.
COME ON, CRYSTAL GEMS.
COMING.
UGH. AS LONG AS WE DON'T
HAVE TO FOLD ANYTHING.
STEVEN.
COME ON.
THAT MEANS YOU, TOO, RIGHT?
[ GASPS ]
[ PANTING ]
YOU'RE A CIVILIFIED PART-GEM,
TOO, AFTER ALL.
GARNET, ARE YOU SURE
WE SHOULD BRING STEVEN?
THIS MIGHT BE DANGEROUS.
PERIDOT'S GOT NOTHING
WE CAN'T HANDLE.
Pearl:
WELL, NOTHING LOOKS ACTIVATED.
IN FACT, IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
ANYTHING'S BUDGED
SINCE THE LAST TIME
WE WERE HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT JUST BECAUSE
PERIDOT HASN'T BEEN HERE YET
DOESN'T MEAN
SHE WON'T COME.
HM.
LET'S DO A THOROUGH CHECK
OF THE PERIMETER.
MM-HMM.
THAT WAY, WE CAN MONITOR
ANY FUTURE ENTRY.
HM.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
MM, MMM, MM,
MMM, MM, MMM,
MM, MMM, MM, MMM, MM, MMM,
MM, MMM, MM...
LOG DATE 652.
THIS IS PERIDOT.
UPDATING STATUS --
STILL STUCK ON MISERABLE PLANET.
THE FUSION EXPERIMENTS
ARE DEVELOPING PROPERLY.
A FEW HAVE EVEN EMERGED
EARLY --
EUGGGH! HUH!
Are the other ones
with you?
OF COURSE. WHY NOT?
Garnet: PERIDOT!
THERE SHE IS!
[ GASPS ] AAH!
THERE'S NOWHERE TO GO!
YOU'RE CORNERED!
HEY!
I CAN'T DO THAT!
NEITHER CAN SHE!
[ GRUNTS ]
HA! MISSED!
HUH?
AAAH!
[ GROANS ]
AAAAH!
DO YOU THINK
SHE'S HURT?!
UGH!
[ CHUCKLES ] NOPE.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOOOOOA!
HOT WHIP!
[ SNARLS ]
YOU CRYSTAL CLODS!
GO AHEAD! WRECK THIS PLACE!
SEE IF I CARE.
I ALREADY GOT WHAT I NEEDED.
GET BACK HERE!
[ PANTING ]
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
I'M GONNA BOP HER
GOOD!
I'LL HELP!
HURRY, GARNET!
[ PANTING ]
IF PERIDOT'S MISSION WAS
TO REACTIVATE THE KINDERGARTEN,
THE INJECTORS
WOULD BE ON.
LOOK.
THEY'RE NOT.
OH.
LET'S SEE WHAT SHE WAS
ACTUALLY DOING.
[ METAL SCRAPING ]
DOWN HERE.
OH.
OH!
YOU'RE BRAINS AND BRAWN --
THE WHOLE PACKAGE.
THANK YOU.
AH.
IS IT 'CAUSE
YOU'RE A FUSION?
I HAVE TO KEEP
SOME OF MY SECRETS.
AW, PLEASE?
I WANT TO KNOW!
[ CHUCKLES ]
IS THE STRONG PART OF YOU
RUBY
AND THE WISE PART OF YOU
SAPPHIRE?
IT'S ALL OF BOTH.
WHEN TWO GEMS COMBINE,
IT CREATES SOMETHING GREATER
THAN THE SUM OF THEIR PARTS.
THAT'S WHY I'M SO GREAT.
WHAT'S IT LIKE
TO STAY FUSED ALL THE --
WHOA.
I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT THIS PLACE IS EVEN CREEPIER
THAN THE LAST TIME
WE WERE HERE.
YES. THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON.
THE POWER'S NOT ON.
WHAT WAS PERIDOT DOING?
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE PULLED THESE
OUT OF THE WALLS.
SOMETHING'S STRANGE.
[ RUSTLING ]
GARNET?
[ RUSTLING CONTINUES ]
[ RUMBLING ]
IS THERE...
SOMETHING IN THERE?
[ RUMBLING CONTINUES ]
AAH!
WHOA!
WHAT ARE THEY?
AAAH!
WHAT IS IT?
IT LOOKS LIKE TWO GEM SHARDS
STUCK TOGETHER.
UGH!
IS THAT
WHAT ALL THESE THINGS ARE?
GEMS...STUCK TOGETHER?
AAH!
GARNET?
WHAT WAS THAT?
AAH!
[ SCREECHING ]
[ PANTING ]
MNH-MNH.
GARNET?
UH...GARNET!
WHAT DO WE DO?!
AAH!
PLEASE!
TALK TO ME!
UNH!
[ GRUNTING ]
THESE WERE CRYSTAL GEMS
SHATTERED INTO PIECES.
THEY WERE BURIED TOGETHER.
WHY AREN'T YOU MOVING?!
THEY WERE FORCED TOGETHER.
THEY WERE FORCED
TO FUSE.
THIS IS WRONG.
I-I-I'M SORRY.
[ GROANING ]
NO! NO, GARNET!
YOU'RE COMING UNDONE!
GARNET!
[ GRUNTS ]
PLEASE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU!
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WE DID IT!
GARNET?
SO, THIS IS
WHAT HOMEWORLD THINKS OF FUSION.
WE COULDN'T HAVE KNOWN
THEY WOULD DO THIS.
THIS IS WHERE THEY'VE BEEN --
ALL THE ONES WE COULDN'T FIND.
THEY'VE BEEN HERE
THE WHOLE TIME!
ROSE COULDN'T HAVE KNOWN.
THIS WAS PUNISHMENT
FOR THE REBELLION!
[ Voice breaking ]
IT'S NOT OUR FAULT!
GARNET!
S-STEVEN.
Amethyst: YO.
WE'RE BACK.
GARNET,
WE LOST PERIDOT.
HER FINGERS
WERE TOO FAST FOR US.
UM...
WHAT ARE THESE THINGS?
PUT THEM DOWN!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
WE NEED TO POOF AND BUBBLE
ALL OF THEM.
WE CAN'T LET
ANY ESCAPE.
[ CLANK ]
OH. HEY, GARNET.
HOW'S IT GOING?
STILL DAMP.
OH.
RIGHT -- THE CLOTHES.
THERE ARE TOWELS
IN THERE.
DO WE EVEN HAVE PLUMBING
UP HERE?
HOW DO YOU GET
THE WASHER AND DRYER TO WORK?
MAGIC.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ARE YOU...ALL RIGHT?
I WISH
YOU HADN'T SEEN THAT.
AW, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
W-WHY?
WHAT HOMEWORLD DID --
TAKING THE SHATTERED PARTS
OF FALLEN GEMS
AND COMBINING THEM.
THOSE GEMS
WEREN'T ASKED PERMISSION.
FUSION IS A CHOICE.
THOSE GEMS
WEREN'T GIVEN A CHOICE.
IT ISN'T RIGHT!
IT ISN'T FUSION!
[ BUZZER ]
WHAT'S IT LIKE,
BEING A FUSION?
YOU'VE FUSED.
I MEAN, LIKE,
ALL THE TIME.
DO YOU FORGET
WHO YOU USED TO BE?
YOU FORGET
YOU WERE EVER ALONE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU FUSE,
YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE TWO PEOPLE.
YOU FEEL LIKE ONE BEING.
AND YOUR OLD NAMES
MIGHT AS WELL BE NAMES
FOR YOUR LEFT ARM
AND YOUR RIGHT.
WHEN YOU SPLIT UP,
IS IT LIKE YOU DISAPPEAR?
I EMBODY MY --
I MEAN,
RUBY AND SAPPHIRE'S LOVE.
I'LL ALWAYS EXIST IN THEM,
EVEN IF I SPLIT APART.
BUT THE STRENGTH OF THAT LOVE
KEEPS ME TOGETHER,
SO I CAN STAY GARNET
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE SO GREAT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GIGGLES ]
[ WIND GUSTS ]
[ GASPS ] OH, NO!
DON'T WANT
TO BREAK UP A PAIR.
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
THEY BELONG TOGETHER.
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
HERE'S ALL
THE ORANGE MAGIC ORCHESTRA ONES.
GREAT, PUT THEM IN THE
TRANSCENDENTAL SPACE ROCK PILE.
AT HOME, WE ONLY HAVE
CLASSICAL MUSIC
AND MOVIE SOUNDTRACKS.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
ANY OF THESE.
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD
THE PHILOSOPHY MAJORS?
OH, MAN.
GIVE IT HERE.
THIS WILL REALLY
KNOCK YOUR SOCKS OFF.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
COME ON.
WHOA! [ LAUGHS ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ NEEDLE SCRATCHES ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
AAH!
YOU TWO CAN FUSE?!
UH...YES?
UH, UH, UH,
THAT'S IN-- INCREDIBLE!
SINCE WHEN? WAIT,
HOW IS THIS EVEN POSSIBLE?
THE GEMS THINK
IT'S 'CAUSE I'M HALF-HUMAN.
PLEASE DON'T TELL MY PARENTS,
MR. UNIVERSE.
THEY DON'T KNOW I'VE BEEN
DOING MAGIC STUFF WITH STEVEN.
I CAN'T TELL THEM. THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO UNDERSTAND -- I --
WHOA, WHOA,
IT -- IT'S OKAY.
I MAY BE THE ONLY HUMAN BEING
ON THE PLANET
WHO'S GONNA UNDERSTAND.
W-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YEAH,
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL...
[ GASPS ] STORY!
COME ON.
[ THUD ]
WE'RE READY.
I DIDN'T THINK I'D BE
TELLING YOU THIS SO SOON.
PROBABLY BEST
TO START WITH THIS.
EVERYBODY READY?
1, 2, 3, 4...
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
♪ WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU? ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO THAT ♪
♪ NO ONE ELSE CAN DO? ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU? ♪
♪ HUMAN MAN ♪
♪ YOU ARE SO MUCH FUN ♪
♪ I HADN'T PLANNED ON FINDING
YOU QUITE THIS ENTERTAINING ♪
♪ I LIKE YOUR BAND ♪
WHOO!
♪ AND I LIKE YOUR SONG ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY
HUMAN BEINGS PLAY ♪
♪ I LIKE PLAYING ALONG ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH,
WHOA-HO ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU? ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO THAT ♪
♪ NO ONE ELSE CAN DO? ♪
♪ WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU? ♪
[ GUITAR SOLO ]
[ GASPS, GIGGLES ]
TSK.
[ FEEDBACK ]
[ THUD ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I GOT THAT ON VIDEO!
WHAT ON EARTH
WAS THAT?!
THAT WAS
RAINBOW QUARTZ.
PEARL THOUGHT A FUSION
MIGHT GIVE YOUR VIDEO
A LITTLE SOMETHING EXTRA.
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
I HAVE TO GO, BUT ARE YOU
DOING ANYTHING LATER?
YOU KNOW I'M NOT.
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU'RE ADORABLE,
MR. UNIVERSE.
SEE YOU LATER.
BYE.
HEY, I HIT THE DRUMS,
SO PAY UP.
HERE YOU GO.
[ CHOMPING ]
YOU'RE JUST A PHASE.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
[ SIGHS ] NO.
I ACTUALLY DON'T KNOW THAT,
PEARL.
[ CHUCKLING ]
WELL, OF COURSE YOU DON'T.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ROSE.
I KNOW
SHE'S SUPER INTO ME.
LISTEN
MR. UNIVERSE.
ROSE MAY FIND YOU
CHARMING,
BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
YOU'RE HUMAN.
YOU'RE A NOVELTY
AT BEST.
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE?
OH [CHUCKLES]
IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
[ CHOMPING ]
HUMANS CAN'T FUSE.
FUSION IS THE ULTIMATE
CONNECTION BETWEEN GEMS.
AND YOU
ARE NOT A GEM.
WELL, HAS ANY HUMAN
EVER TRIED FUSING WITH A GEM?
UH, NO,
I-I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL,
THEN, I WILL TRY!
[ CLANK ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GROANS ]
AW, GEEZ,
WHAT AM I DOING?
THESE THINGS
ARE EXPENSIVE.
[ GUITAR SOLO ]
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
OH, GEEZ! HOW DID
SHE GET HER LEGS TO DO THAT?
[ GROANS ]
HEY. ARE YOU DEAD?
WHAT? OH, NO NO.
I'M ALIVE.
WHOA, COOL!
AAH.
IT'S US FROM BEFORE.
YEAH,
I WAS JUST TRYING TO
GET MY HEAD AROUND
THIS FUSION DANCE.
A FUSION DANCE
AIN'T ABOUT YOUR HEAD!
[ LAUGHS ]
WAIT,
YOU GUYS ARE GEMS.
YOU'VE GOT TO
HELP ME OUT HERE.
I NEED TO BE ABLE TO
FUSE WITH ROSE.
FIRST, YOU NEED THE GEM
AT THE CORE OF YOUR BEING.
THEN YOU NEED THE BODY
THAT COULD TURN INTO LIGHT.
THEN YOU NEED THE PARTNER
WHO YOU TRUST WITH THAT LIGHT.
METAPHORICALLY?
LITERALLY.
SHH. COME ON. I STILL
WANT TO SEE HIM TRY.
UGH, SO IT'S TRUE.
I REALLY CAN'T DO IT.
I'M KIDDING MYSELF
WITH THIS.
I'M NEVER GONNA
BE A GEM.
AMETHYST,
GIVE US SOME PRIVACY!
YEAH!
[ PANTING ]
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
MR. UNIVERSE.
I THINK
YOU CAN DO IT.
BUT IT WON'T WORK
IF YOU DANCE LIKE PEARL.
YOU HAVE TO DANCE
LIKE YOU.
YOU HAVE TO
FUSE YOUR WAY.
GET OPEN.
GET HONEST.
INVENT YOURSELVES TOGETHER.
THAT'S FUSION.
I...
THINK I GET IT.
[ SLOW-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
WE -- WE DIDN'T FUSE.
WHAT?!
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU CAN'T FUSE.
YOU'RE A HUMAN.
I KNOW!
THAT'S THE PROBLEM!
I'M JUST A HUMAN.
THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
I LOVE HUMANS.
YOU'RE ALL SO FUNNY.
UGH.
LOOK, THESE LAST FEW MONTHS
HAVE BEEN GREAT.
OH, YES.
BUT I'M GETTING A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT THE FUTURE.
OH,
JUST ASK GARNET.
I'M STARTING TO WONDER
IF YOU...RESPECT ME?
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, YOU'RE HILARIOUS,
MR. UNIVERSE.
ROSE, PLEASE.
CAN YOU JUST...
TALK TO ME FOR ONE SECOND
LIKE A REAL PERSON?!
I'M NOT A REAL PERSON.
I THOUGHT --
HAVEN'T WE --
IS THIS
NOT HOW IT WORKS?
OH.
OH, BOY.
THIS IS SO WEIRD.
YOU REALLY ARE AN ALIEN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
[ SOBS ]
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
HOW ARE WE GONNA
MAKE THIS WORK?
FUSION?
NO, US.
WE'RE REALLY,
REALLY DIFFERENT.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
LET'S JUST...TALK.
I BARELY KNOW YOU.
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
WE REALLY
RUSHED INTO THIS.
EVERYTHING ON EARTH
SEEMS FAST TO ME.
DO YOU MISS
YOUR HOME PLANET?
NO. NEVER.
HOW DID YOU END UP WITH, UH,
HARPO, GROUCHO, AND CHICO?
HUH? OH, THEM.
THOSE ARE THREE
LONG STORIES.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
SHH!
HAVE YOU LOVED
OTHER HUMANS?
HAVE YOU?
YES.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
IN LOVE WITH A HUMAN?
HOW WOULD I KNOW?
IT'S TORTURE.
GREG.
ROSE.
IS THIS TORTURE?
THE WORST.
I'M SO SORRY.
HUH?
NO. DON'T BE.
WHAT?!
WHY NOT?!
OH, I'M SO CONFUSED!
[ LAUGHING ]
ME, TOO.
WELL, UH,
THIS IS GOOD.
WE'VE GOT
ONE THING IN COMMON.
HA!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
OHH!
WHY ARE THEY
STILL DANCING?
I-I-IT DIDN'T WORK.
Garnet: YES, IT DID.
WHAT?!
IT WORKED.
I THINK THIS ONE'S
MY FAVORITE.
I THINK
HE'S HER FAVORITE, TOO.
WHOA.
SO, YOU GUYS WERE NEVER
ABLE TO FUSE?
UH, NO.
BUT THAT WASN'T AS IMPORTANT
AS TALKING TO EACH OTHER.
LOOK, HUMANS AND GEMS --
IT'S STILL
SOME PRETTY NEW TERRITORY.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
WORK IT OUT TOGETHER.
AND, CONNIE,
IF YOU EVER NEED TO TALK
TO ANOTHER HUMAN BEING
ABOUT THIS,
YOU CAN ALWAYS
TALK TO ME.
MM.
HUMAN BEINGS?
HUMAN BEINGS.
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪