♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven:
♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE CAN'T ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S FINALLY MY BIRTHDAY!
YOU'RE SURE IT'S OKAY WE'RE
TAKING A BREAK FROM THE DRILL?
PERIDOT WILL KEEP US
ON SCHEDULE.
YO, PERI, YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT TO GET IN ON THIS?
[ POP! ]
[ GOGGLES CLINK ]
WE SHOULD CELEBRATE
OUR PROGRESS.
YOUR PROGRESS.
YOU'VE GROWN A LOT THIS YEAR.
-HE CERTAINLY HAS.
YEAH.
YEAH, I GUESS SO!
[ HORN HONKS ]
-STEVEN!
-CONNIE!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
THANKS!
WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
MAY I OFFER YOU
A REFRESHMENT?
OH, STEVEN, HOW GENTILE.
Together: CLINK!
SO, THIS IS THE BARN.
I'M SURPRISED
YOUR PARENTS
ARE LETTING YOU STAY
FOR THE WEEKEND.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT WASN'T EASY.
THEY ONLY LET ME COME
AFTER EQUIPPING ME
WITH EVERY PIECE
OF SAFETY GEAR ON THE PLANET.
WHAT SHOULD I DO
WITH THIS DEFIBRILLATOR?
UM, WE CAN JUST LEAVE IT
IN THE CAR FOR NOW.
[ GIGGLES ]
WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU COULD MAKE IT.
-ME TOO.
-ALL RIGHT, MOVE IT, CONNIE!
I WAS HIS BEST FRIEND FIRST.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
OKAY, SHTUBALL.
LET ME GET A LOOK AT YOU.
-DAD!
SORRY, I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
MY LITTLE BOY'S
GROWING UP SO QUICKLY.
SEEMS LIKE JUST YESTERDAY
YOU WERE A BABY,
AND NOW YOU'RE TURNING
14 YEARS OLD.
[ PBHT! ]
STEVEN, YOU'RE 14?!
YEAH?
BUT I'M ONLY 12 3/4!
YOU'RE OLDER THAN ME?
I-I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
WELL, SURE.
CHECK IT OUT.
LET'S SEE --
WE HAVE INFANT, BABY.
TODDLER -- WHAT'S IT CALLED --
ADOLESCENT.
ADOLESCENT, ADOLESCENT,
WHOA, LOOKS LIKE YOU STAGNATED
THERE A LITTLE BIT, BUDDY.
MR. UNIVERSE, COULD I SHOW YOU
HOW THE DEFIBRILLATOR WORKS?
OH, UH, SURE.
BE RIGHT BACK, KIDDO.
SO, HE'S NOT
GOING TO GROW UP?
WELL,
IT'S HARD TO SAY.
HE'S A GEM, AND GEMS
DON'T REALLY GROW UP.
I MEAN, I'VE KNOWN
THE GEMS SINCE I WAS 22,
AND THEY NEVER CHANGE.
THEY JUST ARE
WHAT THEY ARE.
BUT STEVEN'S NOT LIKE THE OTHER
GEMS -- HE'S HALF HUMAN.
SO I'M NOT REALLY SURE
HOW HE'S GONNA AGE.
WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
YES, RIGHT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
HUMAN BEINGS?
HUMAN BEINGS.
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY, BIRTHDAY MAN,
WHATCHA DOIN'?
I WANT TO HANG UP
THIS BANNER, SO --
DUDE, IT'D BE EASIER
IF YOU JUST STRETCH ON UP HERE.
HA!
HOW'S THAT?
OH, YEAH.
COME ON,
WHAT'S THE VERDICT?
I CAN'T HOLD THIS
FOREVER.
-UH, LOOKS GREAT.
-THERE'S MY B-DAY GUY!
UH, WHAT'S UP, DAD?
WE'RE ALMOST READY
TO START.
GOT YOUR BIRTHDAY CAPE
AND CROWN READY, TOO.
HERE, PUT 'EM ON AND GO WAIT
IN THE BARN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY, NOW SIT TIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS.
♪♪
OKAY, STEVEN,
OPEN UP!
Together: SURPRI--
[ ALL GASP ]
-WOW.
-OH, MY.
HUH?
HM, HM, HM.
STEVEN,
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
HUH.
YOU LOOK GOOD, STEVEN.
[Deep voice]
OH [CHUCKLES] THANKS, GARNET.
DUDE, YOUR NECK!
OH, UH, WHAT ABOUT IT?
YOU HAVE ONE!
SO...YOU JUST GREW
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
I HAD A MAGICAL GROWTH SPURT
JUST NOW.
COOL, RIGHT?
-OH, RIGHT.
IT'S TOTALLY COOL!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S GET THIS PARTY STARTED.
[ BLOWS ]
YEAH!
LET'S EAT
THIS COOKIE CAKE!
HERE, STEVEN.
WOW, THANKS.
OH, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO UNTIE THAT.
IT'S JUST A BOX MADE
TO LOOK
LIKE I SPENT A LOT
OF TIME WRAPPING IT.
[ LAUGHS ]
OHHH, A NEW SHIRT!
WHAT A PRETTY COLOR.
-TRY IT ON.
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, I GUESS
IT DOESN'T FIT SINCE...
NO, DON'T WORRY --
IT FITS FINE JUST LIKE THIS.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
-HERE IT COMES!
I GOT IT, PEARL!
[ GRUNTS ]
Pearl: NICE, CONNIE.
YE-AH!
IF YOU HIT IT,
YOU GET IT.
NO WORRIES.
I'LL GRAB IT!
HUP!
HM...
CONNIE, LET ME.
HM!
OH, COOL.
THANKS, STEVEN.
HM!
NO PROBLEM, CONNIE.
Amethyst: YO, BRING BACK
THAT SHUTTLECOCK!
HUH?
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHEW!
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ]
UGH!
THIS ONE GOES OUT
TO THE BIRTHDAY BOY,
AND HIS BEST FRIEND.
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ BOTH GIGGLE ]
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE ALL THIS
TIME YOU WERE OLDER THAN ME.
YOU SHOULD SNEAK ME
INTO A PG-13 MOVIE SOMETIME.
OH, YEAH.
HEH...HEH, HEH...
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WOULD NEVER ASK YOU
TO BREAK THE LAW.
IT'S FUNNY THAT I HAVE TO LOOK
UP AT YOU NOW, THOUGH.
FUNNY GOOD
OR F-FUNNY BAD?
FUNNY GOOD.
AW,
STEVEN'S HAVING FUN.
WE KNOW HOW
TO THROW A PARTY.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
EXCUSE ME FOR A MOMENT, CONNIE.
I'M GONNA GO...
FRESHEN UP.
BE RIGHT BACK.
[ PANTING ]
[ WARBLING ]
[ Normal voice ]
OH, GEEZ!
IF I CAN JUST KEEP THIS UP
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
NO ONE WILL SUSPECT A TH--
[ PIÑATA CREAKING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHA-- WHA-- WELL, WHAT ARE...
[Deep voice] YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO YOUR BODY?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, HAVE YOU
BEEN STRETCHING YOURSELF
OUT ALL DAY?!
NO, I WAS JUST...
SLOUCHING.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
IT REALLY
ISN'T LIKE YOU.
BECAUSE, DAD,
I CAN'T STAY A KID FOREVER.
WHEN CONNIE GROWS UP
AND BECOMES PRESIDENT,
WHAT IS THAT
GONNA MAKE ME, FIRST BOY?!
STEVEN, YOU CAN'T
JUST KEEP STRETCHING FOREVER.
IF YOU HOLD IT TOO LONG,
YOU COULD REALLY HURT YOURSELF.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M HALF HUMAN,
SO MAYBE IT WORKS
DIFFERENT FOR ME.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO WAIT
AND SEE, RIGHT?
[ SIGHS ] STEVEN...
THAT ONE'S
CANIS HELICOPTERUS.
[ Stifled ]
UH, UH, HELICOPTERUS?
YEAH, DOGCOPTER!
GET IT?
NOW YOU MAKE ONE UP.
MM...OKAY, UM...
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THAT ONE'S,
UH...SNAKE CONSTELLATION.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA THROW UP.
OH, YEAH.
E-EVERYTHING'S FINE.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU KNOW, TO BE HONEST,
I-I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED BEFORE.
THIS MIGHT SOUND SILLY,
BUT I'M REALLY GLAD
THAT I'M GOING TO GET
TO GROW UP WITH YOU.
[ WARBLING ]
STEVEN?
STEVEN, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT HAPPENED?
[ Baby voice ] WHAT?
UH...
[ CRYING ]
WE WERE JUST TALKING,
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN --
HE TURNED BACK
INTO A BABY?!
-YES!
-DUDE, I TOLD YOU!
STRETCHING YOUR BODY OUT FOR
THAT LONG IS NOT GOOD FOR YOU.
[ BABBLING ]
HERE YOU GO, PEARL.
OH, NO, NO,
DON'T GIVE HIM TO ME.
HAND HIM OVER, AMETHYST.
[ STEVEN CRYING ]
HERE YOU GO.
MEH, MEH, MEH,
BLAH!
UH...
[ CRYING ]
MY POWER MEANS NOTHING
TO AN INFANT.
OKAY,
THIS IS MY DEPARTMENT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
DON'T WORRY, I GOT THIS.
[ CRYING ]
[ MARACA SHAKING ]
HOW CAN THE GEMS
NOT KNOW WHAT TO DO?
YOU THINK THEY KNEW THE FIRST
THING ABOUT RAISING A BABY?
THAT WAS ALL ME,
BUT I DON'T GET IT.
DRIVING ALWAYS USED
TO CALM HIM DOWN.
BUT HOW DO WE
CHANGE HIM BACK?!
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK, CONNIE,
LET ME TAKE YOU HOME.
I-I'LL CALL YOU WHEN
THIS ALL GETS SORTED OUT.
[ BABBLING ]
W-WAIT, NO.
I WANT TO STAY.
-ARE YOU SURE?
-YEAH.
I JUST WANT TO BE THERE
FOR STEVEN.
DON'T WORRY, STEVEN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME
WHAT AGE IT SEEMS LIKE YOU ARE.
I WANT TO HANG OUT WITH YOU
NO MATTER WHAT.
YOUR DAD STILL
HAS TO RUN HIS CAR WASH,
AND THE GEMS
HAVE TO DO GEM STUFF,
SO I'LL WATCH YOU
WHEN THEY'RE NOT AROUND.
I CAN COME SEE YOU AFTER I'M
DONE TRAINING WITH PEARL, TOO!
DOESN'T THAT SOUND FUN?
[ BABBLES ]
Greg: LOOK AT THAT --
HE FINALLY STOPPED CRYING.
WELL, THAT'S A START.
-AHEM!
-WHAT'S UP, AMETHYST?
BABY STEVEN NEEDS CHANGING.
OH, MY GOSH.
OHHH, MY GOSH!
DID HE GET EVEN SMALLER?
STEVEN'S MICROSCOPIC!
HE'S REVERTED BACK TO A ZYGOTE!
EVERYONE, STEVEN IS --
[ Normal voice ]
LOOK, IT FITS NOW.
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL!
SORRY
THIS WAS A DISASTER.
I WANTED TO LOOK OLDER
FOR YOU.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID
IN THE VAN.
IT'S REALLY OKAY
IF I DON'T AGE LIKE A HUMAN?
OF COURSE IT IS!
I LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE.
[ Muffled ] OH, OKAY!
UH, STEVEN, YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING ON YOUR CHEEK.
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
ITS A FACIAL HAIR!
-REALLY?
-DAD!
-WHAT IS IT, LITTLE MAN?
-LOOK AT THIS!
HOLY SMOKES,
YOU'RE GROWING A BEARD!
YOU REALLY ARE
GETTING OLDER!
EVERYBODY,
LOOK AT THIS!
UNBELIEVABLE.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
IS THERE MORE
WHERE THAT CAME FROM?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ GIGGLES ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
♪♪
[ CRICKETS BUZZING ]
[ SOFT UKULELE TUNE PLAYING ]
STEVEN.
HI.
WHY DID WE STOP WORKING
ON THE DRILL?
WHY ARE THEY JUST SITTING THERE,
LOOKING AT NOTHING?!
WE WORKED HARD,
AND WE DESERVE TO TAKE IT EASY
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN,
JUST LOOK AT THAT VIEW!
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
IT'S GOING TO BE BLOWN
TO OBLIVION BY THE CLUSTER
IF WE DON'T GET
BACK TO WORK!
WORKING HARD IS IMPORTANT,
BUT FEELING GOOD IS IMPORTANT,
TOO!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?!
[ WHIRRING ]
HEY -- BZZZZ!
WHAT IS THAT,
A -- A "C"?
[ NOTE PLAYS ]
THE DRILL?
YEAH!
[ WHIRRING CHANGES PITCH ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOSH!
NOW IT'S MUSIC!
MUSIC?
YEAH, IT'S MUSIC.
LIKE THIS...
♪ DO RE MI FA
SO LA TI DO ♪
DO MI SO DO.
♪ ISN'T IT PRETTY? ♪
THAT'S
EXCEEDINGLY SIMPLE.
DO MI SO TI.
♪ WE'RE MAKING MUSIC ♪
WHAT IS THE POINT?
YOU'RE NOT MAKING
ANYTHING.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T ANYTHING,
THEN WHY DOES IT SOUND SO GOOD?
I SUPPOSE
IT'S JUST INTEREST.
DO MI SO DO...
DEVOID OF SUBSTANCE
OR PURPOSE.
A HYPOTHETICAL PATTERN.
DO MI SO TI...
FOR THE SATISFACTION OF
BRINGING IT TO COMPLETION!
SURE!
DO MI SO TI...
INTEREST WITHOUT MEANING.
SOLUTIONS WITHOUT PROBLEMS?
AND THEN
YOU JUST ADD WORDS.
HERE'S ONE
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON...
♪ LIFE AND DEATH
AND LOVE AND BIRTH ♪
♪ AND PEACE AND WAR
ON THE PLANET EARTH ♪
♪ IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT'S WORTH MORE ♪
♪ THAN PEACE AND LOVE
ON THE PLANET EARTH? ♪
♪ OH, WHOA,
COME ON AND SING IT WITH ME ♪
SING?
♪ THE WORDS RELATE
TO THE KEY ♪
KEY?
♪ IF IT'S A PATTERN,
IF IT'S A PATTERN ♪
♪ THEN JUST REPEAT
AFTER ME ♪
♪ LIFE AND DEATH
AND LOVE AND BIRTH ♪
NOW YOU SING ♪ MI, FA MI,
MI FA MI TI LA ♪
Both: ♪ AND PEACE AND WAR
ON THE PLANET EARTH ♪
YES, YES, THAT'S IT!
THAT'S SO EASY.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S
WHAT'S FUN ABOUT IT.
YOU SHOULD WRITE SOMETHING.
YOU SHOULD WRITE A SONG!
ABOUT WHAT?
WHATEVER YOU'RE THINKING.
♪ I GUESS WE'RE ALREADY HERE ♪
♪ I GUESS WE ALREADY KNOW ♪
♪ WE'VE ALL GOT SOMETHING
TO FEAR ♪
♪ WE'VE ALL GOT NOWHERE TO GO ♪
♪ I THINK YOU'RE ALL INSANE ♪
♪ BUT I GUESS I AM, TOO ♪
♪ ANYBODY WOULD BE ♪
♪ IF THEY WERE STUCK ON EARTH
WITH YOU ♪
[ LAUGHING ]
YES!
♪ LIFE AND DEATH
AND LOVE AND BIRTH AND ♪
AND LOVE AND BIRTH ♪
♪ AND PEACE AND WAR
ON THE PLANET EARTH ♪
♪ IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT'S WORTH MORE ♪
♪ THAN PEACE AND LOVE
ON THE PLANET EARTH? ♪
WHOA!
NICE WORK.
[ GASPS ] AH!
[ LAUGHING ]
WE REALLY DID IT, HUH?
[ GASPS ] WE?
OH, WAIT.
I NEED TO CHECK SOMETHING!
SHE'S COME SO FAR!
IT FEELS LIKE YESTERDAY
SHE WAS TRYING TO KILL US.
NO, NO,
THAT WAS SEVERAL WEEKS AGO.
COORDINATES!
WE STILL NEED THE CLUSTER'S
EXACT COORDINATES
IN ORDER TO DRILL!
THERE'S A DIAMOND BASE
THAT MAY HOLD THAT INFORMATION,
BUT GETTING THERE
IS GOING TO BE DIFFICULT.
HOW COME?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT ACCESSIBLE
BY WARP PAD, AND IT'S ON...
[ GASPS ]
THE MOON?!
YEAH, STEVEN, THE MOON.
LION, CAN YOU MAKE US A SPECIAL
SUPER WARP TO THE MOON?
[ GROANS ]
COME ON, LION!
WE GOT TO DO THIS
TO STOP THE CLUSTER!
IF WE DON'T,
THERE'S GONNA BE NO MORE EARTH!
NO MORE FUN TIMES
WITH YOUR PALS!
NO MORE LION LICKERS?
NO MORE NAPS?
[ GROWLS ]
[ ROARS ]
GUESS IT WAS "NAPS."
[ PANTING ]
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ROARING ]
GO, LION, GO!
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
LION!
ARE YOU OKAY, BUD?
[ GROWLS ]
GET ME OUT OF THIS
FURRY FREAK -- UGH! OW!
[ PANTING ]
AW, LION, YOU'VE EARNED
YOUR NAPS FOR THE WEEK!
[ SIGHS ]
WE MADE IT.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THE MOON.
HEY, LOOK OVER HERE.
I THINK IT'S A DOOR!
UH...
YEP!
WE ON THE MOON!
AMETHYST, PLEASE DON'T BLOW US
INTO SPACE!
[ LAUGHING ]
WHOA!
LOOK AT ME!
I'M A MOON BOY!
[ LAUGHING ]
HA HA!
ALL RIGHT, MOON BOY!
[ GRUNTS ]
MOON BOY,
QUADRUPLE BACKFLIP!
HEY!
WHY CAN'T I BE
A MOON BOY?
WE'RE GEMS.
WE'RE A SPACE-FARING RACE
DESIGNED TO CONQUER
OTHER WORLDS!
OUR PHYSICAL FORMS
ADJUST AUTOMATICALLY
TO THE GRAVITY
OF ANY PLANETOID!
AW, LAME!
♪ I WAS BOUNCING ON THE MOON
ONE DAY ♪
[ GRUNTS ]
HUH?
HEY, PERIDOT,
WHO IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE?
[ GASPS ]
IT'S BLUE DIAMOND!
WAIT.
ARE THEY ALL HERE?
AH, YES!
THERE SHE IS!
WHO?
[ PANTING ]
BEHOLD, YELLOW DIAMOND!
ISN'T SHE MAGNIFICENT?
WOW!
SO,
WHO ARE THE DIAMONDS ANYWAY?
THEY SEEM LIKE
A BIG DEAL!
ARE YOU JOKING ME?
THE DIAMONDS
ARE THE GEM MATRIARCHS!
TOGETHER THEY MAKE UP
THE GREAT DIAMOND AUTHORITY
THAT GOVERNS HOMEWORLD
AND ALL THE OUTLYING COLONIES!
WE LIVE TO SERVE THEM!
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
I -- I MEAN,
WE WERE ALL MADE TO SERVE THEM
EVEN THOUGH
SOME OF US DON'T ANYMORE.
HEY, I THINK THAT'S
A CONTROL SURFACE OVER THERE!
LET'S TAKE A LOOK!
YEAH!
I THINK THIS IS RIGHT.
THE MATERIAL IS DIFFERENT
FROM THE SURROUNDING STONE.
I THINK
IF I JUST DO...THIS!
HUH?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GIGGLING ]
THIS IS SO INCREDIBLE!
ONLY THE MOST ELITE OF THE ELITE
CAN ENTER THESE SANCTUMS.
WE ARE LITERALLY WALKING IN
THE FOOTSTEPS OF THE DIAMONDS.
THEY MUST
REALLY LIKE STAIRS.
HEY, WHAT'S THIS ROOM?
IT'S NOT
WHAT WE CAME FOR.
CAN WE HURRY IT UP?
THIS PLACE GIVES ME THE CREEPS.
WE REALLY ARE ON THE MOON!
OH, MY GOODNESS!
THIS LOOKS LIKE
IT COULD BE BRAND-NEW!
I MEAN, IT'S A RELIC
BY TODAY'S STANDARDS,
BUT, GOLLY,
IT'S SO ELEGANT,
SO SIMPLE, SO PERFECT!
SO, HOW DO YOU
TURN IT ON?
IDWAEAH!.
O
WAH!
SO, HOW DO YOU
WAH!                        WAH!
HEY, IT'S GOT ONE OF THOSE
GLOWY HAND DEALIES!
YOU CAN'T SIT THERE!
WHY NOT?
IT'S REALLY COOL!
THAT CHAIR IS ONLY FOR
THE MOST ELITE GEMS!
YOU CAN'T GO AROUND SITTING
WHERE AN ELITE WOULD SIT!
WELL, THEY AREN'T HERE NOW,
RIGHT?
[ GIGGLES ]
HEY,
WHAT'S THIS DOODAD FOR?
PUT THAT BACK!
HMM,
OKAY, LET'S SEE HERE.
THERE WE GO.
THIS IS
A REALLY OLD SYSTEM.
GOTTA FIND
THE RIGHT FILE...
AHA!
CLUSTER, CLUSTER,
WHERE ARE YOU, CLUSTER?
AHA!
THERE'S THE INSERTION POINT!
LOOKS LIKE THE BETA KINDERGARTEN
IN FACET NINE.
IT'S THE SMALLER OF THE TWO,
NOT NEARLY AS IMPRESSIVE
AS YOURS, AMETHYST!
UH, THANKS?
BUT WHERE IS
THE CLUSTER NOW?
HANG ON.
THERE IT IS!
IT'S EMBEDDED DEEP
IN THE MANTLE.
RELATIVE TO THE BARN,
IT'S ROUGHLY 2,500 UNITS DOWN.
ALL WE NEED TO DO IS FEED
THIS DATA TO THE DRILL,
AND WE SHOULD BE ALL SET!
THAT'S IT, THEN!
MISSION
ACCOMPLISHED!
YEAH, TEAM!
GREAT.
LET'S GET THE HECK
OUT OF HERE!
WAIT. HOLD ON!
DOES THIS THING HAVE
ANY GAMES ON IT?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS WASN'T USED
FOR GAMES.
AW.
IT WAS USED
FOR PLANNING THE COLONY.
HERE, LOOK!
SO HERE'S A MAP
OF ALL STRUCTURES
THAT WERE ORIGINALLY BUILT
ON EARTH.
ALL TOLD, THIS PROBABLY
ONLY ACCOUNTS
FOR MAYBE 5% OF WHAT
WAS ORIGINALLY PLANNED!
WHAT WAS THE PLAN?
WELL,
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
[ GASPING ]
TA-DA!
A FINISHED EARTH COLONY!
WOW!
LOOK AT THIS!
89 KINDERGARTENS, 67 SPIRES,
A GALAXY WARP IN EACH FACET,
EFFICIENT USE
OF ALL AVAILABLE MATERIALS.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
SHUTTING THIS OPERATION DOWN!
IT COULD HAVE BEEN GREAT!
NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S PERFECT.
LOOK AT IT!
WE ARE LOOKING
AT IT.
YEAH,
THIS PLAN STINKS!
COMPLETING THIS COLONY
WOULD HAVE MEANT
THE EXTINCTION
OF ALL LIFE ON EARTH.
BUT THINK OF THE GOOD
IT WOULD HAVE DONE --
THE GEMS WOULD
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN MADE,
OUR EMPIRE EXPANDED!
ROSE QUARTZ BELIEVED
ALL LIFE WAS PRECIOUS
AND WORTH PROTECTING!
WELL, IF SHE WANTED TO
PROTECT IT,
SHE DID A LOUSY JOB!
THERE'D BE NO CLUSTER IF
THE EARTH HAD STAYED A COLONY!
NOW THERE'S NO COLONY,
AND THERE'S GONNA BE NO EARTH!
SO THANK YOU, ROSE QUARTZ --
YOU DOOMED THE PLANET!
OH!
♪ IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT'S WORTH MORE THAN -- ♪
[ GASPS ]
YOU LISTEN TO ME NOW.
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT THINGS
THAT YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
GARNET, STOP, PLEASE!
IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
LET'S JUST GO HOME.
[ SIGHS ]
Peridot:
WHAT'D I SAY?!
I'M JUST STATING A FACT!
THE REBELLION
DIDN'T REALLY SAVE EARTH.
IT JUST DELAYED
THE INEVITABLE.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY
THEY SEE IT.
THEY'VE SPENT
THOUSANDS OF YEARS
TRYING TO PROTECT
THE EARTH.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU FINALLY UNDERSTOOD WHY.
PERIDOT!
WHAT?
I'M COMING.
LET'S GO, YOU TWO.
[ CRICKETS BUZZING ]