>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: GIVE ME THE --
OH, THANKS.
>> EH, I SAW YOU GUYS COMING.
>> ARE YOU CLOSING UP ALL BY
YOURSELF?
>> YEAH.
IT'S JUST ME TONIGHT.
>> WOW.
THAT'S A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITY
FOR A KID YOUR AGE.
HEY, YOUR DAD MUST REALLY TRUST
YOU.
>> DON'T PATRONIZE ME, SIR.
>> Steven: SEE YOU, PEEDEE!
SO, LIKE I WAS SAYING, PERIDOT'S
BEEN SHOOTING HUGE ROBOTS HERE
FROM SPACE.
AND WHEN YOU SMASH THEM, THEY
EXPLODE INTO GOO.
>> THAT SOUNDS SCARY.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SURE IF --
DO YOU EVER FEEL LIKE THIS GEM
STUFF IS TOO MUCH FOR YOU?
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU --
OH!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> WHAT THE HEY WAS THAT?!
STEVEN?
>> Steven: IS THAT A HAND?
>> Pearl: THE LIGHT CANNONS
SHOULD BE READY.
>> Steven: GUYS!
DID YOU SEE THAT THING IN THE
SKY?
>> Pearl: IT'S A SHIP.
WE HAVE TO ASSUME IT'S PERIDOT.
>> Garnet: LAPIS TOLD US SHE'D
BE COMING WITH ADVANCED WEAPONS
AND REINFORCEMENTS.
>> IT'S HAPPENING.
>> Steven: I WANT TO SEE.
WHOA!
>> Garnet: READY THE LIGHT
CANNONS!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN, LIGHT 'EM UP.
>> Steven: IF EVERY PORK CHOP
WERE PERFECT...
WE WOULDN'T HAVE HOT DOGS.
>> Garnet: NO AFFECT.
>> WHAT NOW?
>> Garnet: WE'LL HAVE TO TAKE
THEM HEAD ON.
THE WHOLE TOWN MIGHT BE IN
DANGER.
>> Steven: I BETTER MAKE A CALL.
TIME FOR SOME...POLITICAL
FAVORS.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>> HELLO?
>> Steven: Mayor Dewey, it's me,
Steven Universe.
>> UNIVERSE!
WHAT'S THIS THING IN THE SKY?
AS A POLITICIAN, POINTING
FINGERS MAKE ME VERY NERVOUS.
>> Steven: MAYOR DEWEY, THE
WHOLE TOWN'S IN DANGER.
We have to evacuate the city.
>> EVACUATE?
HMM.
EVACUATE.
COULD BE STUFF.
UM...I'LL NEED A CATCHY SLOGAN.
>> EVA-CU-ATE!
EVA-CU-ATE!
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
>> PEOPLE!
I NEED EVERYONE TO CONSIDER
EVACUATION.
EVACUATION IS SOMETHING WE ALL
DEPEND ON IN TIMES OF TRAUMA!
>> Steven: OH, HEY.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA, DAD.
YOU SHOULD LEAVE WITH THE REST
OF --
IS THAT MY LUGGAGE?
>> UH...WHO WANTS TO TELL HIM?
>> Amethyst: HEY, I'M NOT GOOD
WITH THIS STUFF.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, I KNOW YOU
DON'T THINK WE TRUST YOU.
I KNOW MORE OFTEN THAN NOT, WE
TREAT YOU LIKE A HUMAN CHILD.
BUT THE TRUTH IS WE RELY ON YOU.
YOUR VOICE INSPIRES US, BINDS
US, REMINDS US WHY WE PROMISED
TO PROTECT THE PLANET.
YOU MUST NOW BE THAT VOICE...
FOR THEM.
>> PEEDEE, COME ON!
>> WHEN ARE WE COMING BACK?!
>> RONALDO, HELP ME WITH YOUR
BROTHER!
>> Garnet: IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
YOU NEED TO BE THERE TO PROTECT
THEM, LIKE YOUR MOTHER ONCE DID.
IT'S YOUR DESTINY.
>> Steven: I WON'T DISAPPOINT
YOU.
>> Garnet: I KNOW.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
WE DID EVERYTHING WE COULD.
ALL RIGHT.
PULL IT TOGETHER.
>> EVA-CU-ATE.
EVA-CU-ATE.
>> Steven: MAYBE WHEN PERIDOT
GETS TO EARTH, SHE'LL SEE HOW
NICE ALL THE PEOPLE ARE AND SHE
WON'T WANT TO HURT ANYONE.
>> JUST LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
>> Steven: YEAH?
>> YEAH.
BUT THESE OTHER GEMS AREN'T LIKE
YOUR MOTHER.
THEY'RE NOT LIKE GARNET,
AMETHYST, OR PEARL.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA START CARING
ABOUT PEOPLE NOW.
THEY DIDN'T THE FIRST TIME
THEY...
>> Steven: THE FIRST TIME THEY
WHAT?
>> I MEAN, IT WAS THOUSANDS OF
YEARS AGO.
IT'S -- IT'S NOT LIKE I WAS
THERE.
THE GEMS SHOULD BE TELLING YOU
ALL THIS STUFF, BUT I GET IT.
I MEAN, THEY DON'T WANT YOU
THINKING OF THEM LIKE THAT.
>> Steven: LIKE WHAT?
DAD, LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE ALIENS, STEVEN!
ALIENS WHO INVADED EARTH!
>> Steven: WHAT?
>> ALL THEY DO IS TRY TO MAKE UP
FOR IT, BUT THEY JUST CAN'T
FORGIVE THEMSELVES.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
LOOK, THEY WERE DOING SOMETHING
AWFUL TO THE PLANET, AND YOUR
MOTHER COULDN'T STAND IT
ANYMORE.
SHE TOLD ME THAT'S WHY SHE HAD
TO TURN ON HER OWN KIND.
SHE GAVE UP EVERYTHING JUST TO
STOP WHAT THEY STARTED HERE AND
DRIVE THE INVADING GEMS OFF OF
EARTH.
>> Steven: SO, SH-SHE SAVED THE
WORLD.
THAT'S GOOD!
>> UH, NO SUCH THING AS A GOOD
WAR, KIDDO.
GEMS WERE DESTROYED.
PEOPLE, TOO.
IN THE END, YOUR MOTHER COULD
ONLY SAVE A HANDFUL OF HER
CLOSEST FRIENDS.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR HER SHIELD --
MAN, I DON'T KNOW.
BU-BUT HEY.
LET'S LOOK ON THE BRIGHT SIDE.
WE'RE GONNA DRIVE BY THAT WAFFLE
PLACE IN A COUPLE MILES.
>> NO WAY!
THE GEMS DON'T WANT YOU GOING
BACK.
>> Steven: I KNOW THEY'RE JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT ME, BUT I HAVE
TO PROTECT THEM.
I HAVE MOM'S SHIELD.
THEY NEED ME!
>> I NEED YOU, TOO!
>> Steven: PLEASE, DAD!
WHAT IF THEY GET HURT?
DAD, TURN AROUND.
DAD!
TURN THE VAN AROUND, PLEASE!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ HORNS HONKING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: DAD...
>> YO, GREG!
ARE YOU AND YOUR KID OKAY?
>> YEAH!
YEAH. WE'RE FINE. WE'RE FINE.
[ SIGHS ]
>> Steven: DAD, PLEASE.
I HAVE TO GO BACK.
I HAVE TO.
THEY DON'T HAVE MY SHIELD.
DO YOU -- DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> YEAH. OKAY.
JUST BE CAREFUL OR I'M GONNA RUN
FRESH OUT OF FAMILY.
>> Steven: STAY WITH EVERYONE
AND KEEP THEM SAFE.
I'LL FIGURE OUT SOME WAY TO GET
BACK TO BEACH CITY.
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Steven: OH, THIS'LL WORK.
[ DIALING ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
COME ON. PICK UP.
>> You have reached the
Maheswaran residence.
>> Steven: AW!
>> Please leave a message after
the beep.
And keep it short.
[ BEEPS ]
>> Steven: Hey, Connie.
It's Steven.
Just seeing what you were up to.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh, don't know if you knew, but
there's some crazy stuff going
on with a giant space hand, and
we all might die, so, uh...I
guess call me back when you get
this, and talk to you soon!
Uh, bye!
[ BEEPS ]
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> Garnet: FIRE!
>> Steven: STAY HERE.
IF SOMETHING HAPPENS, DAD WILL
NEED A NEW SON.
>> Garnet: AT LEAST STEVEN IS
SAFE.
>> Steven: HEY, GUYS!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Amethyst: YOU CAME BACK!
>> Pearl: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GET OUT OF HERE!
>> Steven: BUT --
>> Garnet: IT'S TOO LATE.
JUST STAY BEHIND US.
>> Steven: UH...
>> THAT'S THEM ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT KEEP
BREAKING MY MACHINES.
>> THIS IS IT?
>> JASPER!
THEY KEEP INTERFERING WITH MY
WORK!
>> [ SIGHS ]
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER WASTE OF MY
TIME.
HEY, GET OVER HERE.
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: LAPIS.
>> THIS IS THEIR BASE?
>> YES.
>> Garnet: YOU NEED TO LEAVE
IMMEDIATELY.
>> Amethyst: YEAH, STEP OFF!
>> Pearl: THIS IS NOT A
GEM-CONTROLLED PLANET.
>> NEITHER OF YOU SAW
ROSE QUARTZ?
OH, WHAT A SHAME.
I HOPED TO MEET HER.
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO BEATING
HER INTO THE GROUND.
>> Steven: OH.
>> BUT THIS IS ALL THAT'S LEFT
OF HER ARMY?
SOME LOST, DEFECTIVE PEARL, A
PUNY, OVERCOOKED RUNT, AND THIS
SHAMELESS DISPLAY?
HMM.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT CALLS ITSELF THE STEVEN.
>> HE'S JUST A HUMAN.
HE ISN'T A THREAT AT ALL.
HE -- HE'S NOT ONE OF THEM.
>> I KNOW WHAT A HUMAN IS.
YOU DON'T NEED ME FOR THIS.
JUST BLAST THEM WITH THE SHIP.
>> [ SIGHS ] FINE.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, GET OUT OF
HERE!
>> Steven: NO!
>> Garnet: I WON'T LET YOU RISK
YOUR LIFE.
>> Steven: BUT THIS IS MY HOME,
AND YOU'RE ALL MY FAMILY!
>> FIRING.
>> Steven: I'M -- I'M A
CRYSTAL GEM, TOO!
>> [ GASPS ]
THAT SHIELD.
THAT SYMBOL!
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
>> YOU!
YOU HAVE THE POWER OF
ROSE QUARTZ!
>> NOW DO YOU BELIEVE I NEEDED
AN ESCORT?
>> FIRE A BARRAGE, WIDE SPREAD!
ROSE, WHY DO YOU LOOK LIKE THAT?
WHY ARE YOU SO WEAK?
>> DON'T HURT HIM!
>> YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS!
>> IT WASN'T RELEVANT TO THE
MISSION.
>> FORGET ABOUT THE MISSION.
>> WHAT?!
>> YELLOW DIAMOND NEEDS TO SEE
THIS...THING.
>> Steven: UH, UH...
>> GOOD.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, RUN!
>> PRIMING GEM DESTABILIZER.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
[ CRACK! ]
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: [ EXCLAIMS ]
>> I WAS THERE, YOU KNOW, AT THE
FIRST WAR FOR THIS GARBAGE
PLANET.
I FOUGHT AGAINST YOUR ARMIES.
I RESPECTED YOUR TACTICS.
BUT THIS...
THIS IS SICK.
>> Pearl: UNHAND HIM!
>> I DON'T GET WHAT YOU'RE
PLANNING, ROSE, BUT LOOK.
YOUR BASE IS TAKEN.
YOUR ARMIES ARE RUINED.
YOU HAVE FAILED!
[ SMACK! ]
>> [ VOCALIZING ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
[ GROANING ]
AMETHYST?
PEARL?
GARNET!
[ GASPS ]
WHERE ARE THEY?
WHOA.
>> [ MUFFLED GROANING ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
[ ZAP! ]
[ WARBLING ]
>> Steven: EW!
[ CHUCKLES ]
COOL!
WHO-O-O-O-OA!
[ SHUDDERS ]
I'M OUT.
WHOO-HOO!
OKAY, WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
GOT TO FIND 'EM, GOT TO FIND
'EM, GOT TO FIND 'EM.
OH!
>> [ GROANING ]
>> Steven: UH, HELLO?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> [ EXCLAIMS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
GREAT!
THIS IS JUST PERFECT!
>> Steven: UH...DO YOU NEED ANY
HELP?
>> NO!
I MEAN...DON'T LOOK AT ME!
JUST GO AWAY.
>> Steven: WHA--?
HMPH.
>> HEY, WAIT!
YOU'RE OUT!
HOW DID YOU GET PAST THE FIELD?
>> Steven: OH, UH, I JUST KIND
OF --
>> WAIT!
NO, NO, NO, NO, WAIT.
[ WARBLING ]
THAT'S...OKAY?
[ ZAP! ]
UGH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> [ VOCALIZING ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: SOMEBODY'S SINGING.
>> SAPPHIRE.
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
PLEASE, I NEED TO FIND SAPPHIRE.
>> Steven: IS SHE YOUR FRIEND?
I'M LOOKING FOR MY FRIENDS, TOO.
>> SHE'S ALL ALONE!
I NEED TO FIND HER!
>> DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL FIND OUR FRIENDS.
[ WARBLING ]
A-A-AND WE'LL D-DO IT
TOGETHER-ER-ER!
WHOA! WAIT FOR ME!
>> [ CONTINUES VOCALIZING ]
>> Steven: HEY!
UH, MY NAME'S STEVEN, BY THE
WAY.
WHAT'S YOURS?
>> QUIET!
[ GROANS ] I CAN'T SEE.
THIS WAY!
>> Steven: A-A-AH!
HOW MANY MORE GEMS ARE TRAPPED
HERE?
>> DON'T KNOW. DON'T CARE.
[ VOCALIZING STOPS ]
SHE STOPPED SINGING.
SAPPHIRE!
[ GASPS ]
OH, IT'S JUST YOU.
>> Steven: LAPIS!
LAPIS, I CAN GET YOU OUT.
>> STOP!
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY.
I CAN --
>> NO! I DON'T WANT YOUR HELP.
THINGS ARE BAD ENOUGH AS IT IS.
I'VE ALREADY MADE TOO MUCH
TROUBLE.
ONCE WE GET BACK TO HOMEWORLD,
THEY'RE GOING TO DECIDE WHAT TO
DO WITH US.
>> [ GROANS ]
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
>> Steven: WAIT!
>> STEVEN, WHATEVER YOU'RE
DOING, JUST STOP.
IF WE DO EVERYTHING THEY SAY,
THEY MIGHT GO EASY ON US.
>> Steven: BUT THEY'RE...MEAN.
THEY HURT MY FRIENDS.
THEY HURT MY FACE.
THEY'VE GOT YOU HERE IN PRISON!
>> THAT'S WHY WE CAN'T FIGHT
THEM.
>> Steven: THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO
FIGHT THEM!
I'LL COME BACK FOR YOU.
>> [ VOCALIZING ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> WE CAN'T LEAVE YET!
>> THE WHOLE POINT OF COMING
HERE WAS TO CHECK ON THE
CLUSTER.
>> STOP SINGING!
ROSE QUARTZ TAKES PRIORITY.
GET BACK TO THE BRIDGE AND SET A
COURSE FOR HOMEWORLD.
>> "GO TO EARTH," THEY SAID.
"IT'LL BE EASY," THEY SAID.
>> [ VOCALIZING ]
>> Steven: Hey.
I like your song.
Are you Sapphire?
>> YOU ESCAPED.
[ WARBLING ]
OF COURSE.
>> Steven: CO-COME O-O-ON.
IT'S SA-A-AFE.
>> THANK YOU, STEVEN.
>> Steven: YO-O-OU'RE WELCOME.
>> SAPPHIRE!
>> COME ON!
>> Steven: WHOA!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GASPS ]
>> RUBY!
>> DID THEY HURT YOU?
>> NO, NO. I'M OKAY.
DID THEY HURT YOU?
>> WHO CARES?
>> I DO.
[ SMOOCHES ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Garnet: [ LAUGHS ]
STEVEN, THANK YOU!
>> Steven: GARNET!
YOU'RE A FUSION?
>> Garnet: OH, I-I'M SORRY.
WE DIDN'T WANT YOU MEETING US
HERE LIKE THIS.
>> Steven: WELL, DID I MAKE A
GOOD FIRST IMPRESSION?
>> Garnet: OH, STEVEN.
WE ALREADY LOVE YOU.
>> WHERE IS SHE?!
>> Garnet: IT'S JASPER.
STEVEN, FIND THE OTHERS AND GET
TO THE CONTROL BRIDGE.
>> Steven: BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY ARE.
>> Garnet: [ SMOOCHES ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
FUTURE VISION.
WAIT.
ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO BEAT
HER ON YOUR OWN?
>> Garnet: IT'S OKAY, STEVEN.
I'M NEVER ALONE.
>> Steven: HMM.
>> OH, GREAT.
YOU'RE BOTH OUT?
AND YOU'RE FUSED AGAIN?
WHY?
FUSION IS JUST A CHEAP TACTIC TO
MAKE WEAK GEMS STRONGER.
QUIT EMBARRASSING YOURSELVES!
I'VE SEEN WHAT YOU REALLY ARE.
>> Garnet: [ CHUCKLES ]
NO, YOU HAVEN'T.
♪ THIS IS GARNET ♪
♪ BACK TOGETHER ♪
♪ AND I'M NEVER GOING DOWN AT
THE HANDS OF THE LIKES OF YOU ♪
♪ BECAUSE I'M SO MUCH BETTER ♪
♪ AND EVERY PART OF ME IS
SAYING, "GO GET HER" ♪
♪ THE TWO OF US AIN'T GONNA
FOLLOW YOUR RULES ♪
♪ COME AT ME WITHOUT ANY OF YOUR
FANCY TOOLS ♪
♪ LET'S GO, JUST ME AND YOU ♪
♪ LET'S GO, JUST ONE ON TWO ♪
♪ GO AHEAD AND TRY AND HIT ME IF
YOU'RE ABLE ♪
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE THAT MY
RELATIONSHIP IS STABLE? ♪
♪ I CAN SEE YOU HATE THE WAY WE
INTERMINGLE ♪
♪ BUT I THINK YOU'RE JUST MAD
'CAUSE YOU'RE SINGLE ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO STOP
WHAT WE'VE MADE TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE ARE GOING TO STAY LIKE THIS
FOREVER ♪
♪ IF YOU BREAK US APART, WE'LL
JUST COME BACK NEWER ♪
♪ AND WE'LL ALWAYS BE TWICE THE
GEM THAT YOU ARE ♪
♪ I AM MADE O-O-O-O-OF ♪
♪ LO-O-O-O-OVE ♪
♪ O-O-O-O-OF ♪
>> DON'T TOUCH THAT!
YOU CLODS DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING!
>> Amethyst: YOU GOT THIS,
PEARL!
>> Pearl: OKAY, SHIP.
TURN US AROUND.
O-O-O-OOH.
♪ THIS IS WHO WE ARE ♪
♪ THIS IS WHO I AM ♪
♪ AND IF YOU THINK YOU CAN STOP
ME, THEN YOU NEED TO THINK
AGAIN ♪
♪ BECAUSE I AM A FEELING ♪
♪ AND I WILL NEVER END ♪
♪ AND I WON'T LET YOU HURT MY
PLANET ♪
FRIENDS ♪
♪ GO AHEAD AND TRY AND HIT ME IF
YOU'RE ABLE ♪
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE THAT MY
RELATIONSHIP IS STABLE? ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU THINK I'M NOT
SOMETHING YOU'RE AFRAID OF ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU THINK THAT YOU'VE
SEEN WHAT I'M MADE OF ♪
♪ BUT I AM EVEN MORE THAN THE
TWO OF THEM ♪
♪ EVERYTHING THEY CARE ABOUT IS
WHAT I AM ♪
♪ I AM THEIR FURY ♪
♪ I AM THEIR PATIENCE ♪
♪ I AM A CONVERSATION ♪
♪ I AM MADE O-O-O-O-OF ♪
♪ LO-O-O-O-OVE ♪
♪ O-O-O-O-OF ♪
♪ AND IT'S STRONGER THAN YOU ♪
♪ LO-O-O-O-OVE ♪
♪ O-O-O-O-OF ♪
♪ AND IT'S STRONGER THAN YOU ♪
>> GARNET!
>> Garnet: THIS SHIP IS GOING
DOWN!
>> Steven: WHAT ABOUT LAPIS?
>> Garnet: THERE'S NO TIME!
♪ LO-O-O-O-OVE ♪
♪ AND IT'S STRONGER THAN YOU ♪
♪ O-O-O-O-OF ♪
♪ LO-O-O-O-OVE ♪
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Garnet: NICE ONE.
>> Steven: OH, MY GOSH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE A FUSION
ALL THE TIME!
>> Amethyst: YOU MET RUBY AND
SAPPHIRE?
>> Pearl: OH, NO!
WE WERE GOING TO INTRODUCE YOU.
GARNET, YOUR PLAN.
>> Garnet: WE WERE WAITING FOR
YOUR BIRTHDAY.
>> Steven: WE CAN STILL DO IT.
I'LL JUST PRETEND I DIDN'T KNOW.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
>> [ GRUNTING ]
DON'T THINK YOU'VE WON.
YOU ONLY BEAT ME 'CAUSE YOU'RE A
FUSION.
IF I HAD SOMEONE TO FUSE WITH,
I'D --
[ RATTLING ]
HUH?
>> [ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> COME HERE, BRAT!
AW, DON'T FLY OFF SO SOON.
>> Steven: LAPIS!
>> LAPIS, LISTEN.
FUSE WITH ME!
>> WHAT?
>> HOW LONG DID THEY KEEP YOU
TRAPPED HERE ON THIS MISERABLE
HUNK OF ROCK?
THESE GEMS -- THEY'RE TRAITORS
TO THEIR HOMEWORLD.
THEY KEPT YOU PRISONER.
THEY USED YOU.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO TAKE
REVENGE!
COME ON.
JUST SAY "YES."
>> Steven: LAPIS, DON'T DO IT.
NO!
[ ALL EXCLAIM ]
>> [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
WHAT?!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ STRAINING ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
I'M DONE BEING EVERYONE'S
PRISONER.
NOW YOU'RE MY PRISONER!
AND I'M NEVER LETTING YOU GO!
[ GASPS ]
NO!
[ SCREAMS ]
>> Steven: LAPIS!
>> LET'S STAY ON THIS MISERABLE
PLANET TOGETHER!
>> Garnet: YIKES.
THEY ARE REALLY BAD FOR EACH
OTHER.
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
>> Steven: UH...HELLO?
>> STEVEN, I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
STEVEN?
>> ♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN HOW
TO LOVE ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE THE WAY YOU ACT ♪
♪ WONDERING WHEN
I'M COMING BACK ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN HOW TO LOVE
LIKE YOU ♪