>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> Steven: PEARL?!
AMETHYST?!
GARNET?!
AAH!
>> Pearl: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
YELL, STEVEN.
WE'RE RIGHT HERE.
>> Steven: I KNOW, BUT I
FINISHED THIS DRAWING, AND I
WANTED TO SHOW IT TO YOU.
>> Pearl: OH! UH, OF COURSE.
>> Steven: ALL RIGHT!
HA HA!
GUITAR DAD TEACHES YOU GUITAR!
>> Amethyst: WHATISTHAT?
>> Steven: IT'S MY DAD!
HE'S GOING TO START TEACHING
GUITAR LESSONS, AND HE MADE ME
HIS P.R. DEPARTMENT.
>> Amethyst: WHAT'S THAT STUFF
IN HIS MOUTH?
>> Steven: THOSE ARE HIS
TEETH.
>> Pearl: WHAT ARE THE
LIGHTNING BOLTS FOR?
>> Steven: UH...
WELL, I-I WAS TRYING TO SHOW
THAT DAD REALLY ROCKS ON THE
GUITAR, AND --
>> Garnet: THEN THERE SHOULD BE
ROCKS FALLING OUT OF THE GUITAR.
>> Steven: I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, BUT IT'S TOO LATE FOR
NOTES.
THIS IS PERMANENT MARKER.
MM-HMM!
>> WHAT'S THAT CUTE FLYER FOR,
STEVEN?
>> Steven: IT'S FOR MY DAD!
HE'LL TEACH YOU GUITAR.
YOU GUYS WANT TO SIGN UP?
MY DAD'S REALLY GOOD!
>> MAYBE I'LL STOP BY AND CHECK
IT OUT.
>> Steven: HERE, LET ME GIVE
YOU A FLYER AND --
[ BELL JINGLES ]
>> WELCOME TO THE BIG DONUT!
>> Steven: HEY, BUCK!
>> OH! WHAT?
BUCK, BUCK, BU-U-U-U-CK!
HA HA! WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
WHAT CAN WE GET FOR YOU TODAY?
>> CAN I GET A CAPRESE SALAD?
>> OH, SORRY, BUCK, WE ONLY
SERVE DON--
>> DO-NUT WORRY, BUCK!
I'LL WHIP YOU UP A SALAD -- NO
SWEAT!
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
>> LARS, WE DON'T EVEN HAVE
VEGETABLES HERE!
>> HEH, WHAT'S A GUITAR DAD?
>> Steven: LIKE MY FLYER?
IT'S FOR MY DAD!
HE'LL TEACH YOU GUITAR!
HERE, TAKE ONE OF THESE WITH
YOU!
ACTUALLY, JUST WEAR IT!
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: ARE YOU TICKLISH?
>> THIS WOULD MAKE A RAD SHIRT,
MAN.
>> Steven: REALLY?
>> YEAH!
LET'S MAKE YOUR FLYER INTO
T-SHIRTS!
>> Steven: OH, MAN!
MY DAD WOULD LOVE THAT!
>> GIMME FIVE ON IT.
OH, YOU MISSED.
>> HO!
I THINK IT'S SWELL YOU'RE
RETURNING TO THE FAMILY
BUSINESS, SON!
GONNA HELP THE OLD MAN GET
RE-ELECTED AGAIN, EH?
AW, SON!
>> UGH!
IT'S NOT FOR CAMPAIGN STUFF,
DAD.
STEVEN AND I ARE MAKING ART.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
ART!
>> ART, HUH?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT MYSELF,
BUT A BOY'S GOT TO HAVE
INTERESTS AND AMBITIONS!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> [ GROANS ]
>> Steven: THIS STUFF CAN BE
USED TO MAKE T-SHIRTS?
>> OH, YEAH, I'VE GOT ALL THE
LATEST, STATE-OF-THE-ART
SCREEN-PRINTING EQUIPMENT FROM
YEARS OF CAMPAIGNING AND OTHER
SOME-SUCH MAYORLY THINGS.
LIKE THIS WEEK, I'M
COMMEMORATING A BENCH!
>> Steven: "WELCOME TO...
'BENCH' CITY"?
THRIFTY!
>> [ GROANS ]
DAD, YOU CAN'T USE THIS!
>> WHY NOT?
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO "GANK DAT"
YOUTH VOTE, BOYEEEEE!
>> DAD, STOP.
>> Steven: WHAT'S THIS?
>> WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
[ GASPS ]
I HAVEN'T SEEN THIS IN YEARS!
REMEMBER WHEN YOU DREW THIS,
BUCK?
YOU COULDN'T WAIT TO SHOW IT
OFF TO ALL YOUR LITTLE
MONTESSORI FRIENDS.
>> OKAY, DAD!
THANKS FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
SEE YOU LATER! BYE.
>> ALL RIGHT, KIDS!
I MEAN, PEACE IN THE
MIDDLE EAST, HOLMES!
>> Steven: SO COOL.
>> LET'S JUST GET STARTED
ALREADY.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
>> SWAG.
>> Steven: NOW EVERYONE'S
GONNA WANT LESSONS FROM DAD!
>> THIS IS BIGGER THAN YOUR
DAD, STEVEN.
IT'S ART.
AND IT'S GONNA FLOOD THE PUBLIC
CONSCIOUSNESS.
>> Steven: WELL, LET'S START
HANDING THEM OUT!
>> TOO SIMPLE.
WE NEED TO GET CONTROVERSIAL.
WE NEED TO CREATE -- BOOM! -- A
SCENE.
>> Steven: SCANNING FOR TARGETS.
T-SHIRT CANNON LOADED AND READY!
BEEP, BEEP, BEEP...BIBIBIBI!
SOUR CREAM SIGHTED!
>> WOM WOM...WOM WOM WOM.
>> Steven: GET READY!
TAKE AIM!
>> AND..
>> WOMP WOMP WOMP...WOMP!
WHAT IN THE WORLD?
OH, THIS IS THE COOLEST THING
I'VE EVER BEEN HIT IN THE HEAD
WITH!
>> Steven: RONALDO SPOTTED.
TAKE AIM!
>> WHOA!
WHAT THE HECK?!
HUH?
WHOA! WEIRD!
SOME KIND OF EXTRATERRESTRIAL
SPACE DAD GUITAR SHIRT?
SO, YOU'VE FINALLY DECIDED TO
MAKE FIRST CONTACT, HUH?
WHERE ARE YOU?!
>> Steven: LARS SIGHTED.
TAKE AIM!
>> YOUCH! WHAT THE...
WHAT IS THIS GARBAGE?
BUCK MADE THIS?
[ LAUGHS ]
THIS IS HILARIOUS!
THANKS, BUCK!
>> Steven: CHEERS!
BUCK, THIS WAS SUCH A GOOD IDEA!
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE DIDN'T
COLLABORATE ON A PROJECT SOONER!
THIS WILL MAKE MY DAD SO HAPPY!
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE LOOK ON
HIS FACE WHEN I STOP BY LATER.
>> YEAH.
SHOULD BE GOOD FOR A LAUGH.
>> Steven: HUH?
WHY WOULD IT BE GOOD FOR A --
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> GIRL!
CHECK OUT MY NEW SHIRT!
>> IT'S REALLY CUTE!
WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST LANDED IN FRONT OF ME
WHEN I WAS OUT WALKING.
>> WELL, IF I WERE YOU, I
WOULDN'T WEAR SOME RANDOM SHIRT
THAT JUST FELL OUT OF THE SKY.
WHAT IF THERE WERE BUGS IN IT?
>> RELAX!
WHO CARES WHERE IT CAME FROM?
THIS SHIRT IS THE FUNNIEST THING
I'VE SEEN IN MY LIFE!
>> LOOKS LIKE OUR SHIRT HAS A
REALLY GOOD BUZZ GOING.
>> Steven: YEAH, BUT I THINK
THEY THINK IT'S A JOKE.
>> HEH.
THE ONLY THING THAT'S
IMPORTANT IS THAT THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT IT.
THAT'S HOWREALART WORKS.
>> Steven: OH, WELL, I-I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> UH, HOW'S THIS?
>> HA HA HA. SO BAD.
>> OKAY!
LET'S GET STARTED WITH THE
FIRST LESSON!
HAVE A SEAT AND GRAB A --
WHERE YOU GOING?
OH, UH, I GUESS HE GOT AN
IMPORTANT TEXT OR SOMETHING.
>> Steven: HOW'S IT BEEN GOING
TODAY?
>> REALLY GREAT!
LOTS OF PEOPLE HAVE BEEN COMING
BY, THANKS TO YOUR T-SHIRTS,
LITTLE GUY.
>> Steven: THAT'S GREAT, DAD!
I'M REALLY GLAD I COULD HELP --
>> YOO-HOO! GUITAR DAD!
I JUST WANTED TO SAY I THINK
YOU'RE WONDERFUL AND HILARIOUS!
>> UH...THANK YOU?
HUH. THAT'S KIND OF STRANGE.
>> Steven: WHAT IS?
>> WELL, LOTS OF PEOPLE HAVE
STOPPED BY, BUT NO ONE'S
TAKEN A LESSON YET.
>> Steven: WHAT? REALLY?!
>> AH, MAYBE THEY'RE JUST
CHECKING OUT THE SCENE BEFORE
THEY COME BACK TO GET AREAL
LESSON!
[ STRUMMING ]
>> Steven: BUCK!
>> HEY, THERE'S MY MAIN MAN.
>> Steven: THE SHIRTS AREN'T
WORKING, BUCK!
>> YEAH, THEY ARE.
PEOPLE LOVE 'EM.
>> Steven: BUT NOBODY WANTS
GUITAR LESSONS FROM MY DAD!
>> THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
THEN WHATISTHE POINT?
>> THE POINT IS, IT'S AN
AMAZING SHIRT.
>> Steven: AW, MY DRAWING'S
NOTTHATGOOD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> YEAH, NO.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
>> THAT'S WHAT'S SO GREAT ABOUT
IT.
YOUR WORK IS SO NAIVE.
YOU REALLY LOVE YOUR DAD.
IT'S FUNNY.
>> Steven: I...I DON'T WANT TO
MAKE THESE SHIRTS ANYMORE.
>> TOO BAD, STEVEN.
IT'S SO CURRENT, YOU CAN'T STOP
IT.
I'M A TASTE MAKER, AND I'M GONNA
KEEP MAKING TASTES...
FOREVER.
>> Steven: FOREVER?
>> WELL, FOREVER, AFTER I GO
TO MY DAD'S LAME BENCH
COMMEMORATION.
PEACE.
>> Steven: [ PANTING ]
GARNET! PEARL! AMETHYST!
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> Pearl: WHAT IS IT?!
>> Amethyst: WHOA, WHERE'S THE
FIRE?!
>> Steven: IT'S AN EMERGENCY!
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME GET RID OF
ALL THE SHIRTS AND STOP BUCK
FROM MAKING MORE!
>> Pearl: HAVE THE SHIRTS COME
TO LIFE AND POSSESSED THE BODIES
OF THEIR WEARERS?
>> Steven: NO, THEY JUST --
>> Amethyst: ARE PEOPLE CATCHING
ON FIRE WHEN THEY PUT ON THE
MAGIC SHIRTS?
>> Steven: NO, NO, TH-THEY'RE
JUST --
>> Pearl: ARE THE SHIRTS
DESTROYING THE WEARERS' WILLS TO
CONTINUE ON IN THIS MORTAL COIL,
THEREBY SHUTTING DOWN
BEACH CITY?!
>> Steven: NO!!
THEY'RE...[SIGHS] THEY'RE JUST
USING MY ART IN A WAY I DON'T
AGREE WITH.
>> Pearl: OH.
>> Garnet: EH, WE'LL PASS.
>> Steven: WHAT?!
BUT...BUT, I REALLY NEED YOUR
HELP!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THIS SOUNDS
LIKE A VERY ABSTRACT PROBLEM.
>> Amethyst: IT'S NOT SOMETHING
WE CAN PUNCH.
>> Garnet: YOU MUST LEARN TO
HELP YOURSELF.
THAT'S HOW YOU BECOME STRONGER.
>> Amethyst: GOOD POINT, GOOD
POINT.
>> Pearl: OH, ABSOLUTELY.
>> Steven: BUT!
>> Amethyst: YOU'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT, STEVEN!
>> Pearl: YES, WHY NOT DUST OFF
THOSE CONFLICT-RESOLUTION
SKILLS!
>> Garnet: LET YOUR PROBLEM BE
KNOWN.
THEN YOU CAN WORK TOWARDS AN
UNDERSTANDING.
>> Steven: OH, I'LL MAKE HIM
UNDERSTAND.
I'LL MAKE THEM ALL UNDERSTAND!
>> Amethyst: EH, HE'LL BE FINE.
>> OKAY.
IS EVERYONE HERE?
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
HELLO!
I WAS SUPPOSED TO WRITE A SPEECH
TO, UM, COMMEMORATE THIS, UH,
NEW BENCH, BUT WHAT HAD HAPPENED
WAS I RAN OUT OF PRINTER INK IN
MY PRINTER THAT I KEEP AT HOME.
SO, I WENT TO THE STORE AND
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT?
THEY DIDN'T CARRY THE BRAND I
WAS LOOKING FOR, SO...
>> Steven: Bye!
>> ...I CALLED UP A BUDDY OF
MINE WHO OWED ME A...
[ Speaking in slow motion ] FEW
POLITICAL FAVORS, AND HE WASN'T
HOME!
>> [ Speaking in slow motion ]
LOOK OUT!
NO! AAH!
[ ALL YELLING ]
>> [ Normal voice ] I'VE BEEN...
SHIRT!
BUCK...
DID YOU MAKE THIS?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
THIS SHIRT IS GENIUS!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
THIS IS WAY FUNNIER THAN
GUITAR DAD!
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> THIS BENCH IS ACTUALLY PRETTY
COMFORTABLE.
>> Steven: ANYONE ELSE STOP BY
FOR LESSONS TODAY?
>> SO FAR, NO, BUT, I'M SURE
IT'LL PICK UP TOMORROW!
>> Steven: YEAH, I'M SURE IT
WILL.
THIS IS FOR YOU, BY THE WAY.
THIS IS THE LAST ONE, SO IT'S
SUPER-LIMITED EDITION!
>> AW, SWEET!
THANKS, STEVEN!
>> YO, STEVEN, JUST WANTED TO
SAY, UH, I'M SORRY FOR WHAT I
DID AND UH...
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY, BUCK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY ANY MORE
THAN THAT.
>> YOU'RE A COOL CAT,
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
HEY, MISTER "U."?
>> YOU WANT TO TAKE A PICTURE
WITH ME OR SOME JUNK?
>> NO WAY, MAN.
I WANT A LESSON...FROM
GUITAR DAD!
[ CAMERA CLICKS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU BLINKED!
LET'S JUST TAKE
ANOTHER ONE.
OH, WAIT.
WHAT IF WE GET A SHOT WITH
THE BEAUTIFUL VIEW BEHIND US?
COME ON, STEVEN!
SAY "CHEESE."
Both: CHEESE!
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
DID IT DO IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
PRESS IT AGAIN.
I'VEBEENPRESSING IT.
[ JAMIE CHUCKLES ]
YOU GUYS LOOK CUTE.
JAMIE!
WHAT'S UP, STEVEN?
LONG TIME NO SEE.
OH...MY...GOSH!
[ LAUGHS ]
JAMIE,
THIS IS CONNIE.
GREETINGS, CONNIE.
SO, WHERE YOU BEEN AT?
OH, YOU KNOW,
JUST SPENT SOME TIME
WHERE ALL THE BIG PICTURES
ARE MADE.
UH, WHERE'S THAT?
JUST A LITTLE PLACE
CALLED...
KANNNNSAS.
OH! ARE YOU
AN ASPIRING THESPIAN?
WHY, A-YES, I AM.
WOW. I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WANTED TO BE AN ACTOR.
THAT'S BECAUSE...
I'M VERY GOOD AT ACTING.
[ LAUGHS ]
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE WEARING
THOSE COOL GLASSES
THAT SAY "MOVIE STAR"?
UH...WELL...NO.
I JUST BOUGHT THESE
AT A SOUVENIR SHOP.
I MISSED BEING
A REGULAR OLD MAILMAN,
SO I JUST CAME BACK.
AND, UH, YOU GOT A LOT OF MAIL
WHILE I WAS GONE.
LOOKS LIKE THE POSTAL SERVICE
HAS BEEN SLACKING OFF.
JAMIE'S THE ONLY MAILMAN
THAT KNOWS WHERE I LIVE.
I'M GONNA NEED
A LOT OF SIGNATURES, AS WELL.
YOUR KNUCKLES
ARE SO QUIET.
MY HANDS ARE POLITE.
OH. GARNET.
HI, GARNET!
HELLO, GARNET!
WHO'S GAR-NEHHHHHHHHHHH?
EEEEEEEEHHH.
HOWDY.
WHATCHA UP TO,
GARNET?
I WAS JUST
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN
CHECKING FOR SIGNS
OF LAPIS AND JASPER.
ANY LUCK?
NOPE.
WOW.
HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO SWIM
TO THE BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN?
IT WAS EASY.
I'M A REALLY GOOD SWIMMER.
EXCUSE ME.
[ GASPS ]
Connie: UH, STEVEN,
WHY DID YOU RECEIVE
SO MANY BOXES OF SEA PALS?
UH, I ORDERED ONE AT FIRST,
BUT IT NEVER SHOWED UP.
SO I KEPT ORDERING.
ARE YOU GOING TO
START A FARM?
[ LAUGHS ] NO.
I'M GONNA SET THEM FREE.
INTO THE SEA!
JAMIE!
H-HI. STEVEN.
YOU DIDN'T
BRING MORE SEA PALS?
WHAT?
NO, I JUST CAME TO, UH...
UHHH...UM...
WHAT'S THAT?
UHH, IT'S...UHH...
HERE!
BUT WHAT IS...IT?
JAMIE!
[ BREATHING RAPIDLY ]
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WHOOP, WHOOP, WHOOP, WHOOP,
WHOOP, WHOOP, WHOOP, WHOOP!
[ BOTH PANTING ]
GARNET! GARNET!
GARNET!
THE MOST UNBELIEVABLE THING
HAS HAPPENED!
YOU'LL ABSOLUTELY DIE
OF SHOCK!
I'M BUSY, STEVEN.
BUT YOU GOT A LETTER!
READ IT.
"TO GARNET..."
Jamie:"WHEN I SAW YOU RISE
LIKE AN ANCIENT SEA NYMPH,
A WHITE-HOT STEEL PIERCED
THE DEEPEST ARTERY
OF MY BEING -- YOU.
YOU ARE A CARDIAC SURGEON,
AND I AM
YOUR TRANSPLANT PATIENT.
AND YOU STAND POISED
OVER MY CHEST,
HOLDING MY STILL-BEATING HEART,
HESITATING, WAITING, WONDERING.
SO I IMPLORE YOU
TO JOIN ME FOR DINNER,
OR MAYBE LUNCH
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP IT CASUAL,
NEXT FRIDAY AT THE CRAB SHACK.
I AWAIT YOUR RESPONSE,
AS THE CAMELLIA AWAITS
THE RISE OF THE MOON.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT ONLY
BLOOMS AT NIGHT AND STUFF.
"LOVE, JAMIE."
I THINK JAMIE
IS ASKING YOU OUT --
ON A DATE!
WELL,
THAT AIN'T HAPPENING.
NOPE.
WHY NOT?
GARNET IS ALREADY
IN A RELATIONSHIP.
WAIT, REALLY?
WELL, YEAH.
SHEISA RELATIONSHIP.
OH, YOU MEAN,
'CAUSE SHE'S A FUSION.
RUBY AND SAPPHIRE
ARE SO CLOSE
THAT THEY CAN'T STAND
TO BE APART.
SO I GUESS THIS DATE WITH JAMIE
IS OUT OF THE QUESTION.
THREE'S A CROWD.
BUT, GUYS,
JAMIE PUT SO MUCH THOUGHT
INTO THIS LETTER!
IT WOULD BE RUDE
NOT TO REPLY!
OKAY, GARNET,
IT MIGHT BE BEST
TO PLAY OFF
THE TONE OFHISLETTER
AND START OFF WITH SOMETHING
LIKE, "DEAREST JAMIE."
OKAY,
GO FOR IT, GARNET.
START WITH
THE LETTER "N."
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY. WHAT NEXT?
UH...THE LETTER "O."
UH, OKAY.
YOU CAN JUST
SAY THE WHOLE WORD
INSTEAD
OF SPELLING IT OUT.
PERIOD.
SO, "N," "O," PERIOD?
OHHH.
I THINK WE'LL NEED
MORE THAN THAT.
"THE END. FOREVER.
AND EVEN AFTER THAT."
"YOURS TRULY, GARNET."
HMM.
AT LEAST IT'S HONEST
AND TO THE POINT.
WHERE DO YOU THINK
HE COULD BE?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE COULD BE
DROPPING OFF MAIL
HALFWAY AROUND THE WORLD
BY NOW.
THERE HE IS!
Steven: JAMIE.
OH, HEY,
CONNIE AND STEVEN.
YOU GUYS COME OUT HERE
TO STARE AT THE OCEAN
AND THINK ABOUT LIFE, TOO?
UH...NO?
WE CAME TO, UH --
YEAH.
LIFE IS CRAZY.
ONE DAY, YOU'RE RIGHT HERE
IN BEACH CITY, DELIVERING MAIL,
AND THEN
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE
ON A BUS TO KANSAS
FOLLOWING YOUR DREAMS
OF BECOMING AN ACTOR.
"FOLLOW YOUR DREAMS,"
THEY SAID.
BUT NO ONE SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT ALL THE REJECTION AND
SADNESS THERE WAS TO BE FOUND.
SO MANY AUDITIONS
DAY AFTER DAY.
SO MUCH REJECTION
THAT'S WHY I CAME BACK.
ONE MORE REJECTION WOULD HAVE
DESTROYED MY FRAGILE HEART.
[ WHIMPERS ]
SORRY.
SOMETIMES, I GET CAUGHT UP
IN THE DRAMA ZONE, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, RIGHT.
DRAMA ZONE.
OH, BY THE WAY,
WE HAVE SOMETHING FOR Y--
NO, WE DON'T!
HOW CAN WE GIVE THIS LETTER
TO JAMIE NOW?
HE MIGHT GET UPSET.
HMMM.
WE CAN MAKE ADJUSTMENTS.
WE CAN MATCH
JAMIE'S POETIC LANGUAGE
AND LET HIM DOWN EASY.
I WATCHED SOME EPISODES
OF A TORRID SOAP OPERA ONCE,
SO I'M CONFIDENT
THAT I GET THE GIST OF ROMANCE.
EHHH...
THERE!
"DEAR JAMIE...
YOU, DEAR CAMELLIA,
EXPECTANTLY AWAIT
THE LIGHT OF MY MOON,
YET MY LIGHT
IS MORE OF A SCORCHING,
WILTING, DRY DESERT HEAT.
AND AS
YOUR METAPHORICAL SURGEON,
IT IS WITH A HEAVY HEART
THAT I URGE YOU
TO SEEK A SECOND OPINION.
I RETURN
YOUR HEART TO YOU" --
"ALSO,
YOUR HAIR IS NICE."
"HAIR...IS...
NICE.
YOURS,
BUT NOT REALLY, GARNET."
PERFECT.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
[ VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYS ]
Jamie: [ In distance ]
GARNET!
HUH?
WHERE ART THOU,
MY SWEET SCORCHING SUNBEAM?
OH, NO!
GARNET!
I READ THINE LETTER,
AND I UNDERSTAND!
THOU HAST
RETURNETH MINE HEART!
WHAT?!
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT --
GARNET, YOU LIKE MY HAIR
JUST AS I ADORE YOURS.
COME TO ME, GARNET.
JAMIE!
AH, YOUNG MASTER STEVEN!
PRAY THEE,
WHERE IS LADY GARNET?
SHE...
SHE'S N--
SHE'S NOT COMING.
BUT I'VE COME TO PROCLAIM
MY LOVE FOR MY WOMAN!
NO, JAMIE,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND! I --
GARNET!
YOU'VE COME!
YOU CAN TELL STEVEN ABOUT
ALL THE BEAUTIFUL THINGS
YOU WROTE TO ME
IN YOUR MISSIVE.
I DIDN'T WRITE THAT.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT HERE!
STAINED WITH TEARS OF JOY --
AND NOW ALSO RAIN.
MMMMM...
CONNIE AND I WROTE
THAT LETTER, JAMIE!
WHAT?
I'M SO SORRY, JAMIE.
WE JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU DOWN EASY.
[ Voice breaking ] WILST THOU
NOT SCORCH ME, MY DARLING SUN?
I AM NOT, NOR WILL I EVER BE,
INTERESTED.
GO AWAY!
[ GASPS ]
M-MY PANACHE!
[ SOBBING ]
JAMIEEEEE!
Connie: OH, BOY.
I FEEL SO BAD
FOR POOR JAMIE.
YEAH. BUT I'M SURE HE'LL BOUNCE
BACK FROM THIS IN NO TIME.
HE'S PROBABLY GONNA SHOW UP
WITH THE MAIL ANY MOMENT NOW.
YEAH.
Woman:
EXCUSE ME, KIDS.
I'M LOOKING FOR
THE HOME OF...
STEVEN UNIVERSE?
I'MTHE HOME
OF STEVEN UNIVERSE.
HEY,
YOU'RE GREG'S BOY.
I THOUGHT
JAMIE WAS PULLING MY LEG
WHEN HE TOLD ME
YOU WERE LIVING OVER HERE.
W-WAIT.
WHERE IS JAMIE?
AW, THAT POOR KID'S EMOTIONS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED.
WHAT?!
YEAH, HE'S A MESS!
SAID HE COULDN'T BEAR TO DELIVER
MAIL ON THIS ROUTE AGAIN
AFTER HAVING HIS LOVE
SPURNED.
HE SAID IT
JUST LIKE THIS.
LIKE -- LIKE,
WHEN HE'S IN THE DRAMA ZONE.
THEN HE CLENCHED HIS FIST
AND CLOSED HIS EYES LIKE THIS.
FULL OF DRAMA
TO THE END.
ANYWAY,
HERE'S A BOOK OF COUPONS.
HAVE A GOOD ONE!
[ WATER SLOSHES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
RAH!
[ BLUBBERING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SPLASH ]
YOU LOOK SAD.
WE REALLY MESSED UP
THIS TIME.
BECAUSE OF US,
JAMIE'S FEELING LOWER THAN EVER.
WE'VE SHATTERED THE MAN!
HE'LL NEVER LOVE AGAIN!
I'LL GO TALK TO HIM.
BUT YOUR WORDS
WILL DESTROY HIM!
CAN'T YOU JUST, LIKE,
ZAP HIS BRAIN
SO HE FORGETS
ANY OF THIS EVER HAPPENED?
[ SIGHS ]
Garnet: JAMIE.
GARNET.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO UPSET YOU.
THEN WILL YOU
GO OUT WITH ME?
NO!
BUT I'VE LOVED YOU
SINCE THE MOMENT I SAW YOU.
LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT
DOESN'T EXIST.
LOVE TAKES TIME,
AND LOVE TAKES WORK.
AT THE VERY LEAST, YOU HAVE TO
KNOWTHE OTHER PERSON.
AND YOULITERALLYHAVE NO IDEA
WHO OR WHAT I AM.
BUT I BLOOM FOR YOU, LIKE --
LIKE A CAMELLIA UNDER MOONLIGHT.
NO, YOU DON'T!
YOU MAKE A VERY CONVINCING
LOVESICK FOOL.
YOU CONVINCED THESE CHILDREN.
YOU EVEN CONVINCEDYOURSELF.
YOU'RE A FANTASTIC ACTOR.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO
DO NOW?
START
WITH LOCAL THEATER.
[ GASPS ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
THAT WAS
SOME PRETTY SOLID ADVICE.
WERE THOSE MORE LETTERS
YOU WROTE TO GARNET?
NO,
THAT WAS THE MAIL
I WAS SUPPOSED TO DELIVER
ON MY LAST ROUTE.
WE'LL HELP YOU
PICK IT ALL UP.
THANKS.
♪ IF I COULD BEGIN TO BE ♪
♪ HALF OF WHAT YOU THINK OF ME ♪
♪ I COULD DO ABOUT ANYTHING ♪
♪ I COULD EVEN LEARN
HOW TO LOVE LIKE YOU ♪