>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
>> ♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
>> NOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
THIS HAS TO BE A DREAM!
LARS! LARS!
PLEASE TELL ME I'M DREAMING!
>> GET OFF ME, MAN.
I'M STOCKING HERE.
>> I'M SORRY, STEVEN.
I GUESS THEY STOPPED MAKING
THEM.
>> Steven: STOPPED MAKING THEM?!
WHY IN THE WORLD WOULD THEY STOP
MAKING COOKIE CATS?!
THEY'RE ONLY THE MOST
SCRUMPTIOUS AND DELICIOUS
ICE-CREAM SANDWICH EVER MADE!
DON'T THEY HAVE LAWS FOR THIS?!
>> [ SIGHS ] TOUGH BITS, MAN.
NOBODY BUYS THEM ANYMORE.
I GUESS THEY COULDN'T COMPETE
WITH LION LICKERS.
>> Steven: [ GROANS ]
NOT LION LICKERS!
NOBODY LIKES THEM!
THEY DON'T EVEN LOOK LIKE LIONS!
KIDS THESE DAYS -- I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT!
>> WELL, IF YOU MISS YOUR WIMPY
ICE CREAM SO MUCH, WHY DON'T YOU
MAKE SOME WITH YOUR MAGIC BELLY
BUTTON?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Steven: THAT'S NOT HOW IT
WORKS, LARS.
RIGHT?
[ SQUISH! ]
[ SIGHS ]
OH, SWEET COOKIE CATS, WITH YOUR
CRUNCHY COOKIE OUTSIDE, YOUR ICY
CREAMY INSIDES, YOU WERE TOO
GOOD FOR THIS WORLD.
[ SMOOCHES ]
>> UH...STEVEN?
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE THE FREEZER
WITH YOU?
>> Steven: [ HUMMING ]
HEY, GUYS!
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: [ SCREAMS ]
>> Amethyst: 'SUP, STEVEN?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ MUNCHING, SCREECHING ]
>> Steven: AWESOME!
WHAT ARE THESE THINGS?
>> Pearl: UGH! SORRY, STEVEN.
WE'LL GET THESE CENTIPEETLES OUT
OF YOUR ROOM.
WE THINK THEY WERE TRYING TO GET
INTO THE TEMPLE.
>> Steven: AW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET RID OF
THEM.
THEY'RE REALLY COOL.
[ HISSES ]
>> [ SCREECHES ]
>> Amethyst: UM, YOU GUYS?
THESE THINGS DON'T HAVE GEMS.
>> Garnet: THAT MEANS THERE MUST
BE A MOTHER SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Pearl: WE SHOULD PROBABLY
FIND IT BEFORE ANYONE GETS HURT.
>> Steven: OOH! OOH!
CAN I COME?! CAN I?! CAN I?!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, UNTIL YOU
LEARN TO CONTROL THE POWERS IN
YOUR GEM, WE'LL TAKE CARE OF
PROTECTING HUMANITY, OKAY?
>> Steven: AW, MAN.
[ REFRIGERATOR DOOR OPENS ]
HEY! GET OUT OF THERE!
GO ON! SHOO! SHOO!
AW!
THEY GOT INTO EVERYTHING!
NOT COOL!
[ DING! DING! DING! DING! ]
NO WAY.
I-IT CAN'T BE!
WHA-- WHERE DID YOU GET THESE?!
I THOUGHT THEY STOPPED MAKING
THEM!
>> Pearl: WELL, WE HEARD THAT,
TOO, AND SINCE THEY'RE YOUR
FAVORITE...
>> Amethyst: WE WENT OUT AND
STOLE A BUNCH.
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
I WENT BACK AND PAID FOR THEM.
>> Garnet: THE WHOLE THING WAS
MY IDEA.
>> Amethyst: IT WAS EVERYONE'S
IDEA.
>> Garnet: NOT REALLY.
>> Pearl: ALL THAT MATTERS IS
THAT STEVEN IS HAPPY.
>> Steven: AHHHHHH!
♪ HE'S A FROZEN TREAT WITH AN
ALL-NEW TASTE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE CAME TO THIS PLANET
FROM OUTER SPACE ♪
♪ A REFUGEE OF AN INTERSTELLAR
WAR ♪
♪ BUT NOW HE'S AT YOUR LOCAL
GROCERY STORE ♪
♪ COOKIE CAT ♪
♪ HE'S A PET FOR YOUR TUMMY ♪
♪ HE'S SUPERDUPER YUMMY ♪
♪ COOKIE CAT ♪
♪ HE LEFT HIS FAMILY BEHIND ♪
♪ COOKIE CA-A-A-A-A-A-T ♪
NOW AVAILABLE AT GERGINS OFF
ROUTE 109.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS!
I'M GONNA SAVE THESE FOREVER...
RIGHT AFTER I EAT THIS ONE.
HELLO, OLD FRIEND.
MMM! MMM!
OOH! SO GOOD!
I LIKE TO EAT THE EARS FIRST.
>> Amethyst: UH, STEVEN.
>> Steven: WHA? MY GEM!
>> Amethyst: QUICK!
TRY AND SUMMON YOUR WEAPON!
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW HOW.
AAH! IT'S FADING!
HOW DO I MAKE IT COME BACK?!
>> Pearl: CALM DOWN, STEVEN.
BREATHE. DON'T FORCE IT.
>> Amethyst: YEAH.
AND TRY NOT TO POOP YOURSELF,
EITHER.
>> Garnet: PLEASE DON'T.
[ ALL SIGH ]
>> Steven: AW!
I WAS REALLY CLOSE THAT TIME!
CAN ONE OF YOU JUST EXPLAIN HOW
TO SUMMON A WEAPON?
>> Pearl: OH!
♪ I'LL GO FIRST ♪
[ CLASSICAL PIANO PLAYS ]
PAY ATTENTION TO THESE PETALS,
STEVEN.
THE PETAL'S DANCE SEEMS
IMPROVISED, BUT IT IS BEING
CALCULATED IN REAL TIME, BASED
ON THE PHYSICAL PROPERTIES OF
THIS PLANET.
WITH HARD WORK AND DEDICATION,
YOU CAN MASTER THE MAGICAL
PROPERTIES OF YOUR GEM AND
PERFORM YOUR OWN DANCE!
LIKE SO.
>> Steven: WAH!
>> Amethyst: DID PEARL TELL YOU
THE PETAL THING?
>> Steven: YEAH.
I NEED TO PRACTICE REALLY HARD
SO I CAN DANCE LIKE A TREE...
I THINK.
>> Amethyst: LISTEN, STEVEN.
ALL THAT PRACTICE STUFF IS NO
FUN.
WHENEVER I NEED TO SUMMON MY
WEAPON, IT JUST HAPPENS.
[ FUNKY MUSIC PLAYS ]
SEE? DIDN'T TRY AT ALL.
>> [ GASPS ] AGAIN?!
>> Steven: SO, I'M SUPPOSED TO
WORK REALLY HARD AND NOT TRY AT
ALL AT THE SAME TIME?
>> Garnet: YES.
[ WIND BLOWS ]
OR...
YOU CAN LINK YOUR MIND WITH THE
ENERGY OF ALL EXISTING MATTER,
CHANNELING THE COLLECTIVE POWER
OF THE UNIVERSE THROUGH YOUR
GEM, WHICH RESULTS IN...
AT LEAST THAT'S MY WAY OF DOING
IT.
>> Steven: I THINK MY BEST BET
IS TO RE-CREATE WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME MY GEM GLOWED.
SO...GARNET AND AMETHYST WERE
HERE.
PEARL WAS NEXT TO THE FRIDGE.
HMM. HMM.
AMETHYST, I THINK YOUR ARMS WERE
CROSSED.
>> Amethyst: OKAY, YOUR MAJESTY.
>> Steven: AND, PEARL, YOUR FOOT
WAS LIKE THIS.
>> Pearl: I DON'T THINK IT WORKS
THIS WAY, STEVEN.
>> Steven: AND, GARNET...
UH...UH...YEAH.
THEN I TOOK A BITE OF THIS
COOKIE CAT.
OH! WAIT! I SANG THE SONG FIRST.
UH, HE'S A FROZEN TREAT...ALL
NEW TASTE...INTERSTELLAR
WAR...AND NOW AVAILABLE AT
GERGINS.
AW! IT WAS FUNNIER LAST TIME!
[ SIGHS ]
MAYBE I'M NOT A REAL CRYSTAL
GEM.
>> Pearl: DON'T BE SILLY,
STEVEN.
OF COURSE YOU ARE.
>> Amethyst: AND YOU'RE FUN TO
HAVE AROUND, EVEN IF YOUR GEM IS
USELESS.
>> Pearl: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: I MEAN...YOU'RE ONE
OF US, STEVEN.
WE'RE NOT THE CRYSTAL GEMS
WITHOUT YOU.
>> Steven: YEAH.
EVEN IF I DON'T HAVE POWERS,
I'VE STILL GOT...COOKIE CAT!
MMM!
SO GOOD!
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, IT'S A SHIELD!
>> Steven: OH! WHAT?!
I GET A SHIELD?!
OH, YEAH!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
>> Steven: OH! COOKIE CAT!
I SUMMON MY WEAPON BY EATING ICE
CREAM!
>> Pearl: WHAT'S IN THESE
THINGS?
[ RUMBLING ]
>> [ SCREECHING, ROARING ]
>> Steven: WHAT WAS THAT?
>> Garnet: [ PANTING ]
>> [ GROWLING ]
>> Garnet: IT'S THE MOTHER.
[ GRUNTS ]
HUP! HUP!
>> Pearl: STAY IN THE HOUSE,
STEVEN.
>> Steven: NO WAY!
I'M COMING, TOO!
>> [ GROWLING ]
[ SNARLS ]
[ GROWLING ]
>> Amethyst: WE COULD REALLY USE
STEVEN'S SHIELD RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
>> Steven: HEY!
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Steven: LEAVE THEM ALONE!
>> Together: STEVEN! NO!
>> Steven: COOKIE CAT
CRYSTAL-COMBO POWERS, ACTIVATE!
MMM! MMM! MMM!
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Steven: MMM! MMM! MMM!
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: MMM.
UH-OH.
AAH!
>> Pearl: WE NEED TO SAVE
STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: CAN WE SAVE
OURSELVES FIRST?
>> Steven: GOODBYE, MY FRIENDS.
[ GURGLING ]
WHY ISN'T IT WORKING?!
>> [ SNARLS ]
[ ROARS ]
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
NO.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
[ GASPS ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
COOKIE CAT, HE'S A PET FOR YOUR
TUMMY.
COOKIE CAT, HE'S SUPERDUPER
YUMMY!
COOKIE CAT!
HE LEFT HIS FAMILY BEHIND!
COOKIE CA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-T!
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
>> Steven: NOW AVAILABLE...
NOWHERE.
>> Amethyst: YES!
>> Garnet: GEMS. WEAPONS.
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
>> Garnet: LET'S DO IT.
[ ALL GRUNT ]
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
>> Steven: FAREWELL, SWEET
COOKIE CATS.
I'LL ALWAYS REMEMBER THE TIME WE
SPENT TOGETHER.
[ GURGLING ]
Shh. HUSH NOW.
>> Amethyst: ARE YOU CRYING?
>> Steven: ONLY A LITTLE!
>> Amethyst: WELL, I GUESS YOUR
POWERS DON'T COME FROM ICE
CREAM.
>> Pearl: OF COURSE THEY DON'T
COME FROM ICE CREAM.
DON'T WORRY, STEVEN.
I'M SURE SOMEDAY YOU'LL FIGURE
OUT HOW TO ACTIVATE YOUR GEM.
>> Garnet: YES.
IN YOUR OWN STEVENY WAY.
>> Steven: I'M OKAY, GUYS.
I JUST --
[ GURGLES ]
[ GAGS ]
I-I THINK I ATE TOO MANY
COOKIE CATS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ VOMITS ]
[ PANTING ]
HEY, FRYMAN!
GIVE ME THE BITS!
>> STEVEN, WE'RE CLOSED.
>> Steven: OHH, WHAT?
>> Amethyst: GIVE HIM THE BITS.
THE BITS!
>> Both: THE BITS!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
TAKE IT EASY ON THE COUNTER,
WILL YA?
>> Both: YES!
>> I CAN GIVE YOU ACTUAL FRIES,
IF YOU WANT.
>> Steven: JUST THE BITS,
PLEASE.
THANKS.
[ BOTH CHOMPING ]
AHH, SUNSET -- MY FAVORITE TIME
OF DAY, WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN
AND THE SECOND SUN GETS BIGGER
AND BIGGER IN THE SKY.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH, THAT BIG, HOT SECOND SU--
[ GASPS ]
OH, NO.
WHAT IS THAT DOING HERE?
>> Steven: [ CHOMPING ]
WHAT IS IT?
AAH! MY BITS!
>> Garnet: THIS IS BAD.
>> Pearl: LOOK AT THE SIZE OF
IT.
I HAD NO IDEA THESE THINGS WERE
SO BIG!
>> Amethyst: GARNET! PEARL!
>> Pearl: WE SAW.
SOME OF US ARE TRYING TO PROTECT
HUMANITY.
WHERE WERE YOU?
>> Amethyst: EATING FRY BITS.
>> Pearl: UGH.
>> Steven: CAN I SEE?
WHOA.
IT'S A GIANT EYEBALL!
AWESOME!
>> Pearl: NOT AWESOME!
IT'S A RED EYE!
>> Steven: A RED EYE?!
IT'S GOING TO INFECT US ALL!
>> Garnet: THAT'S PINKEYE,
STEVEN.
>> Amethyst: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Pearl: IT'S GOING TO CRASH
INTO BEACH CITY AND CRUSH US,
ALONG WITH A BUNCH OF OBLIVIOUS,
INNOCENT PEOPLE.
WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
>> Steven: WHAT ARE WE GOING TO
DO?
>> Garnet: THE ONLY THING
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO DESTROY IT IS
A LIGHT CANNON THAT BELONGED TO
ROSE QUARTZ.
>> Steven: MY MOM?
>> Amethyst: IF ROSE WERE HERE,
THIS WOULD BE SO EASY.
>> Pearl: I KNOW, BUT SHE'S NOT,
AND THE CANNON IS MISSING.
WE'LL HAVE TO FIND ANOTHER
SOLUTION.
>> Steven: IF IT BELONGED TO MY
MOM, I BET MY DAD KNOWS WHERE IT
IS.
HE CAN HELP US SAVE THE DAY!
HUH? EH?
>> Pearl: GREG IS...NICE,
STEVEN, BUT I DOUBT ROSE WOULD
ENTRUST SOMEONE LIKE HIM WITH
SUCH A POWERFUL WEAPON.
>> Amethyst: YOUR DAD IS KIND OF
A MESS, STEVEN.
>> Pearl: AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: I'M JUST SAYING.
EVEN IF SHE DID LEAVE IT WITH
HIM, HE PROBABLY BROKE IT OR
LOST IT OR DROPPED IT IN THE
OCEAN BY NOW.
>> Garnet: TRUE.
>> Steven: NO WAY!
I'M SURE HE'S JUST KEEPING IT
SOMEWHERE SAFE.
I'LL GO ASK HIM.
>> Garnet: WE CAN HANDLE THIS,
STEVEN.
READY?
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Amethyst: AA-A-A-A-A-H!
[ THUDS ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
UH, I'M GONNA GO.
>> Pearl: OKAY, GOOD LUCK.
>> Steven: DAD, IT'S ME!
DAD?
ARE YOU IN THERE?
WAKE...UP!
WE HAVE TO SAVE THE WORLD!
[ GRUNTS ]
DAD!
AAH!
[ CAR ALARM BLARING ]
>> WHO'S THERE?!
I HAVE A WAFFLE IRON!
>> Steven: DAD, IT'S ME!
[ WAFFLE IRON CLATTERS ]
[ BLARING CONTINUES ]
[ ALARM CHIRPS ]
>> STEVEN?
>> Steven: [ GRUNTS ]
>> I ALMOST WAFFLED YOUR FACE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP SO LATE?
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE SUN JUST WENT DOWN AN HOUR
AGO.
>> OH. [ CHUCKLES ]
IT WAS A SLOW DAY AT THE CAR
WASH.
ANYWAY, WHAT'S UP?
JUST NEEDED TO SEE YOUR OLD MAN,
PAL AROUND, LEARN SOME LESSONS
ABOUT LIFE?
>> Steven: NO!
I NEED THE LIGHT CANNON THAT
BELONGED TO MOM TO BLOW UP THAT
EYEBALL!
>> EYEBALL?
>> Steven: THAT!
>> Amethyst: AA-A-A-A-A-H!
[ THUDS ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
>> WAIT.
IS THAT A MAGICAL THING?
THE GEMS TOLD ME NOT TO GET
INVOLVED WITH MAGIC STUFF.
IT -- IT COULD BE DANGEROUS OR
INTERFERE WITH WHAT'S LEFT OF MY
HAIR.
>> Steven: BUT THEY NEED MOM'S
CANNON.
YOU'VE GOT TO KNOW WHERE IT IS!
LIKE A CAVE DUNGEON OR A CLOUD
FORTRESS OR IN A CLAM AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE OCEAN.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL
THAT, BUT I HAVE AN IDEA WHERE
IT MIGHT BE.
>> Steven: A MAGICAL STORAGE
UNIT!
>> HUH. NOT EXACTLY.
BUT SOME WOULD SAY THERE'S MAGIC
INSIDE.
IT'S JUST A SHED I USE TO KEEP
THINGS THAT DON'T FIT IN THE
VAN.
IF IT'S ANYWHERE...
IT'LL BE IN HERE.
>> Steven: IF I'M GOING IN
THERE, I'M GONNA NEED SOME GEAR.
HERE I GO!
>> GOOD LUCK.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
COOL!
IT'S LIKE A DAD MUSEUM!
[ GRUNTS ]
HUH?
THERE IT IS!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA! UGH!
DO YOU GOLF?
>> AH, I LIKE TO THINK OF
MYSELF AS SOMEONE WHO WOULD
GOLF...EVENTUALLY.
>> Steven: HMM?
YES!
[ CLATTERING ]
A DRUM.
[ DRUM THUDS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
NO.
[ GASPS ] OH, MY GOSH!
OH, MY GOSH! OH, MY GOSH!
IS THIS...?
"BUY T-SHIRT CANNONS"?
HEY, THERE'S A BUNCH OF COPIES
OF YOUR OLD CD!
>> HUH. OH, MAN.
I COULDN'T GIVE THOSE THINGS
AWAY.
YOU KNOW, BEFORE I RAN THE CAR
WASH, WHEN I WAS A ONE-MAN BAND,
I TRAVELED THE WHOLE COUNTRY.
>> Steven: I KNOW, DAD.
>> WHEN I CAME TO PLAY A CONCERT
HERE IN BEACH CITY, NO ONE
SHOWED UP EXCEPT...
>> Steven: AN ALLIGATOR!
>> NO, IT WAS YOUR MOTHER.
>> Steven: [ Chuckling ] I KNOW.
>> AND WE WERE ALWAYS TOGETHER
AFTER THAT, UNTIL SHE GAVE UP
HER PHYSICAL FORM TO BRING YOU
INTO THE WORLD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT A MAGIC LADY
LIKE HER EVER SAW IN A PLAIN,
OLD DOPE LIKE ME.
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
UH, DAD?
I BROKE A PHOTO.
>> IT'S OKAY, BUDDY.
IF EVERY PORK CHOP WERE PERFECT,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE HOT DOGS.
[ LOW RUMBLING ]
>> Steven: HUH?
[ GASPS ]
THE LIGHT CANNON!
>> OH, BOY.
THAT THING'S GIVING ME THE
WILLIES.
>> Steven: DAD, I FOUND IT!
>> REALLY?
>> Steven: GET THE VAN!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL ]
[ BOTH PANTING ]
THIS THING COULD SAVE THE CITY!
WE'VE GOT TO GET IT TO THE
BEACH!
>> HOW?
IT'S TOO BIG FOR THE VAN.
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
EASY DOES IT.
[ CANNON CRASHES ]
>> Steven: IS IT GONNA BE OKAY?
>> MM.
IF EVERY PORK CHOP WERE
PERFECT...
>> Steven: WE WOULDN'T HAVE HOT
DOGS!
>> THAT THING'S GETTING HUGE.
IT'S FREAKING ME OUT.
>> Steven: CAN'T THE VAN GO ANY
FASTER?
[ ENGINE REVS ]
>> THIS IS FASTER!
>> Steven: DON'T WORRY.
COME ON. LET'S PUT ON YOUR CD.
>> WHAT? REALLY?
UH, COME ON, YOU'VE HEARD IT.
>> Steven: YOU COME ON.
[ GUITAR RIFF PLAYS ]
>> ♪ I KNOW I'M NOT THAT TALL ♪
♪ I KNOW I'M NOT THAT SMART ♪
♪ BUT -- ♪
>> ♪ LET ME DRIVE MY VAN INTO
YOUR HEART ♪
♪ I KNOW I'M NOT THAT RICH ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO GET MY START ♪
♪ SO, LET ME DRIVE MY VAN INTO
YOUR HEART ♪
♪ LET ME DRIVE MY VAN INTO YOUR
HEART ♪
♪ AND IF WE LOOK OUT OF PLACE ♪
♪ WELL, BABY, THAT'S OKAY ♪
♪ I'LL DRIVE US INTO OUTER
SPACE ♪
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
THROW ME AGAIN.
I THINK I'M CRACKING IT.
>> ♪ I KNOW I DON'T HAVE A
PLAN ♪
>> Steven: HEY, GUYS!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
HE REALLY HAD IT.
>> Amethyst: WE'RE SAVED!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> All: WHOA!
>> ♪ ...MY VAN INTO YOUR HEART ♪
♪ LET ME DRIVE MY VAN INTO YOUR
HEART ♪
>> WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
EASY!
>> ♪ ...INTO YOUR HEART ♪
♪ LET ME DRIVE MY VAN INTO YOUR
HEART ♪
>> Garnet: WE HAVE TO USE IT
NOW.
>> Pearl: I DON'T KNOW HOW IT
WORKS!
IT WAS ROSE'S!
>> Steven: DAD, HOW DO WE USE
IT?
>> MM.
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THIS IS
SERIOUS.
THE GEM!
YOU HAVE ROSE'S GEM!
>> Amethyst: THAT'S IT!
>> Steven: AAH!
>> Amethyst: UGH! COME ON!
>> Garnet: STOP THAT.
>> Pearl: IT'S NO USE.
>> Amethyst: FINE! FORGET IT!
THROW ME AGAIN!
>> Pearl: THAT'S NOT GOING TO
WORK!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> I GOT THIS.
NO! WAIT!
NO, MAYBE I DON'T!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: PLEASE WORK.
UNLOCK. ACTIVATE. GO.
PLEASE?
EVERYONE'S COUNTING ON YOU!
YOU CAN'T JUST BE USELESS!
I KNOW YOU CAN HELP!
>> IT'S OKAY, STEVEN!
WE'LL FIGURE OUT SOMETHING ELSE,
SOMETHING EVEN BETTER!
>> Steven: R-RIGHT!
IF EVERY PORK CHOP WERE PERFECT,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE HOT DOGS.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Pearl: IT'S WORKING!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
>> Amethyst: THIS IS IT!
>> Garnet: BRACE YOURSELVES!
[ WHIRRING INTENSIFIES ]
[ PEOPLE SCREAMING ]
[ CAR ALARM BLARING ]
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, YOU JUST
SAVED MOST OF BEACH CITY!
>> Steven: SORRY ABOUT THAT!
>> WHAT?!
>> Pearl: HOW DID YOU GET IT TO
WORK?
>> Steven: I JUST SAID THAT
THING THAT DAD ALWAYS SAYS.
>> Pearl: THAT THING ABOUT PORK
RINDS?
>> Garnet: HOT DOGS.
>> ROSE.
[ ALL GASP ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
MY VAN!
>> Steven: IT'S OKAY, DAD.
IF EVERY PORK CHOP WERE
PERFECT --
>> I LIVE IN THERE!
>> Steven: WAIT UP!
>> GEEZ!
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> WAIT! WAIT!
>> Steven: OH, GEEZ.
>> [ GROANS ]