♪ We ♪
♪ Are the Crystal Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven:
♪ And if you think we can't ♪
♪ We'll always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Amethyst:
Let me get this straight.
Rose Quartz,
leader of the Crystal Gems,
Steven's mom,
was actually
Pink Diamond.
She faked her own shattering
and reformed to be
Rose all the time.
Pink Diamond's
final command to me
was that no one could know,
but now that Steven does, I can
finally tell you all everything.
Whew!
I mean, a pink lion,
a pink sword
and now a pink Diamond?
If you told me
Rose invented cotton candy,
I'd believe it.
Right, Garnet?
Garnet?
Rose.
She -- she...
[ Groaning ]
-Sapphire.
-She lied to us.
She lied about everything.
She held our hands,
looked us right in the eyes
and told us to never question
who we are as Garnet.
We never questioned
ourselves or her.
We couldn't have known.
No.
You couldn't have known.
You never know
what's going on.
That's what I'm for.
-Sapphire.
But I never looked
into her.
I trusted her.
I let her
make fools of us all.
Sapphire, wait!
Guys!
What?!
Please.
We could just stay calm
and talk about this,
right?
Let's just talk.
-Talk about what?
How our relationship
is based on a lie?
What else
is there to say?
Ruby, I'm so sorry.
Come on, Pearl.
Help me explain
everything to Sapphire.
Right.
Sit tight, Ruby.
We'll go and get Sapphire.
Okay.
Maybe she's here.
Steven: Sapphire!
Sapphire: Everything
we were running from,
she was right there all along,
using us for her little war,
smiling at us with
those knowing eyes,
making me believe in a better
future that I couldn't see
because it wasn't real,
and now, here we are, our
friends shattered and corrupted.
Of course she was Diamond.
What a long road she took
to torture us like this.
It wasn't like this.
You know she didn't
want anyone to get hurt.
I don't know that.
I clearly don't know anything.
Pearl: You deserve
to know everything.
I was given to Pink Diamond
just a few thousand years
before she was given
the Earth.
I was supposed
to make her happy.
I just never could.
Could you imagine
that running a colony
would be this dull?
I could imagine it if you would
like me to, my Diamond.
Show me the status
of the prime kindergarten.
Yes, my Diamond.
The first Quartz soldiers
are due to emerge soon.
-[ Gasps ]
-Oh.
Finally,
something exciting!
Hurry!
We've got to see this.
Quickly! Turn it on.
Yes, my Diamond.
Look at this, Pearl.
We're creating life
from nothing.
Welcome to Earth.
[ Sighs ] I wish
I could just be there.
I'll have us warped into
the kindergarten at once,
my Diamond.
-What? No. No.
If I went down
to the kindergarten,
I would never hear the end
of it from Yellow and Blue.
Oh, but could you
imagine me down there,
laughing and playing
with the Amethysts?
Of course I can,
my Diamond.
You look so happy.
I won't be so happy
when Blue and Yellow find out.
-They won't find out.
-How's that?
Because you look
just like a Quartz.
You changed your
shape for a day.
That's brilliant, Pearl.
I'm glad I was
able to help, my Di...
Down here.
Pearl, look.
This is incredible!
We got to get down there
and check it out.
Wha?!
♪♪
-Pearl, this is so...
-Out of my way!
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
These Amethyst guards
can be so rude.
But, Pearl, don't you see
what's happening?
Huh?
We're actually here,
and I am fitting right in.
None of that dumb salute.
Thank you so much
for talking me into this.
I couldn't have
done this on my own.
Uh...you're welcome,
my Diamond.
Shh. Pearl, you're going
to get us in trouble.
Sorry, my Quartz.
Hey, fellow Amethyst guards.
What are we all up to?
There's two more from our unit
that haven't emerged yet,
so we're going
to wait for them.
Here comes one of them.
Oh, wow. Look at you.
Welcome to Earth.
That is the first
and nicest thing anyone
has ever said to me.
What's going on here?
Our orders were to move out
as soon as you emerged!
But 8XM hasn't emerged yet.
She can catch up
with us later.
Go! Go! Go!
-Hup! Hup! Hup!
Pearl:
My Diamond, please.
Let's not draw any more
attention ourselves
than we already have.
Oh. You're right, but things
were getting really fun.
What if we took
some time to explore
some of Earth's
other features?
Pearl, you're so smart.
So it was all just so she could
get out and have some fun?
Well,
that's how it started.
So this is Earth.
And this is just a small portion
of the resources available
for making gems
on this planet.
I have to see it all.
♪♪
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Is everything all right,
my Diamond?
You seem troubled.
All this life that's been
growing wild here on Earth,
none of it will
survive my invasion.
We're not creating
life from nothing.
We're taking life
and leaving nothing behind.
[ Thunder crashing ]
Forgive me, my Diamond.
I shouldn't have brought you
to such a place.
No.
I needed to see this.
So she did want
to protect Earth.
She didn't realize
what the colony
was doing to the planet.
So what? She suddenly started
to care about Earth?
Why did she have to
rope us into all this?
Why couldn't she just stop
the colonization herself?
She tried.
When she told
the other Diamonds
she didn't want to go
through with the colony,
they told her to finish
what she started.
When she told
the other Diamonds
she wanted to preserve
life on Earth,
they created the Zoo and threw
a handful of humans in.
She did everything
she could as Pink Diamond,
but her status meant
nothing to Blue and Yellow,
so she decided
to make a stand
as someone
they couldn't ignore.
She was going to scare
every Gem off the planet,
but everything changed
when she saw your fusion.
♪♪
Rose:
I still can't believe it.
Only on Earth,
don't you think?
where anything can happen.
A fusion of two
completely different Gems.
Can all Gems do that?
How have I
never heard of this?
I've only ever heard
that it's unheard of.
Can you imagine
what that must feel...
Fusion activate!
Whoa!
Oh. I thought if a Ruby
and a Sapphire,
but you're a Diamond.
Forgive me.
What am I doing?
I need to be replaced
immediately.
No.
But I've been
imagining things.
Even when you
haven't asked me to,
I imagined that I ran away
and met you here on Earth,
a Rose Quartz,
and I'm not yours,
but I make you
so happy anyway.
Isn't that ridiculous?
Tell me to stop.
Please don't ever stop.
♪♪
This is very not allowed.
[ Gasps ] That fusion.
We never should have left
her there with Blue.
Who knows what sort of
horrible punishment...
[ Rustling ]
Ouch. Aah!
We didn't mean to fuse.
Well, we did this time.
We'll unfuse.
We'll...we'll...we'll...
No. No. Please.
I'm glad
to see you again.
Pearl: Before Garnet,
Rose was only fighting
for Earth,
but Garnet
changed everything.
Rose wanted
to fight for her.
She wanted
to fight for Gems,
and maybe, she was foolish
and maybe even selfish,
but she was...
-Following us.
-What?
This whole time, we thought
we were following her,
but she was following us.
How could she not after
you swept her off her feet?
Wha-- what? Me?
Steven:
Are you kidding?
You took her on this
whirlwind tour of Earth,
and then she wanted to live
here with you forever.
That's just how I felt
when I came here with Ruby!
Oh, no. We have to
get back right away.
Ruby, I'm so sorry!
Where...
Huh?
Oh, no.
Ruby, I'm so sorry!
Where... Huh?
Oh, no.
Sapphire, you were right.
I need some time to think.
So I am running away.
Ruby.
This can't be happening!
Oh, Ruby! I'm so sorry!
You left before
I could take back
all the horrible
things I said to you!
Well, Amethyst was with her.
Right?
Maybe she knows
where she went.
Amethyst, have you seen Ruby?
Yeah. I've seen her.
She asked me for pen
and paper awhile ago.
Why?
Because she ran away!
Did you see where she went?
I don't know.
Maybe she'll come back!
It's not my job to babysit her.
Hey, Steven! Get over here.
I need a player two.
Hold on a second, Amethyst.
Do you see her coming back
in your future vision, Sapphire?
Oh, maybe!
But she's so wonderful
and spontaneous.
I have no idea what she...
Why would she be a cowboy?
[ Sobbing ]
There, there.
It's going to be okay.
She's going to come back.
She's got to come back.
If she doesn't, then there
would be no more Garnet,
and what on Earth would
we do without Garnet?
Oh, Pearl.
How will I ever get her back?
I don't know! You two
are incredible together!
It can't be over! It can't!
Oh, why don't you two take
all of this into the temple?
Steven and I are going
to play some video games.
No. No. It's okay.
Don't worry, Sapphire.
I'm going to go out
and find Ruby!
What?
I'll be right back
with her in no time.
[ Both sobbing ]
Yo, Steven! Wait up!
I'm coming too.
[ Gulls crying, waves crashing ]
I don't think Ruby
used the warp path.
She said she was running away,
not warping away,
and she's usually
pretty literal.
We just need to figure out
which direction she went.
So how do we do that?
Let's try putting
ourselves in Ruby's shoes.
[ Laughs ]
Now what?
Amethyst, be serious.
She could only have gone
in one of two directions,
either into town
or into the ocean.
Hmm...
Ruby! Ruby! Ruby!
[ Gurgling ]
Ruby!
Okay, so she wasn't underwater.
Ruby?
I really don't think she's
hiding under a seashell.
Maybe Ruby shape-shifted
really small!
You never know.
What a spacious house!
I'll keep it.
Amethyst, you know
I love these great goofs,
but I'm worried about Ruby.
Can we stop messing around
and turn back to normal?
You're the boss.
We need to think.
Where would Ruby go
if she ran away?
Is there anyone in town
that she knows?
Doesn't look like she's here.
Dead end, huh?
We've just got to keep looking.
♪♪
[ No dialog ]
She's not in here either.
This is where I would go
if I was feeling down.
Pizza always cheers me up.
So why don't we get some?
But we haven't found Ruby yet.
Steven, it's cool you want to
help Ruby, but what about you?
Come on! Let's forget about Ruby
for a moment and get some pizza!
I'm not hungry!
[ Stomach gurgling ]
Maybe I'm a little hungry!
Here's your pizza with
literally all the toppings.
Ye-e-e-es!
Oh, and here.
You're going to need these.
Thanks!
Yeah! Thanks, man!
You're welcome!
So...
Pink diamond, huh?
Yeah.
Rose quartz, eh?
Mm-hmm.
So all this time, you thought
Rose was this rebel leader,
but she was just rebelling
against herself?
Apparently.
And the diamond that Rose
supposedly shattered,
I mean, you've got it!
It's right there
under your shirt.
Yeah.
So how are you feeling?
I feel confused.
I thought I had
really finally got it
that Mom didn't have
everything figured out
even though everyone put her
way up on this pedestal,
but now I guess
she's royalty too.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
I'm relieved that she
didn't shatter anyone,
but she lied to everyone!
I mean, I'm not surprised.
I knew she was a liar.
But this is just so much.
But, like, aren't you mad?
Kind of. I don't know.
I can see how she was good
and bad, and bad and good.
But I guess what really
matters right now
is how hard Garnet took it.
But what about you?!
She's your mom!
You were always under all of
this pressure to be like her,
but was she even like her?
Was anyone
ever like her?
She was supposed
to be so great.
to know everything.
She was supposed to
make everything better.
It's not fair!
We shouldn't have to deal
with any of this!
We shouldn't have
to fix any of this!
We weren't around
for her stupid war!
This is everyone
else's problem.
This is nothing
to do with me.
And you! Th-- This has
nothing to with you!
Amethyst, hold on a second.
Are you okay?
No! I mean, yes!
Of course I'm okay!
I'm trying to find out
how you feel about all of this!
She's your mom. Okay?
It doesn't really affect me.
Dude, Kiki, I just got the
biggest tip from Mr. Universe,
and I'm totally going
to buy those boots now!
Whoa! Seriously?
Yeah! He was like all the way
out on Brooding Hill,
which is totally out
of our delivery radius,
comforting some little friend.
She must have been crying
because she was,
like, really red.
Both: Ruby!
Let me handle this, Steven.
No more adults should be
putting anything else on you!
Just let someone else
take care of it for once!
Amethyst, wait!
There's someone else
who needs help even more,
and it's you!
Amethyst, we need to talk!
Can't now, bud!
I'm going to find Ruby!
♪♪
Let me help you
with your feelings!
Get off of my back, dude!
Come on! You can talk to me!
Aah!
♪♪
If you'll open up,
you'll feel so much better!
Come on!
You're hiding something!
Get out of my head, Steven!
Am I getting too personal?
Dude, you're literally
inside my head!
Amethyst, look out!
We're crashing!
But how does that
make you feel?
♪♪
[ Crash ]
Amethyst?
You want to know
how I feel, Steven?
I thought I was
pretty clear about that.
pretty clear, too!
I feel like I don't want
to say, "What about me?"
Okay! And I don't want
to be bent out of shape.
I don't want to be
stuck in the past.
And I'm not responsible
for what Rose did!
None of us are! Not you.
Not Pearl. And not Garnet!
But I am responsible for me.
And right now,
I am not going to dump
another 1,000-year-old complex
on you or anybody else.
I am ending it right here!
I am the ding dong
sunshine future.
Your friend forever!
And I'm not going to
fall apart on you.
Amethyst...
So, Steven, how do you feel?
Pretty good.
Good.
[ Waves crashing ]
Have you been trying to
cheer me up this whole time?
Yes! Jeez!
Don't you know you deserve
it, you great person?
♪♪
Hey, Amethyst.
What?
I can't believe
I'm going to say this,
but I think you're officially
the most mature Crystal Gem.
Oh, no! Gross!
That's what this is, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty much.
No! No-o-o!
[ Chuckles ]
You still want to find Ruby?
Yeah.
All right. Let's go.
♪♪
There they are!
Target spotted.
Let's go in for a landing.
♪♪