>> ♪ WE ARE THE CRYSTAL GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
>> Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK WE
CAN'T ♪
>> ♪ WE'LL ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE OF THIS
WORLD ♪
>> Garnet: ♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
>> Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
>> Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
>> Steven: AND STEVEN!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Garnet: ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
>> Pearl: ONE MORE ATTACK SHOULD
DO IT.
>> [ ROARS ]
>> Steven: YIKES! YOUR ARM!
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> Pearl: NOW THERE'S NOTHING
STANDING BETWEEN US AND THE
SHOOTING STAR.
>> Amethyst: THIS JOB IS REALLY
DANGEROUS.
WHOA! GEEZ!
WHA-- WHOA, MAMA!
>> Steven: AMETHYST!
DON'T WORRY. I'LL GET YOU OUT.
>> Amethyst: [ MUFFLED TALKING ]
>> Pearl: WE'VE GOT TO GET
STEVEN OUT OF HERE!
>> Garnet: I'M SENDING YOU BACK
TO THE TEMPLE.
>> Steven: BUT, GARNET, HOW ARE
YOU GONNA --
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
YOU CAN BUBBLE ME?
>> Pearl: GARNET, NO!
[ WHIMPERING ]
GARNET!
>> Garnet: WATCH YOUR HEAD.
>> Steven: AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
WHOA!
I'M BACK INSIDE THE TEMPLE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
LOOK AT YOU NOW, STUCK IN A
BUBBLE.
HMM.
LET ME SEE IF I CAN...
[ GRUNTS ]
[ STRAINING ]
YEAH!
WHA? UGH!
WHOA!
WHA!
[ GRUNTS, GROANS ]
WHEW.
HUH?
OH, MAN.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
>> [ SCREECHING, SNARLING ]
>> Steven: AAH! THE CENTIPEETLE!
[ GASPS ]
AAAAH!
[ PANTING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
>> [ SNARLING, SCREECHING ]
[ BLEATING, CLACKING ]
>> Steven: EH...
HUH?
>> [ WHIMPERING ]
>> Steven: IT LOOKS...SO SCARED.
UH...HI.
AW, IT'S OKAY.
LOOK, PLEASE DON'T BE SCARED OF
ME.
SEE? I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
>> [ WHIMPERING CONTINUES ]
>> Steven: YEAH. JUST RELAX.
>> [ WHIMPERING STOPS ]
>> Steven: YEAH. THAT'S IT.
DOESN'T RELAXING FEEL NICE?
YOU WANT TO...COME OVER HERE AND
RELAX WITH ME?
>> [ WHEEZES ]
>> Steven: YEAH, WE CAN TOTALLY
JUST HANG OUT RIGHT HERE ON THE
FLOOR.
>> [ SQUEALS ]
>> Steven: YEAH. DON'T BE SHY.
WE CAN BE FRIENDS.
MY NAME'S STEVEN.
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
GET AWAY FROM THAT THING!
>> Amethyst: WHOA, DUDE!
>> Steven: WAIT! IT'S NOT --
AAH!
>> Pearl: THIS WAS A TERRIBLE
IDEA.
AND HE'S EVEN MANAGED TO POP A
BUBBLE AND LET OUT THAT AWFUL...
THING!
>> [ SHRIEKING, SNARLING ]
>> Pearl: IF THAT THING HURT
YOU, SO HELP ME, I'LL --
>> Steven: NO!
IT DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
GARNET!
DON'T HURT IT!
I ACCIDENTALLY LET IT OUT OF ITS
BUBBLE, BUT IT DIDN'T EVEN TRY
TO HURT ME.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE OTHER
MONSTERS.
IT'S JUST SCARED AND CONFUSED.
PLEASE, GARNET, I'M BEGGING YOU.
>> Garnet: I CAN'T SAY NO TO
THAT FACE.
>> Pearl: EXCUSE ME?!
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
>> Garnet: I THINK YOU SHOULD
TRY AND TAME IT, STEVEN.
>> Steven: GARNET, THANK YOU SO
MUCH!
>> Pearl: HMMM.
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
SHUT DOWN BY THE G-SQUAD!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: WELL, LET'S AT LEAST
TAKE SOME PRECAUTION.
>> Garnet: ALL RIGHT, STEVEN,
LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN GET IT TO
CALM DOWN.
>> Steven: UM...IT STILL SEEMS A
LITTLE SCARED.
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ GROWLS ]
>> Steven: MAYBE YOU GUYS COULD
PUT YOUR WEAPONS AWAY AND WATCH
FROM THE HOUSE...?
>> Pearl: ABSOLUTELY NOT!
>> Garnet: STEVEN CAN HANDLE
THIS.
>> Pearl: GARNET!
>> Garnet: PEARL.
>> Amethyst: OH!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU JUST GOT GARNETED!
>> Steven: OKAY, FRIEND, IT'S
JUST US NOW.
CALMY CALM. CALM.
JUST LIKE BEFORE. YEAH.
JUST RELAX AND LET YOUR HAIR
DOWN.
YOU WANT TO COME OVER HERE? HUH?
DON'T WORRY.
IT WON'T BE LIKE BEFORE.
HOW ABOUT WE TRY SOMETHING ELSE?
HMM...
OH! WHAT'S THIS?
CHIIIIIPS?
YOU LIKE CHIIIPS?
YOU WANT A CHIIIPS?
YEAH? YEAH?
AW, LOOK AT THIS CHIIIIP.
YUM, YUM, YUM!
MMMM! TASTY, TASTY!
HMM? TRY IT.
THAT'S IT.
SMELLS GOOD, RIGHT?
[ GASPS ]
>> [ MUNCHING ]
>> Steven: I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU
EAT WITH AN EYEBALL IN YOUR
MOUTH, BUT I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
HMM? HMMM?
>> [ SNUFFLING, CLACKING ]
>> Steven: AHHH...
[ WIND GUSTS ]
HUH?
>> [ MUNCHING ]
>> Steven: [ LAUGHS ]
WHOO-HOO!
HEY, COME ON!
[ LAUGHS ]
♪ YOU LOVE CHIPS ♪
♪ AND I LOVE CHIPS ♪
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH!
>> [ CAWS ]
>> Steven: AAAH!
SHOO! GET!
THOSE AREN'T FOR YOU!
>> [ CAWS ANGRILY ]
>> Steven: AAH! HUH?
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> [ CAWS ]
>> Steven: YOU...SAVED ME.
>> Pearl: BUT WE HAVE TO GO BACK
FOR THE SHOOTING STAR.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> Steven: GARNET! PEARL!
AMETHYST!
>> Pearl: WHOA!
WHY ISN'T THAT THING ON ITS
ROCK?
>> Steven: I TRAINED HER UP.
LOOK!
SQUAAAWK!
[ ALL GASP ]
SQUAWK!
>> Garnet: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: SQUAWK!
>> Pearl: STEVEN, YOU CAN'T
JUST --
AAH!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
THAT WAS AWES-- [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: WHOOO!
>> Amethyst: NOOOOO!
MI TORTA!
[ SOBS ]
>> Pearl: STEVEN, THIS IS
UNACCEPTABLE.
>> Steven: AW, COME ON, PEARL.
SHE CAN HELP US ON, LIKE,
MISSIONS AND STUFF.
>> Pearl: OH, NO.
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
>> Steven: AWW.
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ]
WELL, WE CAN'T RETURN TO THE ICE
CAVERN NOW.
WE HAVE TO STAY AND DEAL WITH
STEVEN AND HIS...SITUATION.
>> Amethyst: WELL, I DON'T KNOW
HOW WE'RE GONNA GET THROUGH ALL
THOSE ICE BOULDERS WITHOUT
CAUSING A CAVE-IN ANYWAY.
>> Garnet: HMM.
THAT'S HOW.
>> [ CLACKING ]
>> Pearl: I JUST DON'T KNOW IF
THIS WILL WORK.
>> Steven: SQUAWK!
ALL RIGHT, CENTIPEETLE!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> Pearl: SHOOTING STAR, HERE WE
COME.
>> All: WHOA.
>> Steven: SQUAWK!
>> Pearl: AAH!
[ GASPS ]
[ ALL GROAN ]
>> [ PANTING ]
[ CREAKING ]
>> Garnet: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: WHOA!
>> Pearl: OH, MY.
>> All: WHOA.
>> Steven: COOL!
>> Pearl: THERE IT IS -- THE
SHOOTING STAR!
AN ANCIENT ELEMENTAL SO HOT AND
SO VOLATILE, IT CAN ONLY BE
CONTAINED IN ICE.
BARE SKIN CANNOT ENDURE ITS
INTENSITY.
>> Steven: WHAT DO YOU DO WITH A
SHOOTING STAR?
>> Amethyst: UH, YOU SHOOT IT.
>> Pearl: GARNET, YOU'LL NEED TO
USE YOUR GAUNTLETS SO AS NOT TO
HURT YOUR HANDS.
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
>> Steven: NO! NO, NO! NOT NOW!
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Garnet: SOMETHING'S WRONG.
>> [ SHRIEKING ]
>> Steven: AAH!
WHOA! AAH!
>> All: AAAH!
>> Steven: AAAH!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
[ GRUNTS ]
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN!
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLS ]
>> Steven: AAH!
PEARL, STOP! IT WAS AN ACCIDENT!
>> [ COUGHS ]
>> Steven: AAH!
SORRY FOR PULLING.
>> Garnet: STEVEN!
>> [ WHIMPERS ]
>> Steven: NO!
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> Steven: AAH!
>> [ PANTING ]
>> Steven: STOP!
YOU DON'T NEED TO FIGHT!
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Steven: THIS ISN'T YOU.
YOU'RE NOT A MONSTER ANYMORE.
>> [ WHEEZES ]
>> Steven: YOU'RE MORE THAN
THAT.
WE HAVE SO MANY MEMORIES NOW.
REMEMBER THE CHIP TIMES?
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
>> Steven: AND HOW YOU SAVED ME
FROM THAT VICIOUS SEAGULL?
>> [ SNARLS ]
>> Steven: AND HOW WE BECAME
BEST FRIENDS?
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER!
THIS ALL HAPPENED TODAY!
>> [ SNARLING ]
>> Steven: [ GRUNTING ]
[ SNARLING STOPS ]
[ GURGLES LIGHTLY ]
[ RUMBLING ]
>> Steven: HUH?
AAAH!
NOOOOO!
>> [ SHRIEKS ]
[ CRIES WEAKLY ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
NOOO!
[ WHEEZES ]
[ MOANS ]
>> Steven: YOU SAVED ME.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, YOU DID A
GOOD JOB TRAINING THE
CENTIPEETLE.
YOUR MOTHER WOULD BE SO PROUD.
>> Steven: [ SNIFFLES ]
SHE WOULD?
>> Garnet: THE TRUTH IS,
ROSE QUARTZ HAD TRIED TO USE HER
POWERS TO SAVE THESE MONSTERS,
TOO, BUT SHE WAS NEVER ABLE TO
HEAL THEM.
>> Steven: NEVER?
BUT IF SHE COULDN'T DO IT...
>> Pearl: WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE WHEN YOU HAVE BETTER
CONTROL OF YOUR POWERS, YOU
MIGHT HELP THEM IN WAYS EVEN
YOUR MOTHER COULDN'T.
>> Garnet: EVEN THIS ONE.
>> Steven: I'LL KEEP IT SAFE.
>> Amethyst: WOW!
>> Pearl: STEVEN!
YOU CAN BUBBLE GEMS!
>> Steven: WOW.
WAIT FOR ME, CENTIPEETLE.
I PROMISE I'LL HEAL YOU UP
SOMEDAY.
OOH! WAIT!
>> STEVEN, HURRY UP!
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Steven: I'M FINE.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
>> Steven: YEAH.
[ CHOMPING ]
>> OKAY. UH, SO, UM...
IS THIS FENCE NEW?
>> Steven: EH...
IT'S A LONG STORY.
>> IS IT A MAGIC STORY?!
>> Steven: M-M-M-M-A-A-A-YBE...?
>> WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?!
TELL ME. PLEASE?
>> Steven: [ SIGHS ] OKAY, OKAY.
BUT IT'S NOT A HAPPY STORY.
AMETHYST WAS HORSING AROUND BY
THE CLIFF.
AMETHYST, BE CAREFUL!
>> Amethyst: [ LAUGHS ]
STEVEN, WHY YOU GETTING SO
WORKED UP?
WHAT -- DO YOU CARE ABOUT ME OR
SOMETHING?
>> Steven: YES!
>> Amethyst: AW, STEVEN, I
DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU --
WHOA-A-A-A-A-A!
>> Steven: AMETHYST, STOP!
YOU'RE GONNA FALL!
>> Amethyst: OOH!
[ Singsong voice ] STEVEN, I'M
GONNA FA-A-LL!
>> Steven: AMETHYST, YOU'RE
GONNA GET HURT!
>> Amethyst: STEVEN, PLEASE.
I'M A GEM WARRIOR.
I'M NOT GONNA FA-- AAH!
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
UGH. THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: [ WHIMPERS ] AAH!
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
I'M OKAY!
>> Steven: SO, I RAN DOWN THERE
[ GROANS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
>> Amethyst: YES, STEVEN.
I'M FINE, EXCEPT FOR THIS!
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
AMETHYST!
>> Amethyst: GREAT.
>> Pearl: SHOW ME YOUR GEM!
>> Amethyst: FRESH!
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, YOUR GEM IS
CRACKED!
>> Amethyst: RUDE! [ SCOFFS ]
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL!
PLUS, NOW I HAVE THIS COOL
GOOGLY EYE!
>> Steven: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Pearl: HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> Steven: SHE FELL OFF THE
CLIFF BY THE LIGHTHOUSE.
>> Amethyst: DID NOT!
>> Pearl: OF COURSE.
HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN SO BLIND?
WE NEED TO PUT A FENCE UP THERE
SO THIS WILL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN!
>> Steven: AND THAT'S WHY
THERE'S A FENCE.
THE END.
[ CHOMPING ]
>> WAIT, WHAT HAPPENED TO
AMETHYST?
>> Steven: UH...
>> COME ON. TELL ME THE REST!
>> Steven: I DON'T WANNA.
>> STEVEN?
STEVEN...
>> Steven: MM...
>> STEVEN!
>> Steven: [ GROANING ]
OKAY, OKAY!
BUT ONLY IF YOU LET ME TRY ON
YOUR GLASSES.
>> ONLY IF YOU GIVE ME THE REST
OF YOUR JUICE.
>> Steven: OKAY, BUT IT'S MOSTLY
BACKWASH.
>> GOOD ENOUGH.
>> Steven: HOW DO I LOOK?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> Steven: WELL, UM, SO...
UH, WE WERE ALL WORRIED ABOUT
AMETHYST.
SO, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
AMETHYST FALLS ON STUFF ALL THE
TIME.
>> Pearl: IT'D BE FINE IF IT WAS
JUST HER BODY, BUT HER GEM IS
DAMAGED.
>> Steven: SO WHAT DO YOU DO TO
FIX IT?
>> Pearl: BEFORE... [ SIGHS ]
...WE HAD ROSE.
>> Garnet: STEVEN, YOUR MOTHER
HAD HEALING TEARS THAT FLOWED
FROM HER GEM.
SHE FELT REAL LOVE FOR THOSE
AROUND HER.
SHE FELT REAL SORROW WHEN THEY
WERE HURT.
YOU HAVE THE ROSE QUARTZ GEM
NOW.
I KNOW THAT POWER IS IN YOU,
TOO.
>> Steven: AMETHYST, SHOW ME
YOUR GEM!
>> Amethyst: YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>> Steven: [ Whispering ] The
power to heal.
[ STRAINING ]
IT'S NOT WORKING.
I GUESS I'M JUST TOO TOUGH TO
CRY.
>> Pearl: JUST TODAY, YOU WERE
CRYING ABOUT SNAKES.
>> Steven: THEY DON'T HAVE ANY
ARMS!
>> Garnet: WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE NEED TO TAKE AMETHYST TO
ROSE'S HEALING SPRING.
>> Amethyst: [ SCOFFS ]
GUYS, I'M FINE.
I'M NOT GONNA GET ANY
WOR-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R...
R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R...
[ POP ]
[ SPEAKING BACKWARDS ]
>> Pearl: AND IN THE CENTER OF
THE GARDEN -- ROSE'S FOUNTAIN,
OVERFLOWING WITH YOUR MOTHER'S
HEALING, LACHRYMAL ESSENCE!
>> Garnet: I DON'T SEE IT.
>> Pearl: WHA...
[ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: [ SPEAKING
BACKWARDS ]
>> Pearl: NOW, NOW!
UH, LET'S KEEP IT TOGETHER!
OUR MEMORIES OF ROSE CAN'T BE
TAINTED BY SOME OVERGROWN
BRAMBLES!
[ CHUCKLES ]
LOOK AT THEM.
THEY'RE A MESS WITHOUT HER
GUIDANCE.
DIRECTIONLESS, PATHETIC,
CLINGING THINGS.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY, GARNET.
>> Garnet: SURE.
>> Pearl: Y-Y-YOU REALLY THINK
SO?
>> Steven: HEALING TEARS!
[ STRAINING ]
>> Pearl: HMM.
MAYBE THERE'S A PATH OVER HERE!
>> Amethyst: [ SPEAKING
BACKWARDS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ IMITATES CRYING ]
>> Steven: PAIN CAN MAKE ONE
CRY.
WHERE IS PAIN?
>> Amethyst: [ GASPS ]
>> Steven: [ YELPS ]
>> Pearl: AMETHYST, NO MORE
ROUGHHOUSING!
YOU'LL EXACERBATE YOUR CRACK!
>> Amethyst: [ SPEAKING
BACKWARDS ]
[ GROANS ]
>> Pearl: [ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: [ GRUNTS ]
>> Steven: AW, RIGHT IN THE GEM.
>> Amethyst: [ COUGHING ]
[ SPEAKING BACKWARDS ]
[ GROWLS ]
>> Pearl: OHH! OH! KEEP CALM.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS GET YOU
INTO THE FOUNTAIN IMMEDIATELY,
IF WE CAN EVER FIND THE WAY
UNDER ALL THIS MESS!
>> Garnet: Shh.
I NEEDED THAT.
THIS WAY.
>> Pearl: [ Chuckling ] WE
COULD'VE PROBABLY GOTTEN IN
WITHOUT HURTLING A GIANT ROCK
INTO ROSE'S MOST PRECIOUS
SANCTUARY!
BUT IF YOU'RE OKAY WITH IT, I'M
FINE, TOO!
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> Garnet: THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
THE FOUNTAIN ISN'T RUNNING.
>> Pearl: WHAT?
W-WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
>> Garnet: I'M NOT SURE.
>> Steven: IS THAT MOM?
OH, OH, I'M GETTING EMOTIONAL!
I THINK IT'S HAPPENING!
UH, I'M REALLY FEELING IT!
[ STRAINING ]
AAH! HEADACHE!
>> SO GIVE BACK MY GLASSES AND
FINISH THE STORY!
>> Steven: [ INHALES DEEPLY ]
AH, COME ON! I HAD IT!
>> Pearl: [ SIGHS ]
STEVEN, IT'S FINE.
JUST -- JUST STAY HERE AND WATCH
AMETHYST.
WE'LL FIND OUT WHAT'S WRONG WITH
THE FOUNTAIN.
>> Steven: NO, NO. WAIT!
I CAN STILL DO IT!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> Steven: WAIT, WAIT!
IT MIGHT STILL HAPPEN!
GUYS?
AAH!
>> Amethyst: [ SPEAKING
BACKWARDS ]
>> Steven: I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
YOU!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING!
WHY IS EVERYONE ACTING SO
STRANGE?
WHY CAN'T I --
WHY CAN'T I CRY?!
[ Echoing ] WHY CAN'T I CRY?
IT'S JUST...
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO FEEL
ABOUT YOU, BUT EVERYBODY ELSE
DOES.
I WISH I COULD HAVE MET YOU.
THEN THIS PLACE COULD MAKE ME
SAD, AND I COULD CRY HEALING
TEARS, LIKE YOU.
>> [ SNIFFLES ]
>> Steven: ARE YOU OKAY?
KEEP GOING.
>> Amethyst: [ HOOTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SPEAKING BACKWARDS ]
>> Steven: [ GASPS ]
AAH!
AMETHYST, WHERE'S YOUR GEM?
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
AMETHYST, I'M SORRY!
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING RIGHT.
NOW I'M GOING TO LOSE YOU, AND
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
>> Amethyst: [ Slowly ] HA, HA.
YOU CARE ABOUT ME.
>> Steven: PLEASE LET ME BE A
MAGIC HEALER.
[ CRYING ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, COME ON!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GASPS ]
>> Amethyst: LOOK AT THIS GUY,
SAVING MY LIFE AND JUNK.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
>> Pearl: OH, THANK GOODNESS.
>> Steven: DID YOU SEE WHAT I
DID?
IT WAS MAGIC!
MY TEARS BROUGHT THE FOUNTAIN
BACK TO LIFE AND SAVED AMETHYST!
>> Pearl: I'M PRETTY SURE GARNET
AND I UNPLUGGING A CLOGGED
CHAMBER BROUGHT THE FOUNTAIN
BACK TO LIFE.
>> Garnet: WE SAVED AMETHYST.
>> Steven: YOU DON'T THINK MY
CRYING WAS A LITTLE RELATED TO
THAT?
>> Pearl: OH, STEVEN, YOU DON'T
HAVE HEALING TEARS.
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE ANY REAL MAGIC
POWERS, AND WE DON'T WANT
ANYTHING MORE TO DO WITH YOU.
>> SHE DIDN'T REALLY SAY THAT.
>> Steven: NO, BUT THAT'S WHAT
IT FELT LIKE.
>> IS THAT WHY YOU'VE BEEN SO
DOWN?
OH.
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR JUICE BACK.
>> Steven: NAH, THAT'S OKAY.
[ SNIFFLES, SIGHS ]
EVERYONE EXPECTS ME TO BE LIKE
MY MOM.
WHAT IF I NEVER GET THOSE
POWERS?
>> THEN YOU'LL BE LIKE ME.
THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
>> Steven: BUT IF I DON'T HAVE
POWERS, THEN I CAN'T HANG OUT
WITH AMETHYST OR GARNET OR
PEARL, AND I-I CAN'T GO ON
MISSIONS!
>> YOU DON'T NEED ANY POWERS TO
BE HERE WITH ME.
[ JUICE GURGLES ]
OW. UGH.
>> Steven: WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I THINK -- [ SIGHS ]
THERE'S JUST --
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG WITH MY
GLASSES.
MY...
MY EYES.
I-I-I CAN SEE!
>> Steven: WHAT?
>> I CAN SEE WITHOUT MY GLASSES!
>> Steven: DID I HEAL YOUR EYES?
BUT HOW?
[ GASPS ]
THE JUICE BOX!
I DON'T HAVE HEALING TEARS!
I HAVE HEALING SPIT!
>> WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL MY
PARENTS?
WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL MY
OPTOMETRIST?!
>> Steven: I DON'T EVEN KNOW!
OH, THANK YOU, CONNIE!
LION, LET'S GO TELL THE GEMS!
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA BELIEVE
THIS!
[ WIND WHISTLES ]