♪ WE ♪
♪ ARE THE CRYSTAL ♪
♪ GEMS ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS SAVE THE DAY ♪
Steven: ♪ AND IF YOU THINK
WE CAN'T, WE'LL ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIND A WAY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY THE PEOPLE ♪
♪ OF THIS WORLD ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN ♪
♪ GARNET ♪
Amethyst: ♪ AMETHYST ♪
Pearl: ♪ AND PEARL ♪
AND STEVEN!
[ BOTH CRYING ]
[ ALL CRYING ]
I DON'T GET
THIS CARTOON, MAN.
WHY DON'T THEY JUST EAT
THE ICE CREAM OFF THE FLOOR?
THEY DON'T HAVE TO CRY
ABOUT IT.
[ CRYING ]
AW, NOT AGAIN.
IT WAS DOING THIS
YESTERDAY, TOO.
HANG ON. I GOT IT.
HOW ABOUT NOW?
AAH.
IT'S NEVER
DONE THAT BEFORE.
[ Distorted voice ]
ON ALL FREQUENCIES...PERIDOT.
[ Normal voice ]
THIS IS PERIDOT,
TRANSMITTING ON ALL FREQUENCIES
FROM ABANDONED CRYSTAL SYSTEM
COLONY PLANET EARTH
TO YELLOW DIAMOND.
MY MISSION
HAS BEEN COMPROMISED.
MY ESCORT AND INFORMANT
ARE GONE,
AND I AM NOW STRANDED.
PLEASE SEND HELP.
THIS IS PERIDOT, TRANSMITTING
ON ALL FREQUENCIES...
OKAY. THANKS.
CONNIE SAYS
IT'S ON HER TV, TOO.
BUT WHERE COULD PERIDOT
BE BROADCASTING A SIGNAL
THAT STRONG?
THERE'S ONLY ONE PLACE.
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ GASPS ]
LION, ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S AS I FEARED.
IT LOOKS LIKE PERIDOT SOMEHOW
REPAIRED THE COMMUNICATION HUB.
WELL, AT LEAST SOME OF IT.
SO WE JUST GOT
TO WRECK IT UP AGAIN, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS
SHOULD FORM SUGILITE.
YEAH?
WELL, UH, IT'S UP
TO GARNET, I GUESS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SHALL WE MASH IT UP?
NO.
BUT...DON'T WE NEED
TO BE HUGE LIKE LAST TIME?
LAST TIME WAS A DISASTER.
LAST TIME WE FUSED,
SUGILITE WENT BERSERK.
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF HER THAT WE
CAN'T EVEN WARP HERE ANYMORE.
I COULD BE RASH,
YOU COULD BE RECKLESS,
AND WE COULD BOTH
GET CARRIED AWAY.
SO, FOR THE TIME BEING,
SUGILITE IS BENCHED.
WHAT WE NEED NOW
IS TO BE CAREFUL.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S YOU AND ME, PEARL.
LET'S FUSE.
DON'T CRY, PEARL.
[ SHIVERING ]
[ SNIFFLES, CHUCKLES ]
COME ON.
LET'S DO THIS.
I'M RIGHT
BEHIND YOU.
WHOO-HOO!
FUSION! FUSION!
READY.
[ STRAINING ]
HANG ON.
IT'S BEEN
SUCH A LONG TIME.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYBODY!
THIS IS THE LOVELY SARDONYX,
COMING TO YOU LIVE
FROM THE SOON-TO-BE
FORMER COMMUNICATION HUB.
HOW ARE Y'ALL
DOING TONIGHT?
[ Unenthusiastically ]
GREAT.
[ GASPS ]
GIANT WOMAN!
OH, MY STARS.
IF IT ISN'T
STEVEN UNIVERSE.
WE FINALLY MEET.
SO...
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WAS I WORTH THE WAIT?
WHAT AM I SAYING?
OF COURSE I WAS.
[ LAUGHS LOUDLY ]
WOW.
YOU'RE SO ARTICULATED.
WELL, AREN'T YOU
THE SWEETEST LITTLE CHARMER?
I COULD LITERALLY SQUISH YOU
RIGHT NOW.
IT WOULD NOT BE HARD.
OHH!
SORRY. I'M JUST SO EXCITED
TO BE HERE.
YOU SEE, I HAVEN'T
EXACTLY BEEN MYSELF LATELY.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
FUSION JOKE.
[ GROANS ]
AND JOKES AREN'T
THE ONLY THING I'VE GOT.
HMM? [ GASPS ]
OH!
[ DING! ]
ARE YOU GONNA SMASH STUFF
WITH YOUR WAR HAMMER?
HMM.
"SMASH" IS THE WORD
ONE WOULD USE
TO DESCRIBE
WHAT SOMEONE ELSE MIGHT DO.
NOW...
THE PROPER WORDS USED
TO DESCRIBE YOURS TRULY ARE...
"SPECIFIC"...
..."INTELLIGENT"...
"ACCURATE"...
"FAULTLESS"...
..."ELEGANT"...
"CONTROLLED"...
"SURGICAL," "GRACEFUL"...
AND...
"POWERFUL"!
BUT, YES, OCCASIONALLY,
I AM KNOWN TO SMASH.
NOW, JUST REMEMBER,
EVERYBODY...
IF YOU EVER HAVE NEED
OF THE LOVELY SARDONYX,
LET PEARL AND GARNET KNOW.
I'LL BE THERE IN A FLASH --
LITERALLY.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
OH!
WHOO!
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU GUYS
WERE AMAZING!
WE WERE? OH.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
WE WERE AWESOME!
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHY DON'T WE DO THAT
MORE OFTEN?
WHY, PEAR?
WHY DID YOU LIE TO ME?
[ Crying ]
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
AW. PEAR.
I'D FORGIVE HER.
WOULDN'T YOU?
MM.
OH, HEY, AMETHYST.
YOU'RE MISSING
"CRYING BREAKFAST FRIENDS."
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE.
BUT IT'S A REALLY
GOOD ONE SO FAR.
NOT REALLY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M RECORDING IT FOR LATER.
[ STATIC ]
IT'S THE SIGNAL AGAIN.
PERIDOT.
PEARL,
THE SIGNAL IS BACK.
AGAIN?
WE NEED
TO GET BACK OUT THERE.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
RIGHT.
STEVEN, WHERE'S LION?
AMETHYST, GET YOUR HEAD
OUT OF THE FRIDGE.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
[ GULPS ]
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
YOU KNOW I AM.
WHAT'S THIS --
AN ENCORE PERFORMANCE?
JUST COULDN'T
GET ENOUGH OF ME, COULD YOU?
[ LAUGHS LOUDLY ]
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET THE SHOW BEGIN!
[ GROANS ]
♪ MAYBE YOU'RE BETTER OFF
WITH HER ♪
♪ I THINK
SHE'S BETTER FOR YOU ♪
♪ I FORGOT HOW GREAT
IT FELT TO BE US ♪
♪ GUESS I GOT
CARRIED AWAY ♪
♪ I HAD TO USE YOU
TO MAKE ME FEEL STRONG ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THAT NOW ♪
♪ I SEE A TOWER
BUILT OUT OF MY MISTAKES ♪
♪ AND IT ALL
COMES CRASHING DOWN ♪
♪ IS THERE
SOMETHING I CAN DO? ♪
♪ CAN I MAKE IT UP
TO YOU? ♪
HMM.
PERIDOT'S
BEEN BACK HERE TWICE,
SO THE ODDS ARE GOOD
SHE'LL COME BACK AGAIN, RIGHT?
BAM!
THAT'S WHEN WE'LL GET HER.
YEAH. BAM!
GARNET WILL BE
SO IMPRESSED.
AND THEN SHE'LL THINK
I'M COOL AGAIN!
MM-HMM.
NOTHING...
MORE NOTHING...
[ GASPS ]
THERE SHE IS!
NO, WAIT.
THAT'S JUST A WEIRD CACTUS.
I DON'T THINK
SHE'S COMING.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IF YOU MAKE YOUR EYES BLURRY,
IT LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S A LITTLE MAGIC SAUSAGE
BETWEEN YOUR FINGERS.
THIS IS STUPID.
IT DOESN'T EVEN WORK.
TRY THIS.
HEY, DON'T MESS WITH MY --
OH!
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, EVEN IF
WE DIDN'T CATCH PERIDOT,
AT LEAST I TAUGHT YOU
A GREAT WAY TO PASS THE TIME.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
I THINK I SAW SOMETHING.
IT'S PERIDOT'S ESCAPE POD.
SHE FIXED IT SOMEHOW?
BUT I THOUGHT WE HAD IT.
DID SHE STEAL IT
FROM THE TEMPLE?
WHOA. SHE'S LIFTING
THE PILLAR GUYS.
AND SHE'S FIXING THE HUB.
WHAT'S SHE DOING UP THERE?
ENHANCE.
HEY, FOR SOME REASON,
PERIDOT KIND OF LOOKS LIKE...
PEARL?
WHAT?! LET ME SEE.
OH, NO.
WHY WOULD PEARL
REBUILD THE HUB?
MAYBE SHE'S TRYING
TO STUDY HOW IT WORKS?
NO.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S IT.
MAYBE SHE'S TRYING
TO GET US MORE CHANNELS?
[ STATIC ]
[ GASPS ] OH!
THIS IS NO GOOD.
W-WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S PERIDOT.
SHE MUST HAVE FIXED
THE COMMUNICATION HUB AGAIN.
GARNET...
IT'S THE HUB AGAIN.
SHE'S EVADING
MY FUTURE VISION.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES I TRY,
I CAN'T SEE US FINDING PERIDOT.
[ SMACKS LIPS ]
COME ON, TEAM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE PERIDOT
IS GIVING US SO MUCH TROUBLE.
BUT IT HARDLY MATTERS,
RIGHT, GARNET?
WE CAN DISABLE THIS TOWER
AS MANY TIMES AS WE NEED TO
TOGETHER, OKAY?
OKAY. I'M READY.
ARE YOU READY, GARNET?
I KNOW WHAT SHE'S DOING.
YOU DO?
STOP!
HMM?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
AMETHYST?
YOU -- YOU SHOULDN'T.
PEARL, WE SAW YOU.
WHAT?
YOU NEED TO TELL GARNET
IT WAS YOU.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST SO MUCH FUN
BEING SARDONYX WITH YOU.
UH!
THAT'S WHY I COULDN'T SEE US
FINDING PERIDOT.
WAIT. LET ME EXPLAIN.
YOU'VE BEEN FIXING THE HUB!
IT REALLY WAS PERIDOT...
THE FIRST TIME.
YOU TRICKED ME.
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, WE JUST NEEDED
A REASON TO FUSE.
I JUST WANTED TO SHARE
A FEW MORE VICTORIES WITH YOU.
THOSE WEREN'T VICTORIES.
Amethyst: WAIT, GARNET.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE
SO MUCH WEAKER THAN YOU.
FUSING WITH YOU IS LIKE
OUR ONE CHANCE TO FEEL...
STRONGER.
Garnet: DON'T DEFEND HER.
PERIDOT
IS OUT THERE SOMEWHERE,
AND PEARL'S BEEN DISTRACTING US
WITH NOTHING.
GARNET...
THAT'S ENOUGH.
AMETHYST, FUSE WITH ME.
BUT...
LET'S JUST GET THIS OVER WITH.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
OF COURSE I FORGIVE YOU.
[ BOTH CRYING ]
MAN.
IT SURE WOULD BE NICE
IF THINGS WORKED OUT
THE WAY THEY DO IN CARTOONS.
YEAH.
IT WOULD.
♪ YOU ♪
♪ LOVE LIKE YOU ♪
PEARL! WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
EH. LOOKING FOR PERIDOT.
FOR A FEW DAYS STRAIGHT.
STEVEN, I KNOW
I MIGHT HAVE...
DISAPPOINTED ALL OF YOU.
I KNOW GARNET'S
VERY UPSET WITH ME.
BUT I'M GOING TO PROVE TO HER
THAT SHE CAN TRUST ME AGAIN.
OH, GARNET!
I WAS JUST LOOKING FOR PERIDOT!
SHE'S BOUND TO BE SOMEWHERE,
RIGHT?
ANY NEW IDEAS?
I'M SORRY.
WHO WANTS TO GO ON A ROAD TRIP?!
UM...IS THIS A BAD TIME?
NO. PLEASE CONTINUE.
WELL, I GOTTA DRIVE OVER TO
THE NEXT STATE, KEYSTONE.
YOU MEAN,
THE KEYSTONE STATE?
RIGHT, THE STATE
NAMED KEYSTONE.
I MET A GUY ON AN INTERNET
MESSAGE BOARD
WHO'S SELLING CAR-WASH
BRUSHES FOR REAL CHEAP!
I JUST GOTTA MEET HIM IN
KEYSTONE AND PICK 'EM UP.
I DON'T LIKE THOSE BRUSHES.
THEY FEEL WEIRD ON YOUR FUR.
WELL, DO YOU LIKE MOTELS?
PROBABLY!
THINK YOU'D LIKE TO
STAY AT A MOTEL
WITH YOUR FAVORITE DAD?
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
MY FAVORITE...
WHAT? HUH?
OH, YOU KIDDER.
COME HERE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET
ROOM SERVICE!
YOU'RE THINKING OF A HOTEL.
WE'RE GOING TO
A MOTEL!
IT'LL HAVE A POOL
AND FREE ICE.
AND IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO
THE BEST DINER IN THE WORLD!
I'M COMING, TOO.
WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
EVEN BETTER!
HEY, GARNET, I KNOW I'M
TALKING THIS PLACE UP,
BUT IT AIN'T EXACTLY
THE RITZ.
I'LL BE THE JUDGE OF THAT.
WELL, IN THAT CASE...
ROAD TRIP!
ROAD TRIP.
WONDERFUL!
I'LL MAKE SURE AMETHYST
KNOWS THAT... [ SIGHS ]
FINE.
WELL, GOODBYE.
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN,
RIGHT, DAD?
[ SNORING ]
[ YAWNS ]
ANOTHER GREAT THING
ABOUT MOTELS --
YOU CAN DRIVE RIGHT UP
TO YOUR DOOR!
[ GASPS ]
I'M GONNA SWIM IN THE POOL,
ORDER A MOVIE, GET FREE ICE!
IT'S GONNA BE GREAT!
NOT BEFORE WE CHECK FOR BEDBUGS,
IT ISN'T!
MM.
GOOD NEWS!
WE'RE BUGLESS!
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
OOP, THAT'S MY CUE.
HEY, DO YOU MIND HOLDING DOWN
THE FORT TILL I GET BACK?
GREAT. I'M OFF TO SEE A MAN
ABOUT A TUNNEL BRUSH.
AN INTERNET MAN.
IF I'M NOT BACK IN AN HOUR,
CALL THE POLICE.
OH-KAY!
BOUNCE WITH ME, GARNET!
[ GRUNTING ]
O-OR WE COULD
LOOK AT BROCHURES.
OOH, KEYSTONE CAVERNS.
CALM DOWN.
[ PANTS ]
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
FORGIVING PEARL!
DON'T UNDERSTAND --
WE MUST!
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING TO LISTEN,
THEN YOU CAN JUST GO!
AAH!
WE MUST MOVE PAST THIS, RUBY.
SHE LIED TO US
SO WE'D FORM SARDONYX!
SHE TRICKED US!
DON'T YOU FEEL USED?!
RUBY! SAPPHIRE!
I --
YOU'RE CHOOSING TO
TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
IT'S FUSION, SAPPHIRE!
WHAT'S MORE PERSONAL TO US
THAN FUSION?!
I KNOW YOU'RE STILL UPSET.
OH, SO IT'S JUST ME?
OF COURSE NOT.
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M COMPLETELY
ENGULFED WITH RAGE?
WELL, IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE IT!
THE SOONER WE FORGIVE PEARL,
THE BETTER IT WILL BE
FOR US ALL.
YOU'RE NOT AS ABOVE THIS
AS YOU THINK YOU ARE!
[ GRUNTS ]
YES, I AM.
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU CAN'T STAY ANGRY
WITH HER FOREVER.
WANNA BET?
RUBY, THE CARPET.
YOU -- I CAN'T EVEN -- UGH!
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN?
NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
HEY, RUBY.
YOU WANNA SWIM IN THE POOL?
IT'S FUSION, STEVEN!
IT'S LIKE SAPPHIRE
DOESN'T EVEN CARE!
AND WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE BIGGER GEM ABOUT THIS.
WE'RE ALWAYS
THE BIGGER GEM!
WELL, NOT THIS TIME!
NOT ABOUT THIS!
COME ON, WHY DON'T YOU COME
COOL DOWN IN THE POOL?
I DON'T NEED TO COOL DOWN!
COME ON, RUBY.
THE WATER'S NICE!
WHY DOES SHE ALWAYS ACT LIKE
I'M BEING RIDICULOUS?
JUST BECAUSE SHE WANTS
TO PRETEND
THAT SHE DOESN'T
HAVE FEELINGS?!
UH, RUBY?
[ GRUMBLING ]
YOU MADE A WARM SPOT!
AH! A HOT SPOT!
BOILING!
[ GASPS ]
UH, I'M GONNA GO BACK
TO THE ROOM.
[ SHIVERS ]
SAPPHIRE?
HELLO, STEVEN.
A-ARE YOU...
D-D-DOIN' OKAY?
I'M FINE.
O-OKAY.
W-WANNA WATCH TV TOGETHER?
SURE.
HUH. THE CHANNELS ARE
ALL THE WRONG NUMBERS.
HEY, CAN YOU USE YOUR
FUTURE POWERS
TO PREDICT WHAT CHANNEL
I'D LOVE THE MOST?
HMM...43.
BUT THERE'S NOT MUCH ON.
[ CHANGES CHANNEL ]
HEY, SAPPHIRE...
EVEN IF I DO,
RUBY WON'T LISTEN.
HUH?
YOU'RE GOING TO SAY
I SHOULD TALK TO RUBY,
BUT IT WON'T HELP.
B-BUT SHE SEEMS
REALLY UPSET.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE CAN'T STAY MAD
AT PEARL FOREVER,
AND SHE CAN'T STAY MAD
AT ME FOREVER.
AND THEN SHE'LL COME BACK
AND SEE THAT I'M RIGHT.
A-A-ARE YOU S-SURE?
I CAN SEE THE PATH OF FATE AS IT
STRETCHES TOWARD THE HORIZON.
RUBY CAN'T AVOID
THE INEVITABLE.
SHE'S JUST LETTING HER EMOTIONS
GET OUT OF HAND.
N-N-NOT YOU, THOUGH?
NO.
I'M...GOING TO
THE BATHROOM.
ALSO INEVITABLE.
UH, SAPPHIRE?
THE TOILET'S FROZEN.
SUCH IS FATE.
AM I FATED TO PEE OUTSIDE
ON THE GRASS, TOO?
YES.
"KEYSTONE STATE"...
HEY, STU-BALL,
I BROUGHT DINNER.
HEY, DAD. HOW'D IT GO?
WELL, HE WASN'T AN AXE MURDERER,
SO THAT WAS GOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUTSIDE
IN YOUR BATHING SUIT?
AND WHERE'S GARNET?
HE'S NOT GOING TO LIKE
THAT IT'S SQUARE.
OH, BOY.
WHERE'S THE OTHER ONE?
SHE'S PACING AROUND IN
WHAT USED TO BE THE POOL.
SOMETHING PRETTY SERIOUS
MUST BE GOING ON
IF IT MADE GARNET SPLIT UP.
BUT HEY, WE CAN STILL HAVE
A GOOD TIME.
SQUARE PIZZA?!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THIS
CRAZY STATE?!
SON, THERE'LL COME A TIME
IN YOUR LIFE
WHEN YOU LEARN TO ACCEPT
ALL PIZZA.
WHY CAN'T RUBY AND SAPPHIRE
JUST MAKE UP?
SOMETIMES PEOPLE THAT
LOVE EACH OTHER
CAN HURT EACH OTHER'S FEELINGS
WITHOUT MEANING TO.
WE SHOULD JUST GIVE THEM
SOME SPACE.
BUT I THINK THEY'D WORK IT OUT
IF THEY'D JUST
TALK TO EACH OTHER.
EVERYTHING WILL BE BETTER
IN THE MORNING.
WE'LL ALL GO TO
THE BEST DINER IN THE WORLD,
WHERE THEY'LL EAT THE BEST
BREAKFAST IN THE WORLD.
YOU THINK THAT'LL HELP?
NOTHING LIKE A LITTLE BREAKFAST
TO BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER.
YOU REALLY ARE
MY FAVORITE DAD.
I KNEW THIS PIZZA WOULD
PUT ME OVER THE TOP.
[ WHISTLING ]
HEY!
THANK YOU.
THANKS!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOT HUNGRY?
GEMS DON'T
NEED TO EAT, DAD.
EH, GARNET LIKES
TO EAT SOMETIMES.
UGH!
WELL, GARNET'S NOT HERE!
MMM.
OH, BOY!
THIS REALLY IS
THE BEST DINER IN THE WORLD!
YOU'RE SHAKING THE TABLE.
OH?! HEH!
I'M KINDA SURPRISED YOU FELT
ANYTHING AT ALL, TO BE HONEST!
I DIDN'T NEED TO FEEL --
I SAW.
EVERYTHING'S JUST SO CRYSTAL
CLEAR TO YOU, ISN'T IT?!
THIS WILL PASS.
SHE'LL EVENTUALLY JUST
BURN HERSELF OUT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
I AM AN ETERNAL FLAME, BABY!
[ GASPS ]
YOU DON'T KNOW ME!
[ ARGUING ]
Greg: HEY, IT'S OKAY, PAL!
WE CAN STILL SAVE THIS!
WHY DON'T WE JUST BAG THESE UP
TO GO AND --
AH, GEEZ.
Both: STEVEN!
I WAS SO HAPPY WHEN GARNET SAID
SHE WAS GONNA COME ON THIS TRIP
WITH ME AND DAD!
HOME'S BEEN AWFUL.
HERE'S BEEN AWFUL!
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO
HAVE A FUN TIME,
BUT EVERYONE'S BEEN
ACTING AWFUL, TOO!
IT -- IT JUST CAME WITH US.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IS IT -- IS IT ME?
NO! STEVEN, IT'S ALL US!
BUT WE MADE HIM FEEL
LIKE IT WAS HIS FAULT.
I KEEP LOOKING INTO THE FUTURE
WHEN ALL OF THIS HAS
ALREADY BEEN SOLVED,
AS IF IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW YOU FEEL IN THE PRESENT.
[ Crying ] NO WONDER YOU THINK
I DON'T CARE!
SAPPHIRE!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT!
I-I DIDN'T WANT TO LOOK FOR
A SOLUTION.
I JUST WANTED TO BE MAD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ALWAYS RIGHT.
I WAS BEING STUPID.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE STUPID!
I'M SORRY.
YOU HONESTLY THINK I'M NOT
UPSET ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED?
I WAS JUST TRYING TO DO
THE RIGHT THING.
I KNOW.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU KNOW WHAT'S NICE ABOUT
BEING SPLIT UP?
WHAT?
I GET TO LOOK AT YOU.
PFFT!
[ LAUGHS ]
BE SERIOUS!
THERE'S MY LAFFY SAFFY!
SHH! YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME
IN FRONT OF STEVEN!
[ BOTH GIGGLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
WELL, I PAID FOR BREAKFAST...
AND THE DAMAGE TO THE BOOTH.
ANYHOO, I THINK I'M
ALL VACATIONED OUT.
READY TO CALL IT A DAY?
NOT BEFORE WE GET OUR FREE ICE!
GARNET!
WE'RE HOME!
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY I KEEP --
OH!
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU ALL HAD FUN.
YEAH, IT ALL WORKED OUT!
GARNET, HOW ARE YOU?
NOT NOW.
SHE'S SPEAKING TO ME
AGAIN...KIND OF.
THAT REALLY WAS
A GREAT TRIP.
[ GASPS ]
CAN WE GO BACK?
MAYBE ONE DAY...
BUT NOT TO THAT DINER.
OH, BOY.
[ CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING ]