♪ We ♪
♪ Are the crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl ♪
And Steven!
Give...me...
the...
Just hurry up and say it,
Steven.
Mm, actually...
what else you got?
You could order
actual fries.
Nah. Let's really try and shake
things up today.
I want to order
"off menu."
[ Sighs ]
You always order
off menu, Steven.
Let me see
what I can find.
I'll be back in a sec.
I really appreciate it!
[ Birds chirping ]
Steven!
Check this out!
Boom!
Mozzarella sticks!
With all the fixin's?!
I can't
believe it either!
They were way back in the
freezer for some reason.
Feels good to fry something else
for a change.
Thanks, Peedee.
[ Humming ]
[ Munches ]
Steven!
What is this?!
Um...
Bread...
cheese...
marinara sauce!
The basic elements
of a pizza!
Where did it come from?
Mm.
Fryman...
infringing
on my business.
I have been ready
for this day!
[ Muffled ]
"Now serving fries!"?!
So...it begins anew.
Eh, Kofi?
Just like old times,
Fryman.
Kofi!
Fryman!
Both: Res-tau-rant
wa-a-a-a-a-a-a-r!
[ Gull cries ]
Oh!
Man: Too many carbs.
Peedee?
Don't look at me,
Steven.
But...
I said,
don't look at me!
W-What happened?
I violated
the food treaty.
What do you mean?
Years ago...
my dad and Kofi
signed an agreement
to not steal each
other's business,
but when I fried up
those mozzarella sticks,
I re-ignited
the hot oil of war.
[ Sighs ]
Don't blame yourself.
I was the one who wanted
to shake things up.
Oh, yeah.
It's your fault.
Hey, Steven!
As a valued customer,
I want to know your thoughts
on our new menu item --
deep-fried pizza.
A-Actually, could I just
get some fries?
Sorry,
we're all out of fries.
What?!
Even the bits?!
We have pizza bits now.
But how can you guys
be out of fries?
This is the Fry Shop!
You're Fryman!
Look at your hair.
What about my hair?
[ Groans ]
I can't connect to
Fish Stew Pizza's Wi-Fi!
Hey, you got no time
for Interneting.
You're doing
deliveries now.
But I don't even
have a car!
You got those wheelie shoes,
don't ya?
Yeah.
[ Phone rings, bell jingles ]
Jenny, you're working
the counter?
I know, right?
Things have been crazy since
the war has been back on!
The phones have been ringing
off the hook.
I'll get it!
Thanks for calling
Fish Stew Pizza.
We do fries now.
Anyway, I'm obligated
to tell you
about our special
new menu item --
French-fried pizza
with a French-fried crust
and twice-baked French fries
on the side.
[ Sighs ]
'Cause we do fries now.
I'd rather just have
my usual --
Steven!
Oh. Hey, Kofi.
Before you place
your order,
you must sign [grunts]
these papers...
and pledge your allegiance
to Fish Stew Pizza!
Not only that, you'll be issued
a brand-new, permanent,
V.I.P.
pizza-eater card!
Aah!
[ Bell jingles ]
Steven!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Come back!
Hey, Steven, y-you forgot
your pizza bits!
What? Aah!
Steven, let me reward you
for being such a good customer!
Aah!
What have I done?!
Thank you all for coming.
Ronaldo...
Kiki...Jenny...
and Peedee, I've called you all
here tonight because...
this war between your parents
has to stop!
Steven, how do you think
we feel?!
Do you know how many metal
concerts I've missed
because of this war?
How many?
Mm, like...one.
Do you know how much blogging
I haven't been able to do?!
I don't,
but this is all my fault!
If only my taste buds weren't
so adventurous.
But I promise to find a way
to work this out!
How?
There's no end in sight
to all this fighting.
Hmm.
We need to stop this hate
with some sort of opposite
of hate.
[ Gasps ]
Ronaldo!
Hmm?
-Kiki!
-Hmm?
You're sitting
next to each other.
Where are you going
with this, Steven?
You guys should pretend
to be in love!
There won't be any time
for fighting
if your families have to plan
a wedding together!
Well...
I guess we could try?
Anything to get this war
over with.
All right!
We'll fight this war
with the power of love!
No way!
We can't do this
because I...
have a girlfriend.
Where's she at, though?
You said
what I was thinking.
Okay, you don't have to pretend
to get married.
Just pretend to be in love
long enough
to get this feud
over with.
I...
got a bad feeling
about this.
Shut up, Ronaldo!
Nothing bad
is going to happen,
and you'll get
to spend time
with the cutest girl
in Beach City.
[ Sputters ]
[ Giggles ]
Ah, Kiki, my darling!
Oh, Ronaldo, my sweet!
My dear, sweet Kiki,
who I love with all my blog.
What the...
[ Giggles ]
Oh, Ronaldo,
you're so sweet and quirky
in a way I can tolerate.
Kiki, why aren't you in here,
working your shift?!
Yeah, come on, Ronaldo.
We got customers
to take care of.
But, Dad, ever since
this war started,
I've had to spend
countless hours
away from my beloved Kiki.
What?!                    What?!
It's true.
The only way for us to be
together is if we quit working!
Are you telling me
that you two
are involved in
a romantic relationship?!
That's right, Steven.
We have been for some time now.
Mm-hmm!
You two are only hugging,
right?
Uh, yes, sir!
Just hugs and longing looks!
[ Chuckling nervously ]
Well, Kofi,
love is a beautiful thing.
Yes, love is beautiful.
We must end this feud in order
for this love to blossom.
Yeah!
The restaurant war
is officially over!
Ronaldo?
[ Wind whistling ]
I come all this way to return
your "Koala Princess" DVDs,
only to find you
with another girl?
Both:
Wha-a-a-a-a-t?!
Jane, my sweet,
this was all just a trick
to get my dad to stop selling
mozzarella sticks!
Save it for your blog --
Keep Beach City Single!
Jane, my ohime sama!
Ohh!
The deal is off!
Fine by me!
Peedee, fire up those fryers!
Kiki, pick up the phone!
[ All sigh ]
[ Crying ] Jane!
Ugh,
what are we gonna do?!
Mm...
Peedee said the last time
the war ended
because your dad and his dad
came together to sign a treaty.
How did that happen?
Well, you know
where Suitcase Sam's is?
It used to be a restaurant
called The Everything Buffet.
Oh, yeah!
They sold everything!
But it wrecked
the boardwalk's economy!
Not one store
could compete.
But just when everyone thought
all hope was lost,
our dad and Fryman teamed up
and ran them out of town.
Hmm.
Another restaurant, eh?
I think I have a plan.
Welcome to the grand opening
of Steven's.
Right this way.
♪ La, la-la, la, la, la ♪
Hmm, nice ambiance.
[ Clears throat ]
It's all right.
There are not
enough tables!
There are just enough
tables, Daddy.
M La, la-la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la ♪
Hello, gentlemen.
May I take your order?
I'm full --
of sadness!
[ Crying ]
I will have
the Fantastic Fries.
Order taken.
I bet they're not
as fantastic as ours.
And for you?
I will have
the Pizza Bagel!
I doubt a Pizza Bagel can beat
pizza that isn't on a bagel.
[ Chuckles ]
Ah, let's see.
Wonderful --
two of our best dishes.
Our only dishes.
Amethyst, order up!
Fire one fry and one pizza!
[ Claps ]
Yes, Chef!
[ Twinkle! ]
Here's your order, sir.
[ Scoffs ]
Pizza on a bagel, indeed!
Pearl:
And for you, sir.
Uh, can I get some ketchup?
Sorry, no additions
or substitutions.
[ Chuckles ]
This place is all talk.
You can't have fries
without ketchup.
[ Munches ]
[ Zing! ]
The ketchup...
is inside the fries?!
Heh.
There's cream cheese
in this pizza bagel.
It adds a whole other level
of flavor!
And with pizza on a bagel,
you can eat pizza anytime!
It's amazing!
It's genius!
Mm-hmm!
Hmm.
Ah, gentlemen,
I hope you enjoyed
your meal.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Steven, we didn't want to have
to do this, but...
Please,
shut this place down!
What's this?
You want me to close
my lovely establishment?
Steven, we're begging you!
We can't compete with a place
like this!
You'll drive us
out of business!
There's already a line!
I'll close up shop
under one condition.
Both: Anything!
Stop this foolish war!
Cook for yourselves and the good
of the boardwalk!
No more cooking
out of hate and spite!
Let's just do
what we do best!
Agreed!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Good job, Daddy.
Do you hear that, Ronaldo?
The war's over!
[ Crying ]
Glad that's settled.
Y'all help me
clean this place up.
Sorry.
We on break.
[ Claps ]
[ Pop! ]
♪ Look at you go ♪
♪ I just adore you ♪
♪ I wish that I knew ♪
♪ What makes you think
I'm so special ♪
STEVEN:
Two forks, it's fancy.
[ Humming ]
Mm-hmm.
Some mood lighting.
Some classy decor.
There! Mwah!
This is so nice!
[ Knock on door ]
[ Gasps ] Pizza time!
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
Kiki!
Ha ha!
Hey, Steven!
Cheddar cheese crust
with double pepperoni?
Oh, thanks!
But doesn't Jenny
usually do deliveries?
I had to take
double duty today
because Jenny busted
the pizza car.
What?!
[ Sighs ] Yeah.
Who knew blasting one
of sour cream's mix tapes
could blow out the tires?
Well, his drops
are pretty dirty.
Guess so.
Anyways, it means I've got
to deliver all these orders
by foot while Jenny takes
the car to the shop.
Oh?
Looks fancy!
You having anybody
cute over, Steven?
You mean, besides me?
[ Chuckles nervously ]
I'm taking some "me" time.
You want in?
Thanks, Steven, but I still
have to run around town
and deliver
all these pizzas.
There's a lot of other people
having "me" time tonight.
But it's all right,
I love running!
Anyways,
got to get back to it!
Later, Steven!
See ya!
[ Panting ]
Poor Kiki.
Pizza time!
Whoo!
[ Snoring ]
Yeah, whoo!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[ Laughing ]
Whoo-hoo!
Those initials are looking
pretty slick, Steven.
Whoa!
Cool!
A pizza dream!
Hey, look!
It's cheese me!
[ Laughing ]
Oh, gross!
[ Screams ] Ew, ew!
[ Coughing ]
Kiki?!
Are you all right?
My leg!
[ Grunting ]
[ Screams ]
What was that thing?!
Keep going!
It won't give up!
Wha?!
I'll take care of this!
Steven, be careful!
Don't worry about me!
Anything is possible
when you have
rockets for bones!
Steven,
that was so brave!
Well, it's cheddar
than nothing!
Oh, hey, dog-copter.
[ Meows ]
See ya, dream Kiki!
Oh, okay.
See you, dream Steven!
[ Laughing ]
Dream Steven!
Man, I can't wait to tell
Kiki about my weird --
Please, Kiki,
just one more time?
I seriously
can't miss this show.
It's Uber Rage's first concert
back in the States
since they got banned!
Jenny, I'm not sure.
I've covered for you
for almost two weeks now!
Kiki, seriously, this concert
is gonna change my life!
And the ticket was,
like, $40!
Is that a lot
for a concert?
It's...
more than average?
Okay, I'll cover you.
Yes!
That's why you're
my favorite twin!
I'm your only twin.
Mwah! I'll get you a shirt
or something.
[ Starts engine ]
Hey, Steven!
Oh, and don't tell dad!
That was really
nice of you!
Yep, that's me --
the nice one.
I came here to tell you
I had the craziest dream
about you last night,
Kiki!
I was flying around,
and I pulled you out of
an ocean of cheese!
And then these hands formed
and came after you.
And then you saved me
and flew off on a rocket dog?
"Dream Kiki" was you?
"Dream Steven" was you?!
I'm -- I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to go
into your mind, I --
No, this is great!
You're not mad?
Steven, I always
have that dream,
and I always drown!
I haven't gotten a good
night's sleep in weeks!
You're my total hero, Steven.
Can you do it again?
Oh...
Of course!
I'd really love to help!
Thank goodness!
Because...
I seriously have that dream,
like, every single night.
[ Telephone rings ]
Oh, I got to go!
Seriously, Steven,
thank you so much!
See you later!
In your dreams!
Ha ha! Nice!
I'm a dream warrior!
[ Snoring ]
[ Screams ]
Hey, Kiki!
It's time
to cut the cheese!
Hyah!
Wow!
♪♪
Dream warrior!
Prepare yourself...
for my grate-est technique yet!
Hyah!
Whoa!
Dream warrior.
Dream warrior...
Aah!
Here I come.
[ Yawns ]
Hey, Kiki.
[ Snoring ]
[ Groans ]
Huh?
KIKI: Steven?
Kiki?
[ Chuckles ]
You're upside down!
Did you sleep okay?
[ Yawns ]
Yeah, like a baby.
What's happening?
Here.
Pizza?
For breakfast?
It's 3:00.
Oh.
More of
a late-afternoon lunch.
[ Chomp ]
Delicious.
[ Screams ] Steven?
Kiki, you got
to quit your job!
What?
I think you have a serious
problem with pizza.
I don't have a problem
with pizza.
I don't know, Kiki,
I think you do!
I'm sorry.
I -- I didn't mean to yell.
No, it's okay.
I get it.
I've been asking
too much of you.
I just wish these dreams
would stop.
Maybe we've been going
about this all wrong.
What do you mean?
Hmm.
We've just been looking at
the toppings of the problem.
We've got to track this
back to the sauce!
But after this,
I can't help you anymore, okay?
I'm just too tired.
I understand.
All right.
Tonight, we end
these nightmares
once and for all!
[ Snoring ]
♪♪
You ready, Steven?
Time to cut the cheese.
Shing!
Sorry for using
the same pun twice.
That's not a pun,
but I forgive you!
[ Gasps ]
Huh?
We can't keep fighting off
the cheese --
it just won't stop!
You're right!
We got to find out where all
this cheese is coming from!
Oh!                          Oh!
[ Gasps ] Look!
Huh?
STEVEN: Whoa!
It's me?
Now, that is nasty.
[ Clicking like dolphin ]
Aah! Anchovies!
And pepperanhas!
Ahh.
That was close!
[ Man groaning ]
Who's that?!
They sound like
they're in pain!
We got to find them!
Jenny?                    Jenny?
[ Groaning ] Kiki!
I'm here, Jenny!
Oh!
Oh, no!
I'll help you, Kiki!
Wait, I think she's trying
to tell me something!
Kiki...
What is it, Jenny?
Thanks for delivering
all those pizzas for me.
Oh, it's okay.
I totally don't mind.
That's what twins are for.
Whoa!
[ Grunting ]
Kiki, you're lying!
What?
You totally do mind!
Aaagh!
It doesn't matter!
Yes, it does!
Your feelings matter,
just tell her "no."
Ugh, I -- I can't!
Why not?
I...
I don't want to let her down!
I'm her favorite twin!
When I said I couldn't help you
anymore after this,
you understood!
But this is different,
she's my sister!
That's right!
And she cares about you, too!
Do you think she'd want
to put you through this?
No.
Does she even know this
is happening to you?
No.
You got to tell her!
Hey, Kiki,
I want to ask you
something.
There's gonna be
a really cool cheese rave
in the pizza cave tonight.
I have to be there.
Will you
cover for me again?
No!
[ Groans ]
Okay, fine.
♪♪
You did it!
Yeah!
All the cheese is gone!
Well, most of it.
Man, dreams are weird.
Yeah.
[ Yawns ]
They sure are.
[ Seagulls squawking ]
Hi, Jenny.
Oh, hey, Steven.
Is Kiki around?
I wanted to see
if she's doing okay.
[ Yawns ]
I just spent all night
helping her fight
her inner cheese demons.
I don't know what that means,
but Kiki is fine.
She's taking the day off.
This morning,
we had a twin talk.
She said I was using up
all her "me" time,
and I was like, if you're just
gonna spend your "me" time
running anyway, you might as
well carry some pizzas for me.
But I can't say no
to my favorite twin.
So where is she?
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
She deserves a break after
working so hard for me.
Right, Steven?
[ Snoring ]
Steven?
♪ Look at you go ♪
♪ I just adore you ♪
♪ I wish that I knew ♪
♪ What makes ♪
♪ You think I'm so special ♪