♪♪
Oh, man, that is
classic cinema.
So good!
Oh, and remember
when the surgeon
tried to cut
the mole queen in half
but then she multiplied
into a million mole babies
and then they ate him?
[imitates chainsaw]
[growling]
-Aah!
-[Webby laughs]
You said this was
an educational film.
Suitable for all ages.
Uh, it's a cautionary tale
about the dangers
of mole monsters.
And everyone
could use a lesson
on chainsaw safety.
[Louie]
Lame!
Where was
the drama,
the heart,
the needlessly expensive
car crash mayhem?
Even if mole men
did exist,
why attack someone
in the shower?
With the water running
there wouldn't be
enough traction to attack
anyone above the knee.
Totally phony.
What is with you guys?
It says
right on the poster:
Based on an actual
true novel.
This is the only book
I trust.
If it's not in the
Junior Woodchuck guidebook,
then it's not a thing.
What about
were-ducks?
-Nope.
-Tri-clopses?
-Not a thing.
-Well, what about
the legendary
Terra-firmians
of Duckburg?
[sighs]
Let's see.
Pterodactyl, terror-dactyl,
terrible twos.
Nope.
No Terra-firmians.
-Must not exist.
-[Webby laughing]
What? Terra-firmians,
the mythical
underground race
that live below
our very city?
[chuckles]
No. That's ridiculous.
No, you're ridiculous.
Children, children,
there's an easy way
to settle this.
Let's go find them
ourselves.
[Mrs. Beakley]
Ahem.
-[Launchpad screams]
-[gasps]
You evil! Evil!
You took the form
of a poster.
You won't get Launchpad!
Stop, Launchpad. No!
It's just an ad.
That's exactly
what the sheriff told
those reckless teens.
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck-blur ♪
♪ We might solve
a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales, whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do ♪
♪ Bad and good-luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ D-d-danger lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? ♪
♪ Just grab on
to some Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there ♪
♪ Making Ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Ducktales! ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh! ♪
Wait, shouldn't we
tell someone
where we're going
before we blindly
explore a network
of dark and abandoned
subway tunnels?
-We're heading down
into the subway.
-We'll be fine.
-Okay, don't wait up.
-Ah, much better.
[Mrs. Beakley]
I apologize
for my associate.
You can bill McDuck Enterprises
for the poster.
Uh, what about the damages
to the men's room?
The men's room?
They come up
through the toilet.
Anyone could be
a mole monster.
Anyone.
Could be him or her
or that baby.
Even him.
All right, let's go
before anything else happens.
Wait, where are Huey
and Webby and... Lena?
[Huey and Webby grunt]
Hmm.
Now what's behind here?
The old 818 train line.
Famous for
Terra-firmian sightings.
That's why
it's closed off.
The signs say
"closed for renovations."
That's what they
want you to think.
Who is they?
Exactly.
What?
[both grunting]
Well, we can't not go in
at this point.
Hello?!
[distant rumbling]
[chuckles]
These old tunnels.
You can hear
train vibrations
from miles away.
That was no
subway train.
The Terra-firmians
are an ancient race
built of two warring tribes.
The Terries
and the Firmies.
They were once united
under a proud king.
After the king's
untimely death,
an epic battle began over
who would assume control.
But one day the
rightful prince
will reunite
the two tribes
and put an end to
their bitter conflict.
And what's that?
Oh, just a drawing
of a candy
I wish they made.
-Webbi-dings.
-And that?
Me as a superhero.
Look, can we just focus
on all the exciting
stuff I just said?
So these Terra thingies
are responsible
for that tremor?
According to the JWG,
earthquakes are shifting
tectonic plates.
Science fact.
No reason for any of us
to go in there.
The book knows
everything.
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
[book thuds, crashes]
Did the book know
I was gonna do that?
Hmm.
[rat squeaking]
Oh, I can't wait to meet
a real Terra-firmian!
I'm totally gonna
sacrifice myself
in the name of
the rebellion.
Oh, and then I can
hunt down your attackers
-and avenge your death.
-Aww!
That's sweet.
There!
Claw marks!
Proof they were here.
Even better!
The tremors exposed
three kinds of rock.
Schist, marble,
and gneiss.
Ooh, do I spy
some shale?
How is that better
than subway monsters?
'Cause my thing's real.
How can you dismiss this
after all the stuff
we've seen
with Mr. McDuck?
Most of that is actually
logged in the guidebook.
Even the headless
man-horse?
It's a big book.
Anything new, I add myself.
Now help me
with the shale rock.
Need it
for my geology badge.
Why don't you ask
your best friend,
the guidebook,
to help you?
Oh, wait, you can't.
It's a book.
"How to properly handle
rock samples in the field."
Hmm. Ahem. Mm-hmm.
[straining]
[Lena screaming]
[Huey gasps]
-[loud rattle]
-[both gasp]
What was that?
[Lena straining]
Um, after you.
-Terra-firmian!
-[gasps]
[Lena laughing]
[sighs]
Sorry, couldn't resist.
Just more subway junk.
Now, if you're all done,
I have some
rock samples
to collect.
-[all] Aah!
-[whimpering]
Oh! Hey, watch it!
Louie?
Granny?
Aah! Those are moles!
Launchpad, it's
just the guys.
Uh, you would say that.
Have there always been
three of them?
I can explain.
You are all
in big trouble.
I assume this was
your idea.
[scoffs] Sure, blame
the mysterious rebel
playing by her own rules.
No back talk!
You made me come
all the way down here,
drag two more children
and one man-child
right into danger.
Man-child? Where?
[shudders]
Easy, LP. Easy.
One monster at a time.
Aren't you supposed to be
crazy adventure family?
This is like an afternoon
field trip for you people.
Well, there won't be anymore
afternoon field trips for you.
I can assure you that.
Granny, Lena didn't
mean to--
[all startle]
Terra-firmians!
Naturally occurring
tectonic shifts!
[sighs] Splendid.
We're stuck.
It looks like the only
safe way out of here
is to get
this train moving.
Launchpad, get to
the control room.
No, Mrs. B.
I can't leave you alone with--
I mean, uh...
I don't know if I can.
I've never crashed
a train before.
Well, maybe you can
drive the train
without crashing it.
Huh?
[sighs] Just get
to the control room
and see what you can do.
Fine. Hey, Dewey,
come with me.
I need someone to help me
for some reason.
Just in case.
I'm going to the rear
to see if I can
detach us from the cave in.
You, with me.
You've caused us
enough grief.
Aye aye,
Colonel Crumpet.
We'll stay here
and be on the lookout
for Terra-firmians.
It must be about halftime
at The Great Games,
so it'll be easier
to spot one.
Okay.
Just stay put.
After you help us
get out of here
you're never
seeing Webby again.
Ugh, okay, lady,
you are real bad
at asking for help.
[sighs] Please talk
some sense into Webby.
You don't really believe
that rock monsters
are playing
earthquake games.
Huey's usually right
about nerd stuff.
Not this time.
Those aftershocks
are actually a revolt
led by the lost
Terra-firmian prince.
He's using the games
as a distraction
to storm the
Califermy Citadel!
It's all in this
artist rendering.
Ooh, that all
sounds awesome.
I want that to be true.
Earthquakes
are a result
of shifting
tectonic plates.
But who's pushing
the plates, Huey?
Who's pushing
the plates?!
Other plates are
pushing the plates.
Now who sounds
ridiculous?
Louie, whose side
are you on?
Oh, neither.
This is just
way more entertaining
than that movie.
[chewing loudly]
What? I got a refill
on the way out.
-It's encouraged.
-[rumbling]
Hmm, probably just
some left over rubble
from the cave in.
[loud banging]
I'm coming,
Your Highness!
[grunts]
Webby, no!
Please, it's not safe!
Oh, this could be it.
This could be the prince.
This could be...
a rock?
Oh, see? Just a boulder
from the cave in.
[loud rumbling]
Can we go back inside
before we're crushed?
No. Just because
this is only a rock
doesn't mean
there aren't
Terra-firmians
still out there.
So we're supposed to examine
every rock in this tunnel?
That actually sounds
pretty fun.
Wait, that's not the point!
[Mrs. Beakley straining]
Looking good,
Tea Time.
Keep it up.
-[Huey]
...to an accurate analysis,
...would be impossible.
[Mrs. Beakley grunting]
This would go a lot faster
if you would give me a hand.
Well, the sooner
I help you,
the sooner I
never get to see
my friends again, so...
Ugh.
-[straining]
-Want me to go get
one of the more
trustworthy kids to help,
or am I still not allowed
to talk to them?
Do not mouth off to me.
It's your fault
we're in this mess.
Who raised you,
anyway?
I know a bad influence
when I see one.
Those are good children
with bright futures.
Yeah? And what
does that make me?
I don't know.
If you're gonna vandalize,
at least do it right.
So, Dew, it's nice
down here, huh?
Kinda natural for you.
Know what I like?
Dirt. Dirt's pretty
cool and comfy, huh?
No grass to eat
without dirt.
-I guess.
-But I hate the sun.
Not into that.
Gets into your
beady, little eyes.
Makes everything all hot.
Plus, it makes it
a lot harder
to possess people.
No, thanks.
Am I right?
Launchpad, do you think
I'm a mole monster?
What? No, no.
Can't believe my best friend
is a mole monster.
I'm your best friend?
Oh, no, it can
hear my thoughts.
Keep it together,
Launchpad.
Gotta change
the subject somehow.
Hey, you know what
we should talk about?
-Another subject.
-Sure.
He doesn't suspect a thing.
[indistinct arguing]
-I say one thing.
-You have a very
-active imagination, Webby.
-You are ridiculous!
[indistinct arguing]
But this is a rock.
Not a Terra-something.
A stupid rock!
That suddenly disappeared.
Ooh, nice twist.
Um, anything could've
happened to that rock.
-Could've rolled off.
-Rolled off up?
And out of this dent?
I don't think so.
Uh, maybe it disintegrated
or a sudden wormhole.
They're always good for an
unexplained disappearance.
Or we could all be
seeing things
because of a methane gas leak.
Let me check the JWG.
-[rumbling]
-[gasps]
Are we all seeing that?
That? That's, uh,
sparks from
faulty wiring.
Or maybe a crazed
sewer killer
with a flashlight?
And I'm still not counting out
a methane gas leak.
Not everything is
a methane gas leak!
-It's gone.
-Oh, that's way creepier.
[power surging]
Aah! My eyes.
Aah! I knew it. Mole man!
Everything I've ever seen
in a movie is real!
[Launchpad screaming]
[both grunting]
Launchpad,
let me in!
Not on your life,
mole man.
Hmm. I suppose you're
good for something.
Ugh, don't hurt yourself with
the compliments, Abbey Road.
-I'm just trying to help.
-All right, I've had it
up to here with your
horrid behavior!
[Lena gasping]
[Lena exclaims]
Come on!
[Lena panting]
[all gasp]
[all screaming, grunt]
[gasps]
[all screaming]
This can't be happening!
Down here!
[Huey grunting]
[Launchpad whimpering]
Aah!
-[monster growling]
-[brakes squealing]
[all exclaim]
-Aah!
-Oh!
[both exclaiming]
[coughing]
Phew! Crashed it.
-[growling]
-[screaming]
Back, mole monster!
You can't take me, too!
Mr. McD won't
give me the time off!
Launchpad, it's me, Dewey.
Aah!
[sighs] Your best friend?
They could be anyone.
They are everywhere.
Yes, anyone could be
a mole monster
in the movie.
This is real life.
Classic mole monster
saying he's "not"
a mole monster.
Ugh! By that logic
how do you know
you're not
a mole monster?
'Cause I'm not.
Which is exactly
what a mole monster would say.
Wait, am I a mole monster?
But I'm a good guy.
Then that means mole monsters
can also be good guys.
Come, mole brother.
This is a new day
for our people.
We will show the world
that we can be good.
[Lena straining]
Leave her, Lena.
She'll never trust you.
She's keeping you
from them.
Leave her and we'll
be better off.
[Mrs. Beakley groans]
-[rumbling]
-[gasps]
[rumbling continues]
[Lena straining]
[gasps]
[rumbling]
[groaning]
[exclaims]
Aah!
[sighs] You.
Yeah, me.
Let's go.
-Huey!
-Where are you?
Huey?!
[gasps]
Huey, come on.
We gotta go!
Can't.
Need to stay near the light.
I can still see.
The Junior Woodchuck guidebook
says I'm statistically
safer this way.
If you stay here
you'll be crushed.
At least I'll know
what's crushing me.
Who knows what's out there.
-[rumbling]
-[all gasp]
We know what's out there.
Terra-firmians!
But if they're real,
then what other crazy things
are out there just waiting
for me in the dark?
The only way to know
is to find out together.
Uh, okay,
I didn't see that coming.
Really came together
in the third act.
-[rumbling]
-[all screaming]
[Webby panting]
Mm.
Everyone here?
Everyone okay?
Oh, yeah.
We're A-okay.
Just a couple of
normal non-monster folk
eager to help out.
A way out?
There's a way out!
[Webby]
Huey, wait!
Aah!
-[growls]
-[startles]
[gasping]
-[gasp]
-Huh?
I told you
they were real.
He must be the prince.
And the others
are his rebel force.
They must've gotten
trapped down here.
This must be the prince
of the bill-faced creatures
of the land above.
And the others
are his rebel force.
I told you
they were real.
[Mrs. Beakley]
Huey!
[both]
Boop.
That was interesting.
We still need
to find a way out.
-[rumbling]
-Look!
They smashed us
an exit.
Thank you, fellow
underground creatures.
Sorry I doubted you.
I'm proud of you, Huey.
Facing your fears,
embracing the unknown...
And... loved it!
No longer unknown.
They exist.
Science fact.
[sighs] That feels
so much better.
Ugh.
I really could get
used to being down here.
I love being
a mole monster!
Launchpad, you are
not a mole monster.
Oh, well, all right.
Makes sense.
Why didn't you leave
the big purple one?
She's getting in the way
of our plans.
[Mrs. Beakley]
Lena.
Listen, dear, I may have been
a bit quick to judge you.
Would you like to join us
at the mansion for pancakes?
Now, when you say "pancakes"
do you mean like actual pancakes
or English muffins
covered in maple syrup?
I mean actual pancakes.
Then yes.
Lena, you're welcome
at the mansion any time.
That's why.
Gotta play the long game.
Hey, wait up!
[hisses]