♪♪
Ah! Good morning,
you gleaming bit of bounty.
- Beakley?
- I feel I should prepare you.
for what's out there.
How bad can it be?
Lid left off
the peanut butter.
Errant roller skate
left on the stairway.
An elaborate series
of cutthroat war games.
Take that.
Dewey, don't yell
at your target
before you fire.
You lose the element
of surprise.
( laughing )
Good hands, Beakley.
When I said you
should spend more time
with your family,
I did not mean
move them in.
Whoo hoo!
Target acquired.
You set traps?
It's just a game.
You're not a player,
you're a pawn.
Webby, maybe take it
down a notch.
- Tell that to my men
you captured in Peking.
- What?
It's part of
my character's backstory.
Grizzled ex-special forces
pulled out of retirement
for revenge. What's yours?
My guy has a dart gun?
Not anymore.
Ha ha!
( gasps )
The foyer's a safe zone.
The foyer's...
This is no foyer.
This is a tomb.
HUEY: Oh, my tailbone!
( laughing )
A tomb.
Sir, this is
out of control.
Kids will be kids.
For everyone's happiness,
we've all got
to make sacrifices.
Um, ocupado.
House meeting now!
♪ Life is like
a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duck Burg ♪
♪ Race cars, lasers,
airplanes ♪
♪ It's a duck blur ♪
♪ Might solve a mystery ♪
♪ Or rewrite history ♪
♪ Duck Tales
Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Tales of derring-do,
bad and good luck tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
♪ D-D-danger
lurks behind you ♪
♪ There's a stranger
out to find you ♪
♪ What to do? Just grab on
to some Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out there
making Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring
bad and good ♪
♪ Not ponytails
or cottontails ♪
♪ No, Duck Tales ♪
♪ Whoo ooh ♪
( all chattering )
All right.
Time for some house rules.
Rule one:
My space is my space.
My study,
my sleeping quarters.
My washroom.
Rule two:
defer to Mrs. Beakley
for all subsequent rules.
I'm pleased to
have you here,
as long as it
in no way
inconveniences me.
Good day.
This may be
Mr. McDuck's mansion,
but it's my house.
So... my house rules.
Exhaustive.
Comprehensive.
Where are you going?
I got unmentionables
to wash.
Rule 58:
If you need something,
ask for permission first.
Did you hear that, boys?
Ask permission.
Rule #23:
No one is above the rules...
Donald.
If you had simply
asked for assistance,
we could've avoided
what I'm referring to as
the "Undergarment Incident."
( kids laughing )
I can take care of myself.
That is not
your decision to make.
You live here,
you answer to me.
I answer to
no one!
- Wait, are they
gonna kiss?
- ALL: Eww!
BOTH: Outside now.
Death Darts
was fun.
Again, just supposed
to be darts.
What do you
wanna play next?
Mystery Murder Island,
Cannonball Fury?
How about a nice,
safe nap?
Oh, how about
Sacky Sack?
Or we could go
have some real fun.
- You mean...
- I do, dear Dewford.
It's time for
Funso's Fun Zone!
What's that?
Only the greatest place
one could ever
imagine imagining!
Where your dreams
become reality,
and reality becomes
some crazy kind of
hyper-dream.
Where punch refills
are free!
♪ Funso's Fun Zone ♪
♪ Where fun
is in the zone ♪
Oh, yeah.
That Funso's.
Of course.
Everyone knows Funso's.
Let's go, boys.
Oh. Well, have fun.
You coming?
What? Yeah!
Let me get my stuff.
I don't know. Webby's great
for treasure hunting
and mine cart chases,
but she's not exactly built
for every-day kid stuff.
I still see the darts
when I close my eyes.
She's been cooped up
in a mansion her whole life.
Of course she's gonna
be a little... off.
But we can help her;
she'll be fine.
All right, Webby,
just a totally casual hang-out
in the real world.
like regular kids do.
Play it cool,
play it cool.
Whooooo!
Hmm.
( humming )
Howdy, neighbor.
Kielbasa?
I'll just live on the boat
while I fix it.
Out of your house,
out of your way.
Causing several
fire hazards.
If you had checked with me,
I could've provided
safe electrical hook-ups.
- I'm good.
- And how would you like
to split the water bill?
Richest duck in Duck Burg
can't spare a dime.
Keep your water.
( excited whimpering )
You've been on a bus
before, right?
Absolutely.
So is it assigned
seating or...
Don't talk to anybody,
don't touch anything,
don't lick anything,
don't go near
the emergency brake.
Ooh, ooh. Ha ha!
I'm Webby.
Have you ever jumped
a ravine in this baby?
Can I try? I'm Webby.
Look, a dog,
wearing a bow tie.
Did he tie it
himself?
Stop the bus!
It was a nice
bow tie.
- Sorry.
- It's fine.
It's just a short walk
to Funso's.
Through the sketchiest
neighborhood in town.
Bet it's
a faster run.
Race ya!
( sighs )
Wrong way.
Whoop.
Hey, is that
the McDuck brats?
- Let's get 'em.
- Uh-uh.
Burger's right.
Ma told us
we's only supposed
to take down the truck.
Forget the truck.
That's the payday.
Think big.
Sorry, Carl.
Same time next month?
Funso's Fun Zone.
♪ Where fun
is in the zone ♪
WEBBY: Pizza?
Games?
A pit of balls?!
Sweet Webbigail,
ball pits are for babies.
Walk with me.
You're in the zone now.
If you wanna get by
in this world,
you gotta know
the people who make it spin.
Josie, new
token apron?
- Nice.
- ( giggles )
Your usual table, sir.
Merci, Toby.
Webby, your money
is no good here.
What do they take?
I have pounds, pesos, rubles.
The oldest currency
in the world.
Ancient obsidian
rune stones?
No, flattery.
Ahem. I can't tell.
Is that the heat lamps
or your natural glow?
Oh, Mr. Duck,
the usual?
Yep. One free cup
for water, please.
- That's not water.
- It's all part
of the system.
You try.
Hey, you.
Uh... Ja-nay.
It's Jane.
I'm Webby.
I was hoping you could
hook a gal up
with one of those
free water cups.
You know,
fruit punch.
You sure you don't
want it for water?
Yes, for water.
Fruity water...
that really
packs a punch.
Am I right?
I don't know
what you mean.
I mean fruit punch.
There a problem here?
What did I tell you about
handing out freebies, Jane?
You pay for
that punch, Duck?
I was just
about to.
Yeah.
Thanks, Webby.
( doorbell rings )
Special delivery
for D. Duck.
Come around back.
Portable generators.
Keep your power, Mrs. B.
This guy is off the grid.
That idiot is going
to get himself killed.
Hmm.
Welcome to Funso's.
There's no place finer.
All cool adults must be
accompanied by a minor.
Ba blee ba blam!
You buyin' this?
Uke Or Puke?
Behold, the best game
ever created!
Japanese import.
There's only one
in the U.S.
and I have
the top ten score,
so I'm pretty much
the best in the country.
You gotta try this.
I don't know.
I've never actually
played a computer game.
Do you play
an instrument?
I took seven years
of cello.
Same thing.
Oh!
Your first strum.
Cherish it.
( computer speaking
Japanese )
Yes, yes, be one
with the flow.
( speaking Japanese )
I am both uking
and puking.
- Time for...
- Strangers are danger!
Webby, no!
I killed Funso.
No, no.
Don't you die on me!
My scores.
No!!
It's like I don't
even know you anymore.
Perhaps we could put
your nephew up in a hotel.
In New Zealand.
No time.
Guest bath's a-callin'.
Beakley problem.
- Ow.
- Room for three more?
You guys aren't mad
I ruined Funso's?
Please. Funso's is
a place of magic
and wonder and light.
Think fast!
Wait. What's happening?
Nope, you're fine.
It's a trap.
I'm sinking.
( screaming )
( fire alarm blaring )
( nervous laugh )
I'm Webby.
You are banned
from Funso's for life.
No, please. I've never been
kicked out of anything.
And this is why I said
we shouldn't bring her.
Thanks, Dewey.
Funso, take them out.
With pleasure.
Call Ma.
You can't come in
without a child.
Everybody out!
This is it, Ma.
The big payday.
The perfect scam.
Save it.
What's so important
that I don't see
an armored car
parked out front?
May I present
our new meal ticket?
( imitates drum roll )
Scrooge McDuck's family.
( all jabbering )
And how did you
manage this?
Well, we cornered 'em,
we captured 'em,
and we sent him
a ransom note.
You did what?
How did someone so brilliant
raise such morons?
I think she's
talking about you.
But Scrooge will
pay a fortune
to get them
ankle biters back.
Do you think he got to be
the richest duck in Duck Burg
by paying people off?
You just painted
four twerp-size
targets on our backs.
Bouncer, Burger,
go wait outside.
What about me, Ma?
You're on
a time-out, mister.
Who are these guys?
The Beagle boys.
They hate your uncle.
Try to break into
the mansion all the time.
Are they gonna
ransom us?
Scrooge will never pay
for all four of us.
You're right.
He'll probably throw
one of us off a cliff
to send Scrooge
a message.
Scrooge, the kids!
The Beagle Boys!
Wait. Something's wrong.
Much better.
Mrs. B., a brick,
a note.
Look who's finally
coming to ask for my--
Help!!
What is a Funso?
Don't capture Scrooge's
brats, Big Time.
Don't stick up
the policeman's ball, Big Time.
Tanks don't float,
Big Time.
She always treats me
like the odd man out
- because my ideas
are too--
- Intense?
Visionary.
Well, I'll show her.
I'll show 'em all.
That's not something
you wanna hear
- when you're tied up
in a meat locker.
- Startin' with you.
ALL: Webby?!
Oops. Sorry.
I'll just...
You could slip out of
those ropes the whole time?
Well, yeah.
That's, like,
Being Captured 101.
So why didn't you?
Because I don't want you
to think I'm weird.
I've been stuck in
the mansion for so long,
and I'm trying
really hard to be normal.
But everything I do
is, you know, not.
Normal's overrated.
We need you to be
Webby-normal.
I'm gonna break
every bone in her body.
Or maybe just tie her up.
We'll see how it plays out.
All right, boys.
McDuck's high-falutin'
hooligan Beakley
is coming here
to take you down.
Are you gonna let her?
Mmm...
No, you are not.
Beakley may be strong,
ruthless and unforgiving,
but you are
the Beagle Boys.
My boys.
It's time to mark
your territory.
Do it for
your dear old ma.
"Dear Ma Beagle,
if you ever want to see
your son again..."
Oh, for cryin' out loud.
You take care
of them.
I'll deal with
the squirts.
Beagle Boys are slow
but quite large.
I'll take the big one
and... Donald?
Give me back
my boys!
Get off me.
I guess he can
take care of himself.
Come on, kids.
I don't have time for games.
WEBBY: Then you're
in the wrong place.
Funso's Fun Zone.
Where the fun
is in the zone...
( grunting )
( shivering )
Oh! You can't outrun me.
You know how many
two-foot terrors
I chased around
the junkyard?
But I'm not outrunning you.
Whee!
I'm leaving you.
Hi, Ma.
Seriously, Big Time?
What the...
Stupid plastic garbage.
Wait, no, stop.
It's a trap!
I know, right? Now!
Boys!
A slipstitch.
Good choice, dear.
Thanks, Granny.
It's okay, Ma.
I tried, and that's
what matters, right?
Shut up, Big Time.
Why can't we have
what they have?
Now flip the circuit
on the boat's panel
and you'll have power.
Thanks, Mrs. B.
So how does a housekeeper
know so much
about electricity
and Tae Kwon Do?
Oh, simple.
I'm a spy.
Nice of Funso's
to lift the ban
and give us
all those free tokens,
you know, to keep us
from suing them.
Yep, the system
works.
So what should
we do next?
I don't know. Webby?
What do you wanna play?
- Really? You mean it?
- Any crazy thing you want.
Oh, how about
a nice game of...
Medieval Dungeon of
Eternal Screaming?
ALL: I'm on Webby's team.